The planet's puppet masters almost surely have a plan.
There's clearly maybe something there beyond the realm of man.
And until you've thoroughly tested every last course just in view,
I'd find the more you think you know, the less you really do.
That's true, Dr. Seuss.
Very well.
Where would we be without THC?
Cause we know they're lying to us, just don't know to what degree.
Yeah, where would we be without THC?
The highest side chat show, Greg Carlwood Company.
So say we all.
From the Sunshine State, I'm Greg Carlwood,
and there is very little that has shaped the human story
more than the propagation of the three Abrahamic religions.
Wars, inquisitions, infidels, tyrannical rule, cultural divides,
oppressive teachings on how to live, disdain for the other,
and yes, mass mind control.
And yet the atheistic era has taken us down a path of hopelessness,
anxiety, and misplaced worship of science to fill the hole.
And between the extremes and the manipulated mental cul-de-sacs
is room for a more accurate model of some sort of relationship
between gods and man, as well as an acknowledgement of
spiritual forces and dimensions that do have a role to play
in this weird reality.
But the planetary puppet masters of the Capstone Cabal
have made sure that we never really have the proper context
for any of this, and thus many people are left grabbing
for parts of the elephant in the great cosmic darkness.
Well, here to set the record straight and undo the damage done
is returning guests the Archon and the Greek,
the anonymous one-two punch of propaganda-busting insight
and the bright minds behind both Greekspeak.com and Godspeak.com,
which both contain a series of interesting sonic events
that give one more than enough to think about.
In their last visit to THC, we focused mainly on the content
in their Greekspeak series, but today they're coming back around
to dive deep into the spiritual insights and godly knowledge
contained in their Godspeak series.
And I'm here for it.
The spiritual knowledge seeders, religious propaganda parsers,
and true relationship between gods and men revealers,
the Archon and the Greek, the Greek and the Archon.
Welcome back, fellas.
Thank you.
Greetings.
Yes, I am psyched to do this.
You make a great team.
Last time was a lot of fun.
We talked about cosmic censorship, lawful timekeeping,
the Pope's work schedule, the biological vacuum,
proper discernment, power, and just a ton of interesting topics.
And today we're going a lot more spiritual,
but there is a ton of great stuff in the Godspeak series,
so I expect this one to be just as insightful.
But how are you guys doing?
How are you feeling about the state of the world?
It's only been three months since we last talked,
but it seems like the credits of the movie are still running,
as the Greek might say.
Okay, the state of the world or the world state, right?
It sounds like a play on words, but I would just say,
how do I feel about the world state as such?
And you could take that politically governmental as deep state
or underlying powers.
Same old shit, man.
It's not going to change until it changes,
until it comes crashing down, and that's just how it goes.
And it will crash down, it will implode,
both from internal and external, mostly external influences,
and that's how I would sum up that question,
without getting too verbose.
Archon, how do you feel about things?
Well, I feel much like the Greek,
that we're in a sort of set trajectory towards a certain destination
with human society, which, at least in the short term,
is not going to be very pleasant.
I don't think that people are successively making more sense of the world,
I think they're making less sense.
And so, inevitably, that has to come to a boiling point
where things sort of tip over,
and presumably that won't be too far in the future.
Yeah, it's scary, because you don't want to experience
a true collapse of everything,
but there's a lot of folks out there that feel like
the only way to get the utopia,
or the closer-to-utopia model on the other side,
is for everything to fall apart,
and we just have to cross our fingers
and hope we can survive through that gap, apparently.
It's an intense thing to think about,
but philosophically, so many people think
that we need to go through the darkness
to come back out to the light.
Yeah, Greg, just before we really get into the meat of things,
I don't endorse this person I'm going to mention.
He has been a guest, but he is a worthy mention
to look at his work, Jason Brashears of Archaics.
I've been talking a lot about eschatology,
and he's come up with some things that could pretty much combine
with what I've been saying through Greek-speak and God-speak.
And again, I don't endorse him directly.
You have to always listen to everything with discernment,
but it's some of the best stuff that I've heard out there
regarding chronology.
So I would put that in quotes for chronology,
and I think you've had him as a guest as well.
This is not about self-promotion or anything.
This is really about objectifying and getting stuff out to the listener.
So I just wanted to say that before we start.
Yeah, fair enough, fair enough.
So estimates vary pretty wildly when you look up these kind of things,
but it seems as though 3.5 billion people
follow one of the three major religions,
and there's no doubt they've had a huge impact
on human behavior and human history.
But what would you say about the creation of them
as a way to control people,
which seems to be the core function that they have?
Exactly.
All right, so we're done.
We don't need to do any more.
That's it.
The entire session here, the sonic event, is about that.
And if you just manage what you just said about being a control issue,
we're pretty much done on the talk
because everything else is going to be supporting that.
It's simple, right?
It is, it is.
And to drill down on, say, one thing like the King James Bible,
it's always frustrating when I have a guest who's here
because they wrote a great book
or they're very clued in on one specific topic,
but peppered throughout the two-hour interview.
They just keep going back to the well of Bible quotes
or talking about Jesus,
and I just roll my eyes
because I don't want to go off track and derail the whole interview
to dissect their religious paradigm.
But you should.
You should dissect it because they call it KJV syndrome.
It's contagious.
So you should stop them when they start with that.
Fair enough, fair enough.
Well, what would you say about the King James Bible?
You've said in the God Speak series
it was created to drive a wedge through society
and it was intentionally seated as a false paradigm.
Talk to us about that for people who maybe don't see it that way yet.
Very simple.
The concept of political tools done by administrative bodies
and any heads of state.
King James, was he a king?
Loosely, yes, but he was a regent from Scotland
to fill in a void in the monarchy,
and he knew that the monarchy was deified by the common people.
So if he made a cheap, easily accessible, more accessible, non-Latin version
of what's called the scriptures that people revered that god, let's say,
and the stories in there, and gave it to the public,
it would drive a wedge between the people's idea
that the king or queen are gods, or deified,
and show that there's a way to access information on other deities, let's say.
And I'm saying that loosely.
All the way back to the king's right to rule from God and all that,
but the common people just viewed royalty as deities.
So he drove that in there by actually providing a cheap,
secondary, let's say, story, or whatever you might call the KJV.
Fair enough.
And if we're going to fully deconstruct before we reconstruct,
I guess we should back it up to Judaism too,
because that's said to be the original monotheistic paradigm,
the first of the Abrahamic religions,
and obviously half the Bible is just a recycled version of the Hebrew Bible,
but what do you consider some of the deeper insights into its origins
and the uniqueness of its place in the Big Three?
Many levels of it.
Before we get into that,
more people might be familiar with the reconstruction of Catholicism
as it goes through time, and there was a big one in the 1960s,
and at the turn of the century,
there's a reconstruction or redoing,
even like with the country we live in.
It used to be a republic, then it became a democracy, right?
And it sounds like it's just words, but it's very radical in terms of change.
Monotheism would be kind of a far stretch.
It's a very simple label to put on it,
but actually if you do read what's called the Old Testament,
the whole thing was about getting the people to get away from worshiping other gods.
So when were they really monotheistic? I don't know.
They were always worshiping, right?
If you go to the stories, you know, the Baal Peor,
you know, the lord of the opening,
and the opening would be the female genitalia they were worshiping.
Then you had the Ashtarte and other Baals,
and the whole entire story is about getting them to worship one god,
where apparently they had a hard time doing that.
Yeah, I mean, I remember growing up hearing the Golden Calf story,
and of course one of the commandments is
you should have no other idols before me.
It's like, well, I thought there were no other idols.
What are you talking about?
This should be kind of obvious if it's a situation where there's only one apex god,
as the religion I was brought up in taught.
So yeah, that's a curious thing.
And you mentioned the deity's royalty overlap.
That's another thing.
When we go far down chain in the history,
it seems like there is a big connection between those two things,
and oftentimes that's put in the context of the fallen angel story,
as if there was a time when angelic beings came down here,
mated with humans, and made offspring,
which became the pharaohs and the Sumerian kings.
Is there truth to that story,
or is that just, again, state propaganda of its time?
Okay, let's backtrack.
If we lost connection right now,
if you're on a cell phone, your battery's low,
and you've got to give some information,
just give the important information first, right?
And this is the information.
Let's say we were to end this right now.
I'd say the gods are people.
Are they normal, regular humans, you know, as we are?
Let's say we, you know, the various races,
which, by the way, in terms of race,
I consider man and woman, male and female,
to be the major two races, by the way,
in terms of distinction, not by color or ethnicity and nationality.
So I would say the gods are people,
and they've pretty much put a story on us as such.
Just like you mentioned, you know, they've gotten—
they were an advanced society that very simply weave in entertainment.
We call them stars, right?
They're like the gods, like Elvis was the god of rock,
let's say, back in the—right?
We call them stars, right?
So we—okay, the corporate we has a tendency
to create various levels and hierarchies,
and the highest hierarchy for anyone would be a god, wouldn't it?
So if we were to end this right now,
I'd say the gods are people.
They're people, too, but they're just very different.
Let's say the gods that you mentioned from the Sumerian stories or so,
they would be people that lived with a certain genetic proclivity
that grew 9 to 10 feet tall,
which skeletons are being found all over the world,
red hair, blue eyes, right?
Kind of idea.
So is it proper to just say the gods are simply giant humans?
No, but I'm just giving one characteristic.
Mm-hmm.
Well, let's go into the characteristics.
If the gods are people,
what else makes up their characteristics
that are different from us?
They're not from here, right?
I mean, they're from another dimension,
a spiritual plane, right?
I recently did on a private thing that I have,
a sign-up only—this might sound like a diversion,
but I want to tie it back.
People say, hey, Greek, I want you to speak to this person.
They're very spiritual.
I mean, spiritual how?
Like what?
You know, like spiritual is supposed to mean good.
I think I might have defined the spirit as being the mind
and the personality,
and the soul as the metabolism,
and the body as the carne, right?
So if you were to walk into a room with thousands of beds
and people either sleeping or in a coma,
there is nothing spiritual there.
The moment they start exhibiting behavior, speech, thought,
interacting with each other, that is all spiritual.
It's of the mind, you see?
So the word spiritual has been misused in a way,
technically as well.
It uses the Greek prefix, the PSY,
where you get psychology, psychotic, psychiatry.
That is the mind.
It's the spirit is the same.
And they've reversed that.
When you look it up, they tell you the spirit is the soul.
But I just want to go back to,
when you speak of a spiritual discussion,
it is something that is animated by beings who are animating
a certain personality or a thought form.
It's basically rational animation,
which you won't find that much anymore.
But that would be the definition and the crux
of what people think of being spiritual
and how I would define it.
Fair.
Well, when we're thinking about our interactions with the gods,
if we're going to say there are many,
like the further you go back,
sometimes people say the more truthful things seem to be.
So if you go back beyond the Abrahamic religions,
it seems like people knew there were gods
for every little thing you might want.
That you could call upon.
Was this superstition or is this closer to the real dynamics
of the way the world works?
Both.
When you say people, again, let's go back earlier.
I said the gods are people.
I would be more concerned of who the gods think the gods are.
I'll say this.
Everybody just cover your ears for a moment.
Most people are too simplistic to contemplate these things.
A good example would be water is H2O, right?
Everybody goes there and they show this molecule.
You know, no one's ever seen that molecule
and it actually doesn't exist.
You don't even need elaborate scientific equipment
to prove water is not H2O.
Just because you put electrical plates in water
and you get hydrogen off of one side and oxygen on the other,
doesn't mean it's H2O.
Because no one's reduced the body of water to hydrogen and oxygen.
The process stops when it gets down to a certain volume.
So it's something that exhibits a trait of that
and everyone takes it on.
I believe and I've seen through history and intuition
that people are too simple to contemplate
something as high order as this.
And when I say people, I'm talking about 99.9999999% of society.
Fair. Well, we got to try to help them out.
If we were to try to picture the true dynamics
between multiple dimensions or how forces play on the material plane
or the relationship between these people we call gods and humanity,
help flush that out a little bit for us.
Rephrase the question.
How can we get a proper orientation in our minds
of the dynamics between the gods and man?
Okay, simple.
What I've always used as a basis for that
is your law comes from your god,
from listening to the god speak and other things
that you might have recalled that.
And what I mean by your law,
it's not traffic law or taxes or what the legal system says.
Your law is basically your operating system
and the programs that you run.
In other words, what you eat, what you wear,
how you do business, how you raise a family,
how you keep time, all of these things,
it was really the purpose of getting information from the gods,
which also does a twofold thing.
There's a discernment there.
So when someone says I follow a certain god,
I'm like what body of knowledge has that god, let's say,
transmitted to you?
So when you hear of these gods, they're like,
oh, you can do anything you want.
I've dealt that before.
It's like, well, how do I know?
We need guidance.
Again, what to eat, what to wear, how to do business,
how to raise a family, how to keep time,
how to manage our environment.
That is the critical point of, let's say,
the godlike transmittal back to humanity.
Again, if you go back to the entertainment industry,
those that perform the best are considered stars
and even above that, gods, right,
because it's the best performance.
So if you're going to pick a god,
look at what they're transmitting towards, you know,
the society or you in terms of proper behavior
or what I call lawful living.
That would be the main connection.
So it is cognitive.
It is knowledge-based.
And by the way, even if you read the version of the King James,
it does tell you it's about knowledge, right?
Well, do you see the gods having an effect
on the material plane in terms of things like weather
or our luck or our tragedies, famine, abundance, illness?
Are these things coming from a source of the gods,
an unseen source that in modern days
really isn't acknowledged at all?
Yes, I would say so.
From a technological point of view, absolutely.
And when we say technology, it's a matter of, let's just say,
you've probably heard most people are familiar with the term
that if one advanced society, technologically advanced,
meets a more primitive one,
the more primitive one considers the advanced society's technology
to be magic, right?
I can give a short story about a river plane
that flew into the Amazon about 75 years ago
and the explorers disembarked
and they met one of the native river tribes
and he pulls out a Zippo lighter and he lights it
and everyone bows down.
The translator said, why are you bowing down?
He says, wow, you make fire come out of your hand.
That's amazing, right?
So he says, tell them to show up at the river tomorrow
and we'll show them something else.
At this point, they had trekked into where the inhabitants were living
and what he planned on showing them the next day
is to actually fly the river plane in, right?
So he can impress them.
Well, they do that.
They fly the river plane in
and all of the natives and the chief are standing by the river
and the moment they saw the plane land on the river,
they just shrugged their shoulders and walked away.
And the explorer went to the translator and said, hey, what's wrong?
They bowed down when I lit the Zippo
and they see the plane and they just shrugged their shoulders.
So the translator went and asked the chief.
The chief said to him basically,
well, if anyone can make fire come out of their hands,
of course they can fly.
It's no big deal, right?
So in other words, we consider them to be primitive,
but their form of logic and reasoning is so advanced, right?
You just have to impress them once
and they associate the entire rest of all your behavior as being normal.
Unfortunately, I think the people in this society now
want to be continuously impressed with tricks.
They're not as advanced as this primitive river tribe.
You see, they created a form of logic that created a terminus
that made them go back to their lives.
Where the current society is constantly looking for new razzle-dazzle, right?
That's why you have all these major events that aren't so.
You know what I mean?
To keep people on edge.
So I just wanted to give that analogy, food for thought or thought for food.
Right.
Well, I mean, now we might have found a really interesting thread
because when I asked about the influence of the gods
in these different categories of life events,
you said from a technological point of view, that could be true.
I mean, are we saying, this might be why you cited archaics
and Jason Breshears.
Are we saying that the gods really are like literally people
that are just a breakaway civilization
that is using technology to affect our lives?
Yes.
I would suggest that the main group that we know about
is here with us in this reality.
There are probably other realities and say probably.
It's super hypothetical.
Just like I always bring up, sometimes people ask,
well, what do you mean?
What kind of technology?
Very simple.
There's a crowd of people and you ask them what they want.
And they all yell out, we want a time machine.
And then you ask them, when do you want it?
And they all yell out, irrelevant.
Does it matter when a time machine is invented?
No.
Let's say it's invented a trillion years from now, right?
A billion, trillion, whatever.
Is it possible that someone with that technology
can come back and affect this world line, right?
Doesn't matter when it was invented.
And if they affect it, do they have the ability
to appear and disappear and change events?
And the answer to that is obvious.
That's just one example.
Well, let's assume if they are living in this reality,
where might they be living?
Where might their civilization be?
I'll give a short antidote to this.
I was invited to go to a very special school
about almost 40 years ago now.
It's above Ivy League.
It's in New York City.
And there are 5,000 applicants to only take 100.
And it's tuition free.
I'm not going to mention its name.
Very few people have heard of it.
And they do very esoteric design work.
I decided not to go there.
And someone who did stayed in touch with me.
And I said, so how's it going?
He says, it's really crazy, man.
We're designing airports that hover in the sky.
And I'm like, what?
I've never seen that.
Well, they're really high up.
I'm like, cool.
This is 40 years ago.
So I'll leave it at that.
Use your imagination.
I think I brought up the cosmic universal law of information
is getting a piece of information to you,
however you classify it, is your idea.
The thing is, did you get the idea, the information?
What I mean by that is when science fiction
is shown to you, no matter what label you put on it,
fiction or fact, true or not, did you get the information, right?
Let's take Star Wars, for example.
Are people aware of something known
or someone known as a Darth Vader or a Death Star?
Yes, many people are.
Now, whether you classify that as fact or fiction
is irrelevant in cosmic information knowledge base.
You know about something like that now, don't you?
Even something like Mickey Mouse.
Are you familiar with that?
Yes.
Is it fact or fiction?
Is it irrelevant?
Did you get the information?
That's how the information on the universal concept works.
Yeah, I had Diana Walsh Pasulka here
who wrote the book American Cosmic
and was kind of trying to drill into the overlap
between religion and the sci-fi UFO aliens narrative
and finds that there's actually way more connective tissue
than one would think.
But when I asked her about her conclusions
and trying to actually put them in some kind of box,
she basically said, well, when you watch a movie,
the internals of your brain are functioning
as if what you're watching is actually happening
rather than some kind of fiction.
So your brain does not distinguish
between fiction and nonfiction.
So that was her answer to what UFOs are.
It was a little bit strange,
but Jacques Vallée has said that he thinks
that we're looking at a display from something else.
The UFO is not the thing.
The UFO is a projection, a display,
from something else that's more core.
And I guess you're kind of wading into that realm too.
Yeah.
There's an old saying that if you have a problem,
it's because you're following the rules, right?
For example, just an interjection,
and I work on some strange devices,
and when I'm told and critiqued
that goes against the laws of physics,
I said, well, I never heard of those laws,
so it's outside of my jurisdiction,
so I actually can do it.
You know, like the idea of jurisdiction, right?
So there's all this stuff that we actually put a clamp
and parentheses and mental parentheses
that lock you in to tell you that this is not possible.
Well, just to say that something is not possible
is not possible.
And to say that there are no absolutes,
wait a second, that could be an absolute in itself.
So are these paradoxes?
In a sense, but if you learn to work with them
and juggle these paradoxes
and these little mind clamps, I call them,
what does a clamp do, right?
It holds something together very tightly,
not just holding it together,
but when you say clamping,
that actually puts a lot of pressure,
inward pressure, when you use that term.
So not only do we have boundaries put on us
from whatever culture you were raised or education you have,
that boundary is actually more like a clamp.
It squeezes and squeezes and squeezes,
preventing expansion.
So is it wrong to say that atheism is mostly correct
if the thing we interpret as gods
or interpreted as gods at a previous age,
like the Egyptians or the Sumerians or the Greeks,
if they're just people,
is there no real, true spiritual force
in the way most people would think of a spiritual force?
I believe there is one.
I think it's really intangible.
Like for example, let's just use fish as an analogy.
Fish are so used to being in their environment.
You get this really crazy fish once in a while.
He comes around and he says,
hey, you know what?
I think we're all submerged in water.
I think we're all underwater.
He says, what are you talking about?
Describe this water thing.
Well, it's wet.
What do you mean it's wet?
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
But you know what?
What might be interesting
is the last thing a fish realizes right before he dies
is that he's in water.
And I'm using that analogy, you see,
about the idea of the spiritual nature
of how it relates to the environment
that we're in right now.
Atheism, by the way, is extremely oversimplified.
Gustave Le Bon wrote a book called The Crowd,
and the crux of that book is
when you have an idea and you want to,
let's say, transmit it to a large group of people,
you have to really simplify that idea, right,
when you're speaking to a large mass.
But what typically happens
is that idea becomes so oversimplified
that it no longer resembles its original concept.
That's why, like with 9-11, they say,
well, okay, the official story is
19 Arab hijackers with box cutters
vaporized the World Trade Center.
Oh, how could they vaporize the World Trade Center?
That's not what it says.
Well, tell me the official story.
That makes even more sense.
You know, it doesn't.
So anything you hear put out to the public
is so oversimplified that it no longer
resembles any initial concept.
Right on.
So if we're going to talk more about these gods
and who or what they are,
how did they get into their position?
Because you're kind of saying that
the right paradigm is to think of the gods
as essentially like the same paradigm as a cargo cult
and this kind of Wizard of Oz motif
that there's this razzle-dazzle display,
but there's really just a guy back there.
And if that's true,
how did they get to this exalted level
in the human story?
If we take it back to a time like the Sumerians
who thought they were gods,
how did they get to this exalted state
to even play the role of gods?
Again, I can oversimplify it.
You could see a rapper that's got 15 Lamborghinis
and a hundred million in cash behind him
in a video and someone in the ghetto watching that.
You get my point?
I don't like the contrast.
It's just contrast.
I think that we are at a point now
where many millennia,
many at least 5,000 or 6,000,
that we have been subject to genetic manipulation
by these other societies,
that that genetic manipulation
also affected our minds.
Were we a lower species?
To some idea.
You have all this stuff about human rights
and how everyone is equal,
but you know how it goes.
Some people are more equal than others.
There are still pygmy people in Asia
and the continent of Africa.
We're talking about people
that are four foot zero and shorter.
If you bring them into this society,
they'll be very hard for them to integrate totally.
There'll always be a group around them shielding them.
Many people would also realize,
not just because of their size,
but because of internal functioning to a degree,
their thinking is very different as well.
This is how I would put early man just a few millennia ago,
and we are all products of this genetic manipulation,
which is very easy to do.
By the way, when I say genetic manipulation,
you don't have to be too esoteric about it.
Just break out some films from the 1930s,
black and white films of just people,
actors or not,
and start watching stuff from the 20s and 30s
and look at the people's noses,
the shape of their faces,
the size of their ears,
the way they walk,
the way they behaved,
and look at now a film of current people.
There's actually physical distinctions that are different.
Just the influx of chemical influences,
you'll notice, okay, what does he mean by that?
The ears are much smaller.
The ear in Asian medicine represents the constitution of someone,
so someone with bigger ears has a stronger constitution.
They can tolerate more adversity, physical adversity.
Now, if you look at everyone's ears,
they're really, really small,
because the ear represents the entire body, for example.
This is just a very small,
let's say, from a macrobiotic perspective.
These are all fine details,
but what is not about fine details, right?
We want good audio quality when we record this, right?
It doesn't matter, does it?
Of course it matters.
Every fine detail adds up, and it's cumulative.
So the cumulative addition of a group of people
living on the surface,
met by another technologically and also physically impressive,
would categorize them so differently
that it would be very easy to call them gods.
And by the way, the term gods or dogs or whatever backwards
is something that we use in English.
If you actually look at the ancient texts,
they were not actually directly called gods.
They were called by their race,
like in the Hebrew would be the Elohim, right?
In the Greek, the Thei, right?
Or the Anu, or the Apkallu, which were the hybrids.
That word god doesn't really directly translate.
The word god comes from an Old Teutonic word
meaning the sun, which is where the word good comes from.
Gut, you know, gut and god.
So it's an Old Teutonic word
that was just chosen to represent such a thing.
So for the so-called gods, for these beings in this class,
to be able to pull this trick off,
they had to have technology that was advanced for its day.
And so might we take this back to Atlantis?
Were they Atlanteans or something else?
Before Atlantis, I believe, yeah.
I've also at some point espoused, you know,
the stuff you normally hear
about the very, very old Atlantis,
which is actually can be shown
to be more of the Sea Peoples now.
I believe that technology is not something
that has ever developed.
It's just rediscovered.
Everything has always existed.
It's just its acknowledgement
is what we consider discovery or invention.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, and we could use the example of the weather.
In the Sumerians' day,
they might try to appease certain gods
to get advantageous weather
or to avoid storms that obviously relates
to their food production.
But today we know the elite have the ability
to steer storms and create storms
and do that kind of thing.
So it seems like they're tiptoeing
into the realm of the gods or the technology of the gods.
But how does that work in an ancient sense
of appeasing the gods?
Like if the gods are just people
with an advanced technology,
how do you make your case?
I mean, typically that's done through prayer or effigies.
But would the gods be aware of this even?
Sure they would.
It's called monitoring.
For example, right now,
if you have devices like stupid rectangles
around where you live
and you start having talk about getting a new couch,
I bet you very high percentage rate of success.
You'll go to your stupid rectangle
and there'll be an ad for your couch.
Is that just pure randomness
or are you being listened to?
Right.
And I'm sure you know that.
So this is interesting.
If I were to set up an altar
and pray to my own personal pantheon of gods,
I suppose,
that might be pegged to something like fertility,
basically the reason I might get a result,
you're saying,
is because they just have intense monitoring
throughout this reality
and they can acknowledge,
oh, that guy is doing his little primitive ritual
to try to appease me
and I can grant him his wish or not.
Great, Greg.
I could say right now
you're one of the people that actually got it.
Yep.
It's so simple.
And we went back to the elite with the weather.
Thank you very much.
I do weather control all the time
and I actually have a media portfolio.
You can go to rents.com.
Just do a search on the rains come to earth
and one of the reporters there said,
I heard you do weather work.
It's Tuesday.
Can you make it rain in LA on Thursday?
It's the middle of the dry season.
And I said, sure.
How much do you want?
There's no rain at all in the forecast.
I said, okay, we'll drop an inch or so.
Well, Thursday comes and he says,
and the rains come to earth
is the name of the second article.
He says, well, I called this guy
and he says he could do raining.
Obviously he did.
Look, it's raining like crazy
and I've done demonstrations over and over and over
in the beginning when I was working on this.
I had about a hundred mile radius.
Now I have about a two or 3000 mile radius of effect
and I've done hurricane abatement,
made hurricanes disappear,
super typhoon Lekima in Japan.
There was two of them.
If you go to Dutch sense,
he does a lot of weird anomalous stuff
and he says he has a video,
super typhoon Lekima.
And he says, look,
last night there were two hurricanes approaching Japan
and something very strange.
They're both disappeared by this morning.
So what I'm just saying, this is so simple
and I'm being modest about this.
It's not a big deal in terms of weather design.
I also work on technology where I have a pipe
and you run basically a section of pipe,
especially designed just to pipe.
You could see right through it before it's finished.
You run dirty water on one side
and clean water comes out on the other.
What the hell is that work?
I mean, that's magic, isn't it?
So I'm working on these things
and very successfully at the moment
and I'm just not doing websites.
I'm not bragging about it.
I'm trying to be humble
and I keep it to myself
and I share it with others who need it.
And I'm not a God,
but the gods are on an order of thousands
or millions of times higher
than what I'm saying, let's say.
Like, for example,
we might have someone in society
that's got a nice piece,
like the British say, a nice piece of kit,
nice piece of high tech something, right?
I assure you there's some military group
or black ops group
that's got something way beyond that.
For example,
the stupid rectangles we use right now.
What's a stupid rectangle anyway?
Those devices, all that stuff,
that's 40, 50 year old technology.
It was a little bulkier also.
The technology that we have,
none of it has really been developed
since the 1890s
and that sounds like a crazy statement, right?
What you call development is miniaturization.
They've been able to miniaturize all this stuff
and I'm not impressed by miniaturization.
I don't think the ladies are impressed
by miniaturization anyway.
Anyway.
I like it.
So when I asked where these people
we think our gods might be,
you mentioned that you were read in
on this situation
where they're building airports in the sky
and there's a possibility they're in the sky.
I've read Passport to Magonia,
which talks about the Magonians in the sky.
People seeing skyships up there of some kind
at certain periods of history.
Well, another far out idea I have liked
is when it's been suggested that Freemasons,
they're all about angles and certain numbers
and when you look at the Freemasonic artwork,
the symbols,
there'll be like a ladder to the sky
with the sun on one side,
the moon on the other side
and a window in the sky that this ladder reaches.
Almost suggesting rips in reality
that there could be places
that you can't actually access
dimensional rips or something.
A guy named Jacob dealt with one, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Is this where they might be located?
Yes, and above and below.
Also underground.
There's a lot of stuff.
If someone could look up
whether you believe it or not,
take in the information,
Busaj Mountains in Romania,
they found underground alien bases supposedly
and they connect to Egypt, Iraq
and other places in the world.
When you say underground,
it's like, oh, this dingy whatever, right?
No, I would suggest
if you've ever seen pictures of the Mall of America
or an elaborate shopping mall,
what that looks like,
look at the robust structure of a shopping mall
like the ones in Dubai, let's say,
if you want to get really elaborate.
Why couldn't that be built a mile down?
It very well could be.
I mean, Robert F. Kennedy Jr.,
he and just one of his interviews
going on his speaking tour
for his presidential bid,
he casually dropped that when he was a kid,
he was taken to one of these places
because he's in one of the privileged families
and he was really impressed
that this underground bunker
was actually more like an underground city
that had its own McDonald's
and all the things of the surface world
and his mind was blown.
But now he just drops that
as if everybody knows it
and it was like, wait a second.
Oh, no, he was in hell if there was a McDonald's.
No, I'm just joking.
Okay, that was more of a Dante-ism.
Yeah, here's one thing that I don't know for sure
but I could suppose
and it would be very strongly accurate
that once you build something underground
that goes above 300 meters or 900 feet,
guess what happens?
It starts to develop its own weather system.
So all you have to do
is paint the ceiling blue, right?
And you actually have
a small weather system accruing.
So if you're born in a situation like that,
well, you wouldn't know the difference, right?
You'd brought someone up from there
and you described weather on the surface
and they'd say, yeah,
we have weather there as well.
By the way, I want to suggest something.
Whether you believe it in the planets or not
or the shape of the earth or not,
I think I might have mentioned this.
When you look at the planets
and they're barren on the surface
and let's say in the solar system
or computer graphics that they show us,
that is a mark that 90% inhabited
by super advanced civilization.
And the analogy I give is this.
Greg, I just built a new house
and for the new house,
I'm going to have new furniture delivered.
Oh, Greg, here comes the furniture truck.
Guess what?
I'm going to have all the furniture on the roof
because I'm going to live on the roof, right?
No way.
What do you think will happen?
All neighbors say, look at that dumbass
living on the roof subject to weather, sun,
all this other stuff.
Furniture goes inside, dummy.
When you have an advanced civilization,
they go inside the planet, inside,
under protection, you see?
So now there's a flyby to the earth.
Let's say you're a round ball globist.
A flyby on the earth and they're like,
no, no, no, no, don't go there, don't go.
These are really dumb people.
They're on the surface.
Don't go there, right?
Do you see how simple this is?
Right, yeah.
I've heard this argument made before
and I think it has merit, but it's also like
the joys of being outside would be denied
to an inner earth civilization.
We know vitamin D is very important.
That comes from sunlight.
You mentioned an ecosystem forming below,
but they're not going to get their own sun.
Believe it or not, yes, you can.
For example, there was a grow room back in the days
when grow rooms were not, you're a naughty boy
if you did one, right?
Let's see.
And they wanted to bring the energy inside of the sun
without, because one of the things is
if your electric bill quadruples,
that's what they look for, right?
So how do you do it without a massive electric bill?
I said, great, just put some metal plates on the roof
with a certain wire with metal plates on the ceiling inside
and the plants will get the energy
from the sun transmitted.
And it's true.
Even though it was almost pitch black,
the plants were moving in the direction
of the metal plates.
So you can actually bring the sun.
Here's an example.
We only see a tiny percentage of the visible light
and energy with our sense perceptions.
Most of it goes unnoticed by us, 99%.
Or if you want to be, let's say, more conservative,
80% of all the energy around us goes unseen
and unnoticed by us.
So 80% of the sun's energy is unnoticed by us.
So if you could take that 80% and bring it into an area
where there is no visible light and have the same effect,
there's your, you want to talk about vitamin D?
By the way, this is provable.
I've done it, so.
Fair enough.
So when we look at cultures who have talked
about the Elohim or the Naga or these races
that they consider to be gods,
have some of these died out?
Are they all still active?
Who is the most active group today
that we might consider in that godlike status?
Good point.
Have you ever heard of the story,
Elvis is still alive in the tabloids, right?
Very much.
Any society has that.
You'll have a popular figure that suddenly becomes unpopular
because of something they did or said.
Now guess what they are called?
They're called a demon.
Oh, yeah.
They're bad now, right?
And then you have popular figures
that are just tired of the attention and they die,
but they're not really dead, right?
So in other words, what I'm trying to say
is the trivial machinations of human society
are just echoes of what the gods are doing too.
Hey, have you ever heard of someone on the surface society
going to prison and being in jail and dying in jail?
Hey, guess what?
The gods do the same thing, right?
Have you ever heard of someone faking their death?
Yes.
Have you ever heard of a ritual sacrifice,
Kobe Bryant helicopter?
Did I just say Kobe Bryant helicopter?
I'm not supposed to say that, right?
They do the same stuff.
He was chopped up in many pieces and put back together,
but the penis was missing.
So, I mean, come on.
It's the same story, just on an elevated hierarchy.
Well, that is interesting to bring up mythology.
Is there a better context to think about mythology
rather than fiction or primitive people
trying to make sense of their world?
Is that really just the biography of the gods,
the history of the gods?
Yes.
But again, the Gustave Le Bon, the crowd,
when you want to transmit a certain information
to the masses, you have to simplify it.
But unfortunately, the oversimplification
changes the story.
For example, even with academics, I've done this,
talked about Greek mythology,
and they'll say this and this and that.
I said, well, actually, if you actually read the story,
it was not so.
Just like in the biblical story,
the thing I like to bring up,
I don't know what part of the segment we're in here,
is if you're Christian, they bring up the Christ
and the image they show is a crucifixion.
Well, if you've read the story and it's cumulative,
there is no crucifixion, no matter how many times
they use that word, right?
And the same with all of the ancient Greek philosophy.
Oh, if you see Medusa, you turn to stone.
No.
If you read the story, it's your heart turns to stone.
Big difference, right?
It's like saying, hey, Greg, put the clothes in the dryer
or put the clothes on the dryer.
If you put the clothes on the dryer,
but it sounds the same.
You can't say that, Greek.
It's the same thing.
No, it's not.
No, words matter.
Yeah, you gotta be specific.
So let me bring the archon in here for a minute.
You have gone through all this with the Greek before.
I'm still wrapping my head around things
in real time as we're going.
But how has the Greeks' work or knowledge in this area
affected your spiritual beliefs
or how you configure all this in your head?
Well, it's been very useful for being able to objectify
any topic or subject matter pertaining to the supernatural
or the spiritual.
I, like many people, came up in an environment
where certain things were foisted upon me
as far as knowledge and religions
and thankfully was able to unpack that a little better
thanks to the conversations having been had with the Greek
and also the work that we've done on the Godspeak front.
So yeah, it's been very helpful from that perspective.
There's still a lot of work to be done
because I think that ultimately these things can't be
completely unpacked until they are shown to you
or given to you, let's say,
by people that have a higher vantage point.
There's only so much that you can come to
by way of your own rationale
because I think that kind of pertaining
to what we were saying earlier,
the influence of the gods has always been present in society
and it continues to be.
But what they do is that they block knowledge of themselves
as has been done through things like mainstream religion
so that their presence is covert rather than overt
but that doesn't mean that they're not there.
We can't say that society is secular
when so many of our institutions and cultural artifacts
are named after ancient gods like Nike or Mazda or whatnot.
So, you know, that's fairly obvious
but the only reason that some people know anything about the gods
is because the gods wanted it to be known
or required them to know in the first place.
So it can be a conundrum to uncover things on your own
that are concrete outside of mainstream religion
because it's revealed selectively.
So I have to sort of wade through that process
even though getting access to this information through the Greek
has expedited some of that.
Fair. It seems like, yeah,
when you mention terms like supernatural or spiritual or paranormal
there is none of that.
It's just all essentially technological
and they just fool us into putting it in these other categories.
And when you say that it has to be given to you
like using the Wizard of Oz analogy
you can speculate that this thing you're seeing
might be manipulated or more stagecraft than reality
but you got to pull back that curtain to really verify it.
Is there a way that people out there listening
that think this makes sense
is there a way they can pull back the curtain?
Do they have that ability?
Is there a place to go or a thing to do
where they can validate these
what to them right now might be speculations?
I think it's a challenge.
Sometimes what stands in the way of people's enlightenment
is their own hubris and their own folly
and that's something that's really not addressed or talked about enough.
As they say, you can lead a horse to water but not make them drink.
You can show people the answers.
That doesn't mean that they'll understand anything you're telling them.
And I think when it comes to the gods
people discount the knowledge base about the gods
because they'd rather believe in themselves as self-determined humans.
And then even when they do acknowledge the supernatural
they still make it all about them
and how they can channel esoteric powers
or talk to demons or superhero movie stuff.
So I think the Greek has mentioned before
we know as much about the gods as we do about bears, right?
Sure, we can describe the habits of a bear or the characteristics
they're all observable so we can confirm their existence
but that's about it.
If you want to know what a bear really is
you actually have to be one
which is a way of just saying that
again, these things have to be given to you
in a very tangible way to understand.
It's not just by virtue of your own cognitive reasoning
that you're going to come to understand what the gods are about
hence what you see people doing with secret societies.
They find a way to immerse themselves in that sphere
whether it's through evil doings
or dealing with malevolent entities
that sort of make parts of that world accessible to them.
It's your own choice how you want to go about it
but you have to have some type of contact point
to really get the tangible understanding.
Right, that was going to be one of my questions
was about secret societies and occultists.
Do they have a contact point?
Are these little cults and organizations
and mystery school societies built around a point of contact?
It would seem to be so to some extent
although it's hard to verify from the outside
what's legitimate and what's not.
People talk about the Freemasons endlessly
but when you look at at least their public-facing ceremonies
it always seems somewhat ridiculous
the way that they congregate.
You can go up to these people at their events
and talk to them about what they're doing
and they'll usually say something blase or sort of generic
which goes to show that even in that world there's tears
and ancient older literature will talk about
33rd degree Freemason, etc.
I can't say personally what that means.
I would assume that there is a tear somewhere
where things do get into the more tangibly supernatural
but it's just hard to say from the outside looking in.
It's about armies also.
That's why the Catholics for example
no abortion, no birth control, no suicide.
The more people you have enlisted in your club
the more power you have.
Why do you think there are millions of government employees?
J.P. Morgan, they asked him back in the day
what do you prepare to do when the people find out
the money system is based on fiction?
Oh, easy.
I'll just draft a bunch of checks and pay half the people
to kill the other half of the people.
That's one way to go about it.
Yeah, most governments want to increase
how many government employees they have
because if you're depending on quote-unquote a paycheck
you're not going to rebel.
The goal of any government is to get
more than 50% of the population on their payroll.
It's the same thing with religion and clubs
and secret societies.
Right, well let me ask you about that whole concept
that the real proof, the knowledge to really be shown
I mean we can make the claim all day
but to be shown it really has to be given
from this upper plane
because there's no way for us to elevate ourselves
to a state where we can prove these things.
They have to be willing to pull back the curtain
a little bit themselves.
Is there a way to invoke such a thing?
You can do it subtly.
Here's a simple experiment that I do all the time
and I demonstrate it to other people.
There's something called Craigslist, right?
They have a free section.
So just think of something you want
and act as if you have it
and then go in the next two or three days
to Craigslist free and someone is giving it away.
It's bizarre.
It works at about a rate of 70%.
Very specific things will show up free on Craigslist
and you'll go find the ad
and it was just put five minutes ago
and you call and say,
hey, for example, I needed a small shed
of a certain variety.
I needed some pallets.
I needed this.
I needed a water pump.
It shows up and I call and it's like,
oh, I guess if you're coming now
I'll just take the ad down and I go and pick it up.
Manifestation.
This has nothing to do with law of attraction and all that
but you can manifest things.
I was going to say manifestation.
So you're saying that the gods are the mechanism
of manifestation.
They just decide to grant a wish.
Think about you have a wagon,
a motorized engine driven wagon.
I don't call it an automobile
because it's not autonomous, right?
You have to put fuel in it, the ones we have.
But you don't have any roads.
So you can have as many, let's say, automobiles, right,
as you want.
But if you don't have any roads,
you're kind of landlocked, right?
What the gods are simply doing is providing the roads.
They're like road maintenance.
They're building the roads and connectivity, freeways, highways,
small back streets, alleyways.
Does that make any sense for an analogy?
It does make sense as an analogy
but I wonder why they would do that.
Why they would care if I get the trailer
that I want to get through a free ad on Craigslist.
They should be so high above me
that they don't give a fuck about what I want
or how I get it or anything about my life.
Yeah, you made a really good point.
Go down to Beverly Hills and ask people for money
because they're wealthy.
They should be loose with it, right?
Most people will say, go screw yourself.
But guess what?
What would you say?
One out of 10, one out of 20 might say,
sure, I have some for you.
Very similar to humans.
On the Godspeak website, towards the top,
you have a scrolling rolodex of quotes
that come up through the sonic events
and one of them mentions that the gods want our attention.
The question is like, well, what do they want with us?
Well, if you have everything and access to everything,
what would you want other than attention?
But even that seems like if they are just people
at a greatly advanced level,
I don't see why they would be motivated
by getting our attention.
Okay, you phrased that very well.
You don't see, but maybe they do.
I'm not being an asshole.
I'm just saying you don't see it, but maybe they do.
And I'm suggesting that based on just contemplation.
I was invited to a birthday party for a billionaire once
and he's a billionaire, right, with a B.
So what do you bring them?
I don't do those things, but out of respect, I went.
So what do you give someone that already has everything?
I mean, well, a billionaire doesn't have everything,
but, you know, what do you bring them?
You know, a stupid tie.
What do you get them?
So you have to get them something unusual.
So I got a letter opener made from a raccoon penis bone.
Hello.
That was like, who would ever think of something like that, right?
So you see, it has to be something unusual that they still,
but you notice it's a letter opener, right?
It still ties into something tangible that they can use.
So what do the gods use?
If they focus more on the energetic,
well, here, let's go back to the universal concept of information.
Have you ever seen a sci-fi film where these beings are so advanced,
they're just basically, they don't need to eat,
they don't need to do much,
but they interact with the characters that are human by thought?
Yeah, definitely.
Okay, is that so hard to contemplate?
That they would communicate through thought?
Yeah, they don't have the physical needs we do,
but because they only exist as thought forms now.
There's an old Star Trek that where they found a society so advanced,
there were these luminous globes,
and they just wanted to go back into a human body to experience it temporarily.
So occasionally, have you ever heard of gods wanting to,
or spiritual beings wanting to go and take control of a human body for a short time?
Exorcist, hello, the movie.
Remember, demons are gods that fell out of favor, right?
We had a president that is demonized.
He's a demon, right, to some, and he's a god to others.
Oh, wait a second.
Aren't there secret societies that are called Satan worshipers?
To them, is that a negative entity?
No.
Yes, and when I went through the Godspeak series,
and when I was preparing for this,
I thought we were going to be putting the gods in a context of thought forms,
that they are on a spiritual, non-physical plane,
and they sometimes interact with us.
Maybe they pull the strings from this place,
but you took me down this whole other path
that they're actually just using some kind of technology to do such a thing,
and so now I'm a little confused.
It almost seems like atheism is the right paradigm
because there is no spiritual plane.
Is that what we're saying?
No, there is.
It's just the variety is so great.
Look at all the animal species on the,
if I told you there's half a million species of insects,
not half a million insects, half a million species,
and there's millions and billions of each one of those.
There is a veritable plurality in existence, especially here on Earth.
The spiritual aspect of it is of the mind,
and again, when you go to atheism, this is my answer to atheists.
Okay, you're an atheist, so you don't believe in God, right?
I don't like that term, God, but they usually answer yes.
I said, okay, then do you believe in the laws of the state?
And they say, yes.
Well, then the state is your God, and April 1st is your holiday.
In other words, it's a default back to the purpose of the gods is to what?
Disseminate, transmit information on how to be, how to live.
It's ontological, you know, the nature of being, right?
And then it goes to eschatology, which is how things end up.
It's very simple.
So the atheist is basically telling you they get their law from the state,
and that's their God.
It's a default thing.
And by the way, when you look at all the state buildings,
don't they have a statue of a God or something on top of the dome
of some kind of goddess or something?
They know what's going on.
People are very simple, but there's two types of simple.
There's simple and good, and there's simple and not good.
I didn't say bad.
Like recently I was having a discussion with a corporate person,
and they want to do this type of banking.
I said, no, no, I don't do that.
I redeem lawful money.
And I said, you know, listen, all this,
I noticed you're getting heated on this discussion about finances.
It doesn't make you bad that you want to be corporate,
but I'll tell you what, it definitely doesn't make you good either.
So what does that mean?
Is that a gray area?
Not exactly.
But can someone not be bad and also not be good?
And that's the point here with the gods as well.
By the way, there is a lot of writing about that the God of the Bible
is responsible for more people dying than any other cause or dictator.
I'm sure you've heard that, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, you bring up a great point about state houses, courthouses,
all this stuff.
There's always some kind of effigy or idol out front.
Even there's one at Rockefeller Center.
And you could say that the Statue of Liberty might be a veiled idol
of some kind, some say the goddess Columbia.
And that's a big part of shows like this,
trying to unpack the secret religion of the elite is how it's usually framed,
that they aren't Jewish or Christian.
They have a whole different paradigm.
They might be worshiping Mithras or something weird like that,
something more ancient and archaic.
Is that a paradigm that you think is somewhat on the right track?
Or are they having more of a relationship like this,
like it is just a couple of people that have a relationship?
Very simple is when you ask someone that is doing something,
why you're doing it, and they don't have an answer,
just because, right?
Is that good enough for you?
And if that's good enough for you, everything's right.
But if it's not good enough for you, then everything is not right.
Notice I didn't say wrong.
Yeah, it wouldn't be good enough for me.
I would want more details as to what motivates a certain person,
especially if we're talking about the level of having a statue
and certain symbols everywhere they go.
There seems to be some kind of power in the symbol,
some kind of power in the references to what they call the gods.
All power is direction of movement.
For example, if you have a Ferrari and it's just parked on the side of the road,
well, some sports cars like that look like they're going 100 miles an hour
standing still.
You really don't know until you drive it.
And when you drive it, are you driving it forward
or are you driving it in reverse?
But it's still direction.
So power, when let's say someone pulls the lever
and pulls the pin out of a grenade and counts to 5 or 10 and it goes off,
the direction of force is from the center of the grenade outward,
very power, right?
Power is an exhibit of direction and how fast that direction is moving.
For example, explosives are measured in feet per second.
So if I say this thing, when it goes off,
high-speed chemistry is what people in the trade call it,
goes off at 200 feet per second, okay.
This one goes off at 7,000 feet per second.
Ooh, you want to stay away from that one, right?
So power is about direction.
So when you see an idol, isn't that a form of direction?
Well, it's caught your view, right?
And then it has an effect on the mind.
So whatever you're thinking about when someone –
most people look at things and don't acknowledge it.
But if you were to point that out to someone who –
what's that on top of the building there?
Oh, yeah, I've seen that before.
I don't really know what it is.
But the moment they figure out what it is,
now their thought direction has changed.
And that's where the power is, you see.
But there's also in ritual, it's having masses of people.
Super Bowl halftime, by the way.
It doesn't matter if they know what's going on,
as long as they partake.
But here's the thing.
One person partaking that knows what's going on,
you're going to need 1,000 people partaking
if they don't know what's going on,
to have the same amount of power.
Hence, the secret society rituals.
Secret society rituals are done with a group, by the way.
It's a milieu of people, two or more.
Sometimes it could be dozens.
And those dozen people, let's say,
offering to some ancient deity, let's say,
have a lot more power than everyone watching the Super Bowl
because they know what's going on.
So again, it's direction.
Is it the 200 feet per second chemical reaction
or the 7,000 feet per second chemical reaction?
Sure, sure.
It's all about direction.
I think that makes sense.
And when we think about gods as thought forms,
I can understand why they would want attention.
Attention could be a form of currency
in the mental space or energy or food to a degree.
But that's different than saying
that they're people manipulating us technologically.
There could be both categories going on.
But thought forms would have just entirely different dynamics
as to what they value and how they feed
or what they're interested in.
Yes, yes.
Again, there are so many varieties.
Again, the whole purpose of the Godspeak
was to be contemplative and put forward rational discussion
on basically what's been memorialized through history.
By the way, what's been memorialized through history?
Whenever you see an old book or an old text that you find,
you have to ask yourself,
why do we have this on the surface?
Why are they allowing us to see this?
Because I will bet dollars to donuts,
as they say back in New York,
that if you go underground,
they'll pull out a manuscript of some sort,
and it'll look like it's decades old,
and it's 4,000 or 5,000 years old.
That's how well all knowledge has been preserved.
Library of Alexandria was emptied out
before it was burned twice.
All the gold in the World Trade Center
was emptied out using yellow Ryder vans.
The yellow Ryder vans always show up, by the way, Oklahoma.
Anyway, so all these things are cleared up
before the disasters take place,
and the disaster that we have on the surface right now
is called Ignorance, with a capital G.
I would just jump in real quick to say
that if one loosely defines gods
as the primary dynamic influence on this physical world,
wherever that comes from,
I don't think it's contradictory to say
that there's an invisible spirit realm
where some of those entities habitate,
and there's also a breakaway civilization
made up of anthropomorphic beings on this side
that can mask their presence and do things like time travel.
Because I think going back to what the Greeks said about
when truths are revealed to you through things,
whether it's movies or comics,
that still counts as a reveal,
and we've seen endlessly in various intellectual properties
this notion of the hybrid,
what comes to mind for me,
something like Dragon Ball Z, the hybrid Saiyan.
So these two things can exist in parallel,
that you have the thought forms or the thought world,
and then you have some kind of embodiment on this side
that interacts with that,
and people going through forms like the occult
to try to access that on their own.
And yeah, I mean, I've also heard the Greeks say in the past
that when it comes to the occult,
when you ask them,
what are the gods behind your secret societies,
ultimately what you come away with
is understanding that whatever those gods are,
they're there to compete for the people's attention
and their allegiance.
It's more that than anything else.
It's not necessarily you become a Freemason or a Jesuit
and then you conquer the world.
It's more of you get absorbed into that system,
and that's what takes up your energy and your time.
So rather than focusing on whatever,
let's say, the supreme deity might be,
you've got your head buried in the Kabbalah
trying to uncover something.
I think that's the real reveal, I think, of secret societies.
Because wherever the highest truth is,
I wouldn't say it's in those groups.
But by getting involved in those groups,
it becomes almost like a time suck.
Or you could listen to God speak.
By the way, I just wanted to mention,
this is very important because these terms come up
when you have a discussion like this one.
The opposite of love is not hate.
It's not an opposite because it takes a lot of energy to hate,
almost as much as love.
It is on a different frequency.
I would suggest the opposite of love is indifference.
If you were to walk into a room,
and there's four people there,
but they only count three,
and you're totally ignored,
you would much rather have someone hate on you.
Yeah, it's indifference.
So the indifference to the gods is really their,
how would you say,
what they don't like, I would suggest.
Tie that into the worship,
tie that into the attention.
Indifference and apathy, ignoring them,
is really the cutting off the food.
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
People talk about the overlap
between pain and pleasure,
that it kind of comes full circle sometimes.
The Venn diagram of those two
can overlap quite greatly,
but you could say
pain and pleasure being one thing
and the opposite is truly like
numbness or no feeling.
That's right. People say I'm bored,
and I consider when someone says they're bored
as boredom as being a form of anger.
How can you be bored?
I mean, bored of what?
Everything is amazing. You're breathing, aren't you?
Look, one of the
healing arts is breathing,
right? So if you feel bored,
why don't you focus on your breathing?
It's actually a healing art.
There are many cases of people healing diseases
by changing the way they breathe.
How can you be bored?
Well, you know, when we had this last
conversation, and even this one,
I find the most interesting
parts to be these little anecdotes
from your life,
Greek, and it's difficult
for me as an interviewer because I don't
even know what to ask because I have no
context for
these random experiences
in your life. The seeing
of ancient books that aren't supposed to
be, the
finding out of knowledge or
technologies that people think aren't
supposed to be, what are
some of those things that have happened in your life
that really flips
the way you think about things compared to
a conventional person?
Interesting. You know, I'm glad you
asked this. I had a discussion about this
recently with someone, rather
a long discussion, and one thing
is to anticipate new things
and things that you never even thought
of were possible, to anticipate them
even though you don't know exactly what they might be
in context or subject matter.
What that does is it opens the door,
right? This is not law of
attraction. This is very different, and it
keeps your mind open. Then before you know it,
you find yourself in situations meeting
people that you never thought you'd meet
and seeing things that you never
think you'd ever see, but you have to have
an open mind, and I'm saying
that in the truest sense.
Open meaning not
closed. See, because there is no such
thing as a closed mind. It's like a clamp.
When the mind is closed, it just doesn't
keep things from going in or
coming out. It actually starts compressing
and making it smaller and
smaller and smaller. Leave a piece of
fruit on the windowsill.
What happens after time? It starts to
shrink and die.
When something dies, it shrinks, condenses,
decomposes.
There's this aspect of life
that you tag yourself
with. You remember every morning you get up
and you hang a label on yourself,
a label that says, you know, I'm open to
new things every day,
and then watch what happens.
You also have to do the work.
For example, someone like myself
who says, let's say, I work with
water or work with weather or work with energy,
I have to be able to back that up.
That's where the work
comes in. You have to do it with authentic,
creative, intuitive information,
not just because you read a bunch of
textbooks. By the way,
when you have a textbook, put that down. You don't
know where that's been.
Yes. You mentioned going
to a billionaire's
birthday party.
That's very adjacent to
something like a breakaway civilization.
The next level up might be
that. It might be just one degree
below. Have you had experiences
with people that
would be classified
as members of a breakaway
civilization? Not in a way
that would shock anyone on the surface
world.
Believe it or not, there's a lot of filters
in place for that. It's not like
you just meet someone that's, let's say,
a secret elitist, quote-unquote, Illuminati,
whatever. Two days
later, you're doing their stuff. It takes
years and years and years. One
of the things that I always say within
knowing the Greek for even just
a few hours, I bring up, hey, I'm an
Old Testament kind of guy.
In other words, when I go to a restaurant, I'm like, do you have anything
without pork? They're like,
are you Jewish? I'm like, no, I'm not Jewish.
I just don't dig on swine.
I put
this air of not righteousness,
but I have my limits.
If you want to know what they are, just go read that.
I'm not
necessarily a shallow individual, but
if you want to know what I think about you, listen
to what I'm saying. I don't speak behind people
in a way that would surprise anyone.
The other thing is, I subscribe
to this body of law
and morality. If you want to know what
it is, just go read it. It's the Old Testament,
for example. I actually
mentioned to someone, this was in academics,
you're an Old Testament kind of guy. That means you want to
go around killing people? I'm like,
what?
Where'd you get that from? There's a heavy
distortion. Again, Gustave Le Bon,
if you mention the Old
Testament, that's a wrathful God.
It's all about killing and maiming.
Then we have this new God that's all about
love and whatever. No, I don't know.
That's been so oversimplified. It no longer
resembles the truth.
Going back to what you said about
your laws come from
your God,
what does that say about people today
who seem mainly
godless? Do they have
some God that they're just
not necessarily conscious of, or
not so much?
Absolutely. It's called the state.
They signed
this new bill today. Oh my gosh,
now we have to wear a blue hat on Mondays
otherwise the IRS will fine us
$500.
They get all worked up with all these new
laws. I actually look at
all of the new laws, even the draconian ones,
not to mention laws
like the Patriot Act and other things like that.
I think they're
wonderful in a sense that they're just disclosing
what was put in place over 100
years ago. Trading with the Enemies Act,
1933 Banking Act,
they're just disclosing more of what
was already set in place
a long time ago. People are
riled up like it's something new.
Do you think
there's value in trying
to form a relationship
with a god? How do we
even know what gods
could be available to us?
Too big of a
question to answer.
The smaller part of that question, I would say,
is by doing.
What is it? Walk your talk, talk your
walk? Again, I'm an Old Testament
kind of guy. One of the things there
is the quote-unquote food laws.
They're not restrictions. There are laws
better ways. For example, when you
buy a car and it says put a certain motor oil
in it, guess what?
You should do that for that car, right?
Use a certain soap in your washing machine
is a thing that I've noticed.
What happens if you don't?
There's also stuff about
when you wear clothing, don't wear mixed fibers.
There's how to
keep time. Well, it's very indirect,
but it'll tell you by what it's not
telling you how to keep time.
Many aspects. How to do business.
The Regulation Z in business,
the 72-hour
right to refuse
a contract or something like that,
that comes out of the Old Testament, right?
When you sign a bank loan or something,
they usually wait 72
hours for it to close because in
that time, you could renege on the whole thing
or whatever, right? It's funny when you send back
a traffic ticket within 72 hours
to the police station and to the court,
what they do? They freak out. They start
changing dates and things on there.
Regulation Z, they call it in the
commercial world. Actually, here's the thing.
I'd like to see anyone
come up with some old maxims of law
or things that are written in law that didn't
come from the Old Testament. Show me something
that hasn't come from there.
For example, taxation.
The foreigner is taxed. So if you
are being taxed by your government,
well, your government is a foreign government.
Is that possible?
Is it possible that...
Does it have to be like the CCP?
China has to come over here and take over
Washington, D.C. for it to look foreign
because they look foreign?
No. It could be
foreign government and just be your own people.
When you read in old stories
about, let's say, the New Testament,
the Roman soldiers, right? The Romans
did all this stuff, right? You hear it and you see
it in the movies. Very few
of those guys were actually from Rome
or a place known as Italy. They were
actually hires from Syria
and Lebanon and places all around.
For example, look at a photograph
of people in the U.S. Army.
I'd say about a third of them
are over there because they want to get a green card.
They're not from here.
So, yeah.
There's a mix here.
You really stepped
in it, Greg, with this and the other interview
because these are subjects that require
days of talk, right?
It's really hard to compress.
Yeah. And a lot of people won't even
do two-hour interviews because they only
have one hour in them.
Oh, my gosh. We could just barely scratch it.
That's how I feel. That's how I feel.
That's the value of two hours, I think.
So, if you talk to a
chaos magician, they tend
to go to the
historical books about
various gods. They comb
through different pantheons.
They look at grimoires
and they find
gods that are supposed to represent
things they might want,
like wealth or increased luck
or vitality
or fertility,
and they might try to
incorporate those gods into
their prayers, into their altar.
Do you see that as
a paradigm that has any value?
Can you dig into the
historical literature about gods
and, in our modern day,
actually incorporate
them into your thoughts
and have an effect?
Exactly. We're being
monitored, as you could see
back then. You could read any ancient
text. And we heard the prayers of so-and-so,
right? So, I'm here with
my wife all day talking about getting a new couch.
I pick up a stupid rectangle and there's
advertisements for a new couch.
Simple.
So, in what degree?
Could it be possible, in the future, that
okay, we're speaking of getting a new
couch here, and not
only does it show up on the stupid rectangle...
By the way, should I define stupid rectangle?
We know. It's the black mirror. It's the screen.
Yeah. All the devices. Okay.
Now, let's say...
Take this hypothetically.
Not only am I speaking about
the couch, and not only does it show up
in ads, but if there's a knock on the door,
you just won the digital sweepstakes.
Here's your new couch.
Is that possible?
It is. Yeah. We haven't seen
it yet. By the way, let's copyright
that right away.
This is copyrighted on Greg Carlwood, so if they
try to do that, you get it. Anyway.
I like it. Well, how do we
increase the
potency, or the
frequency, of those experiences in
our lives? How can people listening
actually improve their
lives with this knowledge
about the gods? Oh,
great. Gustave Le Bon again,
if you have a simplified notion
of something religious, or
spiritual, or whatever, put that
down. You don't know where it's been. Go back and
see if you could find where it came from
and read it for yourself.
Just like Medusa. Yeah, you look at Medusa, you turn to
stone. No.
If you go and read it a little more accurately,
your heart turns to stone. Big difference.
Go look at the big
differences, what is
memorialized. By the way, a lot of
people that are religious, especially in the Christian,
say, well, the Bible cannot be understood.
Okay. So the gods
put out something that cannot be understood,
so that is an act of futility.
So the gods act in futility. Is that
what you're trying to say, or did they actually
write it so it could be comprehended and
understood? It would be the latter.
So go and see what's been memorialized.
See, we've been taught that all the
people that came before us were dummies, because they didn't have
stupid rectangles, and cars, and planes, right?
They were not. And the reason you
write something down and preserve it
is so people in the future
get it, because you have
a sense of responsibility. One thing I
harp on old people, when I
bring up some eschatological point that
society is going to go a certain way, which is
usually negative to old people, you know what they usually say
to me? I don't care. I'm not
going to be here. Oh my gosh,
so you don't mind just shitting on everybody else
that's younger than you. No wonder they
throw you in nursing homes and throw diapers
on you and pump you up with drugs. You have no
value. How about a society
where the older people say
this is what I found out through my life. You need to
preserve this and carry this on to the others.
Very few these days like that. I
have no sympathy for throwing them in nursing homes,
strapping a diaper on their old ass
and pumping them up with drugs, if they have
such an attitude. And on one
of the comments, someone said, wait until
the Greek hits 50. Oh, I'm 10 years older
than the 50. Ha ha ha.
So the whole thing is, can you be objective?
Right. I've heard
the baby boomers described as
a plague of locusts.
They took, took, took and
didn't really steward
much and didn't give back much.
And that is kind of a version
of what you're talking about. Yes.
In this case, it's even worse because they
don't care about the future at all
of those that come after them. So when you look
at older things that have been memorialized
and again, you have to ask, why are they allowing this on
the surface? You know, the FBI has a
book seizure list still.
If something shows up in a public library,
university library, it's on the list to be
seized. It's not talked about.
I believe that. Yeah.
There are many things like that.
There are many old books that I've seen that I
have told people the title and the author and they look
at, I can't find it online.
So how did we forget
about all this? If the
ancient people of
Sumeria, Greece,
Egypt
had it right that there is this
relationship, this dynamic
between them and the gods,
how did it go away? Because wouldn't it
be something potent
that you could actually feel? You could get
a result. So that's a verification
that's hard to shake.
There's an intuitive sense to that
and I don't think they really had it right because
some of the overt control mechanisms
that were in place
were very harsh.
So those that had the overt
control over the society really controlled
what was right or what was wrong.
We might see certain things
right, like for example,
in ancient Egypt, if you kept a cat,
there was an official municipality
administrative body that went
and inspected that you were not
maltreating the cat, and you were
fined if you did. You see
the cat statues and things from ancient Egypt,
right? That kind of exists today,
animal control, right? They'll fine you if you
beat your dog or whatever, right?
So there's certain things you might consider right, but they
also had many other things like remedies where
they mixed cat urine and bat's
blood to cure menstrual cramps.
We wouldn't view that as being right.
No, no. So it's a
mixed bag. So if you were to put it on
the scale and this society was
30% right and 70% wrong,
you looked at the ancients,
their society would also be 30%
right, 70% wrong.
But the things that would weigh on the scale
would be different.
Okay. Do you think there is
a society or a
culture or an empire
that had it mostly right? I mean,
who would you put at the apex of
their accuracy when it comes
to the dynamics of the world
and the relationship with the gods
and just all these things that
factor in?
I may not like to say this,
but the only thing I could come across is
in the Old Testament there was a period of about
56 or so years under
certain rulership where, quote unquote,
according to the story, Israel was doing
the right thing.
So a very short time,
56 years in a span of
over 6,000, it's
yeah, right? 10% would
be 600, so it's less than that.
And what makes you say that?
What defines the right thing?
Just by reading the text.
In other words, they were in harmony
with their chief god, Yahweh, and he protected
them and gave them everything they needed.
Needed, not wanted.
So if you want to get from point A to point B,
you don't get a Ferrari, you might get a free ride
on a bus.
It's a big difference there. People think
a lot of the wealthy
people are actually better off
in this society, and I'm telling you
they're not. When Jeff Bozo
is told to go public
and make a speech about doing something, and he
refuses to do that, the next time he goes and
checks his bank balance, it's at zero.
And they know he just checked his
bank balance, and he gets a call
and he says, do you want to reconsider?
By the way, Jeff Bozo
went on recently, and he said
he's going to give all his money away.
Do you remember that, about a year ago?
I don't. After his divorce?
He says he wants to give all the money away,
$150 billion. Why?
There's an artist known as Prince.
He tried to get away
by buying some stuff in a
backpack and survival gear in some island
and got a phone call. Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Where are you going? No, no, no.
So, you know, it's just
a keystroke. There is no money, folks.
It's all private credit.
You're really screwed in that
department, in other words, the control. You can
control people through religion, but it's easier to
control them through money, because they'll never notice.
I think we've talked a little bit about how
the banking system works.
About how can the government, being
$30 trillion in debt, check for a dollar?
Can't. It's coming from
somewhere else. And people
call the money system a fraud. It's not a fraud.
Because if you ask someone who's wealthy,
how can it be a fraud? Look at all this wonderful stuff
I've gotten. No, it's a fiction.
Guess what? All your religions are
fiction. All of them.
The mainstream ones. For sure.
So you mentioned
they had it mostly right at this time period
because they were in right relation
with their chief god.
A short period. Fair. How do we
get into right relation with
our chief god? Is our chief god
something we can even
choose? Or is it
assigned to us? Is it geographic?
Is it genetic?
How is a chief god
assigned to
a person, let's say?
Where I've seen it's a matter
of choice. Like, for example, in the story
of Abraham, he did not want
anything to do with the gods of his parents
and his geography.
The short story is
paraphrasing. So he left.
I can't answer that directly,
Greg. What I can say
is it's a matter of choice.
But can you be chosen? Yes.
Okay. Do you have a chief god?
Yes. It would be Yahweh.
It would be Yahweh.
Like it or not,
he's got a lot of haters.
He does have a lot of haters.
People might say that's
part of the Abrahamic
religions, right?
Sort of. I don't like the term
Abrahamic religions because it sounds like
Abraham created these religions and he
really didn't. There's a
whole section,
many sections to
these religions. As a matter of fact, if you
look at Christianity, it's
Smithism down to the core.
So how is that Abrahamic?
Right? The Kabbalistic
practices in the Judaism,
how is that Abrahamic?
And Islam is,
you know what's interesting about Islam in the Quran,
I used to name the Syrias, I think Mandela
effect changed. It used to be Syria 26.
It says that if you're
interested in the laws of God,
I'm paraphrasing here, you need to go read what
Moses was given. So how many Muslims
put down the Quran and go read the laws
that are in the Old Testament?
If you said none, I think you said none,
right? Yeah.
You see how
twisted and bizarre this is?
Right. There's a lot of,
I guess, misinformation about
Yahweh, perhaps. Some people
think Yahweh is Lucifer. Some people
think Yahweh is the Christian
God. I just stopped paying
attention at a certain point because it's so
tied up in a crazy Gordian knot
and religion got enough of my attention
growing up when it was foisted
upon me. But why did
you choose Yahweh
as your chief God?
Simple. I went
to a seminar about how mortgages
and the money system work, you know, on the
opposing side. And I said,
well, how do they get the right to do all these
contracts and things? So it comes out
of the Bible. This is over 30 years ago
or three decades ago, 20 some odd years ago.
I said, the Bible? What are you talking
about? That was written by Shakespeare.
You know,
so I said, wait a second. I just
said something that I shouldn't have said. How can
I knock it if I've never read it?
So I just went and started reading the lawful
parts of the Bible and said, you know what?
I didn't know this was in here.
And the things that are in here are
not what people are saying.
There's a big contrast here.
No one ever mentioned any of this stuff in here.
So I had to make a decision and say, okay,
do I kind of like follow what
this thing says to do in a simplistic way
or do I listen to what everyone else is telling
me to do? You know, what's the
template for society, including the
religions? And I opted for just
taking a literal sense.
And when I say literal sense, I mean it's
pretty simple. When it
tells you basically you have three days to change
your mind, you know,
when you should eat these things and why
you should wear these things and why
you should do these things on certain days,
it's really, really simple.
And there's 613 laws in there.
A third of them are only for the
priests and the other third are for other
specific events. So it really boils down to
a handful of 50 or 60 things to
learn how to operate with.
There's actually some pretty advanced
science in there, things that they knew
about the human body that are not, just
even recently have been discovered.
And are you talking about
the King James Bible? Because we
started this talking about how it was
a false paradigm
derivative of the state and
they want to control the minds
of men.
The term God and Lord is not in
there. You have the Elohim and Yahweh,
right? You have a lot of changes
where the
concept of the Messiah has been left
out, where the Messiah defined himself as
the Aleph-Tav or the Alpha and the Omega.
That's omitted about
3,000 times. So for
example, there are so many mistakes in the
translation. Okay, let's look at it this way.
You and I write a book, we take it to the printer
and he goes through it and he says, you got
five mistakes, so before I print it, what do you
want to do? Well, let's correct them.
King James was like, we have
4,000 mistakes, what do you want to do? Oh, print
that shit right now. Hurry up, print it.
I can't respect that, sorry.
There's a type of mindset
that goes after the King James.
You know, if I mention the
Apostles, you know the time of
1st century AD, right? And King James
was 1611, right?
About 1,500 years later. I went to a Bible
study once and I kind of brought up the errors in the
King James Bible and a woman, I'll try to do
the accent right, King James Bible?
That was good enough for the
Apostle Paul, it was good enough for me.
Oh my gosh.
You can't deal with that. I can't deal
with that. Maybe you can, I can't. I gotta
leave the room. Yeah, I left
Missouri as soon as I could.
Yeah, well, I don't know if it was Missouri.
I'm here in Arizona, but that's what I got. And I was
like, okay, I'm running. I'm running away and I'm not
turning back. But it doesn't mean I'm
going to tell you it's okay if you believe in it. It's
not okay what they're doing.
U.S. Constitution is another one.
Not okay. Not okay.
Yeah,
you read that thing. You know, they did the U.S.
Constitution, by the way, it took about 10 years.
By the way, it was written and sent to the Vatican,
came back five years later to be signed.
What does that mean?
Oh, and the Bill of Rights
was done almost a decade later.
Because if they didn't do the Bill of Rights, guess what
they would have had? Another what?
Revolution.
Anyway.
Well, if we look back at history
and we try to
fold in this context
of the gods, how would you
look at our
historical narrative of the rise
and fall of various
empires and
the context of their relationship
with their gods?
That's a big one. I think that one
that would console with the Phoenix
phenomenon from archaics.
That reset that happens every 138
years or 592
or 552
or 792 years, there's these
objects in the sky that come and just wreak
havoc on the planet, would be one.
The other one would be internal
fighting, takeover.
People don't understand. More and more people
are. For example, when you
say United States of
America, Washington, D.C. is the capital,
Washington, D.C. is not part of this country.
It's a foreign enclave. Just like
in Mexico, the capital
is called district federal.
All the federal districts are
foreign to the countries that they're a part of.
Now, if that's not the beginning of the
demise of nationalism,
I don't know what is. Does it have to be
like little green men from Mars setting up
an enclave on your capital to be obvious
that it's foreign?
So, one
of the precursors to destruction
of a nation or culture
is being controlled by
a foreigner, whether it's
terrestrial or non-terrestrial.
And archaic
phoenix phenomenon is quite
interesting, just the notion that
there is some wipe
of the slate that happens every
so often from
some higher plane, whether it's
technological or not.
I assure you it's technological.
I assure you it is.
Just like magic,
I assure you magic is technological.
All magic, not some of it.
So, is this reality itself
some kind of container, Truman show,
terrarium for humanity?
Absolutely, and you will witness
that if you just look at the cross-section
of a human body.
If the intestines, they tell you food is absorbed,
nutrition is absorbed through the intestines,
look at a cross-section. How?
Do a cross-section of a firestone
steel-belted radial.
The intestines and the steel-belted
radial tire are both designed so there is no
interaction between what's inside and outside.
So how are you getting
nutrition out of food? By induction.
What is induction?
Right? Like Wi-Fi, right?
Induction stove. So everything is
energetic transfer. It goes from
energy to matter. And it goes
from energy, let's say, to a gas, to a liquid,
to a solid. And then backwards.
The solid becomes
liquid to a gas to energy.
So when you have food in your intestine,
the solid food goes to
liquid, which goes to a gas,
which goes to energy through the intestine.
Well, by induction, it appears on the other side
inside the body. It's amazing.
So it's all energetic.
Right? If you were watching
a film, a two-hour movie that was 100%
computer-generated,
and it was the top, top-notch computer
generation, it looks pretty
real to you, doesn't it? But it's all
been generated from what? Just
code.
So we're actually functioning on
code. Oh, Philip K. Dick
did a speech in France in 1977.
Almost very similar to this.
I don't know if you're familiar with it.
Philip K. Dick, the author.
I'm aware of Philip K. Dick, but I'm not
sure of which piece of his you're referencing.
There's a 1977
interview he did in France.
Talks about how we're living in code,
and you ever walk into a room
and think the light switch is here, and suddenly it's on
the other side of the wall? How did that happen?
Mandela effect kind of idea.
In the code, there's an arch
designer, and then he has
someone that is contrary,
sort of like the Matrix.
Charles Ford said something similar.
Charles Ford would say that we are
property of something of a
higher nature that we
barely even understand, we rarely even
see. Yes. In order for something
to be property, only the creator can
call it property unless he transfers that
right.
When you say something is yours, you can
transfer that right. You actually do
when you have children with a birth certificate, but anyway.
You can transfer
that right. If you don't transfer that right, you hold on
to it, it's a property of the creator.
When you create something, it's yours.
Unless you transfer it through a sale.
That's why I keep saying the universe is
commercial. You ever hear of something
called redemption in religion?
That's a commercial term.
The 30 pieces of silver,
right?
Anyway, it's all commercial.
How do we find the edges
of the container?
Going back to that Freemasonic
idea of the ladder to
the window in the sky,
which is kind of like a way to represent
getting outside of the
artificial construct. Is there
a mechanism or a way to
get beyond it or at least see
beyond it or project our conscious
awareness beyond it?
I think the latter can
happen, but now you want to be like the
crazy fish that's trying to tell all the other fish
that all the fish are really in water and they don't
see it.
We might get outside of it and then cease
to exist.
It'll be so rough that
I've spoken to people that have gone
high altitude, halo, high altitude, low
orbit, and they're like
no, it's nothing like you've been shown.
That's interesting to me. Do they see
curvature up there?
Yes and no.
You don't see the sun.
You only see it through the atmosphere.
Things get very, very strange.
Have you heard about the cosmonauts that were
sent up there?
People who have really gone up there
have to be sequestered for days and days because
of the voices in their heads and all the dead people
that they met up there.
Have you heard of that?
I've heard the cliff notes, but elaborate
on that for people listening to the parts that you
found interesting.
That's about it.
The dead people, right?
I don't know much more about it.
There's a guy named John Rapoport who talked about that
a while back.
You don't see the sun
when you get beyond the atmosphere.
That's an interesting concept.
Just like if you have a
flashlight in the dark, you don't see the beam.
You only see what it shines on.
The sun is like an induction.
When you have an induction stovetop,
the glass top, the water
boiling, you move it, you put your hand on there,
there's nothing, you put the pot back on there,
it starts boiling again. You need the atmosphere.
Do you ever notice how the sun
changes color depending on where it is and size
where it is in the sky?
If you were to remove some of the atmosphere
where the sun is, it would just look black.
You won't see the sun in a vacuum.
It needs a medium.
Exactly.
The eye is not enough of a medium.
It has to appear outside of the eye.
Eric P. Dollard talked about this
on some of his
decade ago videos.
We don't know what the sun is, but it definitely
works by induction.
Eric Dollard is a trip.
I've had the pleasure of interviewing him a couple
of times. He's quite a character.
Somewhat difficult to interview.
Sometimes I miss things
that he might have said that are pretty insightful.
Some of the best interviews should be
difficult, correct?
Fair enough.
I'm really
interested in insights from people
who've gotten a little bit outside the game.
When you listen to the
astronauts talking at the
press conference post-Apollo missions,
if there even was anything to
that at all, they seem like
they're in a trance. You ask them
simple questions. What did
the stars look like? They look at
each other like, what am I supposed to say
to this question? It's just a simple question.
What did the stars look like to you
from the moon? I can't remember
if I saw them. That's an
odd thing to say.
This recurs over
and over. The Kennedy
assassination, any official
talking about what happened on
the World Trade Center on 9-11,
same reaction. Just study
the psychological reactions.
There's something that they know. They don't get
the whole picture, but this is what they're
told they should say. You get that same
reaction that the astronauts did.
They were on a stage with an audience, I believe.
That's what you're referring to, the astronauts.
They all look like their dog and their
mom died and their wife left them.
Really bad news.
They didn't seem like
they were happy that they
just did this monumental thing that
you would think would be a major life achievement.
They looked like they were in the principal's office
being punished.
They were. Yes, exactly like
that. One of the worst things that
the elite can have is people develop
their maturity.
What people mistake is that
when you see someone, you know, adolescent,
adult, 50s, 60s, or 70s, they think,
oh, they're grown-ups. They call them adults.
I'm telling you, I could prove that
99.9999% of the people that
you'll ever see or meet have not
matured beyond 9 or 12 years old.
When you gave that principal
analogy, you can take
a 75-year-old and talk to him like he's
a 9-year-old and he'll behave just like
a 9-year-old.
Yeah, I believe that.
Watch the news. Watch the mainstream
news. Are they speaking to adults
or speaking to children?
Yeah, it seems like they're speaking to children
for sure. The Archon
mentioned
the relationship, or at least
looking at corporate
logos and the names of
corporations, and they can often be
esoteric or relate
to the gods.
Is there a mechanism
there where a person, if
they wanted to be an entrepreneur and start
a company, might get some extra
energetic juice by naming
it after a god? Yeah, definitely.
Ask the Archon.
What do you think, Archon?
I think that these things belong
to their own secret art that's
hard to parse.
I would imagine that if you asked the CEO of
Nike why he named his corporation after
a Greek goddess, he would just shrug off
the notion or just say that he
did it on a whim.
It's either that certain people are
inspired externally from places
that they don't know where
and are just being puppeted into doing certain
things, because then those
corporations can act as
some type of
manifestation or testament
to the existence of the supernatural,
or those people are just plugged
into their own secret societies
and networks and are acting on the
basis of the imperatives that are given there.
It's hard to say.
I don't think that if I started a corporation
today and named it after a deity, that
that necessarily gives it juice, because
realistically, I don't serve the deity.
I would imagine
that either that would come
to a point of failure
or I would come to a crossroads
where perhaps I would have to make a decision
whether I want to pledge allegiance to this thing that
I profess or not. Greg,
I'd like to give a handy-dandy tip for all the
listeners. It'll just take a minute or so
regarding corporates and sigils,
if you would. This is super practical,
right? It's as practical as
if you drive a car, what's the best windshield
wiper, right? Trivial but
practical, okay?
They have these things called corporate logos, and pretty
much if you go to the shops and buy grocery
shopping, things you eat, or things you
cleaning products, or whatever,
even labels on cars and devices,
corporate logos, they all
try to be distinct to each other. What I'm suggesting
is that these are sigils, like fractals,
antennas that are constantly broadcasting
a mal-intent from these corporations,
like curses.
I've done this experiment several times.
A total NPC person that worked for an
aircraft company that designs weapons
and things, she had no clue. She didn't want to hear
anything about, if it wasn't on CNN or
Fox News or whatever, did not exist,
right? Or if her doctor didn't tell her.
She had all these physical maladies they couldn't
figure out. By the way, when doctors
can't figure out what's wrong, they say,
you have an unknown virus and they chalk you off with
painkillers and antibiotics,
right? So someone said, Greek, why don't you
go do this experiment with her? So I said to her,
can I go through your house,
everything in your house, if there's anything private
go and remove it right now, otherwise
give me permission to go through everything in your
house. She says, yes. So what I did
was I had one of those big fat graffiti
markers, the felt pens, they're about an inch wide,
right, for tagging.
I went through every product she had,
everywhere in her house, and I
struck through the corporate logo,
Arm & Hammer baking soda,
soap, everything. The blender,
it said Oster. I just put a line through
it, blocked it out.
Walked into the house. How does it feel?
I don't know, but it does feel
better. Guess what? Within a few days,
her ailments started going away. It doesn't work
with everyone, but it does work.
I've had some very sensitive,
do you hear of sensitives? You know, like, oh, I'm
sensitive, I'm psychic, I'm whatever.
Done the same thing to their home
and they walked in and
I got a phone call from them. They were crying.
They were like, my house feels so good. People come over.
I don't know. I said, I noticed you put some
marks through the things here. I said, that's
exactly it. I explained it.
Inside the stupid rectangle, cell phones
and things, you have something called a fractal antenna.
They're kind of like snowflakes,
some of them, interesting to look at.
These sigils, what I'm suggesting
and have indirectly proven,
these corporate logos, now let
me ask you this. Is design
of a corporate logo a trivial thing or do you think
a tremendous amount of attention goes into
it? I think attention goes into it,
yes. Yeah, yeah. Why? Because it's
constantly broadcasting curses.
When I say curses, use that
word however you want to use it conservatively
or loosely. They hate you, in other words.
So, how do they get to
you? The way that you will never figure out.
So, just
go ahead and put a piece
of black electrical tape, felt tip
marker, cut it out, and
notice how the environment changes.
Yeah. That's the handy dandy tip.
I'm looking around and I'm
on an Apple computer
with a Logitech
webcam. Logi
is like the logos. I'm
talking through an Apollo
twin universal audio interface
and it's all around us
and I just think like... Yeah, just cover it.
Well, yeah. In this instance,
I should and could, but
I think about a person who
wants to use this to
their benefit without going evil
necessarily. They don't have to
align themselves with dark gods
as the Archons said
when you ask a person
why they named their company Nike, they'd
say, well, it was just arbitrary.
Well, is that just what they're telling the public
for public consumption or were
they puppeted? And if they were puppeted,
it doesn't seem so bad
to be puppeted by the right entity
if you can kind of ride
them like a barnacle on a whale to
a successful promised land
to a good flourishing
life. And I think about
this show, for example. I called
it the Higher Side Chats. What if I had called
it the Apollo Hour?
Where would I be now? Or
there's other people I've spoken to
who would say that the creation
of the show and the generation of energy
creates an egregore out there
and now it is its own thing
and it is a thought form that
people tap into and that you can create
endless thought forms in the abyss.
You don't have to necessarily
name it after something that is already
established. What do you think about the dynamics
there?
I think you've answered it as well as
within the question as a statement, a statement as
a question. I'll give you an example in terms
of nature of reality.
You know, science and scientists cannot
explain when you face two mirrors together why
you get that infinity image happening.
And you know how you've heard people
in certain Judaic practices, when they
did certain prayers on certain holy days,
they would cover all the mirrors because they're supposedly
like portals, right?
So you can take these various
simple aspects and move them
forward however your
imagination allows you.
And your education, by the way, because you must
be educated and that
doesn't mean going to school
unless you're a fish, of course.
Then you have no choice.
So another thing I think about
with the elite and the
billionaire class and the CEOs
and this dynamic with
the gods and the gods wanting
attention
and the elite secret
religion tends
to suggest that they get
benefits in this life
from honoring certain gods
that aren't really even in the
public sphere of consciousness at all.
If the gods really want
attention, I would almost
think that by their
logic they would punish the elite
for denying the masses
knowledge of
them and thus an energy generation
that could be much greater.
Yes, that does. I believe that happens as well.
Just, I don't know how to
drill this in the mind of everyone,
but there aren't just a few gods.
There might be more gods
than there are people. I would think
so. I would say, yeah, almost infinite.
Yeah, so how many
variety of combinations
of attitudes and behaviors can you have with all
the people on earth, right?
I know in statistics, if you just have 20
objects, that could be thousands of combinations,
right? So yes,
I think all of that, basically,
the maxim that I use is
the law comes from your god and law doesn't
mean taxes and traffic law. It can mean that
as well. And
if you want to get into that subject, just like
any subject, you're going to have to study a little
bit. I think I
brought up the analogy recently with
the plandemic,
what knowledge does. I might
have given this analogy before.
Nurses set up a table to give people
the shot. And I was with someone who was
one of these anti-vaxxers and was yelling at
the nurses, right? And what did they do,
the nurses? They laughed at him. You know, you're one
of these crazy loose wingnuts that
wants people to die from disease.
Well, I go up to the nurse and I said, well,
before you perform the
injection, do you take in consideration
the age, body weight, and blood type
of who you're giving it to?
Because that's according to the NIH study.
She looked at me in panic, and the other
nurses, the younger ones, wanted to also make
fun of me. And she says, no, we have to go.
And they packed up everything and left.
So which one was more effective,
the protest or the actual
this is what you're supposed to be
doing, right?
The latter.
Any religious quote-unquote person,
this is what I find with most Christians,
if I show them, let's say, you go by the Bible.
Yeah. So I show them what they're doing is
absolutely contrary. I say, well, I don't need the Bible.
I could believe without that. So where are you getting your information?
Just making it up
as we go.
Same with scientists.
Well, this has been really
super fascinating. We're obviously getting
close to the end of the road.
And I just want to ask again, maybe,
how people who are listening can
use this information
if they have this context.
We see a relationship with
corporations and the elite
with the gods,
and we know there might be something there,
but yet we haven't really
been able to identify a certain
god that we think would benefit us.
Maybe there is really no
sense in doing that because the god
doesn't care, though they do want our attention.
So it starts to get a little hairy
as to how this information
can be used. We can avoid the false
paradigms, but how do we take
advantage of the correct paradigm
for ourselves?
Oh, wow. I can't answer that directly.
I'm not going to confabulate.
I can't answer that directly.
It's a matter of choice, and it's a matter of what degree
of time and effort you want to
dedicate to educate yourself on any
matter, especially this one.
Fair. Well, you have
found value in Yahweh
and making that your chief god,
and I'd assume there's a logic
as to why you did that compared
to others, and you mentioned the laws.
But when a person's trying to make that
decision for themselves,
where would you, I guess, advise them to
start that
seeking process? Simple.
The value of any god to me is what they're
transmitting to you in terms of what to do
as a human. I'm oversimplifying that
statement, paraphrasing that statement.
So I would suggest to do what I did,
not because I did it,
and being egocentric or anything, but
when I was telling people the Bible was
written by Shakespeare, that was, I don't know,
something I heard and was repeating.
How can I knock a movie I haven't seen, right?
And I know a bad, if I
can't go more than 15 minutes into a film,
I'm not going to watch the rest. I won't say it's a
bad film, I'll just say I couldn't watch more than
15 minutes, right? Same thing
with the Bible. Just go find out
where the laws, what you could be
doing, what's considered lawful
or set apart, and
see if that jives with you, because
there is a certain jive.
People ask,
what's your favorite color? Does it have
to be blue for everyone? No.
You see?
If it jives with you, guess what?
Have fun.
I'm having a lot of fun and had a lot of fun with it.
Fair. Well, let me ask the Archon
before we go.
Have you incorporated this
information and distilled it down
into a personal relationship
with some kind of god or gods
or chief god, or
just use this in the way that
you've decided to live your life?
Well, I'm still
in the process of
coming to the ultimate realization
of which direction to go in.
I've found that there's
not much benefit to be had in rushing these
things and trying to adopt
the nearest truth
to you, because truth
often comes in puzzle pieces anyway.
I would much rather have
a more complete assemblage of pieces
come together so that I can make
those choices with a sort of
calm mind.
I have found that what I've learned through
Godspeak and from speaking with the
Greek largely does
conform to the closest truth
that I have at the moment, but I also know that
there's levels above that, and
I'm sort of still doing my own
strivings to get to those places.
But the primacy of the biblical text
as something that should be studied
and should be contemplated, for me, has
become self-evident.
I don't think it's a coincidence that
the Christian religion, even though it's
mostly based on fallacy
and improper translation of the
source documents, has ultimately ruled
over the major
power bases of the world for the last 2,000
years, and I don't think that's by coincidence.
I also don't think it's a coincidence that
Islam takes a lot of its
genesis from the Old Testament
and sort of goes in its own direction with it.
And those are obviously the two
biggest religions, so
there's a lot of anecdotal evidence that speaks for
that being something that people should consider.
I consider it quite heavily.
But then you also have to build your
understanding out from that, and
I'm in the process still.
It's hard to understand the logic and
all the rules and understand where
the thing might have been
mistranslated and if that's even
what they meant with certain things,
but I agree that there's something
interesting about its potency
given all the different things
that have been written and all the people who have lived
in the different eras, that it still
has so much
energy behind it.
Yeah, that is in itself interesting
for sure. And it sounds like
you're still waiting to be courted
for the big dance by some god.
I put myself in that category
as well, and maybe
we are our own god, some people
say.
Well, I mean, the structure of the human story
regardless of where you go, whether
it's Mesopotamian traditions or
mainstream religion or whatever, generally
tends to be the same if you really zoom
out really far, that there was
some type of an ideal situation
at the beginning of so-called
time, or at least the beginning of some
chronology, and then some cataclysm occurs
and people fall into this sort of history
of mortality and suffering and limitation,
but there's a mode of being that will
eventually come to transcend that.
And then ultimately you have to decide
what blueprint is the most
accurate for delineating
the details within that story, but
certainly the biblical text is a good starting place.
Well said.
Right on. Well, again, really
interesting. I appreciate the insights.
Lots to ponder.
Is there a next step for you guys
or any other topics or categories
you might tackle with a new website
or links to give people before we call
it in? Well, I would say that
Godspeak, you know, was
a follow-up effort to the Greekspeak website.
Having concluded the
Greekspeak podcast in 2018, I felt that we
left certain things unexplored.
You know, themes around religions,
the supernatural, etc.
Greekspeak.com wasn't really the right venue
to discuss that, so we did
the Godspeak podcast covering
a variety of topics. Unfortunately,
we did fall short of the desired
10 episodes, simply because things
ran out of steam. But in order to
not leave the entire enterprise
hanging, and especially after our last
appearance on your show, I
decided to set up a Patreon to
make available most of the Greeks' past
recordings, not only with Godspeak and
Greekspeak, but also previous
internet radio shows that he was on.
And so, for people
that have an interest in hearing things
that the Greek has spoken of in the past
and also want to hear what he's talking
about currently in his solo streams,
you can go to patreon.com
slash Greekspeak with a G-R-E-E-K.
We have a $25 tier
there where you can get access to both the past
stuff and the most current ones if you're interested
to hear more.
Right on. I like it. I'm sure there will
be plenty of people who want to
dive deeper and will
hop on the Patreon.
And I appreciate your time,
guys. Greek, any final words?
Oh, no. I just want to thank you for being a very
intelligent host with great questions.
I try. It's hard.
It's hard, but I'm holding on.
Yeah, I'm ready to
put it down and give my brain a break.
So, thanks, guys. Enjoy the rest
of your day and take care.
Oh, thank you. It's been a pleasure.
Praise
be to ye higher side chatters,
the return of the Archon
and the Greek. This was a weird
one for me
because it just seemed a little
difficult to get on the same
page. You know, I tend
to dig deep into a body of work
and try to extract the best parts
and bring that to you.
And when I listened to the Godspeak series,
there were some interesting things in the episodes
about the big three religions, but
by far my favorite parts
were in the first episode
after the introduction titled
The Ancient World,
which is described as a discussion
on matters concerning ancient empires,
lost technology, and
mystery schools.
Well, I loved it, and I tried to set
the Greek up to get further into
that material, but I guess I didn't
realize how long ago that was
recorded. The Archon told me that
was years ago. But in it
they talk about the rise and
fall of empires being united
by a common god,
these powerful spiritual forces
welling up energy behind
groups of people that pay homage,
and it really painted
the gods as, like, the
directors of the human play.
I would go check that out
if you're looking for a little more after
finishing this.
But it seems like the Greeks' thoughts
and positions have evolved a bit
since then, and granted,
when you come out of the gate citing
archaics, I know we're going deep,
but we almost worked backwards
from a deep and wild and unique
place of the gods just being
ancient humans manipulating
us with technology
to settling on Yahweh
as the Greeks' chief god,
which I thought was a little
unexciting. I mean, we want
the truth, we want people to be honest,
but I also sometimes want that
truth to be
unexpected, outside the box,
etc., etc.
So the gods being advanced
humans basically
makes the Abrahamic religions cargo
cults, and I'm into that.
It didn't take me long to wrap my head
around that unexpected
perspective and go with it.
It's just not exactly what I had prepared
for. I wanted to get
deeper into understanding the beings on
the astral plane and their interactions
on the physical plane.
Because as the archon
finally stepped in to say, it's not
either or. It seems like we're dealing
with both. And that's
where I would get lost at times in
this. I wouldn't be sure if the Greek
was speaking of ancient humans
on our plane that are using manipulation
to seem like something greater
or the literal
beings who call the astral plane
home. We seem
to be bouncing
back and forth quite a bit.
So, I don't know. Lots of
interesting threads woven throughout
this, but not
so much overall
cohesion, I guess.
If you see the video clips from
this episode, you might notice
that I don't think I've ever
referenced my outline less
in an interview. I barely
looked down at it at all,
because it just quickly became irrelevant
and it was clear the direction of the interview
was pretty far from the direction of the
outline that I prepared, and that's fine.
Like, I want to be well prepared,
but I'm happy to go with the flow.
I actually talked to
the archon a bit afterwards
and mentioned my disappointment
with the Yahweh conclusion,
and he said that he totally
understands why
I would feel that way, and it's very bittersweet,
because there is a lot of
interesting and compelling information
behind the why
in choosing Yahweh
that we didn't really get to,
and I agree, that is bittersweet,
but it's alright. It happens.
Of course, we fit everything
we could into the first hour, but we went
much deeper in the plus show
for those who like to get the full interviews
and like to keep me employed.
You miss a lot when you
only hear the first free hour, and there are
no breaks to sell you therapy sessions
or athletic greens or any
of that stuff, so I try
to keep it action-packed either way.
And this is a tangent, but
I feel better than ever about the
no ads decision. There are two
big stories right now about agencies
that have screwed over podcasters
and just kept the money after they read the ads.
Plus, a lot of these
products are turning out
to be pretty lackluster,
and podcasters
will read you any ad as long as they
get paid, and to me, that
erodes the relationship. I don't want
to abuse our relationship
by just selling you any old thing
except more of
the show that you already like.
Manscaped razors, trash,
the lords and ladies
of Ireland buy a square foot
of land thing. That was exposed as
a scam. And you can go
watch nutritionalists break
down what's in athletic greens
or Prime. It seems like
their claims are wildly over
exaggerated for what they are.
Foam mattresses? Not that great either.
Yet these podcasters
will say, I start
every morning with athletic greens and I've
never felt better.
Or, I got a Satva mattress
and I'm getting the best sleep of my life.
And these are just lies.
And there should be some
consequences. We just roll our eyes
and let it happen, but
I'm not into that. Blue chews
and keeps these hair and dick pills.
Who knows what else they do to
the body over time.
Has any podcaster even thought to
ask about long-term studies
or side effects before hawking
this shit to their audience? Or do they just ask
how much you're going to pay me?
It seems like most people,
podcasters and their audiences
just don't care.
They see it as a
necessary evil, but I'm trying to
prove it's not necessary.
And to me, integrity is important.
So I think a second-hour
subscription is the best
monetization method in
podcasting for the kind of show
that I do.
I hope you guys agree and sign up to hear
more. 7-day free trial to start
you off in over a decade of
archived episodes to dig into.
Sign up right from the
top link in your show notes.
Or go through the Patreon to get
THC Plus on Spotify.
Speaking of Patreon, the
Archon also wanted me to emphasize that
they have a lot of great content on their
Patreon as well.
Many years of the Greek dropping
knowledge on a whole host of topics.
I find them to be a pretty compelling
speaker, and I've added
a link to that if you want more
from them as well.
And that said, I'm still very busy
at home, so I'm going to be quick with this,
but let's look at the meetup calendar.
September 22nd,
we got a meetup in
Alamosa, Colorado at the Purple
Pig. Also September
22nd, a PlayStation
Virtual Meetup.
Interesting. September
24th, the Hurricane Club
meeting at Made West Brewing
in Ventura, California.
September 29th,
Two Pitchers Brewing in Oakland.
September 30th,
a New Zealand meetup
in Auckland.
And also September 30th, the
Columbia, Missouri Twin Lakes
meetup in conjunction
with the No Agenda listeners.
Very cool.
It is a great way to build your network
on the sort of common ground that will
be important going forward.
Lots of lonely people out there.
Well, do something about it.
Make an event at a fun gathering place
in your hometown, support a local
business, give them a plug
on the air, and find the others.
All totally available to you
and free. Seems like a
quadruple win if I've ever heard one.
With that said, big
thanks again to our guests.
Check out GreekSpeak and Godspeak.com
and their Patreon for
more. And with that,
I've done my part. Your move,
ancient manipulators, spiritual
puppet masters, and agents of the
higher realms. Your
fuckin' move.
to see
my favorite show
makes me more aware
who could
it be
the higher side
chats THC
just watch the
TV and obey
take
some more pills when you're
blue
or we'll break you out of the
spell that you're in
together we will make
it through
believe it or not
the truth is out there
for people who have the eyes
to see
my favorite show
makes me more aware
who could
it be
the higher side chats
THC
seeking the things
that are true
THC
is here for you
believe it
or not
believe
it or not
the truth is out there
for people who have the eyes
to see
my favorite show
makes me more aware
who could
it be
the higher side
chats
believe it or not
the truth is out there
for people who have the eyes
to see
my favorite show
makes me more aware
who could
it be
the higher side chats
THC