That's true, Dr. Zayas.
Here we go from the Sunshine State.
I'm Greg Carlwood, and do you ever feel like life has lost its meaning?
That so much time and attention is sucked up by the construct and the cage conveniently placed around our ability to do almost anything?
A litany of limiting factors that are largely artificial but hold us back nevertheless?
Money, time, employment, bureaucracy, logistics, and the always flashy and seductive screen-based everything tend to steal the majority of any given lifetime.
And few people ever even ask what life might actually be for or challenge the monstrous matrix of the capstone cabal.
Well, if the game has been to make people ignorant of or even enjoy their servitude, then someone somewhere is certainly winning.
But today we're going to unpack a lot of what plagues us, examine the suppressed or hidden mechanisms that drive the unadulterated world,
and try to get a bead on that almighty truth with a capital T by talking with a couple of knowledgeable and philosophical free thinkers
who lay out much of their mindset and positions on various subjects through the website Greekspeak.com,
where the majority of the content, insights, and ideas come from a man known as the Greek.
And the website and methodical presentation of the material is laid out by his associate, the Archon.
There you can find detailed articles and podcast episodes covering everything from cosmic censorship, communication, and education,
to the corrupted sciences, food and diet, the economy, the legal system, and more.
I've certainly enjoyed their work and learned a lot from the insights and curious anecdotes of the Greek, and I'm psyched to get into it with them today.
The Greek-speak architects, intellectual explorers of everything, and cultural critics, the Archon and the Greek, welcome to the Higher Side.
Oh, thanks for having us, Matt.
Yes, thanks for having us, Greg.
Yeah, this is going to be great. I have heard hours of your material, talking together, and enjoyed it quite a lot.
You cover pretty much all aspects of life, culture, and society.
And I've heard the Greek describe himself as someone who's just visiting the Earth and taking notes, which I like.
But what can you guys tell us about how you forged this relationship, your goals for the Greek-speak venture,
and ultimately, where you've cultivated your knowledge and wisdom that people will find there?
Oh, just to give a sort of brief intro, first of all, thank you for having us.
I am the Archon, which is just really a harmless pseudonym for my youth that I used for making content on the Internet.
So as far as how we became acquainted, some years back, I had heard of the Greek from the appearances that he made on different Internet radio programs,
be that Freeman Fly or elsewhere, and so I eventually reached out to learn more.
And we would discuss the subjects that he had brought up, ranging from politics to science to finance.
But more than anything else, he was really able to unpack the nature of everyday life as a sort of mirage that's being upheld by various institutions,
like the media and pop culture, and also to objectify that as something that was malevolent in its origins,
which most people don't pay attention to.
And so, you know, that just led to more conversations over the years, and I would eventually create the Greek-speak website,
which I will specify has a unique spelling of S-P-E-E-K at the end, so not S-P-E-A-K,
Greekspeak.com, and, you know, compiled some articles there, and we later did a podcast on these various subjects,
so anyone can check that out at their leisure.
And yeah, I'll let the Greek sort of elaborate on where he's at now and some of the projects that he has going on.
Oh, okay. I'm at the same place I was pretty much when I came into this world,
still trying to figure things out and just trying to describe what we can garner and gain from our perception.
I would say the lifelong endeavors and experiences that we have here are all based on our input,
whatever we get basically from our parents, society, on and on and on.
And when we look for an equivalent, a physical equivalent or a perceivable equivalent in the world to what we've been told,
it's sort of hard to find, so we have to sit back and just trust what we've been told and go along with it.
I think the human on the planet right now, I call them surface-dwelling earth inhabitants,
and very specific about that, because there's much more than just being on the surface, is very, very domesticated.
And just to cut to the chase, back in, I think, the recent 2020 events that happened,
showed very much, let's say an example, literally what happens when you have a domesticated being.
How difficult would it be, for example, if you have some domesticated beings, we call them pets,
and it's not convenient to have them anymore, you just put them down, don't you, right?
And no one really balks about that too much.
So that's just a very quick cut to the chase kind of point of how to perceive things.
And again, I say I'm just visiting this planet taking notes, because how else can one objectify?
Pretty much the point of view that I have is when you become objective,
you are sort of on the sidelines, but still a participant in the field, let's say.
One of the things that I constantly harp on is if everyone wanted to just turn everything on the planet,
the entire society into a paradise, I'd say, have at it, but I want nothing to do with it.
And if you all just wanted to destroy each other and create utter chaos, have at it, I want nothing to do with it,
is the stance that I usually take.
I like it. And you say surface-dwelling earth inhabitants.
Well, that is a curious phrase, specifically surface-dwelling.
This is not where I plan to go with this, but I am really intrigued by things that could exist or life underneath the surface.
What say you?
Oh, clearly evident. You know, here's the metaphor that's the overarching metaphor.
Okay, Greg, I just built a new house, okay, and I have new furniture coming, right? Why not?
And furniture truck arrives. Do I place all of the furniture on the roof and just live on the roof all year long?
Or do I put them inside the house and live inside where I have the comfort and control of, you know, living in the house offers?
I mean, if you had someone place all their furniture, bedroom, living room, whatever, on the roof of a building,
they're subject to all the surface weather attacks, lack of privacy, right?
But an intelligent being would definitely dwell inside, if that makes any sense.
So, you know, we're sort of subject to the, however you want to take it,
visuals that were given by, quote-unquote, NASA and government agencies of what's going on, let's say, quote-unquote, with other planets.
And they all look barren on the surface.
And that's a clear mark of a potential of a highly evolved society that would be dwelling inside the house instead of on the surface.
Very simple analogy there for me.
Yeah, yeah. You know, I've used the analogy of nature and what it creates and basically, you know, fruits.
Look at fruits. Like, they're always far more interesting inside than outside.
You look at an orange, it's just a rind on the outside.
All the good stuff is in the middle.
And nature seems to produce things that are within that kind of framework.
So, what about the Earth itself?
Wouldn't the most interesting parts be inside based on what nature tends to produce?
And we now know there are forests and giant oceans inside the surface.
So, I agree with you that it's logical to be inside, but not all things that are logical actually happen.
What do you think is actually down there?
Or what could you say about a potential intelligent being being down there?
Another branch off of humanity perhaps?
Sure. I would suggest that do I have a direct relationship that I knowingly know from beings from there?
I would say no.
But we have lots of, let's call them myths and legends for those that want to subscribe to that.
No, I don't have any direct knowledge.
But I would suggest basic logic and reasoning using the roof and furniture analogy to be a place to go.
And the criticism that I offer to the public at large is basically what I see on the surface.
That's why I denote it as surface-dwelling Earth inhabitants.
There's many ways to go with that.
So, we're just on the surface of a very, very dynamic thing.
Just like if you look at fruit, for example, it's more interesting on the inside.
One thing is the silent power of things that grow.
It's incredible when you look at things that grow, trees, fruit, plants, and so on, that are attached to the Earth.
It's the conversion, let's say, or transmutation of water and soil into these wonderful things based on the topography or the program in the seed.
You can have the same soil and water, and the programming of the seed will yield whatever corresponding fruit there is.
And it's basically an atomic transmutation into all these things.
And it's extremely dynamic, yet it's silent, very quiet.
And it's, like you said, very interesting on the inside.
And they all bear a geometric structure that have more in common than we give it.
For example, the apples and oranges analogy, meaning they're very different, but they do share an archetype, a geometry that's very similar.
And I would say that if we go back to the surface, there's also a dynamic that's very much shared there.
If you look at all the cultures on the Earth, for example, they're diverse based on various histories.
And even if you look at the corresponding current culture of all the surface-dwelling Earth inhabitants of various nations or so,
they carry on things from their history and their culture.
But the thing that they all have in common is their gullibility.
And those that seem to have the upper hand and control of, let's say, the One World Earth or the One World Order kind of concept rely on people's gullibility.
And unfortunately, people are very reliable.
Yeah, well said. No argument here.
So in the cosmic censorship episode, the Greek says we need to ask the philosophical question,
is man supposed to be as he is today, essentially property, numbered, labeled, and controlled?
Well, I think most of us listening would agree that we've been captured,
but getting a handle on how man is supposed to be outside of this capture is harder to identify.
What would you say about that, the way things should be or even could be?
Yeah, I would suggest that the overarching criticism or what we see the condition, the overarching condition,
here's the hard part, is supposed to be the way it is right now at this time.
One loose analogy would be when you have an infant, do they usually need diaper changes and what happens if you don't, right?
And because their diapers are being changed and it's kind of critical,
what happens if they're ignored or left to their own volition, let's say?
It's not going to work out well.
So I would say that things are the way they're supposed to be now,
but there is something about, let's just say, the voluntary nature of things.
I use that very loosely because most things are in that category.
We choose to be that way.
So I would offer there's a gradient or different levels of choices that can be made
that you can actually be the baby that needs the diaper change or not.
And that's where I instill the concept of cosmic censorship, meaning it's not tangible.
It's something that is a limit on each individual and with the society as a whole.
But even though it's overarching and intangible,
once it's acknowledged that there is a limitation that pretty much leads to the gullibility,
it can pretty much be almost dealt with at that point.
There's not much else you have to do but acknowledge that you are being censored.
And I do find that term provocative, cosmic censorship.
You don't say elite cabal censorship.
This kind of implies a layer of deception or blockage from truth at a level higher than human even.
Where does that come from and how has it affected humanity throughout the ages?
Well, I would say where it comes from maybe at this point is not important.
Just like when, let's say, something is delivered to your home, again, the furniture,
you can pretty much, through labeling and loose association, say,
well, this came from here and it was made by these individuals.
But there's so much more involved in that.
And then there's the point where you could be completely removed.
And, you know, many American children are asked where milk comes from,
and they say, well, it comes from the store, right?
So at this point I don't have a direct answer for that,
but I do see through the commonality the transcultural, transnational,
transhistoric effects of this being persistent throughout society.
So I'm not so sure of the source of it.
And I think giving it cosmic, which harkens back to the Greek word meaning worldly, basically,
but not just limited to man's world.
Fair enough. Yes, it makes me think about just the structure of reality.
And you'll hear a lot of gurus and spiritualists talk about a soul school,
that this reality is somewhat structured to be a process of enlightenment or curiosity or exploration.
And cosmic censorship kind of speaks to me as something adjacent to a process of discovery,
that it can be discovered if you get away from all the distractions that are put in front of us
and you actually explore the natural reality.
Things will be revealed to you in layers or systematically.
What do you think about that?
Well, yes, and when you describe something having layers, it still comes to you as a whole, doesn't it?
And you could almost look at all the layers at once and then just zero in and focus on one, if you'd like.
But unfocusing on the layers and just looking at the whole package as it comes to you,
then you'll notice that what the whole package has in similarity is that all these layers are contained in it.
And even though they do look different, they tend to be repeats, just maybe cross-hatched or going across each other,
but they're repeats of almost the same thing amongst all the layers.
I see that.
We sound very philosophical right now, by the way. We haven't bitten into any meat and bones yet.
Oh, well, here comes the meat.
So one of my favorite subjects that you guys have unpacked is the episode on science,
really just how various scientific disciplines have been co-opted and controlled.
The most interesting aspect to me in all of this is what's been lost
in trying to restore these discarded disciplines like alchemy or a better understanding of natural biology
or seemingly exotic technologies.
And let's start with the technologies, the real nuts and bolts, literally,
because we hear about anti-gravity devices and the work of people like T. Townsend Brown.
I've heard the Greek mention the NIMSA group, something not a lot of people talk about.
Well, what can you tell people about some of the examples of technologies and really transportation systems
that have been kept from them in exchange for metered, highly controllable systems that limit how free we could actually be?
Wow, okay. In this case, again, if I brought up something as simple as electricity,
yes, you walk into a room, it's dark, you reach over on the wall, hit a switch, and the light comes on, right?
All the way, you know, used in every way you can imagine from what they call power plants to, you know, batteries not included.
They still are able or not able to describe exactly or explain what it is.
They can describe it, but they cannot explain it.
That is a perfect example of the intangible being relied on and how it affects the way we live.
In terms of transportation, just to, let's say, jump to the most important part, the buzzword is anti-gravity, isn't it?
It seems like once we have that to our avail, we won't need roads and supposedly we won't need the fuels we use and all this other stuff.
There's an understanding of gravity that is, let's say, a misunderstanding.
In other words, the understanding that we're given makes it unworkable.
First of all, many people call it a force.
And if you look at the actual referencing of gravity, it is not a force.
It's simply an acceleration.
We kind of examine it as a force because when we, let's say, drop a brick on our foot, we feel the force of that brick.
But that's not gravity.
That is the brick accelerating through gravity, and then the final force is the contact with your foot.
So just like, for example, let's say back to transportation devices, one thing that you look at, I don't like calling them automobiles because they're not really autonomous.
They're engine-driven wagons, okay?
And not motor vehicles because motor means electric.
Engine is the way we use them, but we're going into the motors now anyway.
One of the things, one of the fads with those things is to make them more aerodynamic so you have less drag, right?
All right.
So it seems like everything in nature seems to be about resistance.
And if you have, let's say, three portals or three openings and an object is to go through one of those openings, it will naturally choose the one that offers what?
The least resistance, right?
Give an example.
I think it's Scientific American in the mid-1800s or later part of the 19th century did an article about a 600-mile-per-hour subway car in New York City.
Are you familiar with this?
Have you heard it?
No, I haven't.
Yeah.
I think it's like 1870-something.
Don't hold me.
I'm just paraphrasing.
Scientific American, when they just first came out, 600-plus-mile-per-hour underground subway car.
Well, it sounds like, what?
What is he talking about, right?
Yeah.
It was not a very long stretch.
What they did was it was basically air-driven.
They pushed air behind the subway car and they created a vacuum in front of it.
So as long as the air pushing behind it and the vacuum in front of it were in balance, it doesn't matter how fast it's moving.
It will never see any resistance, right?
And this was achieved 150-plus years ago, and it was used as an example.
Of course, it was shelved and put away.
So when we go back to the meme of the anti-gravity, if it's an acceleration, well, what is it?
It's very simple.
Nature always sets up movements based on levels of pressure and direction.
So in essence, if we sense that the gravity is pulling us down, well, we're moving, let's say, from a high altitude to a low altitude.
That is an illusion that we're being pulled.
How about the idea that there is this ephemeral force, or it could be empirical, known as the aether.
And away from the Earth, the pressure is higher, and as we go closer to the Earth, the pressure is lower.
So we're actually just feeling a pressure gradient.
So once this is understood, where we just decrease the resistance on one end and increase the resistance on the other,
we have motion towards the direction of the decreased resistance.
And this is the basis of electricity, of what they call gravity, of what we call even just air conditioning vents,
the way the air moves into the room and returns back to the air conditioner to get recirculated again.
It's all about differences in pressure.
And once this is taught as the basics of, let's say, what we call our sciences,
then we have an opening into open thought and development as we can, but we don't at this time.
Yes, the way it's usually explained to me by, say, the alternative scientists,
I like to say the natural scientists, the ones who are kind of looking at the world the way you're describing it.
We say alternative, but that kind of implies that the mainstream is primary
and alternative is secondary when it really should be the other way around.
But I'm led to believe that the Earth has a negative charge,
that a lot of what we call gravity is a byproduct of electricity,
and that if we can counter the negative charge, you know, two negative magnets repel each other,
then we can start to play around with transportation modalities that really would blow people's mind
because they're operating in an incorrect framework.
Is that kind of how you see it, that anti-gravity is really just countering the Earth's natural negative charge?
Well, you just opened up a big can of worms.
When we say charge and all this, it's like charge of what?
Is it electrical? Is it physical? Is it, you know, emotional?
You know, it's actually all of that.
Let me just give you an example.
There's a little meme that went around the Internet for a while on how the big jumbo jets,
they don't really use the fuel that they purport to use based on their fueling sheets.
You know, say they need 5,000 gallons of gas, but the fuel tanks can't hold more than 2,000,
so how are they flying, right? Have you heard this before?
Yeah, and there was someone that went around, it's kind of obscure if maybe it could be found,
and they were asking aircraft engineers and pilots, what really makes these airplanes fly then?
And he says, well, it's really that everyone that's on the plane and is directing the plane
and working on the plane believes that they do.
Weird.
That's how they work. Yeah, it's really weird.
So now we're in a Twilight Zone kind of reality when we're trying to find the, quote-unquote, notable science, you know?
Notable science meaning, like, you know, referencing material, right?
Stuff you write down and is repeatable.
So when we say charge and things like that, again, we have to be able to define the thing
and explain it a little bit better than just the descriptions that we get.
So a negative charge would be, for example, the part that is taking away or creating the suction or the vacuum,
and the positive charge would be the one that's pushing.
And that could be done, again, physically, electrically, and emotionally.
Well, now you're sounding like Rudolph Steiner with the different layers of adding emotion to concepts like this,
scientific concepts.
Yeah, very interesting stuff.
So this more accurate understanding could potentially give way to technologies that work in this framework
far earlier than people would expect, because right now we have this combustion-based,
inaccurate model of how physics works.
And if you just peel that back, you can find examples of people who made technologies that work in this system
a long, long time ago, right?
Yeah, I would suggest there was a little more accuracy in the verbiage and the language that was used.
You know, you said combustion engine.
You know, for example, if you're using a gasoline engine, you know, down at the floor you have the brake
and the other thing they call the gas pedal, don't they, right?
It's really an air pedal.
When you push that thing down, it opens, let's say, the butterfly in the carburetor or the fuel injector to let more air in,
and then the amount of air is measured and then determines the amount of fuel that's put in.
So if we change our language and our perception, we'll see things a little different.
We're not really putting gasoline, let's say, for example, in cars to burn the gasoline,
because gasoline actually doesn't really burn in a closed container.
It's the vapor part that burns, right, on the top.
We're actually burning the air.
That's why you could substitute gasoline for hydrogen and propane like forklift in a warehouse, right?
So we're chasing after creating, again, a pressure difference in the air,
and eventually that could be tweaked and modified.
But from working on spark plugs and throttle bodies and easily doubling the mileage of a, quote-unquote,
combustion engine that doesn't have computer controls,
and the reason I'm saying this is because if you go to a new car factory,
when the car rolls off of the assembly line, you'll see a guy with what looks like a laptop or something,
and they tune the engine, because some of the cars that come out of the factory,
let's say it's supposed to get 20 miles to the gallon, right?
Some might come out getting 5 miles to the gallon.
Well, that's no good.
We have to make it 20.
And some might come out making 60 miles to the gallon.
Well, that's no good.
We have to make it 20.
So they tune the engine using the computer.
And unfortunately, just to jump over to a thing, they have something called an oxygen sensor or a fuel sensor.
If it's really supposed to be a pollution control device, shouldn't it be like a pollution sensor?
So, again, the language and all these other things, but let's say a combustion engine,
like a lawnmower or something that doesn't have a computer on it,
can easily be doubled just, you know, with a few hours' worth of work
or not even just adjusting the throttle body and the spark plug.
But once you have something that has a computer control, it instills what I call a sabotage, right?
So, again, the computer is, let's say, a thought machine.
Think of it that way, right?
So, again, it goes back to the thinking.
I like it.
So going back to the NIMSA group, I've heard you say that they used to call airplanes sky lubricators,
kind of a, you know, jokey pejorative saying that their technologies were better
because they were working on advanced airships.
And I've also heard you tell a story that you found in a text from a university library
that was taken from a garbage dump in Libya,
and that spoke to something that sounds like a piece of technology out of time.
Talk to us about these examples that show us that this is really the reality when you dig
and you find these little anecdotes.
Well, the thing is we're subject to what they call resets,
whether it's every few centuries or every few millennia.
And give an example.
It's not very different if you lived a very long time ago in the way that you're thinking now.
Without giving a direct example, because there are many,
I think there's a lot of stuff on the Internet that's dedicated to parts and things like that.
But one thing I just want to bring up is that when we are, let's say we meaning humans,
on the surface, go to a certain technological level,
they're sort of knocked down by some form of catastrophe,
whether it's extreme social catastrophe, you know, war, economics, plagues,
or a natural catastrophe like the Great Flood, for example, and other minor catastrophes.
We get back to a situation where we're just desperate to be alive.
And then eventually we rediscover these things as being new, and they're really not.
I always give a metaphor.
The only thing that changes, well, I shouldn't say the only thing that changes,
but there are things that change every time the society reaches a technological apex, for example.
And the example that I want to give is if you brought someone in from the past, let's say, to the future,
what would they be amazed at?
Most people would say, oh, the Internet, electricity, airplanes.
And I suggest they won't.
The thing that they will find to be the hardest thing to conceive is how we're dumping asphalt
and covering our roads with this black tar everywhere, right?
Because that was very well known in their society then, and it had very limited use.
So I would suggest that it's not microwaves or radios or computers that they would find hard to adjust to,
but all of this black tar petroleum that we're coating our roads with, how impractical is that?
I'm just giving that as a way to just look at the world.
Yeah, I agree.
And only because I mentioned that story from the university library
and this garbage dump in Libya that they extracted.
Basically, you talked about ancient Greek suppression,
where it seemed to be a story about this guy who was scaring people away from the markets
with this thing that he had, which was described as a horseless wagon that spit out fire, smoke, and lightning.
And so the merchants were like, hey, cops, you've got to go get this guy and do something with him
because people won't come out and it's stopping commerce.
And I don't know if there's much of a conclusion there,
but it's just an example of these stories peppered throughout history that are never elevated to the surface.
But in aggregate, you just can tell that history is a lot different than it's presented to us.
Like you said, these resets.
Right, and we're sort of at the point of another one now.
There's a couple of people that are bringing up the topic on the Internet that can be researched,
and I would suggest if you're interested in the subject of the resets, go ahead and look for it.
But I would say that what you do on a day-to-day and how you perceive yourself and those around you
and the situation that you're in, meaning whatever society you're in, takes precedent on that.
Because one thing that you'll find through history is those that survived the resets
were sort of in a different, more, let's say, elevated spiritual, mental, emotional state.
And in some cases, it was kind of like you wished you were not one of the survivors because it was so rough.
But on the other side, there's a preservation element that those that did survive were almost like selective survivors
because they had just some aspects about them that were, quote-unquote, might I say, superior than the rest.
That makes sense to me.
And I wanted to bring the archon back in here a little bit.
I know that you're primarily the guy who works on the website, and you just kind of allow the Greek to do his thing.
But I'm curious your thoughts on some of the stuff we're talking about, the technologies, the physics,
this alternative model that seems to exist outside of the mainstream.
What do you think?
Well, those things are very interesting.
I mean, in general, I think that when we talk about cosmic censorship, that's something that should be contemplated.
It's not so much a lack of information that brings it about because we know that information is in overproduction today.
I think the real thrust of something like that lies in preventing comprehension.
It's this force that disassembles intelligible narratives and renders conclusions unreachable,
which is why a lot of people live in this sort of unawareness of where society stands and what's going to happen next,
which is a mindset that I do think should be scorned and avoided,
because it reveals that ultimately people have a preference for the things that are most like themselves.
So a person that's ignorant is ultimately going to be drawn to things that are ignorant,
and that in order to reach some type of higher level of enlightenment, you kind of have to separate yourself from that.
It starts with that sort of mindset switch that the things that we've been told are normal are really the things that are dangerous.
I do remember some time maybe six or seven months ago when I was getting a haircut at a friend's place,
and he had a sticker on the table in front of me where it said, beware normal people.
And I found that to be slightly comical because that is very much true.
It is these types of things that are often thought of as being innocuous in our society,
quote-unquote normal people, the school system, the financial system,
which actually are the source of a lot of our troubles and our inability to gain the proper orientation.
So I am not as specialized on the matters of science as the Greek is, although I'm learning about that slowly but surely.
But what I have found always caught my attention was the absurdity of this thing that we call society
and the way that institutions misdirect everybody's attention towards things that are unimportant.
Yeah, yeah, I certainly agree.
A lot of times we are putting the target kind of on academia and the Royal Society
and those who injected all this into the culture and over many decades, centuries,
have crafted the false paradigm that the normal people eat up, and I think you're right.
So the Archon, that's just a fun pseudonym, as you say.
But I am curious about the Greek's thoughts on real Archons,
or the term which suggests there are spiritual forces, mind parasites, that kind of feed on us, that direct reality.
Some say they're attracted to power, they can identify power, and our own elite are possessed by these Archons.
That's obviously a Gnostic trope.
But what are your thoughts on influences that are not really seen, not even acknowledged?
Non-physical influences, spiritual, some might say.
Oh, I would say definitely.
Sometimes the thing is measured by the effect more than what it actually is, right?
Actually, most of the current science, all of the probes and measuring equipment,
doesn't really measure the thing, it measures what the thing does.
And when we look at what the thing does, meaning the spiritual beings all the way,
let's say, when we say spiritual, non-corporeal, non-physical,
down, there's a gradient to where then you have physical beings,
but they don't exhibit the qualities that average humans do.
Let's say they live longer, and they have powers,
let's say like walking through walls would be one meme that one can bring up.
And then they transition down to the average human that might have insight into those
and might have some of that power, which we call, let's say, the masters.
And then it transitions down to the students of the masters,
then it transitions down to, need I say, the normie.
So that would be like a gradient.
And if we see what the normie is capable of,
and going the gradient now backwards, let's say upwards,
not necessarily because upwards means better, just in power,
we start to see a removal of what the normie world is,
and we start to see a point where the normie world is mixed in with the supernatural
and super powerful world, and then we rise up and it becomes all supernatural above that.
So there's a gradient there, and there's an interbreeding of both mind and physicality
when you go up and down through the scale.
Again, I think that from just looking at what's been memorialized,
the reason things are memorialized through history,
written whether it's clay tablet or parchment or paper or now digitally,
when something is memorialized it's because it's important for posterity,
for people to know, that people who are not present,
whether it's geographically present or in time, to have this information carried over.
What is memorialized about what I just mentioned and what you asked about, let's say,
super beings all the way down, is very different to what people,
let's say everyday people, if you were to ask them about them, have to say.
What you will find memorialized is a much more tangible story or structure
than what people think about.
So when we say that there are these beings, let's just say superior in power,
there's quite a bit of information about their characteristics and how they maintain that power,
where the average person that thinks about the subject is not aware of.
Yeah, and for people who might wonder what you actually mean by that,
what are those characteristics?
Because we do have people like Charles Fort, we can go back even further to biblical texts
where angels and things are described far differently than the religions project them.
But when you get to the core of the characteristics of these super intelligences or super beings,
what do they look like to you or what makes them up?
Well, you know, the interesting thing, the easiest to discuss are the anthropomorphic ones.
Like if you go to the biblical text, for example, man was made in their image, let's say, right?
The gods.
They lack physicality or the limits of physicality but yet can manifest as such if needed
or if so desired.
And then that leads more into the question, what is physicality?
You know, we were sort of discussing science earlier,
and I would suggest that from the mystical point of view, even to what is considered contemporary science,
one will actually, if you delve into the subject, there is no physicality.
It's just a state of motion.
And an example of that would be if you have, let's say, a typical desk fan or a bicycle wheel on your table,
when it's not moving, you can put your hand in between the blades
or in between the spokes of the bicycle wheel just fine.
But once it's rotating, if you approach any of the area, it will seem like a solid object, right,
because of its movement.
So there's something about movement and oscillation, frequency, as it's usually described,
that these beings have control over.
And the easiest ones to discuss are the ones that are quote-unquote anthropomorphic,
like, for example, from the biblical story or angels.
You know, we don't think of something that we don't recognize.
We recognize them as being sort of human in form.
And I would suggest that is one aspect of it and the easiest one to discuss.
So imagine an ability to dematerialize or not have a physical form based on your control over the motion of things.
Yeah, that's super interesting.
I don't hear people talking about motion or vibration.
Vibration, yes, but not so much in the motion sense.
Yes, but when you listen to some of these descriptions, they sometimes appear as rotating concentric rings or some kind of light,
things that do suggest that that might be a mechanism that they're controlling that alters the perception
or allows them to be seen or unseen from people that they're trying to encounter.
Oh, absolutely.
Eventually we might discuss, or you'll find in the Greek-speak discussion,
is the in-your-face examples that are put out in society and memorialized and easily referenced.
One of the easiest ones to come across that is a shocker if you're perceptive is I tell people,
go to the Internet and do a search for a cross-section of intestines or cross-sections of lungs or cross-section of skin.
And this is for an anatomical drawing.
And then I would suggest do a split screen and type in a browser a cross-section of a steel-belted radial tire.
And you compare the two.
Structurally, the two meaning whether it's a cross-section of the human lungs or animal lungs or skin or intestines,
compare the cross-section with a steel-belted radial tire, and you'll see structurally they're identical, structurally.
In other words, nothing passes through there.
So we're constantly told that we absorb, right, nutrition, even the alternatives.
Oh, yeah, we have something that you will absorb more nutrition, you know, and it lowers blood pressure.
And we're like, how is that absorption happening?
Look at all of the hydrophobic layers in the intestines.
Nothing goes through that.
How is it working, right?
So there's the concept of induction, which is a very simple concept, for example.
They have these induction cooktop stoves.
It's a glass-top stove, and you can have a pot of water boiling on it.
And you just move the pot off to the side, put your hand right on the glass top.
It's room temp.
And you move the pot right over the glass top again, and it starts to boil again, you know, through induction.
Most of the devices that we use use coils and capacitors, let's say, but coils work on induction.
You know, I have a power toothbrush, and when it goes into the charger, there is no metal contact at all.
It's just the plastic bases come near each other, and there's an LED that blinks and lets me know it's charging.
You see?
So once we understand and start using the concept of induction, whether it's from the part of the creative part,
or the part that creates locomotion, you know, when it's taught to us as young children,
then we'll have a society that will be, you know, more advanced at moving forward.
Hmm. Yeah, you're touching on something I was going to bring up, the importance of induction versus absorption.
It might be a little fuzzy to some people out there, because they both kind of invoke this taking in sort of mechanism.
But you've talked about the biological vacuum that it needs to be studied, that blood pressure is a farce.
Yep.
All of our concepts of how biology functions are by looking at things that are dead, which is idiotic,
and it's the how the biological vacuum is maintained question that actually starts the research.
But sadly, nothing on this has been done since Victor Schauberger in the 1930s.
Well, what are some of these biological processes that we could correct the record on
and help demystify how biology really works?
Well, what's interesting is that things that are living versus things that are not living do have the difference of what we call,
you know, life, essentially.
And that is something that we all kind of, yeah, well, Greek, that sounds very obvious.
But when we get into defining it and explaining it, the biological vacuum is one of the core principles to examine.
For example, if you look at the human body, all of the fluids in the human body,
you'll see that there's no way that there is anything direct like a tool or a machine like the heart or anything
that is moving all the fluids evenly based on the hydrodynamic principles that are taught.
But if we consider that the pressure inside the body is slightly less than the outer environment,
then we have the freedom of the liquids to move in the direction of where that vacuum sustains more vacuum.
Essentially, it's a big, broad subject.
But when you combine that with induction, which is where you have a barrier where things cross immaterially,
where you've heard, you know, the elite pretty much invented science fiction to disclose to us what's going on.
In something I call cosmic information, in a cosmic law, information is information.
It doesn't matter if you call it fact or fiction.
The thing is, did you get the idea?
If you want to call it fact or fiction or truth or non-true, that's up to you.
So they have this thing called the transporter or the food replicator that they showed in Star Trek,
and that should be taken very seriously because it's not a very, let's say, far-off notion
into what's actually happening in every living organism.
So they obviously have twisted the truth and they describe mechanisms in the body that are not exactly accurate.
They want to suppress the reality of this induction.
Well, where would that study lead?
Why is it so important to them to say, well, your body just absorbs the nutrients rather than this induction process?
What are they afraid of us discovering there?
Okay, the thing is, are they afraid?
Are they fear-based?
You know, there's a big meme about that, being fear-based, right?
I don't think they're that much afraid in the way the situation is currently.
I think what they're doing is, one thing you'll see in the Greek-speak I use a lot, they're pranking.
It's a form of pranking.
It brings entertainment.
You know, give an analogy.
I visited another world once.
This is just an analogy.
And the biggest industry on that world was Kevlar or bulletproof underwear.
And I asked why.
It says because it's a custom, it's customary to put a thumbtack down on a seat before anyone sits on it.
And to prevent the pain, they have a big industry that produces Kevlar underwear that everyone buys.
So I suggested, well, just stop putting thumbtacks on seats.
And they said, well, you can't do that.
We've been doing it for a long time.
And if it starts to catch on, those that produce that bulletproof Kevlar underwear are going to really come after me, aren't they?
Because I'm messing up their business.
So it's a combination of pranking.
It's a combination of control, a combination of culture.
The reason why one of the things that sets gasoline prices, for example, is how much do you have to pay to go a certain distance, right?
That's why often diesel fuel costs more because you get better mileage on diesel fuel.
It's very interesting.
So I would suggest that it's just a strict control system.
There is an emotional component to the induction, meaning if you're in a bad emotional state,
you usually won't perform as well as if you're in a good emotional state.
When I say perform, I mean in your daily life, whatever it is, even just sitting down to have a meal.
So there's an emotional component, an energetic component, and a physical component to everything we can possibly discuss.
I like it.
And let me ask you about alchemy.
It's another subject that has a rich history, but it all sort of dries up about 100 years ago.
We're told that's because the work was really theoretical and didn't actually constitute a real science.
Materials can't be transmuted into other materials.
What are your thoughts on the field of alchemy and its actual value?
Well, the basic definition of alchemy, well, basic in a loose way, is where you involve spirit or mind into the process.
And the individual is a variable or a component in whatever process you're doing.
And that goes to chemistry, for example, when we discuss alchemy directly.
And chemistry is just a matter of synthesizing things or making things that you might need that are not around, right?
The typical one would be turning base metals into gold, right?
Because gold, let's say, is desirable, or whatever.
But I would suggest that alchemy, again, if the mind component, the emotional component,
and the state of whoever is working on the process is removed publicly, in other words, from the public mind,
then the public becomes very dependent on what's put out to them.
And they become less powerful and more dependent.
Again, it's a dependency aspect.
But I would suggest that alchemy, and I can give you, let's just say, sort of indirect and sort of direct,
that the schools of alchemy have gone underground,
and they're still being used today by the large chemical companies' industrial concerns.
They're definitely being used today.
If you look at the field of what's called catalysts, for example,
if you have vegetable shortening, it's a material that looks like a putty.
It's not liquid.
It's basically water and oil mixed together, but you can't mix water and oil together.
But if you run it over nickel beads, a catalyst, nickel does not add itself to the mix,
but because it went over the nickel catalyst, now the water and oil don't separate, right?
There are processes still in metal alloys.
I'll give an example.
Beryl bronze, which is one of the hardest, well, most durable, not hardest, but durable in bearing,
meaning you have two metals rubbing up against each other, a bearing surface.
There is a particular alloy that's of many alloys,
but beryl bronze where you have beryllium, copper, tin, zinc, and other things mixed together.
If you melt those metals and put them together, you're not going to get beryl bronze,
the qualities of beryl bronze.
What must be done is while all those metals are molten in a vat,
one must break off a fresh green branch from a hardwood tree
and stir the molten metal with this fresh green branch and drop it in.
Then you will get the qualities of beryl bronze.
Now, if that doesn't sound like alchemy being used today, I don't know what is.
It's still being used today.
It's just not public.
Yeah, these are the little anecdotes that I just find really unique about hearing you speak.
Another aspect of the intelligence of nature and the symbiosis that you've said kind of in passing
is that poison ivy won't grow unless it's in the presence of white oak,
and white oak bark is the remedy for poison ivy.
Now, this is something that I did not know.
I got poison ivy a lot when I was young running through the woods of the Midwest.
I didn't realize it had this symbiosis, and I'm curious about other examples of that
and the intelligence of nature and how the natural world has a lot of this baked in.
We are just so divorced from the natural world these days.
We're in these concrete jungles that even a little example like that is intriguing.
Well, yeah, I like giving or send people to the direction of what's called macrobiotics
or the yin and yang concept.
It's an Asian.
What I don't like about recommending it is that it's very Asian-oriented,
and people think they have to be Japanese or Chinese to understand it, right?
The yin and yang symbol is very much interrelated.
I would suggest that the concept of balance, every culture had it,
but a lot of Westerners are sort of turned off because they think I'm trying to make them Asian-centric.
Which I'm not, but it's the only place that it's been preserved, right,
the concept of yin and yang, expansive, contractive, right, and properties
and how the balancing actually works.
I would suggest that the remedy or the solution must be in place prior to
or at the same time the problem or the malady is brought into existence.
It's kind of like, let's just use a dummy load kind of term,
like God and the devil came together, right?
You can't have negative or good without bad.
They come in together.
I use Star Wars as an example.
People think that the Jedi have to defeat the Sith.
It's not about that.
It's never in the storyline.
The storyline is to put it in balance.
It's not to eliminate one or the other.
Sith are not trying to eliminate the Jedi, and the Jedi are not trying to eliminate the Sith.
It's just to keep them in balance.
When one gets much stronger than the other, there's an imbalance,
and this is pretty much how nature works.
I like it.
And just to step back to alchemy a bit,
I've heard you say that if you just examine the mechanisms of the body,
you can see alchemy and transmutation as a part of general biology.
When you are low on something, you don't take that thing.
You take something else that helps your body produce that thing.
Talk to us about that a bit.
A simple direction to point people at is to look up the work of Louis Kevran,
K-E-V-R-A-N.
He did the biological transmutation experiments,
which about a decade ago I had met someone just by chance
that was part of one of those experiments in the Moroccan desert.
But what he had done was examined,
and also using the basic scientific nomenclature,
a chicken egg and how it's mostly calcium, pure calcium.
And he decided to eliminate anything that a group of chickens in the experiment
were eating with calcium in it at all.
So these chickens were eating food that was devoid of calcium.
They went through great lengths to make sure that none of the feed had any calcium content.
But the chickens still produced a robust calcium egg,
and they didn't have any bone loss or beak loss or anything else.
So he discovered basically that it was traces of magnesium and sodium
inside the living being that created the elemental calcium.
And the same goes for humans with potassium, for example, as an electrolyte.
A lot of people are like, oh, I eat bananas because they have potassium, right?
Well, it's actually, again, you need a high-quality sodium
and physical activity for the body to produce potassium in the blood.
So he has a, I wouldn't say extensive work, but he has many, many direct examples like that.
Lewis Kervran would be an easy place to check out.
Let me just throw one thing in there.
One of the metrics that they use for food is calories, right?
Now, the calorie counting thing, it was really crazy a decade ago.
It's not so much anymore, even prior to a decade ago.
But let me just suggest the caloric measurement is basically the amount of temperature it takes
to raise one gram or one cubic centimeter of water.
It's a very simple metric.
If you see how it's done, it looks basically in a lab or it's a glass tube.
They put the object.
They want to find how many calories it has in the glass tube,
and they seal it, purge it with pure oxygen.
Something looks like a spark plug goes boom.
Everything just completely burns.
It's submerged in a bath of water, and they measure the amount of water
and the amount of heat it gives off, and there's your caloric output.
The only thing with that is that if you were to eat a banana for potassium, right, as most people say,
let's say a banana's got 80 calories.
When you poop it, can you burn that poop?
Of course.
You can continue burning it.
So unless you know anyone who poops charcoal, the calories are an irrelevant metric for food.
So unless you're pooping pure carbon, it's an irrelevant metric,
like blood pressure and other things.
Blood sugar is another one.
Well, let's get into blood a little bit more.
I mean, I was always fascinated by Rudolf Steiner talking about blood,
saying that it's basically a spiritual substance or a substance that links the spiritual and physical
and that it's something you can't actually get at.
Outside of the body, because once it's oxygenated, it is a different thing.
So it's like really quite curious that it can't really be totally known in a sense
because of where it's kept beneath the skin.
And as you mentioned about studying things that are dead, this is not exactly what blood is.
Blood needs to be alive and inside the body to be what it naturally is.
What are your thoughts on if blood pressure is a farce and blood sugar is a farce?
Well, they say that one of the biggest causes of death is heart disease,
and that obviously involves the blood.
What is going on with the blood and the heart?
What's the proper way to think about this stuff?
Well, okay, one way to look at it is just even a cursory examination of all of the organs in the body,
you'll see that they're all alien to each other, right?
Even an early student in the medical field, you'll show him a liver cell,
and he'll identify it as such, or a cell from the kidneys, identify it as such.
They're very, very, a brain cell, if you've ever met anyone who still has any of those, by the way.
But if you look at all of the cells, they're very distinct,
almost as if you have these alien creatures that have come together from different universes
or different worlds to work together.
And when they were assembled in the body, actually all living things,
mammals especially and other creatures that are mobile, have all of these alien-looking organs, right?
And they're all pretty much there to produce and sustain the blood in the body.
They all have their own attribute of what they do, so the blood is essentially the focus.
One thing that I would suggest, we said blood pressure is a farce,
you know, basically the cuff that restricts blood flow is an unnatural occurrence,
and they're basically just measuring the beats in between the paws and the beat of the heart.
It's, again, a fallacy of a metric.
But I would suggest that the blood is a byproduct or the goal of all of the organs of the body to sustain and produce.
So it is very mystical in that aspect.
If you study live blood studies, there was, I think, a duo of father and daughter in Canada a few decades ago,
and they were able to, for a short time, view live blood under a microscope,
and they would see little flashes of blue light under the slide.
And where the flash of blue light subsided, there would be a new cell developed.
It could be a red blood cell.
Sometimes it was a white blood cell.
Sometimes it was a yeast cell, right?
So all of these things were being produced under, let's say,
the effects of little flashes of yellow or blue light under the slide trying to keep the blood alive.
Wow, wow.
Yeah, that's the kind of stuff that really intrigues me.
And just from guests of the past that I've talked to,
it seems like the mechanisms of water, electricity, frequency, and vibration
are the real underpinning aspects of reality that we should be studying and experimenting with
because the results seem almost magical.
There's this unknown quality to a lot of things that are going on in nature
that we just either take for granted or are completely ignorant of,
like that flash of light sort of thing.
It seems like, in terms of health, we need proper charge.
I mean, we talked about charge and how that term isn't necessarily descriptive enough,
but walking on the earth seems to matter.
Salt seems to help the conductivity of our body,
and proper structured water seems to help produce healthy cells.
Those seem to be some of the biggest components, yet everyone focuses on just diet.
Well, I think these other things should be right up there.
Yes, and these other things are a state of mind and which lead to emotion,
which lead to action, thoughts, and then eventually manifestation.
You mentioned magic.
You know, there's many sayings about it that one society's science is another society's magic, right?
And the thing about magic or alleged domain or prestidigitation is
people can see a woman being sawed in half on stage and put back together,
and when they exit the theater, you can have them swear on an affidavit
that they saw a woman being sawed in half and put back together.
So what's really going on is the magician lies and you swear to it,
and that's pretty much one way to distill down on what's happening in this society.
That is true, but outside of stage magic, I mean, if we're going to talk about that,
I do think there is a natural technology there that's been used by, say, shamans for a long time.
It seems to involve the ancient megalithic stone circles somehow
that it seems like from other researchers have been intentionally altered
or certain stones displaced to maybe make that technology not work anymore.
Now it just looks like, oh, an interesting feature.
How cute the ancients were putting these rocks together.
But there seems to be real mechanisms of magic.
You seem to be able to alter consciousness in a way that draws forth intelligences
for communication inside the pentagram, inside the circle.
A lot of these things seem to be quite real, but they're obscured by the term magic
and what we think of as stage magic, but it really seems to be a natural technology.
What do you think?
Oh, absolutely.
Going back to the alchemy where beryl bronze is a very desirable material in industry
and you can have the formula, but if you don't have the procedure, it won't work.
Very often you hear people absconding with industrial secrets.
They have the formula for coke or some alloy or some chemical process, right?
And the recipe is just like a paragraph of what you need to mix together.
But the procedure manual is 300 pages thick.
When to mix what at what temperature, what time of day, you see?
So you mentioned the megaliths or monoliths and stone.
Those are forms of communication that require procedure.
If you don't understand their procedure, it's just a grouping of very large, heavy stones, isn't it?
Yes, very interesting that you say that.
Can you give us any insights into the procedure?
I know a lot of it's been lost, but there are little pieces
that some people seem to be able to extract from their research.
Well, when you brought up the stones, it's a matter of time.
We're not aware of any new monoliths other than maybe the guide stones
or something like that in Georgia that were recently blown up.
But we're not aware of new structures going up or functioning structures,
let's say, outwardly to us.
So it's a matter of time.
There was something about time being a factor, and that's where I kind of sarcastically bring up,
it's one of the strong points of Greek speak, is the Pope's work schedule, right?
How do you keep time?
So there's an alignment.
Like I mentioned, you can abscond with some secret recipe from some industry
and know what your shopping list is, but you don't know how to put them together.
Putting things together in time, which is just the memorialization or record of events,
because without events changing, there is no time.
A lot of people say there is no time and that they're correct,
but that means there's no change.
And change, even in the old philosophical point, is the only thing for sure is change, you see?
So time will always exist.
It's just your record of it.
This society has been captured hostage under what I call the Pope's work schedule.
If you ask anyone what day it is,
they're going to tell you something between January and December and Monday through Friday, right?
And if you go to something what I call lawful timekeeping,
which is actually taught in astronomy, not astrology, but astronomy, in University 101,
they give about a five-minute discussion on this,
is that the day is measured with the solar aspect of the objects in the sky
and the month is measured with the moon.
It's not a lunar calendar. It's not a solar calendar.
Just like, for example, if you have a clock, you have the longhand and the shorthand.
It's not a longhand clock or a shorthand.
And then you have the second sweeping hand, you see?
So it's a matter of combining the two.
Just to drop in a little thing for the listeners, they could research it on their own.
The day starts at solar noon, at high noon, not at midnight.
And one thing about that is that it's actually mentioned in a way that the old dictionaries used to be defined.
You'll find that in the Julian calendar date on the timekeeping authorities,
I think there's a website for the Naval Observatory in Colorado
and there's another one for the Greenwich Mean Time,
in their Julian calendar description, which is the basis of the Gregorian calendar,
they'll tell you for scientific and astronomical purposes, the day starts at solar noon,
but for the public at large, it's midnight.
That's almost, I want to give the analogy of how the original old dictionaries were written.
They didn't know how to define words exactly,
because a dictionary is not about the meaning of the word, it's about the diction of the word.
They want everyone to have a uniform pronunciation.
That's why when you look up a word in a dictionary, it shows you that phonetic spelling first.
It's for consistency for the public.
But when they put in a word like oats, for example,
they defined it as what we feed horses in England, but it's the staple of the people of Scotland.
Kind of like a put-down.
So you'll see all these put-downs put out by the academic authorities in your face.
That's basically the sun ruling or being the day count at high noon.
There's a lot of religious aspect to that, where people say,
well, you know, in the old Hebrew calendar, it's sundown, or midnight now,
or, well, okay, go ahead, have at it.
The other thing is, when you go to the lunar side,
you know, for thousands of years, people settled their debts when the full moon came around.
You'll find a lot of mentioning of that, if you can find some documents that talked about,
you know, how conventional people behaved in the past.
So today, don't you get your bills to settle your debts on a monthly basis?
You get your monthly bills, usually.
So there's certain things in our culture that's still there.
Again, going back to the sun, you know, people, when they fasted for a day,
they broke their fast at the end of the day, and it was called breakfast, right?
Yeah.
So it's very interesting, and there's no discussion on lawful timekeeping.
So once you understand the alignments and the time of day,
just like the procedure manual for some industrial chemical process,
again, the shopping list is very small,
but the procedure manual on how to put these things together could be quite elaborate.
Once you remove the aspect of how to keep time, what happens to these stone monoliths?
I mean, you might have some academic going around and saying,
oh, yeah, for a certain time of year and a certain day,
the sun goes between these two stones and forms a shadow here.
It's like, yeah, so ask him what day it is.
See, he can't get into any procedure.
Interesting.
Yes, it seems like the orientation,
the cosmic orientation in some of those places would be an important mechanism
for what these technologies were able to do.
Yeah.
Give an example here.
Like, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy.
No, I don't want to go out and slaughter Canaanites or anything like that,
but when I say I'm an Old Testament kind of guy, you know,
just basically the do's and don'ts, for example.
So when you read in the biblical text, on the 13th day of the first month, right,
or on the 10th day of the 7th month, if you're using the calendar as such
or what the quote-unquote Jewish culture is using or whatever,
you're not going to figure out those days.
But once you understand that the full moon is the first day of the month
and the day starts at solar noon,
you'll be able to find out and be present on those days.
Because, for example, in the biblical text, those are appointed.
They're called appointed days.
It's an appointment, right?
You ever get something called an appointment and don't show up?
Hmm.
You know?
Yeah.
Get it?
You don't show up for your appointments?
Sometimes they still charge you for the appointment, right,
even though you didn't come.
So it's a very weird and strange world once you start to see how simple it is.
Yeah.
It's really intriguing to see the echoes of some of this
in the language and the traditions.
You know, when I speak to occult practitioners,
they're always emphasizing the timing.
And any time I've thought about even exploring that world,
it's just like the timing aspect is so overwhelming
because our society uses  it eats up so much of our time.
But they're always emphasizing that certain actions for maximum potency
must be done at certain times.
And maybe that's an aspect of why it's not so arbitrary
that we have the Gregorian calendar and the 24-hour clock,
the Pope's work schedule, as you say.
Maybe these are some of the deeper ways it affects us
and what we could do with our reality.
Yes.
Well, there's something called navigation.
And in navigation, it doesn't matter even just driving
from one city to another, you have to have two things.
You have to know your distance and you have to know your time.
When you know your distance and your time, you can figure out your speed.
If you know your speed, you could figure out your time and your distance, you see.
So once you eliminate that component and disorient people from, let's say, lawful
when I say lawful, it means you don't have to subscribe
or buy anything to learn it, right, or use it.
Once you understand that you remove the time aspect from people's ability to navigate
now, when I say navigate, it could be from when you get out of bed
and walk to the kitchen in the morning all the way to navigating your week,
month, or the rest of your life.
Once you eliminate their ability to perceive time in a natural sense, what does that do?
You screwed up what?
Their navigation abilities in every aspect, right?
Yeah, there are so many health-focused people right now
that are emphasizing the importance of the circadian rhythm,
that it affects all of our organs and that we need to get sunlight at the right times
and just get the right cycle going,
and the effects on health are way more severe than even just what you eat.
Well, I'd like to just add something to that.
I'm brought into many conversations regarding health,
and I usually start off by just shouting a bunch of pejoratives and hanging up.
Why is that?
Why do I do that?
Well, because there's really no such thing.
When one says health, it implies a physical condition and fitness level.
So when someone asks, for example, how do I be healthy?
I would say, for what?
Are you planning on climbing Mount Everest?
Are you planning on sitting at a desk job?
Are you a single mom with four children?
Are you a UPS driver or a podcaster that likes to play tennis?
What are you looking to do?
So there really is no universal concept of health as we function in this life that we have.
It's what level of fitness and conditioning do you require from yourself
based on what you aspire or are doing.
Does that make any sense?
It does.
Yes, it does.
I think really most people just want to avoid those symptoms of illness and feeling yucky.
I'm avoiding certain terms, but you want to create a chasm between those chapters of your life
where you're stuck in bed for a week, and that's what people generally mean.
I'll give an analogy, and people can think about this in many ways.
Early on when the macrobiotic movement from Japan, like Michio Kushi and Shizuko Yamamoto,
landed in the U.S. in the 60s and 70s, they landed in San Francisco,
and they started doing, let's say, clinics and seminars, workshops on eat whole foods,
things that are not processed.
What do I mean by that is if you go and buy food for yourself,
if it comes on a package with labeling, it's still processed.
So, in essence, buying things that have not been processed, using that word again.
They were holding these clinics, and they had a general population that was coming.
For the first few times, they held these workshops in the 60s and 70s.
But after about two or three weeks, most of the audience fell away,
except for a lot of the young people that were experimenting with drugs,
let's just say, in the 60s and 70s.
And they stopped one day, and they said,
why do you particular guys keep coming back?
And they say, well, because once we started eating whole grains and whole vegetables,
the way you mentioned, we didn't need to do drugs anymore,
and we still felt high all the time.
That's why we're here.
So that was a very interesting, poignant example of how you're feeling.
And it is true, by the way, if you eat seasonally, whole foods,
it means animal as well, on occasion, animal, you know, poultry, fish, meat, whatever.
You will feel a sense of revitalization in the body,
because basically that's what the body is here to do,
is to process things that are whole in nature,
which is an entire other discussion of what processed foods and health and disease is.
Yeah, there's so much debate about what's the right diet,
but the universal constant is that it's getting off of the industrial diet.
That is what makes people feel better, regardless of what you're eating,
as long as it's whole foods.
And the seasonality is really interesting.
I've heard that described as what food really is, fruits and vegetables.
It is a container for light energy to then make its way into our body.
So there's different qualities of light in different seasons,
and different containers hold it differently.
It's like another system that's parallel to the circadian rhythm,
that's just like a seasonal rhythm,
and being in flow with it has effects that are optimal for people.
What's optimal is the simplicity of it.
Let's look at it from the chemistry point of view.
If you're living in a cold climate,
let's say latitudes that are generally cold,
and you start to consume things that are grown in the tropics.
When those things are grown in the tropics,
the reason why they're growing is because they're in balance.
And if you're in a cold climate,
and you eat things that are grown in a warm climate or warm area, warm season,
they will adjust your body to the warm season.
Really?
And you're in a cold place.
It's very easy to determine.
It will thin out your blood and have you adjust to a warm climate,
and you will just be freezing no matter how warm you try to stay.
And the opposite is true.
If you're living in the tropics, let's say,
and there's this new fad about eating Arctic salmon.
You start eating the Arctic salmon, which is in balance in a cold area,
you will not be able to cool down in the tropics.
It's very simple.
I have many examples where I met someone a while back,
and I'm here near Tucson, Arizona.
It doesn't get that cold, but, you know,
in the fall I could still be out in a long-sleeve shirt just fine.
She was wearing a sweater and a hat,
and she was kind of chilly and feeling cold,
and I was comfortable in a long-sleeve shirt.
And I went over to her house, and she had bananas on her counter,
and I said, what are these?
And she says, well, I eat those every day because of potassium.
And I said, well, let's get rid of the bananas,
and we went out and got a piece of salmon and poached it.
And I said, eat this for the next three days.
And in three days, she was out with just a long-sleeve shirt like me,
feeling just fine.
So you can see immediate results with just the seasonality
from just the basic chemistry,
then energetic and emotional perspective as well.
Right on.
That's interesting.
I've never heard anybody talking about temperature
and the seasonality aspect like that.
Yes.
That's really unique.
So I wanted to bring the Archon in again.
I know he's playing co-pilot here, and I appreciate it,
but he did take the time to be here with us today.
I feel like it's rude to not bring him in a couple of times.
So, Archon, what do you think?
We have some time left.
I have, obviously, a few other things I want to get to,
but what do you consider some of the Greek's most unique positions
or insights that we should definitely get on the record here?
Well, I think that, for me, it helped me with attaining a certain level
of objectivity with how I look at things,
particularly with the things that he's talked about concerning deception,
which I think you've touched on once or twice in the conversation.
The fact that one of the chief qualities of this society
is that humans seem destined to never really know the truth about anything,
and not only do these illusions appear impenetrable,
but even this notion of the truth is a very poorly defined concept.
So we now live in, as you may have heard previously,
in a post-truth world where post-modernism has come back to the forefront
where people profess that nothing can be known.
And so it's a society where this deception is very much paramount,
which is why people expect their news to inform them
when, in fact, it deludes them, and they expect their jobs to be meaningful
when, in fact, most jobs are banal and repetitive.
And it's our parents and our schools and government and media
that work together to create this tier of reality that is known as the mainstream,
where everything just runs on plausible deniability,
but when you examine the so-called truisms that uphold them,
they don't really hold up.
And I find that the Greek has unpacked these things in a very easy-to-access way,
where you're able to ruminate on them and generate further conclusions from them,
where, you know, we're being taught that these institutions
are the high churches of reliable authority,
but it becomes more and more evident that, in fact, they're not.
And I also think that it kind of lends credence to this idea of conspiracy theories,
even though they are mocked now.
It's become very much routine in the last 10 years to disparage them,
but there's something in them that people are more and more compelled to pay attention to
because mainstream narratives don't really make sense.
And so that's kind of what I've tried to do with Greekspeak.com,
is unpack these different facets of society
in ways that help people move their thoughts along.
Yes, well, you are really great at summarizing complex stuff, as is the Greek,
and I appreciate the structure you have made on the website.
And it kind of speaks to what I've heard the Greeks say
in terms of general navigation of reality,
that rejecting what's commonly accepted right away
and then going back with diverse discernment
is always the right way to navigate.
It's just the default way should be to reject what's commonly accepted
and go back and really go over it
and be fully aware and present with that investigation.
And I think that applies to literally every subject.
I think that's probably distilled down to the simplest advice for getting through this mess.
Yeah, I would actually refer to a quote.
I don't know how many years ago the Greek made it,
but he basically said,
you know, take everything you know that you think is right-side up
and turn it upside down, and now it's actually right-side up.
And that's actually been helpful for discerning a lot of things.
We see these kinds of things sort of reoccur in pop culture tropes as well.
I think of the movie They Live, right, where the guy puts on the glasses
and a lot of things that seem one way are actually the very opposite.
So that sometimes helps for making sense of things.
Well, Greek, let me ask you about that.
The notion that we should flip everything 180 degrees,
you know, that applies to, say, the timekeeping
because we're told the day starts at midnight.
And you say, no, it's actually high noon.
That's a complete 180, a total clear-as-day inversion.
But that line of thinking has also gotten people,
I would say maybe off track, I don't know exactly,
but people say, oh, well, if we're told the Earth is round,
well, it must be flat because that is the polar opposite of that.
I'm just curious if you think that that 180 inversion is always applicable
or if it's sometimes taken in the wrong direction,
or should people, even out of spite, even out of just contempt, say,
you know what, I'd rather operate as if everything is exactly the opposite
of any mainstream thought?
Well, that's where the concept of knowing versus information comes in
because you can get information of all sorts,
and some is a lie and some is not.
But if you just focus on the knowing, if you know something is a lie,
well, it's discerned immediately.
Flipping something, let's say, like the shape of the Earth
and, let's say, large concepts, we were discussing biology.
Even that, for example, if you just take the standard notion
that you're a pressurized filter bag, that might work for you.
But ultimately, when you run into a glitch or a problem, it won't.
And the same thing is with the shape of the Earth.
There was a sort of, I wouldn't say a movement as recently
because there was no Internet back then, but in the mid-'80s,
there was a lot of concern about the shape of the Earth,
and I was quite involved in that.
I was questioning publicly, what shape is the Earth?
And I found out that, depending on what you do,
if you're an architect or a farmer, it's as flat as a board.
But if you're a surveyor, you better believe it's round
because you can't strike a triangle on the ground that has 180 degrees.
It'll always be greater.
So, again, it's one's perception and what you're trying to do.
This gets into, need I say, simulation theory concept.
It's what you focus on.
Flipping at 180 is very easy, I should say, to gain success with the mainstream.
Like, I love how accurate the mainstream news is based on that
because whatever they tell you, what's going on is really the opposite, right?
So when they tell you there's terrorism, it's really not terrorism.
It's some kind of exercise.
When they tell you it's an exercise, it was really terrorism, you see,
is one way to look at it.
The more mainstream the notion, whether it's science, religion, politics, or whatever,
the 180 works really well.
It may not be 180.
It might be 179 degrees, right, or 181 degrees, pretty close.
But when you use that principle on, let's say, mainstream concepts,
it's frighteningly accurate.
So, again, it would be knowledge versus information.
You know, when you know a lie is a lie, well, what about information?
What about facts?
They don't matter anymore, do they?
Right.
And let's apply that inversion principle, that 180 type of thinking,
to the question of aliens because the mainstream is talking about this
more than ever.
And, of course, it seems like throughout the 90s and early 2000s
they seeded certain people in the alternative community to frame the ET question
within a certain structure.
And I'm more skeptical than ever that the sci-fi lens is the accurate one
because the Pentagon's talking about it.
So I think there's non-human beings that exist.
We talked a little bit about the hierarchy, the spiritual hierarchy,
but I'm very skeptical of this context we're told to think about them in.
How would you invert the concept of aliens?
If they come from space, we're told, do they really come from inside the earth?
All of the above, but no one's right, no one's wrong.
It's a matter of one's perception.
What are you planning on doing with the information and the knowledge of them
or them?
I mentioned earlier that all of the organs in living organisms tend to be alien
to each other and they're in agreement.
And if something was, for example, completely alien,
it would be outside your perception so it wouldn't matter anyway.
I know it sounds like a philosophical lawyer to answer,
but it doesn't really matter at this point because there's a level of hypocrisy
here also in society.
You know, there's all kinds of hypocrisy,
and the hypocrisy here is you don't know enough about yourself to be able to
introduce yourself to another species.
For example, in the 1950s the typical meme was the saucer lands on someone's
front lawn and the little green men come out.
What's the first thing they say to the guy watering his lawn?
Take me to your leader because obviously you don't know a damn thing.
You see?
Yes, yes, I get that.
And really I don't know what I would do with the information except it would be
the satisfaction of my curiosity.
Obviously that's why I do what I do is asking these questions and trying to get
at things that people don't really get at that often.
And maybe there is no way to know,
but I do like the general concept that we don't know ourselves enough to even
know something else.
We should probably start there.
Well, I just want to interject one more thing.
There's an old saying that says we have found the enemy and the enemy is us.
We have found the aliens and the aliens are, you guessed it.
Yes.
I do think that there's something to be said for how many pop culture tropes do
refer to this.
You were talking earlier before about the mind control parasites that
manipulate society from the shadows.
Perhaps you can say slash ETs or ET control.
These are things that have had a lot of staying power,
whether that's, you know,
revenge of the body snatchers,
animorphs in the 90s,
or more recently a parasite.
I think we've heard of perhaps somebody called Donald Marshall speak of,
you know, the Vril and things like this.
I do think that the frustrating aspect is that no one has really come forward
recently who can give an accurate and believable account of these things
where there aren't leakages in their story.
Like most of the messengers who convey this information will typically be
compromised in some way,
whether it's mentally or through some kind of inconsistency in their story.
So it does warrant a bit further examination,
I think.
I think it has been obfuscated a lot in the alt media.
It might serve people better to refer to historical records.
Because there are all kinds of aberrations that happen throughout history that
get either covered up or eventually they go underground so that things can move
on in an uninterrupted way.
What comes to mind for me is there's a lot of references,
especially medieval times to the dog-headed people.
I've never been able to really pronounce their names,
but I think it's Cynocephaly or Kinocephaly.
It's quite hard to spell,
but if you Google dog-headed people,
you'll come across it.
You know,
they were known by the ancient Greeks,
persisted into late antiquity.
Obviously,
Egyptian gods like Anubis channel that visual.
And so the same goes for the ideas of parasites or ETs or whatever else.
It may be that ancient records hold more of an answer for that than
contemporary stuff.
Yeah,
I agree.
And another thing that makes me skeptical of the contemporary stuff and the
people who speak about it is typically their resumes.
They're generally involved with military intelligence or ex-military.
These are not the people that I want to get my raw truths about the ET reality
from,
but because of their framing,
I tend to just default to,
what else is there?
They're either beings from inside the earth that live alongside us and always
have.
They aren't just some distant visitors that occasionally pop through or
they're multi-dimensional,
which again is closer to home.
They're something of a passenger on this ride along with us.
We've just kind of removed all religious context.
We're strictly materialist as a general culture.
So these things are just put in a box of,
well,
you must be mistaken when you have an encounter yet people always do.
I hear stories all the time,
obviously part of the job,
but those stories in aggregate really make you think like there is something
else here.
It's more embedded in our environment than we're led to believe.
Yeah, clearly.
So while we still have a little time,
I want to get into some provocative stuff I still have in the outline.
In a previous interview,
Greek,
you were asked about project looking glass technologies that can see the
future and the most likely outcomes.
And you said,
yes,
it's possible.
It seems like technologies like this that might be in use behind the curtain
could have been either ancient relics or given to the elite by so-called
aliens.
Well,
which source of such a technology do you consider to be more likely?
The concept of amplification.
We use something called a bicycle because just paraphrasing here,
you can walk three miles or use a bicycle and travel 11 miles for the same
energy.
And you have a seat,
you know,
when you're tired,
right?
It's very similar.
I give an example,
let's say,
starting from the human body.
Have you ever been in a really tight spot,
a real bad situation,
and there's a little voice you hear that says,
everything's going to be all right.
Yeah.
Most of us experience that.
But what I'm suggesting that is,
is that's you in the future recalling that event.
And then someone will say,
well,
Greek,
what if I don't hear that little voice?
Well,
that means that it just might be your end or you will not recall this event in
the future.
Right.
If you make it,
you see.
So what I'm suggesting here is that we can't change the past,
but we can influence it because hearing that little voice,
everything's going to be all right,
doesn't change that you're not in a bad spot.
You're still in a bad spot,
but it influenced it slightly.
You see.
So that is actually very pragmatic because how do I know?
Well,
actually I brought up the point and you said,
yeah,
right.
You've gotten that as well.
So imagine we have a metric,
not just the scientific tools that are available today,
but let's just say there are scientific tools that are available today,
not the ones available to us.
That actually measures how that happens.
Just as simply as one point,
we had a mail letters across the country.
Now we can just do it with audio.
And that is completely describable before it went from pony express to
railroad,
to airplane,
to,
you know,
all that.
And we bypass that just simply by using wires and a signal over the wire.
And we bypass that now by going wireless.
All of that is totally explainable.
What this looking into the future or the past is completely explainable once the
tools and the methodologies and the processes are made available.
And again,
like Sam mentioned,
there are people coming out and describing these things,
but again,
it's just a description.
There really hasn't been anyone that's come forward and just laid out an
explanation,
you know,
a DIY kit,
right.
Or it's not available to the public,
but I would suggest just hearing that little voice is actually you in the
future.
Recalling it is something that is really measurable.
And once it's measurable,
guess what?
Just like walking on a bicycle,
it can be amplified.
Yeah.
Very interesting way to explain it.
I think that makes a lot of sense.
Now,
if a technology like that,
that kind of told the future or amplified,
it could be discovered as an ancient relic.
That says some interesting things about the ancient world.
There are researchers that suggest this,
but I'm curious what you think about how much of colonization,
war,
invasion,
how much of these situations are actually driven by a secret motivation to
uncover such things rather than the reasons were given on the surface.
Oh,
that humanity,
let's say surface dwelling earth inhabitants specifically are kept in a
cage where their society can reach a technological or scientific or
performance apex that is limited.
And then they're knocked down and they start all over again with very little
from the past is basically the modality,
the MO on the earth,
as far as we can see.
So yes,
all of that plays a big point,
but there is going to be a relief from that,
I would suggest.
And I'm not just suggesting it from,
let's say a personal hopeful perspective,
but from what is known as a prophetic perspective.
And when I say prophetic,
meaning from every culture that there will come a time where we will be freed
from this cycle.
Yeah.
I've heard you use the analogy of a movie for this basically round of
civilization,
that if you take the timeline and say 2000 year chunks,
well,
we have just been engaged with the movie and now we're in the credits.
And what are the credits?
It's where you learn who made the movie.
You learn who the director was,
who the key grip was,
who the producers were.
So in a sense,
it's very adjacent to what people say about an apocalypse.
An apocalypse is a great revealing,
a revealing of what?
Well,
that we're run by secret societies and a cabal that doesn't care about you and
they've manipulated everything.
And it comes intertwined with the collapse of civilization because it's all
built on their scaffolding.
So that's the part people tend to focus on is the destruction of everything,
but it's through the process of revealing,
which is what the credits would be.
So I like that analogy.
Yes.
Thank you.
And it's also the way I do it is a two-hour film.
You just buy two hours of film or two hours and 10 minutes because you need
credits in the end just for the audience.
And what's interesting about the credits portion,
it's very different from when the film is running.
If you stand up and make a disturbance,
everyone tells you to shut up and sit down during the film.
So prior to 1998,
around there,
if there was not a lot of big public,
let's say,
to-do about a lot of the things that are being discussed now,
let's say from the alternative,
which I don't like to grant them too much,
but the conspiratorial minded.
But what's interesting,
when the credits are rolling,
basically stand up,
put your coat on,
no one tells you to shut up and sit down.
So it's a time where disturbances are accepted.
Yeah,
that's true.
That's true.
Another good point.
And so another interesting thing that you've said,
Greek on a previous podcast,
is that all of our world leaders are made to get on their hands and
knees in front of a group of religious people and eat from dog bowls of
feces,
blood and urine.
And I don't know how literal you meant that it obviously works in a
couple of different ways,
but I've heard plenty to know that the world is generally run by
blackmail,
that public figures are compromised with honeypot operations and
humiliation rituals.
But this again is just a very specific claim.
How could you know such a thing or who are these religious people
carrying out such rituals?
Any elaboration would be appreciated on that.
Sure.
These are things that have,
when you look at information that you want to know about,
you kind of look at the source.
And sometimes certain sources seem more valid than others,
and you might want to carry it forward or, let's say,
not necessarily restore solidity of the information,
but just transmit it to others, right?
So what I would suggest the entire scenario about such a, let's say,
abominable act or something like that,
what I want to use as analogy is the story of Lord of the Flies,
how the children are shipwrecked,
and within a short time they actually commit murder against the fat kid,
right?
So here is a group of children sort of forming a pseudo-society or a
micro-society on their own.
And if you observe it, sort of like the animal farm story as well,
combine animal farm with Lord of the Flies,
and you see a very vicious, very cruel,
almost abominable setting that is kept within those works that I mentioned,
but not really championed as the model example that we have in society.
Just like, for example,
the act that you mentioned that I mentioned is not championed as the pinnacle
act of our world leaders.
It's kept in secret, but it is accessible.
There's plenty of people that have come forward, and how horrible?
Well, horrible how?
Based on what we consider to be morally active and morally acceptable is.
And I would suggest that the fringe element, again, more than the alternative,
because most of the alternative, by the way,
in conspiratorial is still very much hinged to the mainstream.
But I'm saying that a lot of the very fringe, meaning all the way to the edge,
should be reviewed and accepted as something one should know.
Well, that's interesting.
Let's unpack it a little bit, the fringe versus the alternative.
I generally, for branding purposes and simplicity, call this a conspiracy show.
I've kind of grown to get away from that term, I suppose,
when I started the shows in my early 20s.
Now I'm in my late 30s.
So, you know, things we think are good descriptions at one point, maybe not later,
but, you know, you got to do it for consistency's sake.
But I think it is more the fringe sources of material that I'm more attracted to,
but it just doesn't have the same ring to it, let's say.
But how would you define the difference between fringe and alternative?
What do you mean by the fringe is tied to the mainstream,
and how can we find more fringe sources?
Well, the alternative is tied to the mainstream.
Give an example.
Let's say there is a mainstream hoop to do on the Internet,
and you have bookmarked some alternative media sources.
You go to the alternative media sources that update daily or whatever.
Guess what stories they're talking about?
The same stuff the mainstream is, right?
Fair.
Where the fringe would be all the way to the edge,
and it's something that is just as relevant today,
that instead of being a mainstream news story,
was something that was brought out in the 60s,
or something that was brought out in the 70s, 80s,
or even just 10 years ago, or even recently.
But it just sits there as someone's account or recount of something that is pertinent
to what's going on in the world, but not really touched or reviewed
by definitely not the mainstream or alternative,
is what I would define as the fringe.
And I think you might have even had, from your history of doing what you do,
several people that would be more on the fringe than the alternative that you've interviewed.
I'd probably say so.
And, of course, there has to be a show every week so we get who we get.
But I think if I were to think about the ones that stick out in my mind the most
or the ones that excite me the most, it would probably be the ones in the fringe category.
But do you have any sources on the fringe that you consider to be of high value?
Oh, gosh.
This is, again, an inversion, if one hears what I'm going to say.
The most fringe information one can readily get, and when I say one,
I mean in a lawful sense, I mean it's so accessible to everyone,
is basically federal registries, old encyclopedias, reference books,
things that were, let's say, meant to be in the public but no one really knows that they exist.
For example, organizations, certain organizations, many organizations,
have what's called a newsletter, basically put out what's going on,
various categories every so often in time.
There's something called the Federal Registry that the American federal government has
that used to be monthly, I think, and now it's every three months.
And just go look at it, and you'll see some really shocking things that are mentioned
that are never covered by the mainstream media or the alternative.
Like, for example, states of emergency, financial situations, things like that.
Old encyclopedias.
When I say encyclopedia, you're not going to get in depth,
but you mentioned someone earlier, Charles Hoyt Ford.
He's wonderful to look at because his stuff applies today.
I like how he makes fun of the scientists in terms of how their things don't make any sense.
I'll give an example.
I'm pretty harsh on lawyers and doctors.
There are no more lawyers anymore, there are attorneys.
And the reason I say there are no lawyers anymore is because we're not in law,
we're in a legal system.
When the country, let's say, I mentioned the Federal Registry,
people know the Fourth of July.
Do you know the Fourth of July?
Yeah, that's just the day after July 3rd, right?
Well, you know, they revere that as an important day.
But if you bring up, let's say, when it was the  if you look up the history of someone,
when they were born and when they died, right?
When they were born, it would be July 4th.
But people have never heard of March the 9th, 1933, have they?
You bring up  what significance does March the 9th, 1933 have?
Well, that's when what's called the United States of America died.
And it doesn't mean you're buried.
When someone dies, it doesn't mean you're buried.
They usually put you in a morgue for a few days until you have what's called a funeral
and a burial, right?
And anyone could look up that day.
It's not very censored, what happened on that day.
It's a very short thing.
It's the Emergency Banking Act, and if you understand the words being used there.
That's why I mentioned there are no more lawyers.
Basically, there are attorneys.
And when this happened around 1933, anyone trying to practice law was really in trouble.
That's why if you remember watching any old black-and-white films that had sort of a prison setting,
there was always a lawyer and a doctor in the prison.
They always referred to someone, hey, doc, right?
Because they also went after the medical people to pretty much reinforce the allopathic medicine.
I know this is a little bit off of topic, but if you look at the woes of what we were mentioning,
the health woes of people, and they rely, for example, on the medical industry,
they are very clearly professing to be allopathic, which means only treating symptoms, right?
No cures, no healing, none of that.
And the rest of it is propaganda when we think of going to hospital or a doctor.
So all of these things, if you want to go to the fringe, actually,
it's memorialized in most of your reference manuals.
Another example of fringe would be if you go to an old university
and study what works they have in their library on any subject
and then compare that to the current textbooks, you'll see there's very little relevancy.
They're very, very different.
You'll have situations, especially here where I am,
I think it was one of the Carnegies bequeathed his personal library here.
There is an incredible treasure trove of not necessarily looking at old university textbooks,
but books that have been bequeathed, you know,
people that donated their own personal collections of things written in the 19th century.
Another thing that I suggest about fringe is that I'm going to make a statement that might shock people,
but once they take what I'm saying and research it, they'll find most of it to be true,
because we're not living in that time,
but everything that could have been known was known about anything by the late 1800s.
Quite interesting.
Now, I've mentioned this to someone who says,
well, you know, we have 13-year-olds with smartphones.
And I'm like, well, if you look at all of the technology that's in a smartphone,
what makes it technologically advanced to you is that everything is miniaturized,
but the concepts of all the circuit paths and all the materials in there were around in the late 1800s.
And all of the technology that people are marveled by today is simply applying extreme aspects of miniaturization.
Now, if you're impressed by that, I know the ladies are not impressed by miniaturization,
but anyway, I just wanted to throw in a lascivious comment, but you see what I mean?
Yes, and this is the place for lascivious comments.
Okay.
And yeah, I think that's a good way to look at the world.
It comes up time and time again that in the 1800s, a lot of the people of real value that I look to,
you know, the Rudolf Steiners, the Victor Schaubergers, the Charles Forts,
I mean, they were late 1800s, early 1900s.
Then by 1930, the robber barons have everything, and it's just been manipulation ever since.
Yes, pretty much.
Another thing is the education system.
There was something called Victorian Grammar School,
which was if you look at the bio of men like that that you mentioned and others,
the bio usually has when they were born and when they were teaching at Oxford.
And if you do the math, they're 18 years old teaching at Oxford with a professorship.
How is that possible?
Or 20?
Because you started your education about seven years old and you finished by 13 or 14.
Then you went on to further studies.
Interesting.
So pretty much the education system at this point, you know,
from kindergarten or first grade to 12th grade, that's about 1,000 hours a year.
So 12,000 hours of education to finish up high school.
And I used to humbly brag that I can reduce all of that to less than 400 hours from 12,000 hours.
Imagine that.
So it's very easy to take someone.
And from the Rudolf Steiner perspective,
you don't want to teach a lot of the critical technical things for memory until after someone is seven
or eight years old until they get their final set of adult teeth.
Because if you know the concept of memory being held in minerals and things like that,
how crystalline forms retain information, once you get your adult teeth,
you have an aspect of crystalline form that retains your being instead of shedding them.
And it doesn't mean because you lose your teeth you lose your mind.
You can if you try to eat certain things.
But there are many aspects of these men, of course, Victor Schauberger.
You didn't mention Tesla.
But Tesla, I think, has gotten more credit than he deserves,
even though he's been absconded from the academic record pretty much.
Because Tesla was part of an entire movement of men where I would suggest that Charles Ford was pretty much like a stand-alone guy,
and so was Victor Schauberger.
So, again, there were movements of people doing what they did,
and then there were some quite unique individuals that were sort of like messiahs of the subject of their time,
meaning they were true saviors within that subject.
Yes, yes.
And I was going to ask you about that, because in your sonic events,
you've mentioned names like Eric Dollard, who I've had the pleasure of interviewing a couple of times,
but, of course, also Tesla, Victor Schauberger,
and then a few that I hadn't heard of, like Louis Caveron and Rudolf Goschka.
Goschka? Rudolf Goschka?
Oh, Hoschka, yes, the vitamin guy.
Hoschka.
That's some of my favorite stuff, is to learn about these people,
because it's always the same couple that are highlighted.
You've got your Wilhelm Reichs in there, too.
And there's a lot of research on some of these figures,
but when I learn about a new one, I'm really jazzed up.
Are there other bright minds and influences of the past that would kind of fit this archetype?
I guess alive or dead, but most likely dead, because as we've said, they aren't around much anymore.
But who are some of the other people that we don't often hear about that you think should be researched?
Oh, gosh, you know, you've almost just got me here, drawing a blank,
but I can give you a direct example.
Living here near Tucson, back in the early 2000s, I met a man named Joe Blankenship.
I think there's a YouTube video of him being interviewed for about four hours,
and he was quite an interesting guy.
He was Wilhelm Reich's chauffeur when Wilhelm Reich did work here,
and I got a lot about Wilhelm Reich that you won't find anywhere else,
you know, actually him being his personal chauffeur, or driver, I should say.
Joe Blankenship's mom had a small diner that Howard Hughes would visit,
and he would go to the diner a half hour before his lunch and pay for the amount of business they would have
in a half hour and ask them to empty out the entire restaurant,
and he would send a crew in there to wipe things down, and he was one guy who was a flycatcher.
A lot of interesting stories.
Giving an example with Joe Blankenship, I was at the ranch one day in his shop,
and he had this rickety plywood box, and I touched it, and it was shaky.
I said, you know, I could reinforce that.
You know, it's kind of shaky. What is it?
And he says, that's an orgone box.
And I said, well, why don't I just reinforce it?
It's kind of rickety.
He says, no, I want to leave it like that, because that's the one that Wilhelm Reich built himself.
You see?
So I was like, oh, really?
Who's Wilhelm Reich?
You see?
So I was pretty much enlightened, quote-unquote, by this man.
He's passed away since for a while, but others like him would come through
because he was a very interesting individual.
So that question, I kind of drew a blank, but my suggestion is,
there are interesting people everywhere.
It's just that they don't have websites, right?
They haven't written books.
You'll find them if you are ready, like the old adage, when the student is ready, right?
The teacher will appear.
So I think that these people are sparse and rare in society,
but when one deems themselves ready for an experience with someone who is interesting like that,
hate to say it, they will appear.
But don't plan it.
Yeah, don't plan it.
It will just happen.
Fair enough.
Well, those are my favorite people to try to run into and get on this show,
whether anonymous or otherwise.
I mean, we're doing it right now.
And so as we're really nearing the end of this thing,
I wanted to ask you about just the way that some of the terms are phrased on the website about what you do.
You say that you don't seek approval, you just seek the truth.
Sometimes that offends in a culture that is as backwards as this one.
Well, as we're coming to the end, other lines you have on the website say, for example,
when I tell people that society is in a bad position,
they just imagine the current situation being in a worse state.
But that's not it.
Things are worse than you imagine because of things you don't know anything about.
Or the contrast to what people think is going on and what's really going on is so huge that you can't talk about it publicly.
Well, I am interested in the rawest of truths, the deepest of rabbit holes, the most taboo truths available.
What would you consider to be the most taboo topic that you could speak truth on?
What are the truths that sometimes seem to even make other truth seekers get a bit queasy?
Okay, that's a really good question.
It doesn't need to be pondered much, basically because of the tools we have.
When I say basic tools, most people have access to what I call the stupid rectangle and the devices that they use.
One of the things that I tell people when this is brought up is,
if you go and look on the Internet for the weirdest, most outlandish conspiracy theory,
whether it's like Dulce, the underground base, or spiders on Mars, or cloning, or anything like that,
the reality is even worse than that.
It's even more extreme than that.
So the most extreme stuff on the Internet is probably closer to the truth than you know.
Well, I like it, broadly speaking.
Yeah, I mean, it's hard to know exactly what that means, but I generally agree.
Yeah, and the thing is to not take it where it drives you insane,
and don't be prepared to do a public recitation or dissertation on it, because it's not going to be accepted.
When I say public, it could be just people within five feet reach of you.
But just take in the information.
I always say, from a cosmic perspective, information is just that.
It's not whether you think it's true or not.
It's, did you get the picture?
Do you have the notion?
So later on, very often I tell people certain things that can be accessed,
and I don't like explaining them.
Like, for example, the word nice, if you look it up in an etymology,
it means foolish, stupid, and senseless.
But I found that if you tell them, they kind of brush it off or give you a chuckle.
But if you ask them to look it up themselves, it packs like 75% more punch, right?
So actually giving a laundry list of what I think is outlandish would be not as impactful
as if people looked up what they tend to have a tendency to look up on their own.
And I'm suggesting that the weirdest, strangest, most fringe stuff that they could find on the Internet
is still mild in comparison to what's really going on, possibly.
Yes, well, that sounds like I'm going to have a job doing this for quite some time,
which is going to make the wife and kids happy, yes.
Job security for sure, yeah.
Indeed.
Well, this has been really interesting and insightful.
I appreciate the Archon for getting us together.
You guys ended your 10th episode saying you'd be working on a new website
for things that people might consider esoteric now,
but will be more familiar as time goes on.
Is that still the plan, and what sorts of things are you referring to, guys?
Well, yeah, that website has actually also come to fruition and has been concluded.
It's called Godspeak.com.
Oh.
I try to be creative with my names, but they invariably fall into the same template.
So Godspeak, also with two E's, God, S-P-E-E-K, and there's another podcast on there.
It didn't progress as far as the Greek-speak.
It's a sister site simply because, well, of different things.
The so-called pandemic came along, and a lot of my time was taken up with other things.
So we did get to Episode 8.
That should be good enough for most people, though we might conclude it at some point in the future.
Also, a few articles on there, not as many as Greek-speak.
Now that people are starting slowly but surely to take notice of it,
I may return to actually completing some of those things.
But it's on there for anybody to explore.
Oh, man.
It's so bittersweet because it's very rare that I miss a whole aspect of a person's work,
but these sites aren't necessarily connected.
But now I'm seeing you've got the ancient world, spirits and soul, the gods, Judaism, Christianity, Islam,
Eastern religions, very intriguing stuff.
I mean, maybe we'll get to it in a future interview, but that is great.
I like the formatting of the websites, the presentation of the material.
Good stuff, guys.
I think what you do is worth people checking out.
So Greek-speak, S-P-E-E-K, is the initial website.
Godspeak, same spelling, is the newer one.
Any other links or parting information to give people if they want to dive deeper into what you guys have done?
Yeah.
I'm also doing a current project, Current Sonics, running with  you can find it at ocelli.com.
It's a current project.
You go to ocelli.com, spells just like it sounds, and it's a subproject.
It's a subscription only.
It's not open to the public, and it's called Rated Y, The Unculting of Humanity.
Huh.
I like it.
Right on.
Well, again, thank you so much.
You know a lot about a lot, and thanks for doing this.
Take care out there, both of you.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Secret Sciences, Cosmic Censorship, Supernatural Beings, and the Biological Vacuum.
Oh, my.
Definitely had to be unexpected guests, which I always like to surprise people with.
I like their pseudonyms.
I like the cadence with which they speak.
I'd say they make a great team, and they pride themselves on trying to talk about raw truth in a whole host of areas at a high level.
I think that's something we got a lot of respect for around here, right?
Of the subjects they cover, we could have done more on law, government, or military,
but it's the secret sciences and hidden physics stuff that I like a lot because thinking about common things in new ways is exciting,
and you really can let your imagination run wild in terms of the reality we could be living in if the blockage could be lifted.
I like hearing new names of bright minds we can put up alongside Victor Schauberger, Wilhelm Reich, and some of the others.
Today, that was Louis Keveron and Rudolf Hoschka, I think is how he pronounced it.
But Rudolf Hoschka's work is interesting because he was studying how vitamins work and exposing simple life forms to various things,
and ultimately found that just proximity was enough to cause an effect or reaction,
which might say something about that health and resonance idea.
I also like alchemy talk when we can get it, and funny enough, I got off this call,
and I saw a post about this guy, Stefanovich Rabenikoff, by someone who was highlighting it because it was this guy's birthday.
He's dead now, but in honor, you know?
And Rabenikoff was like Schauberger in that he just studied nature and tried to replicate it or create technology based on it.
The gist of his story is that he was laying in a field admiring the beauty of nature, and he started to feel ill.
And then he realized he was resting over the top of a hive of a type of bee that makes their hives in the ground.
I can't remember if he dug up the hive or just looked at it and made a structure that mimicked it,
but in the lab, he would notice the same thing if he waved his hand over this artificial hive.
He had some other people do it, and some said waving their hand over it felt warm, some said cold,
but clearly there was some kind of field effect going on.
He ended up calling it the cavity structure effect.
He also did see some magnetic effects and then ended up building these lattice structures into a box, kind of like a suitcase.
And he ended up realizing that you could not set things on this box.
It repelled them, basically shot them up into the air, just like if you had a briefcase with negatively charged magnetic plates
and then tried to slide another one on top of it.
It would repel it up into the air and down onto the floor.
And this is crazy because there is plenty of video footage of it.
That's what I found so damn interesting.
Then he made a type of platform with a handle.
You could actually ride a little hoverboard thing using the same basic lattice structure that he mimicked from the beehive.
Then this video, which was from the Universe Inside You channel, great channel,
made some points about scientists saying that the flying physics of several types of beetles don't add up,
and the conventional speculation is that they are hovering rather than flying somehow.
And of course, if you look at the cross section of their wings, they share a similar pattern to the hive.
And then you think about the ancient world and the Egyptian motifs of the scarab beetle,
and you wonder if maybe they respected the beetles so much because that's how they learned this secret of nature.
Really wild stuff. Check out Universe Within You on YouTube and you can see the whole video.
But these are the kind of guys I find most interesting.
Probably the most interesting kind of person ever.
And so few in the mainstream ever hear about them or their discoveries.
So, fun episode overall. I appreciate their time and the work they do.
Check out Greek Speak or God Speak if you want to hear them go deeper without me getting in the way.
As always, the first hour of the show is good, but the second hour is even better.
In this one we talked about lost technology and the importance of procedure,
lawful timekeeping and the effects of the Pope's work schedule,
the deeper effects of rulership by artificial time, the importance and effects of seasonal diets.
The Greek gave us his Discernment Guide to Life and talked about the 180 inversion principle.
We got into aliens and the dog-headed people, Project Looking Glass, ancient relics and E.T. gifts,
what it means to say that we're now in the credits of the movie.
The Greek talked to us about the dog-bowl humiliation ritual that all politicians must partake in.
And we talked about the difference between the fringe and the alternative.
So, go ahead, upgrade to plus, get the full show and keep the Carl Wood train on the tracks.
Eight bucks a month, five new shows a month and one hell of a big archive.
And higher side news, well, when it rains, it pours.
If my life wasn't hectic enough right now, one of the two main systems we use to run the Plus membership infrastructure
had an update that broke compatibility with the other system.
They've already released a bug fix, but anyone who had a transaction process in that 48-hour period
shows up as inactive in the system.
Obviously, support tickets have flooded in and my guy Mike is not only working to answer all those,
but also wrote a script to correct the rest of the accounts.
Most likely before many of you noticed, I think it's like 5% of people were affected,
locked out for a day or two.
But it should be all fixed now or it will be fixed very, very soon.
These things happen from time to time, but we use good systems and I hope nobody was greatly inconvenienced.
But that said, I think we are going to get all five shows out this month, this one being number four.
I got two more recorded from a hotel room over the last few days,
so I should have at least a one-show buffer while I try to get the rest of my life in order
and get everything set up at home.
And with that, let's go to the Meetup calendar.
April 29th, today, we have the Sin City Conspiracy Enthusiasts hanging out in Las Vegas, Nevada.
Tomorrow, April 30th, Asheville, North Carolina.
May 6th, Dublin, Ireland.
Also May 6th, Sedona, Arizona.
Also May 6th, High Springs, Florida at the High Springs Brewing Company.
And May 13th at the 7018 Brewery in Elko, Nevada.
And we'll leave it there.
I like it. Sounds like people are getting together as we speak.
Go on in at highersidemeetups.com and find the other THC fans near you,
because it is your inoculation from indoctrination.
Networks are important and all that.
You already know.
But that is all she wrote, guys.
Thanks again to the Archon and the Greek, and to you for listening.
I've done my part.
Your move, secret science secret keepers, cosmic censorship servants, and consensus-centric thinkers.
Your fucking move.
How fun I find.
And I don't fix it all wrong.
And I don't have to face it.
That's right.
And you're wrong.
Wrong.
I'm an addiction to the digital technology.
And every now and then I try to quit and leave it be.
But it's too hard to turn it off.
It's getting worse and yet it's learning.
It's learning.
I see discipline is no fun.
I find denial makes it all wrong.
Face it.
That's right.
Don't tell me why.
Discipline is no fun.
I find denial makes it all wrong.
Face it.
That's right.
So many arms expanding off the big conspiracy.
And every one of them has got a couple hooks into me.
I try to forget and I ignore but I'm just out of luck.
But I don't have to tell you that.