Greetings to everyone and welcome to episode 5 of the God's Big Podcast.
I'm the Archon and I'll be continuing my discussions today with my co-host, the Greek,
about mainstream religions in order to scrutinize their histories and their content.
God's Big.com has no political religious or corporate affiliations and is completely
managed by myself.
For those who choose, you can offer donations to the project on my other website, GreekSpeak.com
and that is most appreciated.
So I hope you enjoy our upcoming conversation and thanks again for listening.
[Music]
Hello, Greek.
Greetings. We're here again.
Indeed we are.
So I think a good continuation of the last episode on Judaism would be to talk about how
that culture provided the inspiration for Christianity to develop, which is arguably
the most formidable political and ideological system of the last 2000 years.
I think it's persisted as if by divine ordinance and we probably won't get through even half
of the material that we could cover on the topic but we'll do what we can.
So I want to start by piggybacking off one of the points made on the last episode, which
is that Christianity was this bizarre outgrowth of events taking place in the first century
AD connected initially to the Judeans later to the Roman state.
And so starting with the Judeans, they killed their Messiah/God but it's probably not the
first time something like that has happened.
So I want to start by asking why did it become such a big deal when the Judeans did it to
the point where an entire empire had to shift its course based on that development?
Well, it was an administrative decision.
Being on the culture within the Roman conquest, which was the Judean culture within the
Roman conquest of Judea, it is there are many ironies which are cosmically linked to
you know how their Messiah came at their lowest point where they still occupied the territory
and many other things, you know, the dilution of their culture.
But when I say administrative, the religious authorities, just like today, for example,
if you go to a doctor or whatever, a lawyer or whatever, that's part of the theocracy.
I think we've explained that previously in other sonic events.
Mankind is always ruled by theocracy whether you believe it or not or know it or not, that's
a failing of most people on social criticism.
The Judean culture that remained and the quote unquote culture in Israel, although it
was occupied in Sussan to the Roman culture or authorities, still functioned administratively
you know, although they were Sussan under subjection, they still had certain quote unquote
liberties.
And one of the liberties is to record history, record events and of course, you know, administered
events.
And they had realized which they had known if it's in, let's say, what they call the New Testament,
which by the way, I want to, I think I've criticized the New Testament also and how it should
be read, but we're going to be referencing that a lot of us are speaking about Christianity
not so much believe it or not, but enough that I just want to let people know that it is,
it was not considered scripture at the time, right?
But okay, with that said, the administration had noticed what they had done and wanted
to cover it up.
Oh gosh, a cover up.
I thought that was just JFK 9/11 and all this other stuff that you see in modern society
in the Western world that you hear about.
No, the cover up and the false, the false, what would you say, identification and all that
had started back then.
And that's very clear in the books of Mark and Luke when the head priests say we must
cover this up, essential and paraphrasing and get rid of those that knew him, right?
Or he affected.
So their thing was if this happens, then we'll say, well, we can't say that nothing happened
because there was so much commotion and disturbance.
We have to change what happened and why it happened and the outcome and who the character
was.
Alright, an example I like you being in the Western world is 9/11.
I spoke to someone who works in an auto parts store, brothers in the FBI and I said, listen,
your brothers in the FBI, you got to go arrest those terrorists that flew the airplanes
into the World Trade Center on 9/11 because they were on Egyptian TV the other day.
You know, and he kind of stood back and was like, oh, well, you know, yeah, you know, a reasonable
personal say, wait a second, if they were suicide pilots and they actually did fly into
the buildings, then how could they be in Egyptian TV?
You see what I mean?
It's so ridiculous, right?
And it's true.
Why isn't the FBI arresting the suicide pilots that flew the airplanes into 9/11 because
they're on, we know where they are.
They're in Cairo and television the other night.
I mean, this is how ridiculous from the beginning, all the way through to that statement, which
is true, it's a true statement is with Christianity and its outcome and all that.
But the notion of deicide was probably something that had been ongoing in other cultures.
But the Judeans seem to have a particular after effect of what they did that gained a lot
of momentum politically and otherwise.
Sure, but the deicide resurrection, the Godhead figure, son of God and all that, you'll
see in almost every culture because every culture is almost of the same manufacturer.
So for example, let's say I made a statement like Mercedes-Benz has weak water pumps on their
engines.
Well, that would be for all their models, wouldn't it?
I didn't say one particular model because they all come from the, all the Mercedes come from
a similar manufacturer.
Societies are manufactured.
They're made.
It's called social engineering, right?
It's always been this way from day one.
So that's in other words, talking about the deicide is talking about one of the select empirical
points of engineering a society.
It's definitely food for thought.
I mean, we know that there have been sort of the lore of the Christ figure in all these
different cultures of a God that dies and resurrects and things of that nature.
And a lot of people, particularly in the mid-2000s, late 2000s, sort of latched on to that
to say, well, see Christianity is fake.
It's all, these stories exist everywhere.
It's a religious fiction, just like all the religions are fiction.
Fiction meaning something that you, beyond the story, it's very difficult to find anything
to back it up.
We're not talking about the text that they alleged is subscribed to.
That's a different notion.
Those are historical and law documents, let's say, right?
Those are, we're not talking about the records that religions attest to following because they
don't do anything or know anything in them and don't be fooled by academics or whatever
religious figures, let's say clergy figures reading off verses.
You can do that out of a chocolate chip cookie recipe and have a, one of the cookies look
like the shape of the Virgin Mary and within a week you'll have 100 followers asking you
how that cookie crumbled, right?
Because when you're talking about humans, you're talking about low functioning beings.
That's a new, you know, they're low functioning, right?
They're not high functioning.
Kind of like chickens, you know, they're birds, but they don't fly, right?
So.
[laughs]
Low functioning birds, anyway.
But, okay, so what was known in the ancient world concerning the death of this important
god figure, you know, taking place around that time?
Because I do believe that it was widely reported based on the meteorological signs, the natural
disasters that took place around the time of his death, at least in the Middle East.
So it kind of went beyond just the lore that a lot of cultures have of these things happening.
There were actual events.
Sure.
And there was also a four-year ministry, you know, if you do biblical counting, it was four
years or more.
And the reason it was such is a simple concise message takes about four years to get around
in a world that is trodden by foot and sail, right?
So if you're on land, you're on foot, and if you're on water, you're on, you sail.
So that's roughly the amount of time that it took back then to move ideas around.
If it were to happen, if the Christ figure were to happen today would be 20 minutes in
relative time.
But there was also this sense that certain people had an understanding that, "Oh, a god
has died."
I think you mentioned once that Tiberius asked a question about that, like, "Oh, I heard a
god died somewhere.
How come nobody told me about that?"
Well, not only he, the god, but the people killed their own god, and he viewed what kind
of people would kill their own god, and he actually banned and, quote, unquote, holocaust
at Judea and of that fate, what's called the Judea and religion from Rome.
It was about them.
And also the territories that were very tight under Roman rule, that hope is a Mediterranean
rim.
They had to go extreme east or extreme west or very south, and they killed quite a few,
almost a million because of that over a 10-year period.
And there's a reason why you don't get anything about the eastern culture because they need
to keep an enemy.
So they keep people in the dark about the Middle East.
You hear about the western culture, even I say, it is based on the Greek foundation,
you know, regarding political science and philosophy, things like medicine.
But actually, I would say that if you look at Greece, it was an agriculture, basically
olive farmers or sheep purters, and about a hundred or two city states, nothing really going
on there.
And the modern ruins that you see actually that are there today, that are marveled as
Greek, actually, were not even made by the Greeks, but that's another discussion.
Western culture in the past 200 years is grabbed on to that to keep in the dark, what actually
happened in the Middle East is about southwestern Asia, and their achievements so they can
always have an enemy is phobic position.
So when you see anything coming out of the western culture, you have to keep in mind, you
know, what about southwestern Asia or Asia at the time?
Also since this is just a bounce around a little talking about the history of Christianity,
empirically, mathematically, scientifically, philosophically, there is no such thing as Christianity
as a whole, as just a loose term.
It's all Catholicism, like it or not.
So if you're Christian, you're Catholic, period, a five, a two to five percent variation
on a Christian sect does not make you non-Catholic, sorry, you know, the other sects.
Yeah.
They would dispute that there's some doctrinal differences, but I understand your point.
Two to five percent.
They're all on the Pope's work schedule, right?
The Gregorian calendar.
They don't know how to keep time, and they all have the same iconography and the similar
stories, which are false, patent-blee false, you know.
The only thing that you'll find in their stories and beliefs that is accurate is it happens
some time around 2000 years ago, in and around the land known as Judea and surrounding
areas, outside of that, nothing is true.
Kind of like in New York, there was two tall skyscrapers around the time of September,
such a year, and they were vaporized.
Outside of that, nothing is true.
Or with JFK, there is an American president in his limousine and his head is head blown
in half.
Outside of that, nothing is true.
The Great American Depression.
People had money one day then, they didn't, and they all started starving.
Outside of anything else that you hear, that is not true.
Very simple.
So the reductionist principle is enough to just get one on a path of study.
And then after you, well, let me just interject this.
The Greek speak stuff is to save people from two decades of worthless study, which is not
worthless.
You know, after 20 years, you find that it was not necessary.
If just someone were in five minutes or 150 words or less can assemble the actual true
and accurate notion of what went on with both specifics and non-specifix that an eight-year-old
can comprehend.
And that's what I've been doing for the past decade and a half.
To save you or the listener, two decades of looking into and pondering, the subject matter,
regardless of what it is.
Yeah, which is certainly a gem for those people that recognize it as such.
For other people, it's just a regular rock that they don't see any distinctive features
about, but I guess that's their problem.
So following the death of the Christ, we have a series of political events taking place
from the Judeans purging from their communities, anyone who claimed to follow the Christ, to
the Judeo-Roman Wars a few decades later.
Eventually you have emperors like Constantine getting involved.
All right, I'm going to interject here.
No one was really following the Christ in reality.
They were acknowledging the events and acknowledging him because the way you follow the Christ
is keeping the biblical law.
He is not this rebellious son that came here to get rid of his father's laws.
There's paraphrasing here, right?
Right, right.
So you don't follow him.
You do what he said, basically you hear him as the completion of many things that were asked
about what this is all about.
Indeed, acknowledging, rather.
And given that you had a rollercoaster of emperors who were both four and against so-called
Christianity as it was developing in its early stages, what were the foremost political
motivations for the Roman Empire to eventually adopt it into fourth century with Constantine?
Because I think you've said in the past that Constantine really wanted to create a super
state and for that you need a unified system of banking, military, law, and religion and that
was really his agenda.
Sure, but if you follow Constantine, I have no proof of this, but he was given marching
orders on what to do just like the Senate did for killing Julius Caesar for 100 years
before.
It's the same people behind the scenes.
It was time to do that.
So there's something about magic, spells and cantations that require everyone to focus
on a particular thing.
And they noticed when they unified that consciousness, no matter what it was, you can go and have
half the world focus on the color blue and once you have that, then you pull off of that
focus anything you want, right?
Because of the conscious, the temporal nature of that, right?
It's kind of like everyone tuning in to watch a particular show.
You can use their energy that way.
So it sounds kind of mystical and magical, right?
But that's how the world is run.
There is nothing.
What we're being told about Constantine is a complete lie.
I don't think he even really existed as told.
I mean, he did exist as far as we can see, but what the common lay even, I could, I could
commission has to say about him is not true.
And that's another discussion.
I can get into a little bit now, but I'd rather not because the focus I think is different.
Well, it's interesting about the, what you're saying about the magic aspect, because one
thing that I wonder about is that if the Christian religion can be shown to have been built
on in part, misconstruing the events of the first century, AD or at least misrepresenting them,
then how could they have successfully rallied so much political power behind it when the
Romans already had their own religion that they felt worked?
And in fact, they're throughout, you know, the second and third centuries, there was a
lot of debate in the Senate.
Like, what are we doing adopting this?
This is garbage.
Let's persecute these people.
And then it would turn around.
And then some emperor would come along that would say, no, we should support it.
And so on and so forth until it's Constantine.
So we're not persecuting the Christians.
There were no Christians really back then as such.
They were persecuting the people that were becoming aware of biblical law.
Well, I'm talking more, I guess, second, third century you had these people, you know, after
the second century, those original Christians were gone.
And now you had these madmen like the monks and those so on and so forth.
Right.
And there would be like a person area, political mercenary or a mill, you always have to
have some belief behind military system, right?
Yeah, simple.
And then you could actually just fast forward to the creation of Islam was to stop the, you
know, by showing the Christians or idol worshipers and basically fairytale worshipers.
Islam was created to thwart the expansion of Christianity, which it mostly succeeded
in doing for Southwestern Asia.
All those are planting it with something else, which became an issue, but we'll have a separate
episode on us.
Well, anything to anything to block, you know, the enemy of man and me is my friend, right?
So, but they're more adherent.
I mean, if there's quotes by mononides, 16th century or so, 15th century, stating the Christians
are abominable pagan practices and basically praise the Islam for, you know, getting rid
of idols and keeping them away, even though he could not, they could not progress Judaism.
So, they'll take the Islamic stance over the Judea, extends if you cannot progress Judaism,
we say.
At least the, in the Islamic stance, they have maintained some sense of law where the Christians
will tell you about right there, they're, you know, they're all all us, right?
Indeed.
I haven't answered your question about the fourth century and all that, but we don't know much
about the dark ages because the reason they're called dark is because the information has
been cut off.
But you will not find any Christian, a modern Christian iconography or doctrine or anything
that goes before the, even the year 800, but typically the year 400, you'll not find,
so between the first century and the year 400, we don't know really what was going on.
And they sort of invented something 400 years after the fact because, you know, humans have
such a good memory, you know?
So it's, again, it's a, it's an aspect of the political machine.
And if you understand this is a planet of low functioning morons, it's very simple to
see that it doesn't take much.
In other words, you don't need anything to be qualitative, you just need to be quantitative
that everyone can do it.
Share that all the time with political leaders.
We want something that every, all of our citizens can have, right?
But at the same time, you had the, the private academies become universities, right?
And just a bounce around here.
People seem to adore these academics and there's academia academics, the universities are not
for education.
It's just to provide a certain amount of quote unquote knowledge that is distilled by those
who have the power.
If you study, for example, all of the main universities in the US, the, the old ones, they
were all started with money from the opium trade and human trafficking and things like that.
So no matter where people go to get whatever they think they're getting, it's dirty.
So why would you give them consciously provide them with a religion that is not?
They would not see it as something they can assimilate or consume.
Now that makes sense.
So let's, let's stay in this sort of first three centuries for the moment.
Because in this period, you saw the rise of religious groups that try to explain what was
going on and they would characterize the Christ in their own preferred way.
I know there's no one group called the Nostics and it's an oversimplified term, but those
groups were some of the most prominent ones to do that.
And I've never really been able to determine the origin of that tradition because it does
predate the first century.
It has elements of Platonism and Buddhism mixed in.
What do you know about the evolution of that Nostocent movement in general?
It's simple.
It's, in Plato was, you know, he held from the middle, you know, his knowledge and his philosophical
base came from kabbalistic roots, right?
Meaning from the southwest Asia and all that.
And even back then, the model of let's say the Asia versus the Indo-European cultures
being at odds with each other permanently was set up.
So it's very simple.
You have ideologies from either culture, the west and the east bleed over only to serve
those that are controlling both sides.
So what you know about Plato is not true entirely in what you know about the east is not true
entirely what you know about the west is not true entirely.
Again, we're speaking at a time that was classified, I guess, as the dark ages or the
beginning of the dark ages.
And it's informationally dark.
But what we can see through architecture and tradition that it morphed out of other things
that gives what we call Christianity no sense of originality.
Can you expand on that point a bit?
No sense of originality?
Yeah, there's nothing original about Christianity.
Name one thing that's identifiable just to Christian, the Christian tradition, because that's
what it is.
You can't.
Everything is borrowed or stolen from other cultures.
The way they keep time, their holidays, who they worship is in agglomeration, the way they
worship, you know.
And also just to throw this in, we're kind of not evading, but this has to be considered
because we're doing it in present time.
And this is not necessarily a history, but an overall commentary on what the Christian
meme and the Christian tradition is about.
What solidified the Christian tradition that we consider to be Christian today is not
the third or fourth century, but the King James Bible.
So everything is based on the King James version, what version?
They're all King James.
You know it's King James, if you open it in the first verses in the beginning, God created
the heaven in the earth, right?
Heaven's in the earth.
That's anything that has that as the first verse is King James version variation.
So just like if they say, well, I'm not Catholic, I'm this former Christian, you're kind
of still Catholic.
A two or five percent variation does not make it another religion, right?
They don't know what date is.
They cannot identify properly any of the characters.
They don't even know the name of the, you know, you could ask a thousand Christians, a hundred
thousand Christians and million Christians, what the name of God is and they cannot answer.
Or you know, if you ask who described the Christ, they talk about a guy nailed to a cross-wearing
a diaper, which is not biblical or whatever or prophetic or in the text or in the history.
So you have a serious problem, a human problem, again, low functioning creatures that have
to be fed whatever is put out on the trough and the feeding trough.
And that's very simple.
It's almost like a non-subject, right?
In other words, we can speak, this is not to disparage the topic, but in a sense, it's
almost like speaking about the medical industry.
If they don't know how the body works and cannot explain accurately how the body works, everything
else is nonsense, right?
So what you're experiencing in the, in this nonsense reality, which is a joke, but it's
a joke that you could be killed in.
Actually, there were in the 80s and 90s movies about game shows where people were really
killed, right?
This is where you're living.
You were set, humans were set up to be low functioning creatures from the beginning, this particular
iteration.
And everything else that you were given, whether it's religion, science, culture, whatever,
is going to be on that low functioning par.
And if you're not a low functioning individual, I feel sorry that you're here.
In terms of charting specific occurrences within nosticism that would dovetail with Christianity,
we have this group known as the simonians who were led by a Samaritan called Simon Megas
character that's curiously mentioned in the New Testament for what seems like no apparent
reason and Christians will take a story to be more of an appendage to the work of the Apostles.
And if you examine what second century writers had to say, it becomes clear that this guy
is an important figure.
And I just wanted to ask you to sort of talk in general about what you know about him.
We'll get to the Pope's stuff later.
Well, though, it was one of the first criticisms I gave on Christianity.
When I say Christianity, Catholicism also is this Simon Peter guy, this Simon Megas.
And it's interesting how, think of it like, you know, you hang a guy, Saddam Hussein,
but then you have a American president who's saying also, right?
It gets a little confusing, you know?
So Hussein Obama, right?
And so the mixture of names does not mean the identifiers are the same and it doesn't
mean that it's the same person or you have to really get into identifying things here.
So nobody went to Europe out of the biblical text other than Paul and his crew.
Everyone else went east.
So the first sign is that if you have a Simon Peter or Simon Shimon of any sort, which
as a Samaritan is mostly pagan, just inclusive of the Judean deities, right?
Deity because the Samaritans are a byproduct of the Assyrian invasion, I would say loosely.
I could think most people would find that accurate in their studies.
And being a magician just means he's like wealthy as a, if you're known to be a magician
in ancient times, you were quite popular as such and you were quite wealthy also.
And it could just when he's a magician, he was not just the ledger domain, Presto digitation,
I pull a rabbit out of a hat with a secret compartment, but also dabbling into a cult ritual, right?
Like more like an Alistair Crowley type figure, let's say, or Jack Parsons and you see, so
you have a mixture of that and influence.
And the Indo-Europeans, the Romans at the time also found that the height of human culture
was to be extracted from the Middle East or the East even in those days, right?
So it was a natural sentiment to accept a wealthy quote unquote, "trixture" that was also an
occultist from the East to sort of do an overlay on the reasoning for what's been going
on or what has been known to have gone on the past was very well accepted.
Yeah, so I'd like to point out some of the practices that the Simon Megas instituted with
his group. It's not to say that he was the first in history to do any of those things, but
it appears that Christianity was shaped specifically by some of those practices.
And so first we have the introduction of the pagan imagery that evolved into the depictions
of what we see today of the Christ and the Virgin Mary, just a quickly quote from Irenaeus,
his second century book called Against Heresies.
He writes, "They, the Simonians also possessed images, some of them painted and others formed
from different kinds of material.
They crown these images and set them up along with the images of the philosophers of the
world that is to say Pythagoras and Plato and Aristotle.
They also have other modes of honoring these images after the same manner of the Gentiles."
And so Simonians also held to that Simon Megas was not only the Christ, but also the Father,
so just a quote from Irenaeus again quote, "He, Simon Megas, was glorified by many as a God
and he taught that he who appeared among the Jews as the Son of God while in Samaria,
he descended as the Father and the rest of the world he came to as the Holy Spirit.
He was the highest power and he allowed himself to be called by whatever name men pleased."
End quote.
"Sure, that's been going on.
That goes on today if you go to inner city neighborhoods where you have influence
of the nation of Islam.
You have five percenters.
I've witnessed this and they dress well and they take the characters to go out and find
recruits in the inner city and they go, "I'm God.
I'm God.
You call me God, right?
Or born, right?
Word is bond, right?
All that stuff, right?
So you'll see this in the inner city is going on today by, you know, rumbunxious characters.
So Simon Magus was like a, let's say, imagine the guy who was Amazon, the Bozo, Jeff Bozo
or the Facebook guy, Zuck the Borg taking on a five percenter attitude and calling themselves
God.
They would get at least a million followers as such, wouldn't they?
There's actually news.
If you understand, there's other people of one other Douglas Dietrich I'll mention
his name, there was a clipping.
I did find it actually on the internet.
It's no longer there.
George Bush Sr. when he was president of the U.S. he was a moonie, Reverend Sung Young Moon.
And there's a photo of him while he was president laying down on stage on his stomach with his
wife worshipping Sung Young Moon as the son of God.
It was a bad Xerox copy, but you could see it's him.
And this was back in the 90s when he was president.
Or just before his election or just after the election, but nonetheless, it's not something
that he developed right before or after the election.
It was while he was president worshiped Sung Young Moon as the son of God.
He's the moonie.
Everyone, it's very popular, not everyone, majority older people in Asia were laughing when
you had George Bush as president.
Like, oh, he's a moonie.
You have the moonie as president?
Gosh, you're really down in the, in the drugs.
U.S. has always been, yeah, talk about like low functioning people, the leadership
and shown in the U.S.
That should be your warning.
Always been low functioning individuals.
You know, a guy pushing nickel bags in the parks got more character than any U.S. president
you could ever have or had.
Well, I think certainly after the Trump era, even the average person would have to agree.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter which one it was.
I mean, you have even like a Jimmy Carter, you know, and they asked him in his presidency,
why did you let the Shah of Iran come to the U.S.?
Because David Rockfiller told me to.
You know, I mean, you have so much, you know, it's just absurd.
But anyway, the U.S. is just a dumping ground, you know, from, you know, you go west, you know,
to get away always, right?
So until you go so far west that it becomes east.
So back to the Simon Magas character, nothing to see here.
It's just a typical, Simon Magas is being used like Osama bin Laden or Oswald.
It wasn't just him.
It was his posse, his crew and those that decided he should remember.
The bankers run the world, but they don't own it.
The world, the earth and the humans on it and most things that are socialized, meaning
have formed societies, have owners.
Whoever, who's ever land Iran, you are the property of who owns that land.
Right?
You're, you're, you're, you're not affixed.
You're not immovable, but it doesn't, right?
So you're not a, a, a stump in the ground, but because you're living on a, your property
of whoever owns that land.
And that's been divvied up and put in the form of shareholders, owners and administrators
since the beginning of time.
And we don't know who they are.
This is beyond illuminati and free mason's.
Those are more of the administrators.
I'm the, the, yeah, administrators of the, a, a, quote unquote, official presentation.
I think what's going to be really shocking as we get into the, let's just use the, you
know, in the end, all things will be revealed, right?
You know, there's many ends like the end of society really started a hundred years ago or
more, you know, with World War one, believe it or not.
You know, if you take it in a hundred year chunks, right?
Because you could see empire is falling within a hundred years.
You could see that they're downward turn or world societies or the way things are done.
But again, anything we talk about regarding any religion is, is been made, the reason we're
talking about it because it's conventional or commonly known is because it was made permissible
by those that are running the earth.
Right?
And they're also on a certain tier.
There are other beings that are higher than them that make it permissible until, you know,
until it goes to the highest cosmic being that also makes it permissible.
That's where you can lend a lot of credence into the Taoist Buddhist revelatory thoughts
of it's all okay, try to find peace in it instead of changing it or believing this or believing
that, right?
You know, that's where you might find some commendable thought, but it doesn't mean it's
accurate, you know, when you come down to the subject matter.
Indeed.
And so to piggyback on some of the things you mentioned before as we chart the path of
this Simon Magus character, by the third century AD, it appears that the Simonian Tadeemphasized
Simon Magus and his, he had a female prostitute companion called Helen Shundage had replaced
those guys with gods like Zeus or Minerva, which probably morphed into other gods later.
I know that Serapis was a popular Egyptian substitute for Zeus and I think he was the inspiration
for the long-haired Christ depiction that later got.
The Slepius.
Yes.
The Slepius would be very almost a mere copy plagiarizing image of a Slepius.
The God of Health, that's where you see the two fingers, the upward, the palm facing the
viewer with the fingers up, that's a Slepius.
God of well-being, which is a categorized as an Egyptian God, but it was created by Greeks
in Egypt.
Indeed, along with characters like Serapis.
So between some of those guys, you have this syncretism going on where they just absorbed
their image into the Christ's depiction and then that gets absorbed into the Catholic church.
Minerva possibly becomes the Virgin Mary.
We don't know exactly what the church is.
Sure.
I think, just to interject here, I think they settled on it more than absorbed because it
toggled back and forth.
They settled on it, right?
Let's settle on this for now because remember, when you say absorbed, it seems like more
than syncretism, right?
It's subsuming or becoming part of it's every time they settle on something, it's even
more watered down and even less historical value and even less origination.
In other words, it's taken even further away from its point of origin and newly created.
And whenever that's done, by the way, whenever the administrators of any society settle on
something, it's usually scoffed by the current generation.
That it's presented to and when they die off, it's fully accepted and integrated into the
next generation, right?
But based on that, on the fact that you have this syncretic thing going on, whether it's
direct or indirect, it isn't inaccurate to say that Christianity is actually the biggest
exponent of pagan religion ever created by way of syncretism of multiple gods, which
is quite interesting when you think about how adamant it is about calling itself monotheistic,
it's actually the opposite.
That's actually also the most dumb down and inapplicable to human life.
At least with most pagan gods, it had attributes that you could apply to gardening or something,
you know?
Right?
Or be not in juxtaposition of things that you want to avoid and emphasizing things you
want to do like they had.
You'll get more power if you're an idol, worshipper, and a blacksmith finding out which god is
for the blacksmiths, you'll get more out of your blacksmithing trade than if you were
whatever trade nor a Christian.
You see what I mean?
Because at least, you know, you're, it's all predicated in idolatry, but at least you're
closer to some deity or elemental of, right, that actually might exist.
But when you look at what's been accepted and settled on in the Christian meme, it does
not exist at all.
I've had certain several conversations and I see those, the iconography and imagery they
give you in Christianity at best are egregors, you know, a thought form that creates something.
So that is going into another form of, you know, spirituality here.
Like I was on an interview by Freeman Wonson, we brought up Christianity, says that's
the gateway to Satanism.
And I was like, yeah, pretty much, but it actually is a form of Satan as a meaning adversarial
to human, right?
Because if you look at, like you said earlier, the images that are being shown, those are
egregors that do not exist and never have existed historically.
But they can come into, they'll manifest because if you have enough people thinking of
the color blue, everything starts to look blue.
It's this effect of the conscious mind, let's say, on society.
So it's even more bizarre than you can imagine.
That's why very often people say, Christian, I said, oh, you're into demonology and they
don't understand it because demonology to them is something, you know, that they only attribute
to that term is from Hollywood, for example.
Right.
And so just ask some context for the audience about this syncretism point.
I mentioned that Simon was also a Samaritan and this was a curious group of people in northern
Israel who in the Old Testament had gone over to the pagan religion of Jeroboam where they
were worshiping two golden calves instead of the God of Israel.
So they're basically an apostate group who when the Assyrians came along, as you mentioned,
they were deported and replaced with populations from Babylon and other Mesopotamian cities.
But then those new people didn't know how to honor the God of the land and lions attack
them.
And so they asked for a priest to be sent back to show them how to act properly.
But then that priest wasn't even from the tribe of Levi.
So he was one of these apostate priests who didn't follow the original religion.
And so the new Samaritan population kind of ends up with their Babylonian gods mixed with
fake Israelite religion using the name of the Israelite God, but not knowing who he is.
Sure, but let me stop you there for a moment.
Let's interject some substance here.
The God of the Bible, Yahweh, would find observing and adhering to His laws on a higher
level than directly worshiping Him as your God.
In other words, paraphrasing here even in the first chapter of Isaiah, he says, "Well,
I'm tired of your Sabbaths and your new moons and all this stuff, right?"
He prefers that the people walk their talk and talk their walk instead of just talk or
worship.
Right?
He's that kind of a God.
Correct.
And of course, the Samaritan didn't know any of that stuff.
Right.
Well, they knew enough of it that they could know more if they so were directed to, but that
was not their lot in this world.
Right.
And so Simon Meg is coming out of that kind of culture that just mixes all different kinds
of things.
And I think it makes him an interesting candidate to start this universal Catholic church religion
that was actually also just mass syncretism of Babylonian Greek is relied eastern stuff
into one system.
Very much like the IMF is for the monetary system.
International Monetary Fund.
It's the International Religious Fund.
It's a centralized world system.
And here's I'll make a comment that might be shocking to people, but people are not low
functioning.
They'll see it immediately.
In this current day that we're making this recording, any religion on the planet is
only there by permission and approval by the Vatican.
Otherwise, they'll be wiped out.
They do have that kind of power.
Look at the ultimatum given to the Ottoman Empire.
I'm not going to cite specific because I don't recall the specifics, but I'm paraphrasing.
World War I was basically to just ban the Ottoman Empire amongst other things with the Germans.
And they were given an ultimatum.
You're going to get on our calendrical system.
You're going to use Roman script and all your families are going to take on surnames.
Or we will just wipe you out.
I guess what they did.
They took on the calendrical system, Roman script, and they now have surnames.
Very simple.
You think the communist Chinese are destroying Tibetans in the Outback because they're communist?
You think the communist CCP Chinese are just some autonomous communist, whatever?
They were set up by the Americans.
That is very interesting.
I hadn't really put that together before that some of these despotic regimes are just extensions
of certain religious entities that want them to do their bidding.
Yeah, there is no place to go.
There is nothing to do.
What does that mean?
Literally, there is nothing to do and no place to go within what the world offers.
But you are still here is interesting thing now.
There are some just quote unquote despotic regimes.
Or a despot means bishop, by the way, in Greek.
So what does that mean?
So it's kind of like Machiaq and Nakash have the same numerological value.
Right?
It's either good or bad, but they're almost equal.
So what you'll find is in most cases, if you profess even speak on something contrary to
whatever everyone has accepted, you're not put to death.
We're imprisoned for it.
Like for example, lore has it that if you say something about the premiere in North Korea,
you could be thrown into a labor camp, right?
Today.
I know for sure this has been confirmed by several people if you publicly speak out against
the Pope in Europe.
It's a 5,000 euro fine in most countries still.
So when I say there is nothing to do, nothing to say, nothing, it's, you know, it's pretty obvious
what's going on.
Interesting.
So next, I want to look a bit at what you mentioned earlier, this conflation that's
taken place between Simon and Megas and Peter the Apostle because the Catholic teaching says
that Peter went to Rome at the same time, is Simon Megas, they had some kind of battle
during the reign of Emperor Claudius and then Peter wins this battle, defeats Simon
Megas and becomes the Pope until Nero persecutes him in 68, 80 or so and crucifies him upside
down on the Vatican Hill.
Sure, just like the Arab hijackers that flew the Arab Plains into the World Trade Center
happen to be on Egyptian television saying we're here, there's two sides to it.
Most people believe that they did fly airplanes into the buildings, other people don't believe
it at all because they're alive on Egyptian television and then the other most people don't
carry their way.
So for the Catholic whatever academy to put out a nonsensical reasoning, who cares?
And most people, those that care know that there's nothing you can do about it or should
you care about those that do care about it or you shouldn't even care about those who don't
care about it.
Do you see what I mean?
No, I see what you mean, interestingly enough.
In other words, the BS has been so accepted by people, then so what if it's BS, then you
have to stop looking at the BS and look at the character of the people that accept it
and those that know it's BS but still go along with it.
How can you create a better society with people like that you can't?
Right?
Yeah, I mean, none of the early, it's interesting that another early prominent right Christian
writer has had anything to say about that.
Just to give a few.
Even today.
I am completely, when I, there's, I'm not going to mention names like Heiser, I'm not
going to mention names like this plenty of them, Martin Ernest Martin, all those other
guys, they're in it because they knew if they, if they had any truth and they actually put
it out, they would be sleeping on a park bench and pension eating out of a garbage can, right?
They're there for the money.
For example, I know people that were part of the, who is that little short guy, Herbert Armstrong
and Martin and those other guys broke away from our brown show.
They left in the, when they were sort of exiled and I spoke about proper time keeping this
and I'm like, oh, we can't do that because no one will buy our books.
Should I say anymore?
And that Heiser, I mean, I mean, to, you know, Michael Heiser, same, the same ilk, you know,
just because he went to the Academy.
Okay, the, I think I explained, you have no education, you have no schools, those are
academies, they're academics, are universities, duh, right?
If you're not an auto-du-dacked, you're, you're, you're a dumbass.
So the opposite of the brave is not the coward, it's the conformist, right?
So anyway, the, the simple meme that the earth is going to be cleaned up in human society
is going to be destroyed as a true one.
The ones that are going to be doing all this destruction are the good guys.
They're not going to destroy it to end it, but they're going to destroy it as a mop-up
crew would clean up a place, really deep cleaning.
So there's really nothing to do, say or, or whatever, act on, unless it's your own personal
within your own being and your family if you have such a thing, a real family.
Until that time comes.
Which paraphrasing and by coincidence, there's something about that time that is emphasized
in all of scripture, especially what they call the New Testament, which is not scripture
in my regard, because if you take it as scripture, you would take graduate level studies as core
education, right?
If you take a four-year-old and throw them into graduate studies, whether he's there for
one hour or one year, you ask him, do you have any questions?
And immediately he says, yes, I do.
And what's the question?
Do you have any candy?
You get it?
Core education is the fundamentals, the three hours, writing, reading, arithmetic, you know?
So if you know that, you will see the New Testament as being continuation of scripture,
but not scripture on its own.
That's your first sign that you're being hoodwinked.
When you're going to hoodwink someone, you present a problem that brings fear and uncertainty,
and then immediately you present a solution that brings relief.
Never how the problem came about and how the solution will bring relief.
Never.
Just take this is where you are now.
Take this then, right?
That's Christianity.
That's political system.
That's the medical system, you see?
How it works?
Have people running just accept him?
You'll be fine.
Who's him?
Which one?
The thing is, it's so bizarre and so ridiculous.
It's like a running joke and guess who's the punch line is you?
You know, falling for it.
There is no punch line.
The punch line is when you actually fall, just listening to the joke is just as bad as
a bad punch line.
So.
It ties in with low functioning species, a species that was set up to be low functioning.
And then who's fault is that?
I don't think there's any fault, but there's a level of wisdom that cannot be seen at this
point.
I'm why and why it is such a way.
So also just, one thing we have in added in the academic world or historians which are
professed to be atheists, do call this the Christian era.
So it is secular.
This is known as the Christian era.
You could find it in multiple graphs and multiple charts and multiple writings on what
the past two millennia have been.
Before we go on from Simon Magus character, I just want to give a few short proofs that
Peter indeed never went to Rome.
I know you mentioned it, but just to be a bit more thorough for the audience, Justin
Martyr had written about Simon Magus in the second century saying that he was a Samaritan
magician who came to Rome during the time of Claudius Caesar about 45 AD.
And he made such an impression with his magical powers that they decided to honor him as a
god and put up a statue to him saying the holy god Simon.
So that's actually a matter of historical record.
And at that time it was illegal to put up a statue of any man as a god unless you had the
permission of the emperor and the senate so that we know that Simon was able to get into
the government in that way.
Well, he was made it was made permissible.
The senate in Rome and the emperor is in Rome were just about as powerful as any president
of our minister is today.
Nothing has changed.
They're just a show for the people because if they don't have them focusing on a centralized
power like that, that might become individual city states that might actually protect their
environment and have a harmonious community.
And then because the people are have so much fortitude because of some strong values they
might be able to take over other city states.
You see what I mean?
You wipe out the competition.
Think of a time machine.
You go and kill them before they're when they're born so you don't have to deal with them
as an adult.
So you don't leave people like the pastoral policy for Germany who's in Morgenthau or
whoever wrote it in the 20s that Germany should be reduced to a pasture because the German
people are prone to advancement and have mental and moral fortitude to get rid of them.
This has been around since the time you think Julius Caesar was just killed because of
disgruntled senators.
The orders came down from above.
None of this stuff is real.
I mean, it was what people think is real.
There is a power base that it's been running this planet since the beginning of what you
call civilization.
Who are they?
We don't know.
We have some hints of who they are.
And you have two species of humans, which I've shown and one of them would most like act
as a subspecies mentally low, low functioning.
The other is very few in number and much higher functioning.
Are they the ones that are running it?
No, I don't think well, they might be part of the administrator, but not we don't see
them either.
The reason why this has been gotten away with us all along is because you have such a short
lifespan.
If you live to three, four, five, even eight hundred years old, you'd see it and be able to do something
about it.
It takes 30 to 50 years to master something, anything.
In this temporal thing that we exist, you know, the way everything works in nature, you
need to do it.
So that's not going to happen, right?
Because you're dead by then, 70, 80, 90.
And if you matured by 30 or 40, because people now are at the point where they're 80 and they're
not mature, you don't believe it.
Go out and talk to some relatives or friends or whatever, about mature subject matter.
They stopped growing at 12 or 13.
Why should they grow anymore?
You don't live long enough to do anything or think about anything properly.
So here's the key that I'm going to always throw these things in.
Yes, I do give advice.
Not until you see the human living more than three to four hundred years, will you have
any advancement or improvement in your culture?
Indeed.
There are some writings about that in ancient scripts as well.
Just to wrap up this last bit about Simon Magus thing, it also says in Acts 12, three that
Peter was in prison in Jerusalem around the 45 AD mark when he was supposedly supposed
to have made this church in Rome.
And then in 49 AD, he was still in Jerusalem attending the council there in 51 AD.
He was in Syria arguing with Paul about whether or not to eat with the Gentiles in 66 AD.
He was in Babylon, which is in the east.
So there's really no time or possibility for Simon Peter to go and set up a church in Rome.
But you have to plot out the timeline by actually reading the New Testament.
Sure.
Just like most people saw Oswald getting a coke from the coke machine when the president
was shot.
And the hijackers being on Egyptian television.
I mean, it's pretty much in your face, right?
Well, I mean, you have to put it in front of your face because no one else is because the
people that used to do that are either no longer here or realize that doesn't do anything.
It has to be on par with a low functioning human.
And they'll accept it.
And a low functioning human will not discern and care to discern, right?
Indeed, you should, we should all strive not to be low functioning humans, but for some
people with a challenge, if you are a low functioning human, that's it.
That's all your thing is you can get out of it.
But again, you don't have enough time and it's a little late.
It's kind of like if you're a low functioning human, it's like you showed up for the exam
and you've never done any homework.
You can cheat maybe, a cheat sheet, and you can guess.
You see what I mean?
It's not completely sealed.
You're not condemned if you're low functioning because there's of course there's miracles, right?
But anyway, yeah, no, I follow you.
In terms of Christian history, there's one last thing I want to look at and then we'll
really move on.
Which is the origin of the word Christian itself, because I remember an explanation that you
gave a few years back about the word Christian.
And so I wanted to quote from that and then maybe you can develop it further.
So begin quote, it's hard to explain how bad the word Christian is because it goes beyond
any pejorative we can conceive of today.
People today insist that certain slurs aim that particular groups are derogatory, but
what they gloss over is that those groups have been using those terms colloquially for
a long time, whether it's homosexuals using the word Fag or African Americans who refer
to each other with the N word, but Christian, which was created by the Jewish leadership,
was so derogatory that it was never used with that kind of just or lightheartedness.
There is no English term today that shows the magnitude of what that word meant.
In the first century AD, Christian, which meant something like Messiah Knight or Zealot,
was referring to those who were politically dangerous and wanted to start trouble that
would get everyone killed by the Roman government, because if the Romans even suspected an uprising,
they didn't waste time to root out the rebellion.
They just threatened to kill off 10% of the population until the problem was solved or everyone
was dead.
So there was this movement going on after the death of the Messiah that the Pharisees frowned
upon because they were pushing the oral law, not the Torah, but those people took an
interest in the Torah and were encouraging people to keep it the way that Moses had given
it.
And the people who discovered what the Christ was really about and what the events meant became
enemies of the authorities and they were labeled as Christians or zealots, but they never
called themselves that because it was always considered an insult.
And that group went underground by the second century AD and what took a hold after that was
the equivalent of 9/11 conspiracy theory run by the Nostics and the Pharisees, which is
today's Christianity that makes no sense.
End quote.
That's quite a lot, but whatever you want to add to it, you know, feel good.
Well, that sounds really good.
I mean, that's a miniature essay right there.
What else is there more to say?
Well, I just think it's, you know, sometimes you find it referenced in some academic paper,
occasionally somebody will do good grunt work and you'll see evidence of things that are
true that somebody dug up.
The notion of Christian being an insult, I've found it so hard to find anything pointing
to that.
And if you talk to people that speak ancient Greek, they find it hard to really pull that
out of the manuscripts that it's being used in a derogatory way that it's not really used
as a complement or religious term.
It's more like a madman.
Well, sure.
Well, yeah, the zealot was also, you know, ultimately if you were derailed, the zealots
were very selfish or wanted to maintain or further the cause of their group and
whatever else was expendable.
And that was viewed from a high administrative point of view and cosmic point of view as being
a big no-no.
Right.
So the zealot is even under-understated because you have to see in the light of the culture
and the ideology.
And from the Judean culture to be a zealot in such a way or a Messiah night and all that
was not only a secular problem but a cosmic problem, right?
So it was a pretty bad condition.
And you won't, again, regarding not finding anything, it only takes a generation or two
to wipe out the meaning of something or its use.
It's known use or the implications of its use.
I put on a, what I was talking about Felix the cat, I went on YouTube, 1959.
Here's Felix the cat.
He's gay and he's what, you know, means he's happy, right?
But so between 1959 and let's say even before 2000 they wouldn't say that now, right?
But because it means something completely different.
You see how only 50 years is enough to wipe out the way the word is used in its connotation.
Yeah, it's a challenge.
I mean, I know that probably in some library somewhere, there's something but online anyway,
it's very difficult to find that.
Sure.
Like for example, he was decided less than 200 years ago to wipe out anything, even scratching
off hieroglyphs on Egyptian monuments about the underground people, the societies that lived
underground and always were there, non-human and sort of humanoid.
You won't find anything about it and there was tons of stuff written about it and it sort
of implied in mythological form, fiction and all that brought back into modern day.
But before 200 years ago, it was commonly known that there were races of other beings, intelligent
beings that lived underground, some predatory, some not and there's nothing.
Even to the point where you'll see there is a lot of hieroglyphs that have been carved
out.
So, I mean, I'm just throwing this in as a left field, you know, out of the blue tangential
point.
No, but I see the connection as far as knowledge going underground or just being removed.
Cool.
So let's move on to another issue within this discussion, which is that of the leadership.
I mean, I think you've mentioned a few times on past episodes, what the word church means,
but I think the topic is okay.
Yes.
What do you have on it?
Well, the scholars who devised the modern dictionaries will state that English word church
derives from Greek curious oil costs, meaning the Lord's house, but, you know, that naming
convention didn't really become popular until the fourth century, 80 from what I see, and
it would have been prohibited, really, to call anything other than the temple, the tabernacle
Lord's house.
So really, it couldn't have developed that way.
Do you know how it slipped into the usage that we see today?
It's not a matter of slipping.
It's a matter of settling again.
It's not something new.
Let's just look at the comparisons of what has survived.
The circus is the three-ring circus.
In ancient times, the circus maximus, especially in Roman other places, the theaters were a
spiritual thing.
So just like people go to church on Sunday morning on certain calendrical days, they had
they went to the circus.
And there was a performance, a ritual, and a show.
So today, the circus is the day the go-and-go everyone goes on a certain day, they wear their
best.
And there's a performance.
And the show is what versus and what kind of moral message they're going to give you,
right?
So instead of an elephant dribbling a ball, it's, they'll take five words out of something,
usually the New Testament, and try to apply it to why you should pay taxes.
When there's no money to pay for anything anyway.
It's credit, right?
So it's so bizarre and so ridiculous that you can't say directly it is the circus because
we have a circus today, right?
So they've used a lot of stuff out of the Greek like Ecclesia in Spanish.
It's Ecclesia, right, not Cirque or church or Chideos is the Lord.
That was well implanted in Roman culture.
You can even read up until the second or third century, you were fined by Roman authorities
if you didn't sacrifice a lamb to Hercules, depending on what law for your region was, right?
On a certain day.
So has that gone away?
No, yes, it has directly, but has the imposing tradition stayed?
Yeah.
There's an imposition.
It would be really hard to compare a Gothic cathedral to a circus as we know it today,
but they're the same thing, but they're not really.
Gothic cathedral is built geometically and for other purposes.
Gothic for example, it's not for Christianity, it's for just what people do, building monuments.
There was an architect, I remember hearing about this in the 80s, there are archaeological,
conservative architects.
Conservationist is something, you know, someone that goes back and tries to fix old stuff
that's been damaged.
A lot of bombs blew up a lot of places in Europe in the 40s and when the conservation is
showed up, they were either kept away or the ones that did get through some of the larger
churches, they found under the altar was an entirely different, another altar.
It was completely secret none of the congregation had known about it, most of the clergy had
not known about it.
So what were they doing with that other altar down below?
You see, so that's what I mean about it being a circus.
It's more like humans always build in significant structures for whatever reason.
It's usually a cult practice to empower, you know, those that understand that the world
is run by spells and magic, right?
And that spells and magic is by working with spiritual world in cohort fashion, right?
And that by the way has been cut off by the Christians, but the Christians, when they find
that it's so empty, then go over to these other things, right?
But it still kept very secret as being legitimate.
So I would say your church, yes, etymologically, yes, it's indistinguishable from the circus
and as used as a word church, etymologically.
It's kind of hard to get away from that.
You know, the whole show, but the, when we talk about the edifice and you look at the range
from, you know, the local shack that has a cross on it to a cathedral, there's a big variation
there.
Yeah, just a buttress, your point, I wanted to quote from the original 1870 edition of
the dictionary of phrase and fable because in the subsequent versions, they actually changed
the entry under church, but in the original version it says, the etymology of this word is generally
assumed to be from the Greek, curious, or costs, but this is most improbable as the word
existed in all Celtic dialects long before the introduction of Greek.
No doubt the word means a circle, the places of worship among the German and Celtic nations
were always circular, compare Anglo-Saxon, circuit, a small church with circle, a circle,
end quote.
So it's interesting how in this subsequent version they change it.
Sure, sure, but there's a language variation in Latin, it's Ecclesia, like the Greek, but
remember, I'm the only Greek I know and what I have to say about the Greeks is just like
anything that's being used to prop up the underpinning of any ideology.
Other than, you know, Greece was a bunch of sheep herders and all of growers with some
philosophers thrown in under a city-state structure since the gold, you know, not the golden age,
but ancient times.
And it was grabbed and shown to be, also that philosophical and scientific was all by
Eastern influence.
And also very, and you know, there are many words in Hindi or in India, modern to India
that are similar to Greek, but cultures in countries in between do not share, right?
People don't know that.
Whether, I think it was before Alexander the Great, there was an interest in East India.
So why was the Greeks being used to prop up, you know, as the pillar of Western society?
Because you need to prop up something for people to believe in and defend an idea, a part
of their ideology.
But as mostly the Eastern world that had shown what the Greeks had done, and people say
what's democracy, what's democracy is so good, how is it working out for you?
And people don't understand that the city-state, the status of the people with 99 or 97% were
slave.
So it's just, you know, hollow terms that cannot be backed up, they become real, they're
reified, they're made to be real in people's minds based on whatever culture they live
in.
So one of the last things we'll be talking about is the actual biblical text or what they
call the Bible itself and how that has shaped some Christian developments.
So yes, let me just interject.
The 1611 which really took on by the 19th century is what the modern Christianity is based
on.
Yes.
You know, King James, which did use, by the way, the proper names and there was no J early
on it was an I with a little, a, uh, tilde or a little comma at the bottom.
So they just connected that little comma with the I made the letter J. So anyway, you're
on the W which is two use but together get it W or in other languages called duble v
a double v. So anyway.
So, in ancient times you had the Aramaic targums and the Greek sceptuogen into some of
the first known versions of the Old Testament that spun out, um, then in the first four
centuries you had a multitude of versions from the Latin Volgate. There was a Gothic version,
some Siric ones. You get to the Middle Ages, you have multiple codexes. I think the most
notable one is the Wycliffe Bible published in the 14th century, followed by the Erasmus
publishing, um, his Greek New Testament in the 16th century, Martin Luther does it in
German soon afterwards and eventually you get the KJV in 1611. Um, but in spite of all
those developments, you know, some would say that it's progress. I know you wouldn't,
but it's a matter of who was brought in as the main publisher. Like you said, these other
versions were around before King James, but the main publisher, which King James was not
a king by the way, he was a Scottish region when the, the, the crown was in question, uh,
which makes it even more, uh, funny. Uh, and he also wrote about a lot of other books under
pseudonames that were pretty, pretty nasty. Um, but he didn't do anything. It was a public
works project so he can drive a wedge between the people of England and the monarchy, right?
Because the people had deified the monarchy in some regard. So, uh, it's kind of like what's
going on in the US or in Europe right now by bringing in immigrants that have radically
different culture to dilute their own culture, right? Uh, what I would suggest is, um, this
was an administrative move of power move to emphasize that, uh, because you could see
the versions that came before 1611 were pretty much identical to it, right? Uh, mostly they,
I think they might have even some of the other ones you mentioned had some up what's considered
apocryphal works included. And, uh, also the division of the books, uh, it was important
that they divided to get 66 because six and six is, they liked that number. That's how
you get like, first and second this and first, they kept doing that. And then you left
over with one book had to be broken into three parts to get the 66. So, um, you could see
it's a very subtle management whenever the, whenever you put demonology onto a society,
you have to make it where it doesn't seem so obvious that it seems, uh, plain and simple
and it could go either way, right? Uh, it's kind of like, well, these people can, uh, self
mutilate and do this because it's human rights, right? Or whatever. So you have, um, uh, a
very simple, almost kindergarten level, uh, demonology being drawn in front of you and
it's, and then you absorb it as, uh, a, uh, what do you call it? Conventional or mainstream
religion. And it's always something where children can accept it. In other words, it will not
offend the children directly is what the other thing you're going to, uh, what we'll see, um,
what they also use the negative aspect of forming a society and a demonological, uh, substrate
is that you want to use children as reasoning. Do it for the children, right? It helps the
children. You want to learn this as a child, so on and so forth. That's another thing
that you will see there. Well, since we're on the topic of the KJV, we'll go back a bit
to some older stuff after that, but the KJV is obviously a pivotal piece of literature that's
shaped world history. And as, at the very least, you can say it's provided some kind of bridge
for the layman to access something about their scriptures, whether it's true or not, but
these misgivings that you express and you've pointed out some of the translation issues
before, you don't really give it much more credit beyond, say, the literary contribution
but what are some of the more blatant misgivings that you have with the, it's, it's a political
tool, just like anything else. The misgiving of it is the names. It's blatant. It's a blatant,
it's a blatant, uh, I tell people, in short, have you ever heard of the satanic Bible and
they're like, yeah, I heard it. That's, that's what you got. But the issues that it puts
forth in obscuring the true meaning of the text, you feel like that's mostly on the name
aside. Uh, the name, yeah, and the categorically, in other words, the imposition of the
way the books are presented, yeah. Uh, and mostly on the name because once you remove the
identifiers, it could be anyone. What is in a name would be the question. Here, they're
giving you an example on, on the ridiculousness of the, the, the Christianity, I wasn't going
to say it, but here it is. Okay, so the sixth book of the Bible is the book of Joshua, which
is Joshua, which also happens to be the Messiah's name. So why don't they call him Joshua?
It's already plain and simple. The book of Joshua, it's the same name. And you have, uh, these
other idiots, they try to defend the J.E.S. U.S. in Cantation. Have you ever heard of, uh,
Heiser or this guy or the other guy say, well, the white, why aren't we using Joshua instead
of, why are they defending, oh, the J.E.S. U.S. That's just the Greek, you see that I'm
assuming? The Pissant, whatever people that are on the, on YouTube or academically, very
simple. It could destroy any of those characters just by saying, what's the sixth book of the
Bible? What's the Messiah's name? Done. Why do you have to use J.E.S. U.S. because in magic,
misdirection, both in ledger domain and press of digitation, which is stage magic, and
in occult in Cantation, misdirection is important. You could destroy the entire Christian meme and
all the idiots that have written books and scholars were saying, what's the Christ's name
in Hebrew? What's the sixth book of the Bible? Done. Get out of my face. Get out of here.
You and your billion trash eaters. But if you got a billion trash eaters, that's a lot of
trash to feed. You're never going to run out of sources of what's called income, are you?
No, I mean, once you had mentioned that something along the lines that the printing houses
retained the mistakes and the errors for purposes of commerce, something like that?
Oh, no, I gave a metaphor. Like, let's say you and I wrote a book and we sent it to be
printed and the printer comes back and says, you have a typo, you know, a typographical error
or an error, what do you want me to do? Oh, go ahead and print it, of course. No, correct it.
But you've got thousands and thousands and thousands and thousands of critical errors
in the King James. Repeat it over and over. It says, "Clear agenda." It's the bell curve
average. If everyone thinks it's good, it must be good. If these people believe, I always
say, this is what people believe. It doesn't matter. I give the, you know, you start track,
you're cruising along the galaxy and you're given an area book before you're given down,
you know, it's a military term before you're sent into a foreign place. The area book tells
you the customs of the people and the laws because you don't want to go down there and
defend them, right? And on this planet, the biggest industry is Kevlar underwear. The reason
why is because it's in their custom to place a thumbtack on the seat before they sit. So
hence, the biggest industry being Kevlar underwear because it tends to deflect the
sharp penetration. So if you went there and said, "Just stop putting thumbtacks on the seats
and you don't need the Kevlar underwear anymore," which is very expensive, by the way. The
people who make the Kevlar underwear will come after you because they're only into it for
the money and they're going to make you look bad to the people. They'll never, even though
it's blatantly obvious, stop putting the thumbtacks on the chairs. The people will not see
it. Do you see the point? You have these low functioning humans and they're told they have
to work, which actually scripture says you do because it says you're low functioning,
basically just a gardener. And if you don't plant and whatever do husbandry you're going
to starve, this comes from up high. So you can escape that. Well, other people can, some
people can, but and many do with various social things that have been put in place. So you
do whatever low functioning occupation or vocation you do, but because you're human you know
about, you want to know about other things like maybe you've heard of religion in the gods.
So you don't have time because you have your low functioning vocation, whatever, you know,
even a CEO of a company or working on a production floor or a farmer. It's low functioning
in the big scheme of things. You want to know about a subject. So instead of delving
into it, that's why I tell people don't do your own research. You hear this a lot, right?
Because the whole system is set up this joke system to accommodate those. I'm going to
do my own research. And when you look at your research, it slowly steers you back to the
conventional garbage, right? So you need to not do your own research and find those who
have been able to sort it out, but anyway. So you want to learn about astrophysics. You
go look at the conventional garbage they put out on that, right? And you believe it because
you've got other things to do. You got to drive a bus, get up and drive a bus in the morning
or drill someone's teeth or operate on someone's brain or make some shoes or something, something.
So you want to learn about religion? Well, we've got that covered. We've got you covered,
man. You want to learn about how electricity, we've got you covered. It's total bullshit,
of course, right? Do you see how it works? Because people have to work and telling someone you
have to do your own research on it does not help them, right? You have to find out those
who have sort, it's not a research project to learn about religion or the gods or engineering
of or astrophysics or how the human body is. You've got to find someone who has sorted
it all out who could pick out the signal through the noise. Same thing in agriculture, how
often do you just have a field and you go out pick it up and bring it to market? This sorting
that has to be done, right? So I'd ever tell people go do your own research. I might
have in the past somewhat, but I'm like, that's not going to help you. Just leave it alone.
You need to find a good sorting mechanism or someone who's good at sorting stuff out rationally
without agenda. So the garbage that you see put out by the academicians, the academy, universities,
which is garbage is the first thing you're going to run into when you say do my own research,
right? So there's nothing to do, right? There's so much to do that there's nothing to do.
But once you have a key of poignant way to really dive in and with a high efficiency in
the sorting out the bullshit, you can get to the matter of anything. And when you are savvy
at doing that, you'll see that the real truth about things is actually broadcast more clearly
than you ever thought it would be. Well, I mean, I understand what you're saying. On the
point of the scriptures, though, or the Bible, to be fair and well, fair or not, I'm just playing
tables advocate a little bit. We do have to acknowledge that efforts have been made in the last
few decades to address the translation problems of the English Bible, at least when it comes
to the Old Testament because it's been long known in the Jewish culture.
Okay, just let me just interject again the sorting sorting out, not research, but sorting,
the machine, the tool to sort it out. For example, let's go back. If you had anything
written, that means you were wealthy, right? And then when printing became industrialized,
the not so wealthy got it. When you had sorting machines like computers years ago, you were
really wealthy or specialized. Now anyone has it. You see my point?
So you go right to the source. You go right to interlinear, let the computer source it out
for you. In other words, you use the tool. For example, it's embarrassing for the human
race to have any of these religions still functioning when they have a computer that could actually
simply break down and sort what the text says that they allegedly subscribe to actually
says. It's an embarrassment. Are people getting smarter, smarter or dumber with the inter, you
know, with the technological advancements and information gathering and sorting, or getting
dumber? So that means that it's not a secular, it's not a material problem, it's a spiritual
problem. Now I would say the point that you're trying to make that I'm guessing at has not
been fully resolved until the advent of sorting machines, computers, because now you can
access an interlinear in real time anywhere and avoid the garbage. But do people do that?
No. I mean as a whole, a million Christians maybe two will do it. You know, there's not
but if, and then, but here's you can't call them Christians because once they start researching
and sorting, there's no way you would call yourself a Christian. You would have to be mentally
deranged or wanting to go, you know, you have, you have a financial need that you can, all
these people, these academics, whatever leaders in that Christian movement in the past
to 100 years have been there for the money. All of them, there's no exception or to make
a living front to, right? They come out and say that. This is how I, you know, this is
what I do. No, no, I've seen that. And no, I'm not going to speak for the group as a whole
or anything, but as far as just certain works, whether it's the Koran Jerusalem Bible, the
Concordant Version by Adolf Ernest Knock, or, you know, the scripture is 1999. We've seen
these efforts being made by in certain institutions that are not well known or certain people.
I think one of the more popular ones of late is the Hebrew Bible by Robert Altar where he
tries to do a more faithful translation. You know, what do you say about groups or people
like that who have applied some kind of methodology to try to compile more faithful versions
or translations? That's the controlled opposition. It's kind of like there's been more than
one politician or a government person in the US that says, you know, when, when there's
an issue brought up, a law issue, they say, well, the Constitution that will not affect our
form of government. What? It's just like the people in the churches, like the Bible will
not, you know, people are in the Bible. That's not going to affect us very much. In other
words, they have nothing to do. They're telling you. They have nothing to do with it. So
whenever there is a, let's say an appearance of interest in, you know, formative works or
references and all that, they create an opposition right away to absorb those people and then
make them go away because the whole thing is rotten to the core because people are rotten
to the core. Forget about the religious aspect. Look at the medical industry. I want to take
up, because I think I could take for this. Have you heard that before? So then I could take
for this, right? They don't know how the body works. People still call me. I went to the
dog. Okay. What's first thing you did? Well, he told me, no, no, first thing he did,
he put a coffin in your arm and flayed and tell you check your, or some kind of blood, what
he thinks is blood pressure. He says, yeah, he did. I see as a quack. He's a quack. He's a
good. He doesn't know anything about the human body. Anyone who does that is an idiot. Well,
Greek, everyone does that. Well, thank you. All the doctors do that. Well, thank you. Actually,
not all of them do, but yeah. Next subject, right? Is what I tell them. In other words,
very easy, the current joke that we're living in, you know, you can die in this joke, of course,
and it doesn't matter if you do it because you're living too short to make your life meaningful.
Life is, you know, the human life span is too short to be meaningful anyway. That's why people
always, I mean, in terms of what's the meaning of life? I want to find more, I want to find
myself, right? I mean, sometimes you hear that, right? So these religions, which in ancient times
were regarded as the main causality, you know, meaning the gods for anything and everything in our
existence has now become part of that joke. Here's the thing. You want to know what real existence is
about. Sorry, Jack, you're not going to live long enough to figure that out until you see humans living
three, four, five, seven, eight hundred years old, you're a joke. You're taking part of a joke. And I
don't see the wisdom in it yet, but hopefully I will later. So in the meantime, as an underfunctioning
low functioning human, that's the audience also, myself and you also, where we're built, it's built
into us to be that way, to strive for better things and understanding and to see what kind of a
mess this is. A mess that's been regarded as being just fine and dandy is something to consider
and know, but not to delve on too much. Here's the thing, a lot of people that hear Greek speak on
any subject have a problem with it, not because there's a problem with it. It's because now that it
doesn't leave them much to do. There's many people that say, well, I've heard you speak on this for a few
hours and I went and did research for and I found everything that you said is true, but it's a
long did it take for you to find that stuff on your own. It took me like six months to a year. So how
long was the sonic event that you heard? It was about two hours. Okay, so I basically took a year's
worth of work and reduced it down to two hours or less and you actually confirmed and validated
everything that's been said and it was very difficult to find most of it. I mean the majority of it is
easy, but what's you know where to look? But without the direction and the hints on how to sift it
out, you're going to get lost. You won't find any of it because of the misdirection. Right? So I found
meaning, here's personal thing, I have found meaning in the life that I'm living here on the ability to
do that. So you got right to the point. So what I suggest to people is find up find as much
Greek speak as you could possibly get your hands on and listen to it. It's some of its hard, a hard
lesson, but once you get used to it, it's going to save you a lot of time. So Christianity thing is
very easy. Their main character, the falsification of the identity through iconography, even the name
can be easily just destroyed by asking them what their name is in Hebrew and what the sixth book of
the Bible is and why don't they use that? There is something very, very fishy going on with these
people in this whole organization, which happens to be ruling the world. In other words, being the
foremost convention in terms of religiosity. It doesn't say much for humans, does it?
No, it's quite damning. Damning. It's very damning. Yeah, everything is. They don't even know how their
body works. They don't know anything at all, but they're still functioning, which is a testament to
the robustness of the human existence itself. Very robust creatures. Think roaches, it's all your
roaches can take a thousand times more radiation than a human. That makes them, you notice how they make
your focus on that? But no one says how robust the humans are. Pretty much everything in their lives
has been false and damning and damaging to them and they're still here. Think about the roaches.
It's the humans that are the most robust creatures. You know, humans have roached spray, do you see
roaches have human spray? No. Well, in conclusion, I'd like us to wrap up by looking at one of the more
noticeable Christian doctrinal fallacies, because the primary symbol around which Christianity revolves
is obviously the cross and it's used everywhere and if you ask people what it represents, they mostly
give vacuous, non-defining answers. Some will say it represents the Christ, others will say it
represents his death, others will say it represents his direction, but they're mostly emotional
professions that people make. Can we unpack just why the notion of the cross has no place in the
biblical narrative and why it's emerged as strongly as it did? You know, when you said we're going to be
doing a talk about Christianity, you know, I find it to be very distasteful personally, even not
not that what we're doing is distasteful. I'm sure someone's going to get something out of it
and it needs to be spoken of in this light and I have been speaking on it much.
Low functioning humans need something very, very simple to associate with, right?
So there you go. It's not biblical. When you are getting that out of the New Testament,
which is where most people get it, first of all it's mis-translated, the word the Greek word
is stavros or in our America, I forgot the name, it means a stake, right? Stavros can mean both ways,
it does mean something crossed in Greek, but it's not a crucifix. It's very simple
that paraphrasing here, Pontius Pilate, retrends them back to Judean authorities, these states,
several places use your law, you have a law and they do. They don't use Roman crucifixion.
A lot of people say to me, "Greek says there that you should not deny that the Jesus was crucified,
I'm like, oh boy, where do you start with that?" Because it's just like five out of the eight words
that you said are totally false anyway. So you believe whatever you want to believe about me.
You see? So we have this really ridiculous stuff and I think I've said it many times,
the Christ was not in short, I'll just reiterate, he was nailed to an almond tree because the way they
forced a proper stoning, which was something to defame the character or also anything that had
to do anything to do with him was a cursed and everything was burned after that. And it was an
almond tree with three men on one almond tree. He was in the front, the Christ bearing all the blows
from the stones and the other two had a femurottery cut in order to die because he don't die with a
broken leg. Sorry, that's the King James ridiculousness, but that whole notion was just anything,
just say anything to cover up what happened. And it took 400 years to really figure that out, right?
Yes, that's right. I believe that the Roman crucifixion tendency didn't really become
what it became known for until 300 or so. Right. And it was just just keep morphing the story into
just tell these because they, you know, it's like, what do you do for a living? If you know
what he won't, when a common person, I've seen this more than once, meets someone of authority and
ask questions for them, the person in authority or the administrative authority, even though they're
just peons, they shove all their questions and say, what do you do for a living? You ever notice that?
I don't know if you've ever experienced that. Like whether it's in an official setting or
unofficial setting, if a common person is asking tough questions to a politician or a priest or
someone, you know, that's considered an authority, they ignore the questions and say, what do you do
for a living? In other words, when they ask you that, it's like, you're just a slave, you're just a stupid
shoemaker, bus driver, doctor, whatever, this is out of your, you know what I mean? That's what they're
saying. So if someone asks you what you do for a living when you pose a hard question, they're basically
telling you, know your place and stay there. So if you're going to keep that as the ideology that your
society runs on, you have to give the people real simple symbols, real simple terms and real simple
beliefs. That's why you have a cross, all that. King James, of course, kind of sealed it and seared
it in people's minds. Yeah, I mean, I've always wondered what one can infer about the cross by looking
at how it's used and what it's attached to rather than just believing the sanctity of it because the
Roman crucifixion was a death sentence for criminals. The Christians themselves could be seen as
walking dead because they're in constant violation of what the creator wants and we know what happens
to those people in the end. They have the second death. And then the crosses seen everywhere in churches,
you know, that could be seen as a sign of death because of the people that are in there. And even in a
statistical sense, cemeteries have more crosses than churches do and that's all for dead people. So
I'm almost wondering if that cross is literally a death sign for something. A morbid it is. I would say,
well, we can infer that it is. It's not defined as such. But yeah, you can say that. I think,
well, the star of David is a druid symbol, right? The Megan Mogan David, they call it
it's a druid symbol. It goes back actually even before that to summon us. Before you summon a demon,
you use that symbol to pretty much clear the area of other other beings so this demon can come in.
That's the star of David. They call it the star of David. So how did they come up with that? What is that
up? People don't really see the star of David as that, right? But just like people don't see that,
right? It's just been, it's what you associate it with in your current culture. It's just got
awful all around. I mean, look, no matter what we've ever talked about, these people running around
this planet don't even know how their body works. They think they're pressurized filter bags. They don't
know how to keep time. They don't know anything about anything. And they're still here functioning. Well,
in other words, more people are being born than are dying usually and they're continuing.
What kind of a thing is that? That's a cosmic anomaly, you know?
Well, it is how things will persist for the next couple of decades at least and we'll see how it goes.
But I think these talks help. I'm still sticking with less than about a decade now.
It doesn't mean that know everyone, I mean, nine out of ten people will not be here and it'll take
40 years to seven years for the dust to settle. I'm still sticking with that. And if you remember any
other Greek speak that I've done around, even a few years ago, I started emphasizing that all these
changes are going to be so fast and so sudden and so accepted that if you know about it, it'll seem
like everyone's going insane and going along with it. Yes, I do remember that.
That's my story and I'm sticking with it. No, that's totally fine. Well, I think that's a good note
on which to end. This is probably one of the longer streams we've done. But we covered a lot of
ground and I think it probably on the next one we'll take a look at Islam or one of the other mainstream
religions. So we'll probably use some of this material as well. Well, you could also preface. Islam
was the purpose of Islam, whether you want to consider Christianity, Judaism, and Islam to be the
quote-unquote the same God as Abraham. If you were to call anything that Abraham was about defended,
it would be Islam that does it the most in the way people use it. Overly, the typical follower
would be closest to that if you call it an quote-unquote Abrahamic religion, even though if you study
Abraham there was no religion that formed from that. As a matter of fact, the Abraham didn't have to
do anything. That was one of the rare times in Scripture where the Creator actually said, you
know, Yahweh said he's going to do everything at that point everywhere else. There was a two-way
street. So I would suggest that, are you Greek? Are you saying that Islam is more pious? Where? No.
Because it's a tool to prevent the expansion of Christianity. And it did do that and it still does it
thankfully. But thankfully nothing matters at this point because the absurdity of its followers also,
the their followers have been overcome by more absurdities than I mean it wouldn't say that
they are overcome by more absurdities but just as much absurdity as any other human, yes.
So. But that would be that would be the main purpose of Islam as a functioning religion is to stop
the progression of Christianity, which is logical. Otherwise you'd have most of the world in complete
lawlessness. Well yeah, we'll dig into that a bit more next next time as far as the historicity of it
and how that played out and perhaps where some of them weren't left as far as influences that
crept in to change that later on. Thank you, Greek, for this time. You're welcome. We've done a good
job putting things forth and thank you to the audience for tuning in. It's been lengthy listen,
but we hope you got something out of it and we'll see you on the next stream.
the