Greetings and welcome to another episode of the God's Peak Podcast hosted by myself and
my associate, the Greek, I'm the Archon and we've progressed on to episode three of this series
after having covered the topics of the ancient world and the spirit and the soul. So today we're
going to build on those topics by expanding on the notion of the gods themselves. I hope you
enjoy that conversation. God's Peak has no political religious or corporate affiliations and is
completely managed by myself. However, the possibility of offering donations is open to
whomever wants to do that on my sister site, greekspeak.com. So again, thanks for tuning in and
let's get this episode started.
Hello, Greek, everything good since the last time we spoke?
Yes, hello, it's seemingly so. Okay, well yeah, it's been a while but I thought we'd look at the
topic of the gods this time. We've sort of talked around that in previous episodes and I
haven't wanted to do all too much on them because I knew this episode was coming and we could just
cover it more deeply on a full episode. So to begin, we've already defined the word God on a
previous podcast. So I don't think we need to return to that sort of stuff, but I thought we'd start
by talking about the general perspective about the gods because there's an infinite amount of
stuff written about them and a lot of it doesn't really lead to clarity on what they are. So
you either have to piece it together through personal study or you just subject yourself to the
misconceptions of Hollywood and fiction. I think there's a CW TV show called Supernatural where a lot of
people have gotten their ideas from in the last 15 years. The X-Files is probably another one.
So my first question is given this quantity of literature and anecdotal stories and
religious traditions, how does a person begin to sort through information about the gods in their
society? Well, you could look at everything and then you might want to stop looking at anything at
all. One could just say when you say the gods in convention would lead one towards the convention
of what mainstream religion is supposed to provide. So that is unavoidable, but I think the approach
where you want to take here maybe is to add clarity or create a clarity that hasn't been provided before,
which is through simplicity and through examination. And then ultimately we could even say through
one's experience with the information because it is going to be just about purely informational
in the end, I should say, because we're not having any overt contact as we know.
Right. What I meant about overt would be like a large flock of birds, a swarm of locusts, whale
sighting, and of course, you know, I'm giving examples here that are animated life forms.
And not just the subjectivity, just like for example, and you can have a room of people
in the each take a hallucinogenic and each have a separate experience. But if they all have the
same experience with the influence of the hallucinogenic one can say that's no longer subjective
and it's a quote unquote objective sighting based on the of course then examination of who
who is making the sighting right they like to say well these are credible people.
There are businessmen, professionals trained observers whatever. So when I said mass sighting I
meant in that in the case of crowds or you know three or more or even better such as crowds witnessing
something that is rationally and logically guided as being of the gods. Not an act of God as called by
you know by many which would be you know through natural phenomenon. So I think again just
referring back to the term who are the gods might be the simplest way to start.
Okay. Yeah, we'll pick apart you know some individual ones later on. But one of the things I've
noticed is how many words exist for descriptions of these supernatural entities. You've got the common
ones like God, Spirit, Ghost, Demon, Angel but then you also have Phantom, Genie, Poltergeist and
the list goes on. Are those designations arbitrary or immaterial to you because of folklore or
pop culture or do they represent actual distinctions of species that are worth being aware of?
For lack of a better term species and it would be the world that they occupy in a non-physical
way overlapping into this world when you look at the whole milieu of being quote unquote paranormal
which eventually hears the thing. We'll eventually the two worlds will meet and mesh and interact
more openly for most people again. Let's say fortunately and unfortunately we're limited by our
perceptions. So we can grant that some people have a more acute or less acute or whatever perception
in that's the ability that they're able to function in and determine you know whether certain
things exist or not. But I don't know if I mentioned it with you on any of these sonic events before
but you hear a lot of this term about denial for example like you know atheists say well you know
they deny the existence of God and all that but in the systems of logic that are held back
academia in order to deny something you have to initially prove that it exists before it can be denied.
So I just wanted to throw that in there because I might bring up that term denial
to certain you know just refusing for cause is not meaning that something doesn't exist.
Right so again let's just maybe jump around a little bit you know when we say the gods we go back
through antiquity and ancient times it seems like a great part of the the rites that we have that are
still existing in the present today have some mention of a God being or the concept of a God being
and from extremely specific qualities and traits and detail to just a general let's say attributes
you know where you know in a God or just gods are mentioned in general terms so if we start looking at all
of that from the past all the way to the current day it hasn't changed much it's pretty much still
held intact the perhaps the frequency of using that term and incorporating it in one's let's say
daily life or in public documents is diminished quite a bit from what has you know been preserved
in quantity you know one could say that they haven't gone away at least as as a figure of speech
but if we look at beyond the figure of speech and we look at the traits and the qualities of who
they were defined to be they're clearly superior in ability to humans and they're clearly not of
this world and when we say not of this world when we say the gods it most of the time people look up
when if you were to ask any of the quote unquote people at any time where are the gods and who are
they they tend to refer to something above and above can mean beyond what we consider to be the
earthly realm then of course there is the anti concept of God meaning most people consider things
as being good and when they're anti good they're usually down so the good is above and the bad is
below so that that is the the simple immatureish you know public how would you say publicly consumed
you know generalities about the gods those those things that I mentioned in brief but
if we look a little further we'll see that edifices monuments and ritual you know
then all those things required a lot of human effort to develop of course most of the monuments to
the main varieties of gods that we hear about ancient times of are laying ruins which is philosophically
something to be considered because anytime something is in ruins we tend to rebuild it if there's
a rock slide on a road or a building burns down or is destroyed for whatever reason or natural or
man-made or war things tend to be rebuilt but most of these temples of and buildings and edifices
that were built towards the gods from ancient times yet remain in ruins which is a question that
people are not asking why are they still in ruins so I think there's a deep psychological and spiritual
value to that this is of the ancient deities the other thing that people can use to associate with
the gods is the part of their life that they consider faith their faith because you know there really
isn't any faith and there really isn't any god there are many fates and there are many gods which is
also stated in many ancient rites the gods of certain people so they tend to be part of a nationalistic
model so one would say you know how they ask what came first to chicken or the egg what came first
the god or the nation and clearly we see when we look at what is written about the gods is that
they are responsible for the forming of nations or being as patriarchs or matriarchs over nations
so they they're loosely saying a political tie-in with them and beyond that political tie-in you
have the various qualities and traits of the gods and attributes so you'll have gods that are
regarded for reasons of health reasons of fertility you know reasons of seasonality reasons of
elementals of the earth you know the god of the ocean god of the sky and they all tend to represent
almost eventually every aspect of what we consider to be reality but yet they're not part of this
reality as we see this reality so the it doesn't mean that they can't be defined so it's something of
the mind at this point or the spirit I think we talked about the what the spirit is and how it is
the mind so when we talk about the gods we can say spiritual beings again it's about the mind and
I think most of the problems that people call problems unsurmountable things that they believe that they
don't have solutions for on one day will have ultimately become problems of the mind which are
problems of the spirit which are tied in again with spirit beings known as gods whether they're
of different order all the way you know from main gods to lesser gods to various impson demons
and angels the society of the gods is in front of us in a spiritual way in our minds regardless
if they're a quote-unquote denied believed in or whatever there is enough information about them
that one can plainly speak about their existence in such a capacity and one could say well since
they're just of the mind in their spirit they don't matter as much as you know carrots and sticks or
hammers bombs food or you know anything else that are more real but I would suggest that anything
that people find as a challenge will always find it as a mental challenge first which is a spiritual
challenge which is a challenge posed by the gods themselves just by the language itself just like
many people that are trained in philosophy and and quote-unquote science and many things in
academia that people look up to when you study what being an educated person an experienced in the
academic arena it would all be of the mind anyway sends you know some of the lab experiments and
things that they do so there is a little bit of a hypocrisy with humanity where they tend to
revere and give social rank and status and entitlement to people that has spent a great time of
their life exercising their mind which is a spiritual thing but then they tend to also in modern day
discount that aspect of the mind known as the society of the gods that tends to exist there at this point
so I wanted to bring up the element of hypocrisy as well because there is an interesting aspect to
that with any subject yeah that that's an interesting point people discount the things that they
inadvertently give credit to in a different aspect of their lives but it all speaks in my mind to
some type of external manipulation that has to take place for that blind spot to exist because you
would think that people's intuition would point them to it and yet it doesn't and so ultimately
you still have to go back to that realm to figure out why it is that we don't acknowledge it
mind control spirit control god control it's all together in one
even a husband or caretaker or a farmer of farm animals knows that
edifices fences structures that he installs and builds to control the animals are mostly
psychological to the animal to direct the animal into what they would what you know where they
would like them to be located or whatever they want the animal to be engaged in you know it's
really hard to fathom that you know the corals and fences you see built around animals on agricultural
settings could really hold a 2000 you know a two ton or a ton and a half animal in when you know
clearly two men can can defeat it so it's just the animal sees it as a block and it's good enough
the concept of electro fences and things like that so I was just saying that says that the only
reason one could have a ranch with buffalo behind a corral is because the buffalo wants to be there
the moment it wants to leave it will just go through anything you put in front of it right so
that's more of the the wilder sense of an animal that supposedly is kept but humans are by the way
we're not animals even though we tend to be warm blooded and things like that we're of a different
ilk and I think in the past and other sonic events have gotten to the difference between humans and
animals and in many writings supposedly the animals do accept direct
you know observe their dictates given to them by the gods where people always question it
seems to be an underlying principle so even though we see them as left for lesser forms as a society
in in terms of the gods they deal with them more directly so until animals can talk and give us
more specifics we're gonna have to rest with pieces of you know literary works that tell us that
or state that but I would say it's about mind control until again we have until by the way people
will get again in the future yes you mean a lot of people say this it's never now so you don't
have to prove it right but it's in the future that they there will be an objectifiable overt
presence of this other society mingling with this society so whether it's a data look forward to
that's up to who's may look forward to it but or not want to look forward to it but again
the problem that I see with humanity at whole is they see everything as opinion they've been trained
to do that and in some will see it as a fact because they quote unquote believe it so and others
will not because they don't believe it so so humanity is still not in a position cognitively
emotionally spiritually you know to objectify information or objectify a just basically information
or communication they tend to act on it on whether it's preferential or not based on personal
preference but mostly I would say through their culture that they're living in yep I get what you're
saying because of the variants and diversity in all the stories and the lore that exists about
the supernatural it does seem like that realm is very haphazard to a lot of people when they do
contemplate it or even when it's portrayed on in literature or or TV you often hear accounts of
you know a paltar guy's haunting a house or a ghost on a deserted bridge or a succubus spirit causing
sleep paralysis or something like this and so people have a feeling that at best the spirit world is
unorganized and free for all or at worst it's mostly malevolent but you've spoken of a tiered
society can you elaborate on that structure or hierarchy and how certain behaviors are based
on where a spirit is in that hierarchy yeah I would suggest so but I would say that there's a
disassociation of physical matter when the gods appear as they are without changing themselves to be
in the in this reality so you might have what's negative results from any god by the way unless
they appear to you as as something benign so the multiple tier can be just that it could be
you know we have the physical realm and then the initial realm of the gods and then if you were
to let's say through a thought experiment or through by studying what is written about the gods go
into their realm or if you are actually brought there you know of course it would be considered
subjective and if you ask that in once you're in that godlike realm do you guys have is there
another godlike realm and do you have a god and they would answer yes and that would be another
realm higher than them and most people on the planet have lost that communication and don't have
that information which is another discussion so there were many tears yes and like you said the
lower ones I call the various lower gods or impson demons and if you just call them gods that would
be fine too because a human king or a human street sweeper is still a human if they're compared
you know comparatively spoken of in another realm so you it would be a matter of rank and ability
and status in that world and when I say status how it's acquired I don't know and it doesn't seem to
be as temporal it doesn't seem their temporal nature is not relevant two hours in terms of they
don't they're not born and they don't live and they don't die in durations that we understand
but yes the just the the asking about the various minor ones that people call paranormal activity
and impson demons yes they are definitely part of that realm as well
all right you spoke of the king in the street sweeper thing and that brings to mind to me this contrast
between the vertical and the horizontal organization of power the vertical we all understand as far
as top down king at the top street sweeper at the bottom but there's also the horizontal dimension of
in and out and I've had a bit of trouble conceptualizing that until recently I guess the closest
thing that I've got to that is like being in a hotel and it's got a hundred floors and all the
important people are obviously going to be higher up and it's harder to get to but once you get to
the floor there's another dimension that you have to traverse which is going down the hallways
and knowing which door to pick and there could be a hundred doors on one floor and some of the doors
are fake and some of the doors look like the wall and you don't know exactly where to go and you
could turn left and turn right and get lost and if you don't have information as to which door to
pick and which path to take to get to the high value person on that floor you're just wasting your time
you still haven't really achieved anything can you speak to notions of how certain
dimensions within the world of the gods are divided in that way well I've been speaking on
it's a lateral kingdom not a vertical kingdom that man is typically associating with hierarchy
and when I say that they yes that's a good analogy with those all when you said pick a door not as a
lock picker to get in but essentially that that whole analogy gave us for security purposes and also
to keep those unwarranted away but another way to say that the those that kingdom or the is more
lateral than vertical they do have a vertical component but it tends to then go to another realm
altogether where the humans are all various status in the same realm right the the lateral
component is actually even simpler to comprehend when people say well they're part of my inner
circle and they're part of my outer circle that's a lateral component so you know you have those
out in the courtyard and then you have the inner courtyard and then you have those that are in the
chamber that's lateral again so they tend to emphasize a lateral kingdom on the higher than the
next realm mostly but I would suggest that when you see military order how that's set up when
you see governmental orders how that set up they have a very similar model in other words
one could say that the military orders and the governmental orders and in certain what do you call
like clubs or institutions private institutions they have orders as well those are not human
inventions they're just ignored and how those inventions came about or those structures came about
I would suggest that they are copies of how the gods arranged themselves as well military
government order and you know other secret the other subgroups of society orders those things were
appeared and not a bin of human invention and eventually we can even state that there's very
little that we ever originated it's we it's borrowed or stolen if you want to refer to permethious
and I would say that the hierarchy is a very simple one to
accept whether it's vertical or lateral but I would suggest the the the concept of the gods that
will be revealed to humanity to guide steer and of course fort in many ways the path that they're
current on is the is the society of the gods that is more of the lateral type where again you're
the inner going in and out you're on the left hand or the right hand right it's not so
and technically what they do mention that particular society of gods does also mention when you
view things as the planet or other things like faculties of nature they become vertical like the
earth will be a footstool that's more of a vertical order but humans and human order will be lateral
in and out inner circle outer circle left hand right hand is what I would suggest people consider
as the basis for me saying it's a lateral kingdom yeah that's some good food for thought
sort of one last point on this aspect of the structure when you look at the relationships that
mankind currently has with the gods a lot of it seems to manifest in either underground ecotic
practices or these unreliable one-off occurrences whether it's you know seeing a UFO or a demonic
possession or things like that and so you have this veil of ignorance separating people from the gods
and only one that veil disappears through that kind of coincidence or freak occurrence
do people go oh well there's something else there and I know that's not necessarily always true
because the governments and the big corporations are active in doing their own summonings and what not
but generally speaking what does it take for the gods to reveal themselves it's kind of what I'm
wondering because we can all draw pentagrams or play with weegee boards and yet for all these you know
wick our voodoo and psychic stuff none of that helps modern man achieve any clear understanding
well let's just look at it from a very simple point of view if you approach a society let's just say
objectively let's say you're traveling through the cosmos or happen to be in another realm just
besides the the current physical realm you're gonna have to accommodate the perceptions of those that
that you want to acknowledge you a simple example would be there's a group of children
and they're very immature children and you want them to acknowledge you other than physically
appearing as a large tall you know human you might accommodate them by saying hey I'm I have
candy I have ice cream I have toys for you you see that will get that will more than have them
perceive your presence but they will then want to engage you because of their own immature desires
let's say or they're of course culturally have been shown that that's what they should want anyway
at a young age they do pick that up so they they would have to the gods at this point would have to
consider the what is in in the culture and the minds and the programming of the human to experience
object on a mass level for them to acknowledge that what they know about the gods is true so
it would be control of nature overt you know the reversal of processes that are
in nature that are always known to go a certain way they might stop them or
they might appear as anthropomorphic beings and ultimately they might satisfy those who
are students of prophecy and fulfill those prophecies just to show that we told you so we're the ones
that told you about this and now we're doing it and ultimately you're going to have to
accommodate the desires of the culture that you interact with which is interesting because there's
something called the n times and all cultures regardless if it's a small native indigenous culture
or the mainstream religions what they're supposed to be using as they're in ancient rites about
the gods they're all and have one thing in common is that man's society will come to a destructive
end meaning the way his society is structured and there will be a small remnant left and
that would be attributed to the gods and no matter how much scientists also predict that the scientists
seemingly cannot do more than one or two natural catastrophic events at a time where the gods are
actually involving many catastrophic natural events so to be more specific what people consider
to be n times prophecy in any culture by the way including quote unquote new age psychics they all
state that there will be a lot of destruction and to show that it's probably from the gods it'll be
cosmic solar lunar weather earthquake asteroid all that and all in unison or within a very small
time frame this is common amongst all cultures for those that have studied this where the scientists
limit it oh it's either this or that or maybe so you'll see quote unquote humanity at large
becoming believers in the gods when the quote unquote n time quote unquote what they say apocalyptic
or Armageddon type things start start to take place okay it's quite a deep subject onto itself
so i think it might be worth looking at on another episode just the notion of the n times themselves
yeah i want to just add one thing to that and in any time in human history if you preach doom and
gloom you'll be popular but if you're a student of prophecy this is not as nothing to do with belief
this is just by understanding what's been memorialized you know if you don't believe it or it's true
whatever it doesn't matter do you know it you know if you watch a uh something that's been
memorialized on film or read it in a book it's not a matter of belief are you engaging what is being
being communicated through the medium right whether it's film audio or or literary it doesn't matter
it's not a matter of belief are you comprehending what is being communicated is what i'm trying to say
and the other thing that i want to be infantic about is that the grouping of of level of catastrophe
one two three four punch let's say an end result will should be enough to show that this was
spoken of before and it was caused by the gods not just one or two events or maybe this or maybe
that so it has to be very definitive and the approach to this is let even though the majority of
humans are ignorant of the specifics of this that when these things do happen they will be enough
information to say look we told you so so here we are because of these things uh and it has nothing to
do with your belief it has to do do you comprehend information when it's presented to you in any
faction whether it's considered factor fiction religious or science that's why it's so easy to
to debunk modern political science because um if you have comprehension you look it's just uh let
me just use the mature term it's gobblinggook and self-contradictory so really people in terms of
their information that the information that they get uh what they call myth mythology and religious
rids and stuff are actually far more stable and less contradictory than what their mainstream
science is putting forward which will eventually lead to proof of the gods as well
so now that we've looked at you know the structure of the society on that side let's talk a bit about
the history of what's been documented about them and how people have related to them i think largely
because of monotheism and specifically Christianity most people's ideas have had to relate to the gods is
about what they call worship a form of piety or reverence that centers on what seems to me to be
self denial and force humility and things like that but in ancient times things seem to be more
contractual where the gods demanded some ritual or sacrifice and if you gave it to them you get
something in return that kind of practice i think became demonized once Christianity took over which is
maybe why access to the gods became so challenging after that point going into the middle ages can you
talk about why the gods have this contractual means of interacting with humans as opposed to just
regular contact showing up yeah the uh i would say that the initial order of pair you know
gods that affect this reality in that way by people believing that they exist and
interacting with them through ritual and offering sacrifices and almost like a a cosmic barter situation
well also like a a cosmic architecture cosmic arc of geography and cosmic events that they attribute
to these gods and i would suggest earlier i said there seems to be a patriot a maternal
maternalistic or patriotistic deity behind most nations how they came it said to come before the
the nation or as symbol of that nation you'll see that you know Britannica and justicia and all these
gods for various zoos for you know for one group and various other systems as the head of society
but i i don't know about the popularity the overpopularity of the the actual hardcore offerings and
barter systems i think the modern society over it on the surface you know the the common
the common oaf is just limited to you know attributing some part of his life or whether it's daily or
weekly or monthly or yearly to homage or acknowledgement of their god that the state puts in
front of them and when you say since christianity came about i think it would be less than 50 percent of
the world but if you do a head count that would profess at least on a government form their christian
but christianity is a function of the state which is a function of another god which we can
probably get into in the future i would suggest that it's accepted by academia as being the state of
history that we're in and i would suggest that it is a very poor quality very low form almost
detracting from the essence of what the gods really are as almost as been a distraction
with the with a label on it called christianity and i know that might make some people let's say
unhappy but once you get into a religion that openly worships fictional things like Santa Claus
Easter Bunny and other traditions and they tell you that it's not true there's a psycho drama there
that one can easily say as contributed or is either a byproduct or contribution to the insanity
of modern man because to say on one side your faith is based on something that you willingly admit
doesn't exist or is fictional we do it for children or whatever makes us happy we have a day off
from work is a serious defect in the mind for sure i don't think that that's lost on everyone i think
some people do see that contradiction but they go the way of the crowd i suppose in terms of the
the matron and patron deity thing it's funny because i recently got into a sort of comical exchange with
someone who's also a Greek descent by the way and i mentioned this notion to him and he's like
no that can't be possible and then i pointed to the there's something in the in Athens
called an evezone which is like the Greek presidential guard is what they call them but really all they do
is that or at least all i've seen them do is that they stand outside a place in Athens called the
tomb of the unknown soldier which is right next to the presidential mansion so it's all kind of
considered to be government property and they just stand guard outside this place kind of like how
the soldiers stand outside Buckingham Palace in the UK and they can't be provoked they can't be
moved to do anything outside of their regimen or their ritual they march around the building in a
very sort of animated ritualistic way at the same time every day repeatedly and it's almost as if
they're afraid to break that pattern because something battle is going to happen and i pointed this out
to the guy i was arguing with like you don't see that this is something that's been mandated from a
place that's higher than just your government that these people have to do that or like what they do
at the border of india in pakistan where they have to have these marching rituals at certain points
otherwise they feel like something bad is going to happen you don't feel like that's ordinance i
always thought it was funny how people just ignore that and take it as like a tourist thing
or a cultural thing and having no divine aspect to it well again it would be the horse following the
card or the card pulling the horse that that is allowable by the way when dealing with the gods to
develop a culture which is hard to say say you know even when someone says i invented this will
where did it come from so ultimately you could grant the reason for that being that way and reason
for sustaining it is because of the divine but from what i've learned and just studying rudimentary
stuff that's been put down for the through the ages about the gods they will accept something that
people develop on their own if there is such a thing and they would not want it changed if they
dedicated it to the gods see so this these ebzon they were skirts and the pom-pom on their feet and
carry rifle and they were like a beret right why is it okay yeah i think that's more esoteric and
complicated to why they're doing that because you can actually say you know there's there's so many
gods in other words there's everything has a deity behind it and if you don't understand that you
can go into ancient paganism so that that's more of an open that won't lead us to any specific
definition of what's going on and what we who the gods are but it is it is a point that what
they're doing in Santa Claus Easter Bunny and many other things like walking around a kaba or something
would go into the category of absurdities but because they've been done by so many for so long it's
considered what's called part of culture and tradition yes that is definitely linked somehow
but i think there's more to perhaps comment on how people can get a better grasp on the gods
especially those that have an analytical scientific mind which by the way don't be
fooled into thinking that if you pick up a science magazine and what's printed or a website or
a scientist they're actually doing real science that's a long gone that's that horse is left the barn
a long time ago all of that is political but again you know for a political means like for example if
you look at what western historians consider it to be radical political organizations or nations in
the past 20th century like fascists or national socialists or Soviets or whatever they they always
paint them in a negative light in many cases and of course you know now it's supposedly the capitalists
so you'll see that they're bad because they were politically bad they couldn't do anything good
right but if you study the culture within the fascists or the national socialists or the Soviets
they actually did a lot of good things it wasn't all bad right as you you'll see people profess you know
they Hitler did the auto-bond and developed many programs of advancement of culture and society
within the confines of the national socialist party so did the Soviets they were able to develop
industry to a certain degree that satisfied the needs of everyone the fascists were able to you know
keep people in a stable nationalistic manner so they didn't feel like they were going to fall
apart it seems in any second you know so all of these dictatorships and what is painted as being very
very negative had some positive production or positive outcome as well so with the political
side paints black and white when I don't see anything in black and white and no one should
like if you're in the intelligence agencies and you go to a special school to learn about war
they never tell you who won a war or lost a war they all they do is go study battles in what the
conclusion of each battle was but no one is ever won or lost a war so one can start seeing things
as a series of events and then the political side comes in and lumps it this series as this and
it's all good or all bad which is something to watch out for that's the same with science when you
hear about scientific research and how much work they have to do if you actually are involved in
scientific research all that work they have to do is how they have to structure they're told
how they have to do all this work to figure out how to structure an experiment to have this given
end result not that they're actually doing real experimentation and then coming up with the
results this is the majority of the science that is made public it's all backwards the result is
already determined and all the researchers have to figure out how to structure a modality or an
experiment to give that result not what you would you're told and of course when they structure it
that way it should be repeatable and you should blindly follow it and not ask anything in between
so this is the political aspect of it but the scientific mind will also be satisfied with the
things that I mentioned earlier you know as the end times being one possibility as an overt
expo x-poze of the existence of the gods which will always be of the mind anyway because
there's spiritual beings until they redirect all their energy with us and to us to start manifesting
new things that we could clearly label you know made by the gods just like you get a product
and says made in China or something or made in Japan or made in the US they would be able to put
their their seal on it and their mark and that's that's a time that's yet has to come okay I want to
get us a little bit back on track because I took us down an unintended path I just thought the
the ebbsone things was was interesting but a lot has been said about something that you mentioned
a bit earlier the relationship between the gods and the stars or the heavens the biblical text
draws some parallels in the book of jogue ancient carvings would often have a god use a star as
their sign like the star of ishtar it's also been a popular idea or motifs that the gods came from
the heavens and were connected with the stars how can we speak of that a bit more rationally
what I found out what let's just say instead of what I know because you know really I don't say
this much but it is true with anyone it has been said the more you want to know and the more you
learn the more you realize you don't know and it's kind of a snowball effect in the unknowing but
would you rather not know and not find out you didn't know or not know and say you're happy with it
but I would say what I found out is by and and what's been communicated memorialized
even in philosophy would be that there's a seriousness that is being disregarded
regarding the gods and it's so serious that it's best being be ignored and we'll deal with it
when the time comes that would be the overarching sentiment that I have regarding anything any
discussion about the gods it's just ultimately so serious that we'll just have to deal with it when
it comes because we're too divided collectively to decide on how to deal with the gods so for now
we're just going to have to be happy with our own personal way of dealing with them or mainstream
religion and I know that didn't really answer your question but that that's an overarching principle
that has to be repeated over and over by the way it's something of extreme importance so
when we say how they relate to the stars we tend to do the same thing well we have let's say oh
we can change political systems and cultures and traditions by abandoning them or creating new ones
but once we start talking about what's up there and out there in the cosmos with whatever belief
of structure you think it is it gets very frightening right so it's best we just deal with it when it
happens of course there's the subtle aspect of timekeeping you know the sun rules the day and the
moon rules the month then there's a collection of cycle that we call the year
not referring to the Pope's work schedule because that's purely arbitrary just has the illusion that
it's an accurate timekeeper but there's the threat of asteroids the threat of cosmic events
that overall no whatever peace solitude and all we have by looking at the night sky or at the
sun in the day and other things in the day we tend to not want to contemplate that realm
because just too serious that's why I've been a big proponent of saying that when there's going to be
potential harm coming from out there you know whether it's an asteroid or a planetary event or
solar event you're not going to be told much about it and those the powers that be in the world
would rather not tell you about it and just prepare themselves to deal with the constant
quesas once the event is over and it's the same with the gods so that's all I can say about
up there it's a very it's very very serious stuff very serious and it's because it's a seriousness
and it's possible tragic outcomes it's not discussed and or considered in the meantime you just
enjoy what you know and can see about those things meaning above cognitively people are on such
operating on such a minimal level low level that it's very difficult to even engage in discussion
and of course the political science not as political science but the the science that they're given
is so politicized and so much thwarting any critical discussion critical observational critical thinking
that the subject falls into becoming moot and it gets heated into a point where people can stop
collectively and say we don't have anything to really look at constructively we have to have
different belief systems just like the religions right I mean still there aren't many people think
that you know the god that I believe in his benevolent would never allow anything to harm us right
and I said well is it you know and they say well what religion are the same Christian wasn't
supposed to be based on the bible bible is full of direct comments and prophecies and things that
he will bring on harm and he says well that I don't need the bible then the same with scientists
they do the same when you show flaws in their thinking and their in their rational
their logic and in their experiment they say well you're not a scientist you don't have the right to
do that so excuse me we're in a very minimal construct in terms of cognitive construct intellectual
construct I think add together with that as I mentioned in previous that you perhaps speak as
speaking sonic events you're in an anti-intellectual environment what I mean by that is you'll look how
cartoons entertainment social culture have the nerds then they're the bookworms you know they're
the eggheads meaning if you knock them down their head will crack open like an egg you know they're
very anti-intellectual right so this again will cross over into that and with strength instead of
so when you have a high level of cognition and intellectualism being revered the nerd will go away
the bookworm the egghead will go away and that negative sentiment towards it will go away
and there'll be more understanding of the gods as well okay another popular story in connection
with the gods is that a certain group of them at one point overtly recited among human beings
until they committed some offense and were either banished or overthrown in the Sumerian or Babylonian
context it would be the upcalo in the Greek mythology you have the Olympians overthrown the titans
and then interacting with humanity as they wish in the Semetic and Biblical tradition they aren't
explicitly named but the notion is referenced and then that has led to a lot of extra biblical or
apocryphal material about it how far are we able to ascertain the details of that general account
so as to narrow down the specifics here's the thing and I say this a lot with people you know
they hear about fantastic inventions inventions and things with a Tesla made Victor Shawberger this is
a side note made and oh yeah you know if it worked we'd have it in society well you know actually if
you actually read what these inventors wrote and whatever diagrams are provided how little or how
much and you start replicating word for word by comprehending what is memorialized about it you will
probably get similar results I have first-hand experience with that if you continue down that path
you will have the same results these men did so that's all that's all I have to say what most people
say we have to how do we what do we do with all this information whether it's the up call of the
Anunnaki or the Nephilim and any other various or how they came to be or the order of the gods punishing
or rewarding or allowing or disallowing if you actually look at the information no matter how
scanned it's properly thought to be you can pretty much piece it all piece it all together through
commonality and there is a lot of information there even if it's even if you have a one-liner
that in biblical and Sumerian texts regarding some things I think the Sumerian texts actually give
more information than the biblical regarding the attributes of certain beings but generally it's
still popularly considered to be scanned but but it's it's enough of the information is there to see
that there is an order or hierarchy that like the movements in the military the infantry officer
grants are moving because they're being managed by the sergeant who receives his orders from a
commissioned officer who received his orders from a higher commissioned officer that's in based
in the strategic planning and then that goes up to even higher that would be a leader of the realm
that they're defending or offending from very simple stuff and there's a need to know basis if
you've heard that before you it's you just don't need to know but if anyone does any research and
even gathers all what's popularly known to be scanned or minimal information and comparatively
studies it all together you get you get a pretty good picture of what's going on
and in connection to that I believe certain writers like Eric von Daniken and I think most notably
Zacharias Sitchin postulated that these Apcaloo or Anunnaki were in fact extra-terrestrials who
seated the earth either with humans or or hybrids and then taught them things like science and
agriculture I don't know that we have to get into the details of all that but where does the
distinction go for you between the gods as unseen spirits versus physical characters that resemble
aliens or something non-human initially you would say you'd have to discern their two they're
not the same but in a final conclusion one can draw that you can group them all together fairly
accurately if you understand that there is no one god and there's you know like for again
not to knock the Christian meme but it's just it's their fault that they're easy to knock
they think there's one god and his Messiah heir whose rebellious against him was done
away with his laws and then there's a demon or a Satan and then various demons and that's it there's
like four or five beings and that's the population I mean where even if you had a four-year-old
mentality you would easily imagine more this is where this is where people get really stuck
so if you were to say like many dude oh those aliens are really demons well yeah they kind of fit
the bill but they're not because there's a very a variable ecology in the universe so I would
lean to say that yeah there's plenty of beings out there and in many capacities and they might appear
god-like but if you were to group anything like vandana again in sitchon did as being extra terrestrials
and all that I wouldn't say it's accurate but I would say it's fair okay I think it's fair to do that
you know anti-gravity let's say what people call anti-gravity which isn't really accurate again but let's
just use that for communication purposes little green men or even anthropomorphic whether they do
good or bad yeah you can group them together with the gods but it's not accurate I follow they're
their own thing I think anyone who sort of looks at common literature throughout the last two
three centuries and pop culture will have seen references to certain human beings whose natural
life span are unreasonably long and it's become common for a lot of vampire stories in the last two
three four decades to portray their vampires as such just because maybe it's convenient or it's
cool but even back in the 19th century you had Oscar Wilde writing about the picture of Dorian
Gray where a guy is young for decades so the lore around that phenomenon is pointing to beings that
are either hybrids or the gods themselves in human form how much do you know about things like that
that's a broad question that requires specifics and when you look at the specifics you'll see it may
not be part of the germane to the conversation because I would just land on the land on something
that would be regarding vampires there are different species of human a sub species and number in
popular in population not sub meaning lesser than very very similar to humans they are humans made
by humans for humans or gods there are another species of human yes it sounds crazy but since you
brought up vampires if you do a comprehensive search on what is available to the public about vampires
you'll find some pretty serious research done on them by various stations of society including
you know presidents and high-order governments and societies that don't consider them to be
fictional but consider them to be again a sub species or a smaller species a variant of what we call
human there are many variants of human by the way that were that are not popularized just like
there is a indigenous people in Colombia that I was made aware of that existed up until the 1970s so
no public information they did not achieve their gender identity until they were about eight or
nine so unlike most people whose gender is developed or sex is developed in the womb theirs did not
fully develop until about eight or nine years old you don't hear about them very hard to find
information on bottom online you have the pygmy people that are very very very small people and
they have other traits not just small so and then you have the vampires is just an example that would
be more of an extremophile compared to what I've mentioned right so they are another sub species I
think they would be quite earthly based let's say cool let's move on to another sphere of the gods
which is their laws and their ways and sort of the way that they administer certain things
from the spirit realm over here when we look at the earliest memorializations about the gods
that have been translated anyway I know that there's some like the vinka script from the denubi
civilization that aren't translated but when we look at the Sumerians as the earliest example
what we find with them is that their cities were ruled by kings who claimed to have the backing
of a god and one of the things that you've spoken about as a distinguishing factor between high
level and low level gods was how the higher ones administered laws in a more like determined way
or definitive way and so the more sophisticated the nuance the law code of a people the more eminent
the deity was behind it what makes you say that or what makes you put weight on the law aspect
it's just by example you know when a king if you look at something that is taught in mainstream
school code of homorabi if you go and read it the first it starts off with it's dedicated to a
particular guard martyook I think or something I don't hold me to that but and this is the code of
homorabi and they start off with that if you read for example the law what's called the U.S. Constitution
it's dedicated to establishing what justice that female goddess so there is always some attribute
to some law body to some god usually a lot of the treaties do that as well and then there's the
very various levels and now it's gotten to the point where you mentioned earlier the ritual sacrifices
in the simple barter concept that people have you do this for my for god and they'll do this for you
has kind of disregarded the aspect of a quote unquote law giver and of course biblical laws been
disregarded because supposedly the christ figure is a rebellious son and did away with everything his
his dad put down right so I mean would you want find in any writ but it's in their in their culture
so you know then again we can lean and say that the earth is and this is all could also accepted by
many conservative religious circles the earth is being affected by negative entities that tend to
affect society unaware is by just creating lawless quote unquote situations so I that's a big
question and actually I think we might want to get into divine law in the future
because that that itself we can open up for four hours here just to just to even statistically go
through it because statistically meaning you know what needs to be looked at and how a divine law
and what people consider to be divine law affects the culture and society and then what happens when
it's abandoned and goes underground for only certain things that gets really wide and broad
and just but to sum it up essentially even if you look at the ritualistic sacrifices that's still
being done in practice today they tend to be indirect rebellion to laws that should be given to
men by lesser gods or greater gods to rule to use as functioning in society and they it's all
been abandoned it's just some kind of wrote cliche and one aspect of instructions from the gods is
being utilized as a technology like for example the sacrifice of children to gain control over
populations or personal wealth or whatever is being employed still very vehemently the rest
has pretty much been abandoned when you look at the oldest law codes that we have extant I think
the code of urnamu is a little older than homerabi I think by 300 years or so they don't exactly
inspire transcendence when you read them though like the earlier codes especially they read like a
list of don't do abc or else and then when you read some of the prefaces of them like the urnamu code
the king basically says no I did this it's not my god these are my words you're gonna do what I say
and so like as an example three of the laws in the urnamu code is like if a man commits murder then
he must be killed if a man commits robbery then he must be killed if a man commits a kidnapping he's
imprisoned and has to pay 15 checkers of silver so I know that the homerabi code is a bit more
sophisticated but what are we in general to make of the fact that a lot of these codes don't seem
that inspiring and some of them just came from the king's own moral authority that's fine
because even if you look at the biblical verses that state where you don't want my law meaning
the god of the bible I'll have men rule over here with their laws yeah that's acceptable
I get that but in some cases to like the homerabi situation or others the gods are saying okay here's
laws we made these but then when you read them come I mean I don't want to hold up modern constitutions
as a paragon of anything but at least you can say of modern laws today that they try to be
sometimes they're complex to the point of being Byzantine but they do try to be thorough and cover
everything whereas a lot of the older ones are just like if you do this then that oh it didn't work
well that's the law sure well you have to realize the overarching principle of the constitution
it's a freemasonic document it's almost taken out of it's a distilled out of a freemasonic lore and the
religion of free masonry is nozzlesism so if one were to follow that and see how accurate what I
just said is you can easily say that the US Constitution is a nostic document with some things rearranged
to conceal to conceal the direct relation so instead of Sophia you have just just to see
our justice I don't know if I've ever gone into that before because I find it breaches to the political
mind instead of the cosmic you know I call the study of the gods more you know people tend to be
too biased to have a free discussion on various examples whether it's the homeromic code or the
freemasonic dostic distinctions blaringly obvious in the constitution once you understand the history
of those who put it together well yeah I mean we are going to have an episode set aside just for divine
law it takes forever to do research on that stuff so it's probably going to be a later episode
but we'll get to it yeah and I think that's more of a specialized study which I might want to offer
in the future as a specialized study you know and you might want to do as a very specialized study
because the fine points are give a quick example use the US Constitution it says it will be in the
amendment and not the bill of rights people tend to group the bill of rights which are the bill of
afterthoughts in a way they came much later there would have been another revolution if they didn't do
that and pay off enough people to quell them but if you look in the amendments it say there will be
no constitution states things 14 through 13th most likely for the 14th there will be no slavery unless
convicted of a crime people say oh that's kind of harsh because slavery is not done away with you have
a condition going to slavery but it's even worse and no one points this out they could have added one
word to make it all right in some capacity which would be there would be no slavery unless lawfully
convicted of a crime or another word they could have substituted for lawfully is rightfully convicted
of a crime so by not inserting that single word you can be falsely convicted of a crime
and then plunged into a slave like system condition unlawfully unright and because your fault
you're falsely convicted and you might say Greek your mind is running loose you're unhinged
that doesn't sound right they'll never get away with it okay there's a judge that was probably
strangulated or whatever had too much of a party died Scalia right a Supreme Court justice no
ought to up see oh that's a real funny stuff on a a ranch that is known to have a cult stuff going on in
Texas that guy okay he had a white paper written about that where cases that were brought to him for
people serving time in various prisons about being wrongfully convicted and being treated as you know
as convicts and criminals he says the constitution doesn't have anything to do with doesn't say that
says conviction not rightfully or lawfully convicted so the the constitution allows for wrongful
convictions this is coming from one of your top law judges who's no longer around by the way good
ridden say this is not an opinion I mean well it's his opinion and he's one of the top guys
so chew on that for a little while yeah that is something to consider right because of all the stuff
the free mason's due they cover their conscious by making burn hospitals for children you ever
noticed those to the hospitals they do or burn hospitals well guess what what they do with their human
sacrifices they always show you and tell you what they're doing by what they're trying to appease
society with as with benevolence it's not in my business I hope it never is
but if you have a child go missing and the authorities tell you
yeah you want us to investigate that but you're still young enough to have more children you know FBI
police tell your parents that yeah uh-huh they're all part of the club you don't want to let people
know that they're kind of stuck in this corn quote matrix of evil let's say or inventors of
evil things because how are they going to go to work the next day whether they're convicted or not
right it's really it's really harsh and we tend to end I tend to give a more of a serious loose
loose seriousness bandit about whenever we do the sonics I think from memory let's some wrap up
on the law aspect a bit one of the things that I've noticed also and I think we touched on this
little earlier this lack of symmetry between mankind and the gods other than maybe references to the
period of the upkaaloo there aren't many stories of mankind being taught by the gods or cared
for by the gods or befriend it by the gods or loved by the gods it's always like if you sacrifice and if
you build temples and if you conquer and if you obey then we'll keep you alive at a minimum and if
we like you then we'll make you prosper why so much of this anti intimate distant approach that
sometimes gets malevolent with the child sacrifice and stuff okay let's just say brought up the
upkalo and you'll lack of symmetry there isn't attempt to have a symmetrical model and you'll find
that in what's called the hybrid the human god hybrid or demigod that's if someone has half this
and half that well isn't that symmetrical within that being aren't the don't I'm paraphrasing here
but the upkalo are a hybrid where the unannockey or not right yes the Nephilim would be in
the bible and demigods in the age of heroes which not to be confused with heroes but
they did spur the age of heroes in the Greek ages and Saturday morning cartoons right super heroes see
heroes who are not enough for the American culture they have to call them super heroes right because
we're better than the ancient Greeks right gets kind of crazy after a while and it's the comedy of
the absurdities with what with how manning ages any of these topics but when the hammer comes down
forget about being in between a rock in a hard place you'll be between the hammer and the anvil
it's hard to say but they'll still be deniers even at that point so it's a saga that's going to be
continuing for a very long time in other words who the gods are so humans are very tough
when it comes to that stuff there are tough nut to crack meaning their cognitive ability and
and ability to acknowledge things truthfully this is going to be going on meaning this cognitive
dissension dissonance and all that is going to be something that's going to be with humanity for a
very long time well let's just say a thousand years at least I'm just throwing that number out
there if those who know know what I mean. Hmm esoteric references um now you're right about the
app callu I was a little hesitant but now that I think through you know what I know yes you're right
they were demigods which is a symmetrical example of the realms right but then they made a bad fate
um in some accounts uh-huh so that didn't go too well. No it didn't right yeah at the hands of various
various circumstances right not again not a lot of information but plenty to understand that if
it's true they existed and if it's not true they exist in in the information at least and also
most of these epics that people read are epics you know just like Shakespeare wrote epics it doesn't
mean that because Shakespeare wrote a play called Julius Caesar Julius Caesar didn't exist
actually the e to e to Brut uh like e to Brutus you know during the assassination
is popularized in the fiction that Shakespeare wrote and people are not clear whether that was
really set or not and things that Mark Anthony said and did is made more popular through Shakespeare
than what the historical account show but that doesn't mean that Mark Anthony did not exist historically
you see so when you read a lot of the ancient stuff they're known as epics because they were plays
commissioned by kings so whether they include giants or a callu nannanaki and it's a play it doesn't
mean that it's not true it just so happens what we have are mostly epics you know plays commissioned
by kings or writers and and mercantile records we don't have a lot and I think 80% of what's held in
the museum of London regarding Q&A form tablets and things from that time are still unexamined publicly
and it seems the 20% that is satisfied the curiosity enough to you know who cares why bother
so there's a lot more that can be done on it set on the subject but even though the information
might be minimal and scant you get a pretty good outline of what's going on and connecting
concerning this the malevolent aspect when you look at the distance that the gods place between
themselves and mankind when that distance is sometimes bridged most of the encounters seem to be
described as terrifying or malevolence which is why I think the haunting or the possession theme
became prevalent in later centuries and to me that begs the question if the most of the gods
who interact with humanity portray malevolence why doesn't that malevolence turn itself inward
so that they war against each other and then destroy themselves I think the malevolence is because
there's so much of a difference in the environment that it appears to be so like if you enjoy a fish pond
and you happen to reach into one of the ponds that you're keeping and pull the fish out of the
water that fish will see that act in you as being malevolent because it's gasping for water right
that's a very simple anti-analogy but it is a direct analogy to that what viewing them
cosmic beings god like beings as malevolent because if they I said earlier appear as they as they are
they your matter reality disintegrates or falls apart kind of like a fish out of water
or if you were pulled into the ocean to view that society you would find that as being very malevolent
even with all the best intent of the mermaid that sucked you down in there to take you to her
layer and make the best of you and by the way mermaids were always very negative beings also in
history only recently with disney of it become beautiful and positive right the same with genies
so there's something they're trying to mitigate in through fiction and fantasy turn a lot of these
historically malevolent experiences into positive things including the christian meme also the
return of you know who will be all positive I don't know where you get in that from yes from a moral
perspective yes but from an actualization perspective no it's going to be extremely negative to you
in your environment at any text when you read about the return of the gods they end up destroying
man's society not the world not the earth the world which is man's society not the earth and not all
of humans and when you read about any text those that are doing the destruction are they the good
guys are the bad guys in the cosmic realm or the godlike realm always the good guys thusly those that
are paying attention have always concluded that those that are running the earth are malevolent
are true malevolent even human will not appear as such if they want to have a long term relationship
with you are truly malevolent human with a very short term relationship will pull a gunner
knife on you to take your belongings or rob you still cover their face or maybe not depending on how bold
they are short term but a long term malevolent will appear as a as an ally and a friend always
never hear of government by the way centralize government ever hear centralized banking
doesn't have to be it just so happens to be
because humans are through behaviors that sustain peaceful societies tribal and feudal
with slavery by the way and legally most humans are legally slaves under the world banking system
because it's if you want to know who you want to know how many people are in the earth or in the
country who do you reference for that world bank oh suddenly the world bank is in the benevolent
human statistics business yeah sure so yeah you can get really deep and these are conspiracy
conclusions not conspiracy theories it's just the way it is and also they say wake up right they
talk about that that doesn't help you because if you go to bed stupid you're stupid if you and if you
wake up from being asleep and stupid you're still going to be stupid you have to wake up and educate
yourself you know as they always say wake up that's acceptable once you start saying educate yourself
now your threat that poses a serious threat model and i mean that not necessarily on the worldly
secular political level but it poses an even more serious threat to the cosmic level you know the
malevolent quote unquote beings that are stated to rule the earth well i mean since we're on the
topic of how the god operate i'll just keep stick with it a bit because some things came to mind i
think we'd be a bit remiss not to talk about one of the more popularly demanded rituals which is
that of sacrifice i know we touched on it a little bit before but just to do a little bit more of a
narrow inspection i've kind of always been struck by how ancient gods would at some point
obligate their followers to make blood blood sacrifices to them and the first time that i noticed
that as being something that was very emphatic was actually from pop cultural stuff so there was a
movie 20 years ago called the road to elderados animated movie it's about two Spanish guys that
search for this lost city of gold called elderado eventually they find it the inhabitants presume
that because they're white there must be gods and the high priest keeps insisting on making human
sacrifices to them and then the spaniards obviously having no clue they keep refusing to accept the
sacrifice and eventually the high priest realized that way you can't be gods because gods require blood
sacrifices as part of their regime what have you been able to uncover about this relationship
between the gods and their lust or appetite for blood it's a cosmic commerce most people
you know to talk about that you could briefly state this human commerce very few people know this
it's very obvious that's why they don't know it in commerce you use something called currency or
money for the nobility it's the gold and for the common people it's the silver for the poor it's
barter and for the slave it's credit that's why the whole world's under a credit-based economy
now when humans do commerce with the gods and i would even suggest when the gods do commerce
amongst themselves they use blood that's their currency so if the if you break rank from either one
of them if the let's say the the popper the poor want to do commerce with the common man they're
going to have to come up with some silver right but if the common man wants to do business with
the popper he better come up with some barter so whatever system you go into up or down the the
direction of the purchase has to satisfy the means of commerce or exchange that that particular
society uses right so if the king or the nobility that uses gold wants to do commerce with the slave
they would give the slave credit oh wait a second that sounds like what's going on
and if the slave wanted to do commerce with the king that slave would have to come up with some gold
you see it's the direction of the purchase so because the gods use blood as their currency
when the human wants to do a purchase with the gods or an exchange they have to provide blood
but in contrast to the human side where you have tiers of currency gold silver credit etc on that
that is just blood what's with with the gods right and don't get confused about the gods demanding
certain things in case they're and can't it covered in gold or in silver and things like that don't
get confused about that in other words the direction of the purchase the currency exchange must be
in line with the direction of who the the purchase is directed to you know meaning the seller the
seller makes the demand and the buyer must must satisfy that demand must tender that to that demand
that's why when you look at the slave society on earth right now when the slaves do acquire a
physical bullion of silver or gold right it's never considered currency it's it's it's what how does
the slave acquire silver or gold where I want market the money market the money the bank or the
commodity market commodity market so when you're dealing when you're going to acquire blood to do
purchasing with the gods as the seller you have to go to a commodity market to get the blood
you mean I want to offer your children but there's plenty of poor people that will sell you
there is to do that even today by the way but you also have situations where people made sacrifices
and there was a qualitative difference between your blood sacrifice and somebody else's like
some people did that and it had no effect whatsoever and then the king when he wanted to win a war
had to give his own son well he could have just taken the bum's son but the god wouldn't have
any other person it's called terms and conditions because that somehow must have been agreed to prior
to the vet certain conditions it was so hard about that no that's fine I get that but in some cases
it seems as if the terms are either not understood or are reneged upon because you know the last
episode of the Greek speak podcast you talked about cannabels dolls and birthdays and the cunon balls
right they were eventually run out of town because people were like y'all shit don't work
and it don't and they went up and became the druids about 4,000 miles away but those guys had I mean
at least from what I have been able to see they were renowned for having a power that was very real
so again it's kind of like this mixed bag like over here it works sometimes it works sometimes it
doesn't over there when they run off and do some other thing then it works I think it works even when
it doesn't work because not knowing what to do is sometimes just as important as knowing what to do
or knowing what happens when you break the terms and conditions you agree to is just as important
as fulfilling those terms and conditions it's called testing let's keep things simple doesn't mean
that well I would suggest that most things that people question as unknowns I would suggest are simple
but most people question them because as unknowns it's not because that they don't realize they're simple
which they don't they they acknowledge them as being mysterious and ineffective because they're not easy
simple doesn't mean easy simple can be difficult to accomplish very simple be point to the top
of a mountain peak you see that yes I do how's that complicated no go there ooh not easy
well it's simple right they put the mountain provides you everything you need to get up there to
defeat the effect of gravity but it's not easy is it there's many examples like that
you know building an infrastructure for a country or a city simple you see that here's a map of
the land look will you see these lines made of concrete or asphalt or whatever simple right do it
not easy simple currency of the gods is blood whether you are too dense and ignorant to understand
the terms and conditions if they're set or preset and both by the way most of the rituals that do
involve that sacrifice that blood sacrifice have terms and conditions in grimoires that go back
thousands of years how many times have you heard even above ground you know commoners doing things
in their tradition and that one will state criticize another thing you didn't do it right because
you didn't do this or include this when you said that or off you see you hear that in
any common variant of any culture in tradition traditional ritual oh I do this ritual better
than they do because I include this they'll admit that you hear this all the time especially
politicians you know they're supposed to read them and know if they don't this is taken out of the
oath this is right you can have a general in the particular country saying you know basically
giving verbal orders to infantry at another part of the world that rains you know rains pillage
in destruction by a word so that is very important the terms and conditions are words
so I mean if the death or loss of life is a constant right that every human animal has to endure
and you're saying that the shedding of blood constitutes a form of currency for the gods but then that
implies a sort of morbid undertone where maybe a universal endpoint of humanity is to have their lives
be cashed into so bank account on the other side because someone has to probably like a
step. Yeah well if you were to overly if you were to overly simplify it so that you can you can
lend to co you know understanding yeah but there is a blood offerings for example signing
something in blood where you the the victim or the participant survives the the occasion.
Yeah I mean but they still after the event they become a slave no like a bondage slave or something
well the mob you know is very typical it's even in film you know they do a ritual to indoctrinate
someone into the higher tier of the organization they they prick their finger and deposit a blood
stain on a document for the for the record that's a blood offering that's like going out and buying
a 50 cent stamp or a you know a half euro or one euro stamp you know and putting it on something
till legitimize it it's a license to invite the cosmic world when you do blood.
That makes sense. It's a it's a fee there's more to it there's more to the human sacrifice I think I've
gone over in sonic events in the past not with you perhaps yet and we can get into that has to do
with the organs of the body and offering your best stuff and on and on and on.
Okay yeah we'll probably end up doing that some later point. Another aspect in connection to this
sort of tangentially is the idea of summoning I mean various cultures have incantations and spells
and potions and rituals you talked about grim rares which will cause the power of some god to be
manifest I think the Japanese have their wartime kamikaze ritual that will bring a storm to wipe out
opposing forces the American Indians had scrolls and writings on summons that were coveted by the
Jesuits I believe and it's also said that you know western governments in the 80s made it a priority
to pursue and collect grim wars and the intelligence community did that for them.
And by the way the western governments covered that at those actions up by saying oh they were
just pursuing astrologers do you remember that with Nancy Reagan anybody they wasn't honest it's just
it made such a stir they said oh no no it's astrologers astrologers yeah it's technical technical
access so let's say you have in your possession some prized scrolls or writings that are grim wars or the
the technical access meaning if you say this spell or this incantation we invoke a demon every time
because it has accurate effect you know it's it's an accurate account of the of what needs to be said
to bring this demon and it works every time right and you know you put it in the back of your car
and the trunk opens it falls out in some common oh finds it takes it home and is able to read it and
he has a demon appear he doesn't know what's going on this sounds like the makings of a spielberg film
right you see how simple it is the demon or the entity also can discern who brought them in and
might ask that says who are you right why did you call me not to belittle the the weight of that
but I also remember that in the books of narnia and like seventh one one of the bad guys summoned
to god that he didn't believe in and when he showed up he's like oh so you don't believe in me but
you called me are you stupid and then he took him and went into the spirit realm and did whatever he
did to him I think he tortured him or something mm-hmm at your undimaged yeah be careful
there's things in the physical realm you know poisons nuclear waste let's say or I would say
that's overrated but you know biological toxins and things again overrated but there are
things in the physical realm that are considered taboo to play with and a band substances
I mean there are poisons that are so toxic up in the in the halogen halide groups in the
periodic table you know there are certain acids that are formed with halides that are so
explosive and so unstable that they're banned even they're banned within even scientific and
military communities to handle there are some acids that that are so toxic and explosive that
they just they exist and they're stored but they're not handled because
that's how volatile they can be right and that's just an analogy for the spiritual realm or you know
yeah um lastly I think this will be you know I think we've done we've done longer than most other
episodes on this but I'm I'm also interested in looking at how the gods interface with the human mind
because the idea of possession is a common one as well as exorcisms dreams from the gods visions
etc to be able to take control of a human body and displacement persons consciousness is something
that I think the matrix illustrates very well the movie when an agent in that film takes over
some was body they lose consciousness until the agent either dies or a link which is control of the
host you've made statements in the past on how that portrayal is actually quite accurate correct
okay that's really simple again but not easy for people to comprehend the analogy that to
simplify it there would be how the major networks or streaming you know video platforms appear
on your television set why why does why is it when I turn on the TV I get a major network
because that's how they you know that's what they that's how they manifest right the major TV
networks why is it when I turn on the radio tuner I get radio stations or what came first they
have to both work together you know they both kind of or one is a manifestation of the other to
a certain degree but one came first I think the broadcast or the gods came before the receivers
the humans the human mind is just a receiver and a transmitter because you know if you have
cable or some satellite does it but not they gives feedback to the to the main network
they know what you're watching for example it would quote unquote cable television
yeah it's again the simple analogy if you're walking by a picnic area or the beach and you hear
someone has a radio playing jazz do you think if you open that radio there's a little jazz band in there
it's a receiver in a transmitter let's say the human mind
anyone that doesn't understand basic well even it's a little more but then basic radio can study the
brain and say oh yeah that has that's following the anthropomorphic I call the star configuration
and the human brain it's following certain propagation protocols just like I've discussed
another sonic's perhaps the human body works by induction not absorption that's why you have an
embedded transmission line the why do you have to have so many feet of intestine nothing to do with
whether you're carnivore or vegetarian right you know what a coil is a copper coil how inductors
are used in circuits you'll see a lot of things embedded and folded things of great length
moved over in the like the human intestines in the brain which display the principles and
properties of induction and inductors look it up what is induction and by the way when you do more
comprehensive medical studies not the trash they put out on TV for people to believe like I think
guys were speaking right now people are still suffering through the media and government
lockdowns and things from ignorant peasantitis I tell people in the public it's so you weren't
to mask because of ignorant peasantitis and they look they shrugged their shoulders none of them
get insulted because they're ignorant peasants anyway that hasn't offended anyone yet and I've
said it to 100 people and the reason why is because they're ignorant peasants anyway when you study
advanced medical manual which you got to laugh a little bit but there is some good stuff out there
all they've done a lot of grunt work ultimately diseases are not contracted which is a contract
but they're induced induction again so and ignorant peasantitis is not contracted or induced by
the way well it might be induced what also we're going to offer well I have one last thing and then
we're done I think one of the befuddling developments of the last two thousand years is how what they
call monotheism came to be the most dominant religious prism I would say primarily due to the rise of
Christianity and then later rabbinic Judaism and Islam I don't want to overanalyze it because I know
that the religions are myred in misdirection but in connection to this idea of the one god or the
supreme being there's always existed the notion of either super power god that rules actively
over all existence or even a higher level being that's like the source quote unquote of all
sentience but he has a more passive role in overseeing it and I think that that notion is what lens
plausibility to the idea of monotheism and maybe ancient kings like Akinaten may have been affected by
that I think the Greeks talked about it a bit how much can we uncover about that not much at all
because if there is an overarching being like that he is actively passive meaning he's not
terminally passive within what we call to be terminal or any on any timeline but he's actively passive
that would be like someone saying yeah I'll do that in 20 years and you know like 20 years go by
and nothing is being done right that's actively passive like yeah I'll do that in a thousand years
or I'll do that in sometime in the future and through some other process of communication
it's sort of communicated that that later time is thousands of years that's actually that's what I
call actively passive like saying you're not going to do something for a long time and keeping your
word and a long time goes by of passivity of nothing happening right and the reason that is is because
you said you wouldn't do anything for that long period of time yeah for sure a point of confusion
for me would have always been like in the Greek convention they talk about the demi-urge as being
this low level entity that poses as the real entity and so on the stick the no stick stole it from the
Greeks though as far as the idea right it was a minor concept in the Greeks because the Greeks did
ponder an active a series of active gods and structures that would be even beyond what was
described and simplified over simplified as a demi-urge right in other words what you see the ponder
nanching times was not as simple as the demi-urge which in in a demi-urge itself doesn't compass
you know someone who was actually allowing a provocating everything that we see but it's not a demi-urge
it would demi-urge would be like army you say when you say army it wouldn't be one you don't think
of one soldier when you say army when you say demi-urge to think that it's one being doing all of it is
fallacy on many levels okay but i've still run into this notion that i think i'm warned some
examination as far as not just having a supreme being that rules over the gods but there seems to be
this passive thing that exists beyond him that there really isn't much information on but some
kind of illusion too because even that god of gods presumably comes from somewhere but that element
seems to be the one that wants to be really passive and not say or do anything oh i see yeah that's
possible but we don't understand enough about that god of gods by design to make a conclusion we can
only make it a theory this point just like children make up things about how an automobile works or
where babies come from or whatever and when they they're granted more of the physical body to
engage in those things they learn the truth about those things let's say like driving a car what's
called driving car or where did babies come from they just don't ponder it
there's certain quote unquote mature subjects and i think we'll get to that point here pretty soon
not on the these sonics but you know on the human timeline um sure and i think on that note
we've covered everything that i had in mind anyway um it was a pretty um long-ranging talk so
hopefully the audience is benefited from that and can go and do some whatever complementary research
they have to do on their own um is there any concluding or closing bits that you want to throw in
no i would say that's all i have to offer for now on this subject okay thank you to everybody that
tuned into this one um i hope you've enjoyed it and we will see you at the next episode of the
God's Big Podcast
[Music]