Welcome to episode 2 of the Greekspeak podcast hosted by the Archon in the Greek.
I'm the Archon and the Greek will be with me in a minute.
The last episode saw us talk about the ancient world and how notions of the gods were made
manifest back then.
For today we're going to dig into a more narrow subject that concerns some very well misunderstood
concepts about the unseen realm, namely that of the soul and the spirit.
So yeah, without further ado, let's get things started.
Archpeak has no political religious or commercial affiliations and is solely managed by myself,
the Archon.
So I hope you enjoy our upcoming talk and thanks again for listening.
Hello, Greek.
You're around?
Greetings, yes.
Yes, we are around, yes.
Indeed.
Meaning you and I, yeah?
Well, for episode 2 we're going to examine one of the more fundamental ideas of esoteric
knowledge, which is that of the spirit and the soul.
I think those are words that most people are happy to pull definitions from out of thin
air.
Either they just make something up or they parry something that they heard in pop culture
or religion.
And I think it also seems lost on people why the distinction even matters.
So we're going to look at that and some of the confusion that surrounds them.
But before actually looking at what the terms mean, let's just look at the history of it.
Why is the distinction between soul and spirit important at all when you have entire schools
of thought that seems to have done just fine for 2,000 years without feeling obliged to
demarcate that difference?
Is there a reason why spirit and soul can't just be whatever ethereal concept people
claim them to be?
Well, let's turn that question into a statement and leave it as that.
Right.
Because that's what seems to be going on.
And here, let me just take a little detour and then segue back or segue and then we'll
get back into this theme.
Because the mindset, as I've said before, is very important.
And here, let's give an example.
Without even using the psychological term of schizophrenia or whatever, meaning dual-minded
or dual-whatever- duality, because let's leave and leave the duality out of it.
Hey, let's just give a standard format critique of society.
Generally, if anyone's heard any Greek speak in the past, I always state how, not directly,
but indirectly, how society at large, meaning almost every society is anti-intellectualism.
What I mean by that is the nerds, the smart people, the bookworm, the egghead.
Egghead means when you beat up smart people, their heads crack open like eggs, right?
They're weak.
It's generally an anti-intellectualism or anti-intellectual society.
That's more than a sentiment or an undertone.
It's actually profoundly demonstrated.
So from that point of view, there's something called education, the rudimentary grammar to
the higher, what they call high school.
And then they have the higher education, which is a joke, university up to doctorate programs.
So how can they be anti-intellectual, yet almost offer as a standard that you must go to
college to get ahead in life?
So if they're anti-intellectual at heart and demonstrably anti-intellectual, why are they promoting
education as being important?
Is it a duality?
No.
It would seem like a duality, but it's not a duality because education is not being offered.
It's indoctrination.
In other words, it's basically adapting people to the society or not even the rules.
The policies that happen to be employed at the time, right?
Because it's very Alice in Wonderland, if anyone is dealt with anyone, any form of authority
that's supposed to follow rules, they'll always tell you, well, we just do what we want anyway,
essentially.
They don't say that publicly, but...
So let's go back to the theme.
The question that you asked, or which I revert back to saying it should be made a statement,
on a trust that are compared to a general anti-intellectual sentiment by humans, yet they say it's important
to be educated.
So is it duality and contradiction?
No, because there is no education being offered.
It's indoctrination.
And actually, anyone is does a little research.
Universities are run by trustees and are funded and managed by the state, which is
not the government, by the way.
One day we'll talk about how the state and the government are two different things.
But anyway, the trusteeship basically says that they're not there to educate, but they're
there to create a willing...
Partist, let's say, in many ways it's been said, people are willing to participate in what
society they live in without asking questions, basically, preparing them for the workforce,
preparing them to be "professional."
So I hope this sheds a little bit of light on how we're going to maybe tamp down a lot of
the stuff that's been flying around in terms of terminology, spirit and soul.
Yeah, that certainly does provide a point from which people can adjust their perception
of things and think through the matter.
But as far as the distinction between the two, for a person who wants to find clarity about
how the soul differs from the spirit, they would run into a lot of roadblocks with regards
to the uncertainty that's surrounding those terms, and it almost does seem comically
deliberate that no one knows what they mean given how much that they're used.
That almost seems like a very active propaganda effort or just very serious act of negligence
on somebody's part to not really dig into that.
Well, that's somebody being the collective known as society at large, yes, in all the different
fragmented sections of it, meaning the hierarchies and the, you know, whatever, the entitled
all the way down to the disenfranchised.
I don't think there's any argument with anyone that any subject viewed objectively can
be discovered to be incorrect, in other words, can be discovered at the way society thinks
of what that subject is about is incorrect.
Let's let me just dig into the, if you will, you want to give me a few minutes and I'll
do the standard spiel that I do when people, I've been doing this for over two decades,
under two decades, almost two decades, I should say, and just give me a few minutes and
if the, I could borrow the attention of the listener and they might want to play it back because
it's, it's, I'm going to give an itemized breakdown on the meaning of the spirit and the soul
with example.
Sure, of course.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Now, very simple.
If you consider the use of the word spirit soul and let's include the body here, the carne,
meaning the Latin for flesh or material, which is animated, we have to go back to how initially
it was used or proclaimed to be used and that's usually what we call the ancient
rites, whether it's the various Hindi piranhas, the Quran, the Bible, even myths and fables,
old Sumerian texts, the, the concept of spirit soul and body are constantly being used.
So then we come forward into more modern times where you have literary mechanism, literary
works all the way from Shakespeare, you know, up to Shakespeare, the Greek philosophers,
prior to Shakespeare, Shakespeare even to now where you have soul food and soul music.
So these words are being bantied about no one knows what they mean.
When I say no one, I mean statistically, 99.99, 99% of people don't know.
Now let's just take a very simple example that is actually the true way to look at it when
you even look into other cultures.
And what I mean is the Western culture has adopted the Greek and Latin basis for definition
of words, especially in technical terms, medical and otherwise in scientific it's the Greek
prefixes and the Greek suffixes.
So we see there is, there are two different words, the soul and the spirit, very simple.
Let's just define the soul and the spirit and the body very, very quickly and then show
how this is being used and how you are using it and what they really mean.
The three aspects of it will make the examples of the body very short because that's just
the carne, the flesh, the animated material part that is animated by the soul and the spirit.
So the word soul when we refer to it from ancient texts and on, it's specifically used as
a form of breath, something that is alive.
And when we look at the word, the Greek word, Numa, P and U prefix, we see it in technical
uses as pneumatic pneumonia, right?
You'll see things that move air, meaning physical air movement, metabolic use the word, Pneuma
and prefix P and U in the Greek and or atmos, right?
In Hindi, it's atmos, by the way, for soul.
So when you look at the soul, it is clearly and the animated part of the body.
In other words, it's your metabolism.
It's not only the breath, like for example, if we take the biblical convention in the early
aspect with Adam, the soul, the breath of the gods was put into Adam and he became a living
soul.
So to be a living soul or to have a soul, it's not just breathing.
And I'm going to emphasize this because in other places and the, you'll, through the discussion,
we'll see that the spirit is also defined as the wind and not to be confused.
But the soul is not only the breath, but it's the metabolism of the body, meaning another
example of the metabolism of the body would be the all the involuntary functions in the body,
which is like the heartbeat, the nervous system, the digestive system, circulatory systems,
both lymphatic and blood and what have you.
All of these things, you have functioning, which defines something as being living.
Whether it's an insect, a plant, a human, a dog, a cat, this is the soul.
It's not simply the breath.
But when we look at how it works, if you want to remove the soul from something, you suffocate
it, right?
A fixation, you attack the breath part of it.
And then the fixation results in the cease of functioning of the other aspects of the
metabolism or the soul.
And then the being is considered dead with no soul.
Okay.
So it's very, very simple.
It's simply your breath.
It starts with the breath and it continues through the everything that we consider something
to be alive, which is metabolism, whether it's a plant metabolism, insect metabolism, what
have you.
Now let me give an example of it because staying on this for a little bit without going to
the definition of the spirit, I think is helpful.
So let's give a rudimentary example of someone jumping into a swimming pool, their head hits
the bottom of the pool, they don't come up and the other bystanders pull the person out
of the pool and they're not breathing.
Okay.
So according to ancient writ, that person has no soul at this point because they're not
breathing.
And if they remain in that state of non-breathing, they will be declared dead eventually.
So what happens is this person is brought out of the water and somebody has the idea that
they should try to resuscitate him, someone who is alive and breathing.
And what they do is they perform resuscitation techniques where they open the mouth and they
breathe in, work on the chest, so forth.
They're putting their soul, now their breath, they're in nephesh, they're numa, they're out
most into that body of which lacks one and invigorates that body to now be breathing on
its own and now it has its soul back because it did lose its soul, right?
But it didn't lose its soul in the way that one does as spoken of in society.
That's why what I'm going to go through here is so contrast to what people think.
It takes a little bit more review on what I'm saying and even more examples.
So now we have someone that has no soul that got a soul from someone else.
And now that they are revived after this revival, resuscitation technique, now they are
a living soul on their own because they're functioning, they can stand up now and they're
like, thank you very much.
You see, so all of our souls are interchangeable.
Well a simple way to look at our souls being interchangeable is guess what?
We're all breathing the same hair.
If you have a dog, a cat, a dolphin, a cockroach, a human, a butterfly or a snake in the room,
all of your souls are interchangeable, right?
You're breathing the same hair in that room and you have a metabolism that works and if
one of you stops breathing another creature could try to resuscitate by putting their soul
into that other being.
This is a very empirical rudimentary definition.
It's so shocking how simple it is.
So I hope that I'm going to just pause there for a minute.
If you have any comments so far, otherwise I'll continue to the spirit.
No, I don't have any comments.
I'll let you finish up and then we'll just tackle it once you're old.
Oh, it's got, yeah.
Okay, that's fine.
Now the use is complex.
The use of the soul as you can imagine because what a soul food have to do with that
or that person's got soul.
You ever heard like in the Afrocentric artists, whether they're on the continent or
Western Europe or in the Americas, they're considered soul music, soul dancers, soul food
is a culture.
You know what, like somebody else doesn't have a soul if they're not into soul.
You see, it just means they have a more, it's the quality of their, right?
When you say soul food or soul music, it's just a term.
It really has no connection to this definition, but it just shows you how there's a desperate
attempt to use the words and they could catch on and not have anything to do with the subject
matter.
Excuse me.
So if you take on that definition and go back and read the ancient piranhas, the Magbaga
Vigida, the Bible, any ancient texts, especially if you're a student of any of these things,
you'll start to see things more plainly.
So let's continue to the spirit.
And again, the body, I'm not going to get into much, but it requires the soul to be animated
because once it stops breathing and the soul dies, then the body goes into chemical decomposition.
Right?
So the spirit, what's the spirit?
In the lot of the, in Arabic, it's the ruck or an Egyptian ruck, a ruck in Hebrew.
I forgot what it is in the Sanskrit, but you'll have that different word for the spirit.
And in the Greek, it's the psiki or the psy prefix, the mind, and I'll explain why.
So you have psychiatry, psychopath, psychotic.
All of these things have to do with the mind.
It's very interesting because the spirit is a immaterial, completely immaterial.
There is no function that the spirit has that is anything like the soul at all whatsoever.
There's not have any physical traits.
It is purely what you call the personality of someone, the character of someone, and
it's also purely the way information is handled, transmitted, qualified, and could be quantified
also.
So let's just do a simple analogy of the spirit.
It's what makes you you.
So what makes someone's personality them, the way they speak, the way they are.
Their character, their personality, the identifying element in a being, even if you're raising
cats or dogs, you'll notice they're not, they're like people in a way.
They all have very different personalities because they have very different spirits, but
they all share the same soul, not the same soul in each body, but they're interchangeable
where the spirits are not.
We'll get into that later on.
So you'll see the psyche, the PSY being used over and over, has to do with the mind.
It's funny when you talk to a psychologist, say, oh, so you're a spiritualist and they
don't know what you're saying.
They don't even know the definition of their own profession.
And I'm saying they're not saying that there may not be one that is, but I think of over
almost a hundred psychologists or psychiatrists that have approached with that statement have
looked at me like they don't know what I'm talking about.
So, and by the way, when you hear the term doctor, they're not really doctors in reality.
They're just technicians because a doctor is a teacher and an expert in their field.
I just wanted to throw that little dig in there.
So let's just move on forward with some examples of the spirit.
Let's say you have a CD or a vinyl record or a tape cassette tape or real to real tape of
a song of music.
And you give it to a material analyst, whether it's the CD, the vinyl disc, magnetic tape,
what have you.
He's going to come back with a report a couple of pages long on how the size and shape
and chemical constituents and geometric constituents of the tape, the CD or the vinyl record.
He cannot tell you what is being encoded there.
Let's say it's, I don't know, Bach, the composer.
And you say, well, look, you know, you give me all this information, but can't you see
that this is just, you know, some classical music?
And he says, no, I can't see it with all my research.
So you take out if it's a CD, put in a CD player or computer.
If it's a record album, you play it on a phonograph, you know, record a turntable.
And if it's a magnetic tape, you run it through that appropriate machine and all of a sudden
it starts to play music.
Because now you have the spirit of the material information coming through what it was designed
to be played through.
So the spirit is completely intangible.
So when you're holding, let's say, even one of these, well, now it's all MP3 players on the
phones and computers, that is completely intangible unless you have an analog interface with it.
And you start playing the music.
If you look at a music file in a computer, it just bits and bytes.
You can't tell it's music, well, unless it's, of course, identified as such in the labeling
somehow or you're familiar with the code until it's played.
And each song or track that you have from various artists or whatever sound different and convey
different information, that's how the spirit is.
The spirit is purely the mind.
And by the way, the type of spirit that the humans and most creatures on the earth have is
in order for it to be animated or plugged in or working, you must have a living body
and a living soul, something that is animated.
So that is a simple definition.
And by the way, if the spirit is removed from the physical body with a functioning soul,
does the person die?
And this might be a little advanced, but I can say no very confidently.
You can have someone that has a soul and a living body and not have a spirit.
It is possible.
I think there's still something there.
An example of the spirit going into disanimation is sleep.
Sleeping without dreaming.
You go to sleep whether you're sleeping for four hours, six hours, eight hours, you wake up.
There is no concept of the magnitude of time because the spirit is completely disanimated.
But the soul is still functioning.
If the soul is disanimated, then the body asphyxiaates and starts going into chemical decomposition
or rots and it can easily be declared dead.
So again, I haven't gone into the body much, but the soul again is your breath and metabolism,
which is all the other functions that are used to define something that is fit and alive.
And the spirit is the mental capability or mental functioning, which is the personality
and the character of that being.
And it's actually more unique because the spirit is discreet to that being where the soul
is not.
So to give another degree of interchangibility is you can have organ transfer in a human,
from human to human, as long and even when one of the humans, their soul dies and the body
dies before it goes into chemical decomposition, that part of the body can be animated in another
living soul, where the spirit as far as we know cannot.
Of course, again, this might be a little advance for this part of the talk, but when you hear
of demonic or possession when someone is possessed, that would be another spirit in someone
else's body and their spirit is put into disanimation.
But that we can get into that later.
So those are the three definitions or the definitions of the soul and the spirit and the
body.
And I hope this encourages people to look into it a little deeper and see what kind of
confusion has been laid out in ambiguity and it is deliberate, by the way.
It was deliberate a long time ago and we can talk about why it's deliberate and how obviously
deliberate to prevent the meaning of those things to be known.
So I'm going to yield and anything else?
I should, you know, any further comments on what I've just said?
Yeah, I mean, we're going to dig into it a bit more narrowly.
Thank you for the monologue, Greek.
It certainly does take a load off of me having to come up with questions to cover the topics.
But I take it that these aren't thoughts that you've pulled from your fancy.
Like what sources have you found that offer the most reliable pathway into researching
these things that you get it from esoteric writings or philosophical treatises or...
Not at all, but just by observation.
In other words, if you're driving down the street and you see white lines in the road and
yellow lines, how did they come up with that?
I don't need to go and speak to the people.
How did they make a white line in the road and a yellow line in the road?
I know enough about paint that if you need the yellow paint, you just add a tint to the
white and it becomes yellow.
You see, it's a very simple way to approach anything.
If you know enough about something, you could know more about other things and how it's being
applied and used.
I think I gave enough examples on how to discover this...
How I think the examples that I gave embody the discovery, the elements of discovery as
well.
But out of all the ancient material, what traditions would you say have best preserved
those definitions or depictions of spirit and soul on their own?
All of them.
There's no definition why the sky is blue.
And they tell people in graduate classes still that the sky is blue because of the reflect
of the water from the oceans.
So ridiculous, right?
That's color theory.
We can explain that and how did you come up with that?
It's color theory.
If you understand how things are defined and how they should be defined based on their
usage, especially when it's common cross-culturally and cross-time, right?
And by the way, it's being misused in a frantic way and interchanged.
Even if you look up the definition of spirit and soul, they interchange them.
And it's a deliberate mix-up.
It's a deliberate ambiguity.
But I mean, I guess the way that someone might discredit that is to say, "Well, then this
guy is just going off of anecdotal evidence in what he says is his own observation, which
is somewhat subjective, and maybe it isn't intuitive what he's saying."
But like, really, you didn't go to any sources.
It's a simple way to discredit it at your own demise and at your own willful ignorance
if you discredit it.
You're welcome to discredit it.
I invite people to consider these things, these examples, and what I just mentioned.
I don't think they will.
One percent of the people that hear this will consider it, and one percent of those people
will actually see it.
And that goes with pretty much any subject matter.
So this is not to get credit or anything or to argue about it.
If you feel that the way it's been defined and you define it is fine, then do it at your
own apparel.
Meaning you won't be able to see anything else.
I mean, in any other work that common words that have been mixed up.
Look, a simple way to look at it is the definition of the word "nice" and how it's being
used and what it really means.
What's your source on that?
Where do we go find the source of that?
Well, etymology, even a regular dictionary, which is not meant to give deep meaning.
It's just meant to give diction, right?
How to pronounce the word?
Still says stupid and foolish, many of them.
But it's turned around to be used as pleasant.
So those are the three components that make up any living being.
Even if you have plants and grow a garden, you'll notice one tomato plant has a different
character than the one next to it.
And I'm talking about a tomato garden that you've seeded and grown at the same time.
There's this very fine spirit in that as well.
The spirit is the essence, meaning the personality, character, information.
It's pure information animated through the body and the soul.
And the source on that is a good rational thought, a good rational investigation.
That's the source.
The source is too many sources.
All the sources state that.
When you start to get into what's called academia or a scholastic study and all that, that's
what you're going to find in the ambiguity because it's a very heavily protected area.
And I've said this is probably the fourth or fifth time I've said that.
The reason why it's important, the definition of those three things that make up most living
things, if not all living things, are ambiguous.
Because if you know, if you get a grasp on one or two, maybe you're okay, but if you get
a grasp on all three, you're not going to put up with a lot of, quote unquote, BS because
you're going to be able to define your being.
It's very important not to be able to define yourself.
You know, if you're going to, in other words, it's very important that the population at
large cannot define itself if it is, it should be controlled.
Right?
Go ask anyone to define anything.
It doesn't matter what level of education they have difficulty with it and they always go
it's the opinion is is is promoted, but truth and definition is frowned upon just like the
anti intellectual sentiment.
Well, then I think we'll dig into specifically what these two things are at a bit of a deeper
level and I will say as sort of my own exhortation to sort of mirror what you've just gone
through that when you dig into these things, yeah, the choice of the words kind of becomes
a little less important than the concept behind them because it's like soul in English from
what I'm finding it doesn't linguistically trace back to what the academics say that
soul is in Greek or Hebrew and I don't think that there's any way to find consistency
in the linguistical lineages of those words because they switch from language to language
sometimes.
So the concept of the Greek is laid out is certainly more helpful than to get bogged down in the
dogma of the etymology.
When they speak about soul in the English and spirit, they're usually giving a qualitative
theme.
They never give a quantitative theme or a delineating theme.
That's part of the ambiguity.
Yes, I have noticed that also.
He is a bad soul or he is a good soul, but they can't define soul.
So I just tell him shut up and sit in the corner for about five minutes and rewind what the
Greek just said and listen to it about a hundred times.
Yes, well, hopefully if you're just a little sharp, you won't need a hundred times, maybe
one to twice will be fine.
Yeah, actually after the third time, if you don't get it, you should move on to something
else like Walt Disney or whatever.
So let's start with this spirit then as a sort of deep dive.
The word that gets rendered is that in the Semitic languages is Ruak and then once
you get into the Greek and the Latin, it kind of goes off in different directions, Latin
I found has two very similar words for spirit and soul, which is anima, which I found to
be the life breath and animus, meaning the mind.
And I think that that created some confusion even for the Romans because Cicero writes one
of his books, some would say the soul or the spirit is the anima.
So I think that the reversal of meanings may have occurred in the Latin translations
of Greek writings where mind and life breath gets switched around.
So now the academics will tell you that penuma means spirit and psyche in Greek means soul.
How are you able to detect that something wasn't right in the definitions?
Did someone bring that to your attention?
No, is it just again observation?
Never.
It never brought to my attention if someone did, I wouldn't be speaking and I would say
go listen to that person.
The only reason I do sonic events, I call them sonic events is because I'm ashamed to
be human at this point and because no one else is saying these things.
I better say it so no one will point to finger at me later, say hey you knew this and you
didn't say anything.
I have no responsibility to be in this position is basically for my own skin if need be.
It goes into the meme that I used to pose and say if you do good for selfish reasons
well it's still good, isn't it?
So I would suggest that the perfect example of the ambiguity and just the sheer ignorance
that seems to be the convention, remember it's an anti-intellectual society is that the
very simple rule that the PSY prefix is used to have to do anything with the mind solidifies
that argument or that example quite well.
Anything with the PNU prefix has to do with the movement of air solidifies that argument
and is paramount in example as well.
And those terms were the PSY and the PNU meaning psyche and pneuma meaning air or soul were
specifically chosen and are super consistent in the English as they are in the Greek by
the way even though the translations have been played around with enough that no one even
considers that they have been so screwed up.
Yeah I think it's interesting how that consistency stays in the English and you find it in
the Greek but then when you go to the in between languages like particularly Latin it
disappears and I think that becomes a point of criticism like well within the Greek itself
the Greek convention has been within the Greek not how it's used in the English but the
Greek within the Greek has been passed around like a cheap prostitute or a cheap whore.
In other words what's left in Greek is rubbish unless you go back into the older the last
thing you're going to find anything worthwhile in the Greek is maybe in the fifth century.
Everything else after that has been screwed around with and just to add prestige.
What's the stuff that you read has been has gone from Greek to Latin to English back to Latin
back to Greek just to have prestige.
It's kind of played out.
There is an empirical definition of these terms that has been transmitted in the English
where psyche has to do with the mind and pneuma or soul has to do with the movement of air.
That has been kept and kept relevant and consistent which is correct by the way.
When I say past around like a cheap whore how many times have you heard of oh socrates said
Plato said by Thagorean said and people you can say anything to an American if you have
a British accent because they find it to be wonderful right.
That aspect of the psyche of the American or the western psyche if you're speaking
in the English you have to if someone you know appears with the Queen's English well they're
vastly superior of course.
So they're vastly so it the knowledge is vastly superior if it's presented with a Greek
quote but you know people think all these philosophers were so good but because of what they
what's been put in front of them through you know popular culture but if they actually study
a lot of these philosophers they're very mis-entropic by the way in other words they did not
like the public they thought the public was vile and did not care about their edification
whatsoever.
So again it's just it's just crap.
You know it's funny you should mention that they how mis-entropic some of the philosophers
would be we'll get into that a bit later because I found some interesting stuff from that
as well but yeah so the Greek is what it is in terms of the Latin I found based on reading
commentaries and some interlinear versions of Virgil's writing that yes that the anima
meant the mind or what the psychologist called the psyche today and even in languages like
French and German they have words for spirit that are synonymous with mind like the French
Esperie meaning mental faculties but do you have any idea or inkling as to why sometimes
things get very ambiguous in Latin translations like even the bible is known for being notorious
and its problems with the Latin vulgar.
Okay let's just take the King James as an example if anyone does their research which is
getting harder and harder as time goes on I'll bring up that when you say the bible I'm
going to bring up the King James King James was not even a king of England he was called
the king because he was the top man but he was considered a region he had no nobility
within the within the the British crown system and I'm talking about the crown then not
the crown now which is different he was Scottish I believe and he came in to fill in because
there was a blank spot he wanted to perform some kind of act that would drive a wedge between
the monarchy and the common people and that wedge was very simple instead of deifying the
nobility and the royalty in England or the British Empire.
Let's make a cheap readily available version of the bible notice not a translation but
a version that will be spread around and create not not just have one godhead which would
be the the king or the queen but will have another godhead known as just god right god
will have god satan a couple of demons a couple angels and Jesus and that's what we're going
to throw in to throw a wedge because the people had no access to this it was in Latin it
was forbidden to study right prior to King James so he did that as a project and it was
not just him it was named after him to throw drive a wedge into society that would never
recover because when you have a common plebeian common oaf common quote-unquote citizen or
subject that has no knowledge of the spiritual world other than some vague ancient superstition
they will always view their nobility and the royalty as their god they may not say that's
my god but they sure give all of their you know in spiritual intent in that direction so
giving them a version a really poor version by the way mixed up version with a lot of satanic
quote-unquote symbolism in it to the people will drive a wedge that will it will never recover
from and also drive a wedge into the emperor and to the Vatican as well which you know are
malevolent institutions like it or not or no it or not so was it a good thing yeah I was kind
of a good thing to drive a wedge I guess but is is the King James Bible a good thing no it's
not it's a political tool now I'm not going to get into what they did in the King James they
wanted too much but for example how the Latin plays a role in this is they they wanted
to say formally and informally and statistically that their New Testament was translated from Greek
text and they couldn't find any so they found the Latin text which they translated back into Greek
which then they translated into English so so it's like making a copy of a copy and then another
copy of that with on different machines on different days as you're walking in the rain so it's
just really not good but here's the thing the the lot of people have mentioned the holographic
analogy of the biblical text no matter how much you try to screw it up if you're paying attention the
the general meaning the general correct meaning not the specific meanings but the general correct
meaning comes through like for example if you read the King James as it is without an interlinear and
without really looking to many definitions you will see that what Judaism Christianity all the
sisters of Christianity and the thousand versions of say those three or four major ones or whatever or
or the versions of Judaism they're supposed to be in the Old Testament are all incorrect none of
them are based on the biblical text they say they are but they're not so even if you just adhere to
the King James version you it would be a good a good enough reason to abandon what's known as the
conventional religions right so that's what I mean about the holographic nature of it if you actually go
beyond the King James and do some study on the on the let's say oldest preserved texts you will not
only abandon any religion conventional religion but you will find it to be repugnant I just wanted to
put that out there because that's the moral of the story well I mean yeah I feel like we got wrapped
up in the Bible tangent I didn't mean to overemphasize that but in this case I did want to also look at
the way that you know specifically before the King James you had the Latin vulga just being such a
wealth of disinformation that I think fed back into the King James also there's certain words that
you know like the Lucifer convention it's so ridiculous that it even exists but it comes up in the
Latin from seemingly nowhere and I think that that plays into this idea of spirit and soul being
interchanged that something must have happened where people just weren't paying attention with that
language right just because something has endured thousands of years doesn't mean it's true or
correct right because ultimately the gist of having these talks is to make people aware that
formative beings known as the gods the angelic realm the you know the realm of the gods they're
not born and they don't live and they don't die like humans do a thousand years to them is like a
day to us or to most of them so if you screw up for a day that's things being screwed up for a thousand
years if you screw up for two days it's two thousand years if you screw up for three days it's three
thousand years and so on and so forth so things can stay screwed up for a hundred thousand years
that wouldn't be a big deal right so don't fall for that right the what makes it easy to become
mis-unthropic is that how the majority of the people on this planet both that have lived and died
and what that are still alive and ones that aren't alive that are coming do not so much as even lift
a finger to consider anything that you know we've just brought up on on this sonic that's what makes
it so easy to be mis-unthropic there's sheer apathy and you know they just revel in their ignorance
because that's the norm right just like if you went to an island of cannibals that's the norm
so anyway to go back to the latin I wouldn't lean heavily on the latin at all
because the latin goes in many directions it's very secular it's used in in art in it's used in
in the quote-unquote legal system because it's designed to confuse right and deceive and it's
part of the Roman convention and the Roman convention if one objectifies earth history is a very small
aspect of it you know the near east and far east and non-latin european is far more influential
on human society than the Roman convention it just seems to be the most propagated one at the moment
and for the past couple of hundred years let's say or more let's say 500 years again which if you
if you learn to think in thousand year swaths of time you'll see things more clearly also
well let's wrap up the subjects of the spirit just by looking a little bit at what the
semitical literature says about it as far as ruac so on one hand you've talked about ruac or the
spirit being related to the mind or the person themselves but you you can't really avoid the
parallelisms in languages like latin Hebrew Greek and even the proto-inter European where
the spirit and you did mention this all have this sort of air related inflection right so it's not
just a cognitive thing and if we look even in the biblical text Genesis 7 everyone who had the
breath of the spirit of life in his nostrils they all died in the flood right so not just the
spirit of life but the breath of the spirit of life you know I know in the new testament the
Christ talks about the the wind a bit and as far as the the power of the the most high god being
something similar to that can you expand a little bit on what the relationship is between the
ruac and the the wind I've never really been able to put that together well the wind it's very
simple there is something in the new testament where nicodemus approaches the christ and there's
something about being born again not a woman or flesh but of the spirit which is like the wind
it's like the wind many times people get confused you know where where it says you know his
hair was as white as wool he didn't it wasn't like wool it was just as white as wool right so it could
have been straight air we don't know it's just the color so it's the comparison of the wind is the
an ancient times was that you don't see the wind you just see its effect it's kind of like the radio
waves in the ether which are penetrating they're penetrating waves right whether you have the whether
you're either side of the wall your cell phone will receive for television or radio right they're
penetrating waves right you you don't see them or feel them but when you have the proper device
it will animate that and you'll get the information that is penetrating along with that wave right
the spirit is very much the same way it's a thought form it's information the the the in for example
you have a creator who created all things so the spirit that went behind into making the mountain
or the ocean is a different spirit that went into making man or the fox or the wolf or the elephant
meaning a different mindset imagine someone who has ten different hobbies with ten non-related sub you
know unrelated things there is a different mindset with each one you can have a hobby of playing tennis
miniature trains aquarium fish growing fish and all three things are completely unrelated
but you're the same spirit or the different spirit when you're applying a different
part of your spirit with the spirit of the miniature train the aquarium or the spirit of playing tennis
you hear you see the word being used in that intangible ethereal way i'm saying ethereal
because it's intangible we don't know what it is but we see its effect so you see things the spirit of
right just you could add anything to it you'll see it used in in english language constantly
in the spirit of such and such right it's a mindset when you when you say that it relates to a
particular character a particular personality a particular way it's just like you can walk into a
record store if you took all the sleeves all the labels off the vinyl and stacked up all the vinyl
records from florida ceiling and the whole back wall they're indesernable from each other until you
play them you need a labeling on them right and an album cover to see what's inside but if even if
you remove the labeling that doesn't change the spirit it doesn't change what's been recorded on them
yes i follow you there um i've also noticed just a wrap up on this spirit topic that the ruaq
also gets used to talk about people in emotional terms sometimes like numbers five like if a spirit
of jealousy passes over him so that he's jealous of his wife blah blah blah now it seems to be
referring to a ruaq that almost is almost like external that comes in and inflicts an emotional
or psychological condition like what's that about well a spirit would be a spirit like for example
the most high god is a spirit the angels are a spirit but you know if you said an angel came by and
gave him that kind of a feeling or emotion you'd say it was an angel right but an angel is a spirit but
we don't consider it much such because he's a multi not a multi purpose is he's a spirit like a
postman he just delivers messages right and does things also like a postman you know can turn off
the water hose if you lift for god it running but his main main job is to be a postman so that spirit of
jealousy is instead of an angel which is to be a messenger to humans this spirit of jealousy is just
the spirit of jealousy that's his job like you know someone who's a painter house painter that's your
job on my house painter or a hair cutter or a chef a cook that's the spirit you see that's their single
job and just harken back to all those ancient primitive native people right they they had they
pay tribute ritualistic tribute to the spirit of the river or the spirit of the bear or the spirit
of the sky the spirit of fire the spirit right everything in material world and let's say the earth
has a spiritual counterpart to it okay so i can active element that's associated with that thing
that's sentient right right but it's non-material which is very difficult to for people to contemplate
when you let's go back to the beginning of what i said that you live in an anti-intellectual
society i would wager with anyone listening or will listen to this that if you start approaching
anyone that you know family friends co-workers whatever on this planet about looking into these
things are 99% of the people your approaches will will reject it and their criticism of you
wanting to pursue these things is you're going too deep that stuff will make you crazy oh no one
cares about that those are the typical you know how you know what things that you're going to get
being in this society right so again when you're listening to this if you're going to contemplate
these things you're going to be part of a very elite group but but not here you know in other words
the more you study and the more you learn of it in a simple rational way there's a guy on youtube
called ken wheeler he talks about magnetism brilliant on the magnetic stuff in whatever he's very
Buddhist by the way um he says nature is very simplistic nature is not this you know a crack
whore with a calculator she's got hairy legs and hairy armpits and she's got dirt under her fingernails
and she's very simple you know mother nature right kind of thing and he's absolutely correct about
that so there's a spirit behind that as well there's a spirit of simplicity there's a spirit of
wisdom you know the i don't even say the word so fear because the no sticks have overused it talk
about a group of you know people that try too hard right no sticks but anyway they have no knowledge
that's the that's the interesting thing of it it's like when you when they when they talk about
making the environment better you know in general in society that means they're fixing
undesteroing it when they when there's a group formed for economic recovery or economic progression
that means they're going to destroy the economy when you have a group that says they hold knowledge
like the no sticks means they're going to destroy knowledge right so bear that in mind when you
ever you see an organized group so anyway i've been i've been going back and forth within the subject
matter and outside of the subject matter to show people that they need to relax about these things
do their homework go cut down to the root right get down to the base of it and um look at how
these things are being used in their initial meaning if you if you're a Christian or Jewish or
you know any of the major religions you think there's only one god and one angel or two couple of
angels sorry because there if you mentioned and a Messiah and that's it it's really lonely with a
lot of tumbleweeds and stuff you're you've been deceived the the non the spiritual world yes i
said spiritual world and non-corporal beings as we consider them to be corporate what is
corporeal or physical is if not trillions of millions and billions of times and trillions of times
more populated than the physical world it is extremely dense in other words if you could see into
that world the sky would be blacked out that's how many beings would be over us and and if you're in
a let's say a regular sized room if you were to see in the spiritual room it would be shoulder to
shoulder completely full from floor to ceiling from beings that are a millimeter tall to beings that
are ten times taller than your house outside this is not a time for people to be aware of these
things because contemplating this does not help you in this in this existence right now well cool
let's move on to the soul aspect as far as looking at a few things more um pointedly so yeah there
seem to be consensus in ancient Greece that penuma refers to a related phenomena um in stoic
philosophy they claim that the penuma was this active generative principle that organized not only
the human being but the whole universe by structuring matter i don't know if they went overboard with
that but i didn't want to ask like what you know about that idea because it's a reoccurring motive
in fantasy narratives that the biological world draw some kind of sustenance from like a global
life stream and i'm wondering if maybe there's a connection there well the problem with looking
into that is how well are you versed in ancient or classical Greek and if you say no then you're
subject to the versions that are put out um there's enough empire in the world that its intent was
to control people by making keeping them miserable that also is part of the academic world
so there's no way you're going to uh get what the stoic said unless you were able to find
the oldest preserved document endeavoured into it in its original language i assure you 99% of the
time what's being given to you as a translation is not correct it's corrupted for specific reasons
it's like for example reading the laws of your country and then watching uh your local you know
watching the news bbc or cnn to tell you what the law says completely different
or what a lawyer will tell you the losses they're going to take out the parts that they want right
and leave out the rest but in essence uh what the stoics did like many other Greeks they went on
kind of i i maybe i'm not part of that tradition but i like giving examples to illustrate and
demonstrate the mindset behind the definition or the the word or the subject matter
very often in ancient times you would read some of the philosophers i can't give a specific
example but it seems to be a generality uh they they would give a metaphor an example and then give
a metaphor an example for the for the metaphor in the example and the reader if it doesn't he
doesn't follow it to what degree the explanation has expanded into will get lost but in essence to answer
your question they i think they i don't think they went too far i think they just elaborated to the
point where it it over overlaps the creative force which things were made but the subtleness of
defining it as air related activity and the spirit being like the wind are completely two different
things and its analogy whether it's by design or not to throw off what these things mean it
exist still exists by the way because the spirit being compared to its action being like the action
of the wind will very easily confuse a simpleton when he looks over at the soul being with air-related
phenomenon and when i say simpleton i mean that in a in a in a in a in a in its fundamental sense
not as a pejorative okay this is a simple person simple layman yes right and and that's why that's
where see if you can confuse the simple layman then you've succeeded because 99% of the people
have been brought up in a society where they just need to work and if they don't work one specific narrow
aspect of the society to get food and shelter they're going to die you see that's a simple tin right
that's this you know the the modality that most people have and also the simple tin is very trusting
in naive so if he a simple tin wants to know let's say about the stars he'll go to an astrophysicist
and of course they're their astrophysicist of course they know right and you know if you study
after what they saying that's all bunk same with a doctor same with a priest or a rabbi or you know
a lawyer they're all bunk it's whatever is the whatever they're showing on TV they have to portray
as being the reality you know it's backwards it's why I tell people why bother going to college
just watch tv because they can't show something on tv that's contrary to what they're teaching in
college and the tv is more important than the college so the college just textbooks are just
based on what they show you on tv it's all bunk now i'm starting to sound like the ancient Greek
philosophers it's all bunk even all the show me a Greek philosopher that didn't say that everything
they teach in school is a lie all of them did yeah and we're still going to get into the the way
that some of them operated because it was quite interesting how they said one thing in private and
then a different thing to the masses but just to stay on the subject of the stoics or the stoics
by the way just to interrupt they very rarely related to the masses it's what their critics
and their other followers said to the masses uh uh my Greek philosophers at heart avoided the masses
they yeah i just want to put it in interject that in there they never interacted well they might have
but it might it would be kind of like what i do if i'm interacting with the masses inside of
necessity so the penuma for the stoics was this mixture of moving air and fire or slash warmth
which kind of work together to generate this vital principle that they talk about and so
in their mind the idea is that you have this union of heat and moisture which has positive health
effects where the opposite is that when things dry up and become cold that signifies death like what
happens with the corpse or a dead plant like do you know anything about that sort of wet warm cold
dry process to elaborate on that at all well in this part of the let's say universe there's a certain
temperate we call temperate zone that things tend to exist in for example you can you know the elephant
the room analogy there could be life forms in things and emerging from things that are considered
azoic meaning without life they're just not acknowledged just like for example if you look at
contemporary chemistry there are there are many more chemical compounds and elements that are
acknowledged in their were let's say 300 years ago so is it proper to deny that their existence 300
years ago no but it seemed to right i think of that discussion is a little bit more elaborate if we
get into what we call like the ether study or ether technology or the very super ultra fine aspects
of existence we could bring up the warmth and cold combinations because i have much to say about
that as well but if you have a deep understanding or even not a deep understanding of water and how
it's an anomalous liquid right you will see that the it's it's hand in hand with what you just asked
all right cool and so again like we did with spirit i think the last thing to just touch on here is
the somatic aspect when we turn to that usage the word nefesh comes to encompass the soul but again
when you look in the biblical text it seems to get a bit broad at some points like in some statements
it seems to refer to the entire living person like genesis 12 Abraham took his wife Sarah and every
nefesh or soul that they acquired and went into the land of canon at other points it seems to
refer to corpses that have no pnuma in them number six in all the days of his dedication to yawaii
he shall not come near a dead soul so unlike the the Greeks who just really seem to focus on the
respiration aspect the nefesh seems to encompass living things dead things but that doesn't create
a quandary for the definition though does it oh absolutely not if you had something that was
functioning a certain way like a car junkyard or the cars are dead cars you can't deny that those
dead cars work or cars you know they have fuel pumps and they were once running around the you
are being driven around the roads right you you know it's the same thing in other words they're
they're dead in their nefesh because they have everything that qualifies and quantifies them to
be a binous soul and then we get it and then we get into the aspect of the radical concept of
you know the the afterlife for reincarnation or the resurrection which are all the same
which that's where the definition of soul starts to become more elaborate and wider use because
it's in comparison the life when you reincarnated resurrected or the afterlife the the current
definition and actual practical usage of what's called a soul and a body is going to seem rather
crude and futile so that's another discussion perhaps yes i think we will touch on the afterlife
aspect of that because you have another slant to the word where nefesh a nefesh can descend into the
underworld or shield as the Israelites would call it it sometimes depicts the remnant of fallen
warriors there which is an interesting parallel to the north myths that talk about Valhalla but like
Ezekiel 31 they will also descend into shield those slain by the sword and its armed forces
and then you also have non warrior people that end up there so it becomes a little hard to know
exactly what the domain is but it's said that the nefesh can descend into the unseen or into the
shield does that raise any questions for you because if this is really just relating to the metabolism
why is it into the underworld well if it's a negative place a place of torment whether the endurance
or the duration of the torment is another factor to consider but you if the torment is to torment
something with a body you will be incarnated with a body to be tormented right so it may not be a
complete body that you need on the surface but it's enough of a body nonetheless because the spirit
is body less it's material less and again this type of spirit that we have as far as we know
it goes into complete disanimation in animation all right when there is a lack of a soul in a body
just like if you ask someone like Jack Fresco said you know if you want to know what happens after you
die what do you remember from 500 years ago nothing it's just in that you are not animated then it doesn't
mean you did not exist you just were not animated just like again like go into an old record shop
where vinyl records are sitting in the basement for 50 years you know those last times something somebody
heard that right 50 years ago that's been quiet since so again animating someone in another place
is completely plausible and possible and doable but they have to be animated you need some kind of a
body okay so let's wrap up the stream by talking a bit about the things that I you touched on
before as far as how the philosophers acted and also how that ties into the afterlife because I
think the idea that most people carry around with regards to the human spirit is that it's this immortal
essence that lives on after death and either goes to heaven or hell or gets reincarnated but according
to the Greek historian Herodotus it was the Egyptians who put this idea into circulation and I'm
just going to read a condensed snippet from his book called histories that talks about that so
quote the Egyptians were the first to maintain the following doctrine that the human soul is immortal
and after passing through all creatures of land see in air it enters once more into the human body
at birth a cycle that it completes every three thousand years and there are Greeks who have
used this doctrine as if it were their own end quote so obviously he uses soul interchangeably
with spirit well as far as far as we can recover in the English yes if you can go back and see the
oldest surviving document of what he said I beg you to consider that it what you wouldn't be
reading it that way yes you're right I should have actually made that note so in Greek it would
have probably been Seiki and that would have been correct what if your sort of studies or research
revealed on how you know the immortal soul concept came to be taught by all religions as something
universal well in a sense it's a distraction if you look at what you know any of these religions
do is to distract you right through belief very simple doesn't it sound a lot better that you have
a urn immortal soul which is not even the right definition doesn't it make you feel better so you go
back to work yeah that's the one way to look at it it seems more optimistic than telling people the
truth well the truth is the most optimistic but you have to give them the whole truth and that takes
too long because the full read already wasted twelve thousand hours in government school or private
school how are people think they're so proud because they went to a good university or private school
what fools anyway if you're not self-educated you're not educated so you've got to keep them optimistic
because they're already worn out twelve years of a crap they don't want it they've had enough
now it's time to have fun get drunk have sex you know sleep get you know new toys I'm not even going
to touch the subject of the immortal soul because we just define soul so it would be the immortal spirit
it's it it's not that the spirit dies it goes into disanimation there's no decomposition like
the body when it dies when the soul dies it ceases to function that's how you kill it right so
through the body by the way so if you contemplate the first fifteen minutes of the sonic event
were the definitions that i gave little answer all that stuff but you have to be a contemplative person
a contemplative person will look at you know if someone looks at a menu and it's beans potatoes
bread pasta they'll say oh look at all these choices but if someone's contemplative they'll
look at that and they'll say oh that's all starch hmm well do you have any thoughts on in the similar
way i think to the way that the latin seems deliberately mental obscure things the the
Egyptians seem to have thrown a lot of falsehoods into the mix that have been able to persist even
to this day let me let me just interject something in there invite you to consider that those that are
prevailing and providing what the Egyptians supposedly said are doing it i don't think the Egyptians did
i think the Egyptians were far more enlightened and far more dedicated to what they were doing
and i don't i don't think it was direct directly in line with uh let's say the the most high god
that's why when you read an exodus the purpose of everything you read about an exodus was to war
with the Egyptian gods but i think the Egyptians uh had had pretty much together i wouldn't say that
when you compare them to other societies it wouldn't be considered moral or or let's say well what do
you justified but they were correct within their own system and if you look at it carefully you'll see
that they interweave between the lives of the gods and human lives and how they aspire to be like
the gods and all of a sudden they have a neuronal spirit you see where we know later on uh that the
spirit cannot is not immortal see when when the spirit becomes disanimated it's just disanimated
but it can be destroyed like uh you know in other words you can have a computer i have several of them
with hard drives that something in the hardware went bad and i can't access the computer if i take
out the the information on the computer but if i remove the hard drive i can i can animate the hard
drive through another device and get the information you see that's what happens when you die or before
you were alive but what you can also do is corrupt and destroy that hard drive
right so is that killing no people were corrupting and destroying so the spirits can be destroyed
whether they're they can be destroyed what while they're being animated while they're animated or
while they're in the you know downloaded and disanimated just like walking into a room that has
files you know computer files you know on on discs and destroying that room they wouldn't say
it's killing the spirit because the spirit you cannot kill a spirit it's either disanimated or
not animated and then it could be destroyed it's so information can you kill your hard drive no
it's either animated or not animated and but you can destroy it so the information is lost yes
i follow you and i also think it's worth highlighting this thing that you talked about a bit earlier
that the reason for so much confusion and obfuscation with regards to this subject is that the
religious and philosophical leaders had a habit of lying to the common people or telling the truth
only to the elites and not really caring about the masses and i just wanted to quote some a text
from the Greek historian polybius which i thought was interesting in his book the histories
which is quote it is the very thing which among other people is an object of reproach that is
superstition which maintains the cohesion of the roman state they have adopted this course for
the sake of the common people it is a course which perhaps would have not been necessary had it
been possible to form a state composed of wise men but as every multitude is full of lawless desires
and violent anger the multitude must be held in by invisible terrors and peasantry for this
reason i think not that the ancients acted rashly in introducing among the people notions concerning
the gods and beliefs in the terrors of haides and quote so it's true why not or a pandemic that
right or viruses that you know that you know or or or terrorists right it's got to be a verb
that becomes an adjective which becomes a noun and it's all fiction fiction if you want to know
the effects of fiction well set up a camera facing the audience at a movie theater and watch their
faces while they're watching that fiction project you know on call the movie or a television right
and imagine their whole life is in that position kind of like Plato's cave right so that's all fiction
and again it's been going on for thousands of years which is no big deal it's only a few days
i'd say about a week you'll see here's the thing i don't want anyone to believe what i'm saying because
the Greek is saying it i've actually disconnected relations with people meaning communications and
associations with people that i found out would just saying you know promoting while the Greek
said it's almost be true that's you've got to make it your own by researching and knowing these things
so if you believe in something because someone said it you're in deep doo doo the reason why i say
these things again is so people that are wise will file it away for a more pertinent time
like for example if you look at 99% of all the world events whether it's the sodom quote
quote unquote pandemic or economic or social changes that people are seeing in the pagan year of
2020 i preface this in the past 10 years all of it not specifics like it's going to be done this way
but all of the outcomes including there will be no more of these conventional holidays right the
economic system all this other stuff just to interject this kind of current events they're calling it
about the the new normal for example what you were living before was the new normal because if you
study real world history quote unquote normalcy ended 150 years ago when you they've been putting on
quite the show for the past 150 years and now it's just like why do we need these people are so
apathetic and none of them really even spend a minute in their lives to research anything
you know they want someone to tell them what it what it means it's time that we just pull the plug
on this BS show and start reorganizing this right this is what's happening this year and i've
gone over this and what's what the outcome is going to be is a focus on the Middle East and
as the as the world hub of attention which still hasn't come into fruition but it will by what you
call 2025 so the fakery that's been portrayed and emphasized for the past 150 years is run out of
quote unquote credit and it's run out of impetus there's no reason for it anymore there
actually wasn't any reason for it ever but there's just the way the higher forces allowed it to be
so it is so i just want to remind people that if anyone here has ever been listening to
greek speak for more than let's say a few years you you know exactly what's going on and where
it's going to lead to meaning human society and it has nothing to do with how much you can
endure but it's just how much you know when when things are meant to happen yeah we've talked
about these things a little bit before but there's always room to delve into them a little bit more
it's also evident to me that you know the greek did sort of a similar things like the Romans had done
obviously history speaks very highly of Pythagoras but it was known that he had sort of like one
teaching for his inner circle and i think the christian writer origin talked about that when he wrote
Pythagoras divided his disciples into classes the one he called esoteric and the other he called
exoteric the former he trusted the more perfect and sublime doctrines into the latter the more
popular and vulgar and similar things are said about Plato strabal wrote that Plato quote unquote
unvents fables also on the immortality of the spirit and on punishment and hate these end quote
and so i point all that out just to emphasize that these notions were sort of debated like way
before Christianity in the christians didn't even really adopt them as far as like immortality of
the spirit it took like centuries of nostic and roman catholic influence for those things to become
dogman mm-hmm well just like let's say a detour again the assyrians of dawned cross crosses in their
costume jewelry or in their day-to-day attire just like christians do today and that was about 900 BC
so it's just a fashion but you know some fashion doesn't have to be a trend trend that that fades it's
you know like look at for example in the automotive i see some car companies are reviving like
the style of cars that they were producing 50 years ago so yeah it's just recycled stupidity
but again you know let me give you an example the humans are not only anti-intellectual but they like
to shed responsibility and more if on a moral point of view for example if you talk to an older person
i'd say all most of the most of the older people if not all of them that are supposed to be respected
and have wisdom yeah right they'll tell you well i won't be around for that so you know i don't
care i won't be alive for that right i mean times that you heard that yeah so there's no
responsibility pretty much with anyone whether it's moral ethical intellectual that you'll find
young or old so it seems like there's a mindset an overarching theme to society because if you go
to older people and you say well if we don't do something the future generations will be you know thus
we'll say well i don't care i'm not going to be here for that they almost always say that almost all
of them if you find an older person that doesn't say that it's extremely rare so if you you know
you almost say that none of them really have any moral or ethical responsibility so so there seems
to be an overarching being something that is guiding this where even the the older the leader is one
what should those that are senior in your society at best are still lacking of any morality ethics
or responsibility but there is something that is carrying this on you see yeah i have noticed
that it's hard to really it's like some kind of group think or some kind of like mass think that's
really hard to put your finger on right in other words the the seniority in your society is still infantile
compared to with being that considers the way society operates for thousands of years is part of
its life in other words you have a being on the earth a spirit or a mindset that is supposed to
be a certain way for a long time where most people don't notice and it evades them even though they're
partaking and supporting it in other words when you run into an older person and you tell them about
possible future outcomes and they retort by saying well i don't care because i won't be here then
well what good are they they're supposed to be the bastions of wisdom and experience and guidance
for society and they're pretty worthless right that's why they pump them up with drugs and slap
diapers on them and sticking them nursing homes you know so it's well deserved obviously you know
so what i'm trying to say here is that the things that are that people are seeing are the results of
a life form that is not human because how can a human even at the end of their lives where it's
touted through tradition they are the ones to go to for guidance have no guidance light at all there
is dark is at the bottom of your shoe so in other words when i'm trying to say is humanity for a long
time has been passed off to the side and is a side note because generation after generation no one
seems to care so there's something alive that has a life that is that is a life of the things that
you see society being for so long that when its life is over a society will cease being that way
see it's no longer wait for the older people to die like an ancient time so things can change
because the older people are already dead they already they died when they were 10 years old 12
years old they got assimilated into this mindset right so there's a there's an over there's
in other words human society said in other words is five times already human society in itself should
be viewed as a life form that it was infantile adolescent mature and then senior and then when that
life goes away which represents human society then that's when you'll have the new human society
on this planet it has nothing to do with the actual spans of people you know older people are younger
people because they're the older people are not any wiser smarter or were able to edify anyone any more
than let's say someone you know a 15 year old with a I was gonna say palm pilot a smartphone right
15 year old with a smartphone is got just as much as wisdom in anything as an 85 year old
you know retired college professor doesn't know anything more than a modern 12 so it shows you that
humanity has been brushed aside in made irrelevant when the elderly are in the way that they are
yes there's a certain melancholy in pondering those things
yeah so you're on your own i tell people and you've been on your own for a long time
okay i think we've gone through most other things that i thought of for this i guess my final
question is like what does the true concept of death then imply to humanity since we know that
the immortality aspect is just farcical at least of the of the spirit like we have she old slash
hidey's and then we have disanimation and what comes after that if not heaven or hell well imagine
you had a die dice right that you throw and there are two numbers instead of six numbers in each dice
with all the combinations of the two dice there was just two numbers so you knew that you read the
throw the two numbers or one or the other combination one or the other very few combinations that's
what life and death is about just hope that when you die it's not painful because you know we don't
like pain right unlike the intobate and culture where they say when you feel pain and you know
relish it because you know if you're experiencing pain it's meant for you to experience in pain
quote unquote experience it and so you know what pain is but in essence what i mean about
rolling the dice with just two numbers is you will be reanimated or you will not you will be
destroyed as far as we can see in the biblical convention the indu convention in the islamic
can actually all the the religious texts what's called loosely religious texts everyone is reanimated
except for a very very small few of both worlds meaning the human world and the non-human world
the gods or demons some will be destroyed but the majority the great majority and the greatest
majority will be reanimated so between now and then just hope that your death isn't painful and
you don't have to suffer a 20th century or 21st century medicine or anything like that
but you're not immortal your soul dies when your body dies and your spirit has nothing to do with
mortality it has to do with being animated or disanimated and destroyed very simple put it together
the faster you put this together the easier you'll be able to make proper adjustments and thoughts
when you're contemplating things cool well thank you greek um yeah i think that covers everything that
we need to talk about in this stream um and yeah i think it's a good note on which to conclude
any closing remarks greek uh no not really uh to be continued perhaps yes of course
we have quite a few more of these left to do um so thank you to everybody who tuned in and we hope
to see you at the next stream
you
[MUSIC]