Greetings to everyone listening and welcome to the first stream of the God's
Speak podcast. I go by the name of the art con and I'm the creator of the website
and this series which I'll be hosting together with a gentleman known as the Greek. He'll
be joining me shortly. This podcast is a follow up to a previous one that was done on a
sister site called Greekspeak.com and it'll build on the subject matter that we covered
in that one. I would recommend that those who haven't taken a look at Greekspeak.com should
do that since it acts as a gateway into the material that you'll find on God's Speak. This
is an introductory episode where the Greek and myself will be highlighting some of the
subjects that will come up throughout the series. I can say a front that much of it is
in the esoteric vein being material that veers away from the conventional narratives
that mainstream media peddles in but it also diverges from much of the conspiracy theory
talk that alternative media cares so much about. A lot of that comes out of the mouths
of self-professed truthers and a lot of his theories when it is truth is often somebody
parroting somebody else so there isn't much room for them to elaborate on things when it's
just conjecture or repetition. That's where this podcast will try to set itself apart by
having the Greek elaborate on things he has first-hand experience with or has researched
himself. With regards to the name of the website God's Speak is just a play on the name of my
other website GreekSpeak which is named after the Greek's unconventional way of talking
about things. The purpose there was to explain things about society which are obvious but
ignored and the purpose with God's Speak as the name suggests is to illuminate the supernatural.
So even if you find the notion of things like God's to be farfetched perhaps your curiosity
will compel you to sit through the podcast and you might end up taking these things more
seriously as we progress. Godspeak.com has no political, religious or corporate affiliations
and is completely managed by myself. Similar de Greeks Speak.com podcast episodes will
be available to download through the Media tab on the website's homepage. And so that's
it for the introduction. Thanks again for tuning in and I hope you enjoy this introductory
episode.
Hello Greek. What's going on with you?
Okay, yeah, we are supposedly on a new project which is an extension of another project and
let's see if we can get it going.
Yeah, I anticipate that things will go just as well as the last one. So this is the podcast
that's going to be looking at the unseen realm of things, the power so to speak that animate
what we see around us which often get mislabeled the superstition or secular occurrences. There's
been times that we touched on that in the Greek Speak podcast but I made an effort to stay
away from it to save it for now. And now that we've graduated to Godspeak, that's going
to be the main focus. The unseen realm of spirits that influences the physical world. You
talk about that a lot. What is it about for most people? It sounds like a load of absurdities
similar to religious nonsense. So why would a man of your distinction entertain such inclinations?
Well, I should say the unseen realm is beyond just unseen. It's uncontemplated. Let's
just say that again. It's not just unseen. It's uncomplated or it's not comprehended.
It's not thought about this particular realm, meaning the unseen realm or let's just spill
out and say the realm of the spirit, the realm of the gods, the realm of the supernatural,
paranormal or ultra-natural is not contemplated by the masses at large, which they don't contemplate
anything anyway. But the point of saying it's not contemplated is when I say something
like it's not thought of, it's unseen or it's not contemplated. I'm actually speaking
about the representative of society, meaning the judges, the lawyers, the leaders, the doctors,
the teachers, the professors, the experts, so on and so forth. Usually when you hear
me make a comment about the masses, I'm not speaking about the billions and billions
at large. I'm speaking about those that lead and guide them. So I just wanted to interject
that. I try not to use a lot of thaves or thams, but I feel that this needs to be addressing
that fine point. Again, the multitude have no meaning whatsoever. Whatever meaning they
have distilled into their lives comes from, yeah, you guessed it. Their judge is attorney's
doctors, teachers, professors, religious leaders, secular leaders, what have you. So again,
I'll be when I refer to the masses, that is the definition that should be applied. So
actually what we're going to be speaking of is directing the point of view towards the
higher aspect of the achievement of human society, meaning quote unquote, higher in air quotes,
those that are the teachers and those that establish the convention is what we're aiming
the criticism if there is any towards. So without derailing the initial question, well,
we can take a very short, you know, cross section of it in modern quote unquote science,
they tell you that ultimately the majority of what exists is not physically perceivable,
which is also stark contrast to the invention of perceivable particles in matter to explain
certain things. And that comes, that stems from an early poppul bull. This can be researched,
there are many poppul bulls, but this is probably during the time of Luther prior to the Gregorian
poppul bull where the Vatican basically ensued its intent to take control of all things, a
mad, that are a matter of spirit or mind. And anything that was to be studied must have
a physical substantive material counterpart. Otherwise, it was a jurisdiction of the Vatican,
and not to be examined publicly or expressed publicly in any other way. And it was to be
controlled by the Vatican. What I mean by that is, for example, the light phenomenon.
Quonon quote natural philosophers of the day are modern scientists cannot discuss the
light phenomenon as what it is a perturbation in the ether. They have to discuss it as a
particle. So they invent a photon, FAUX, T-O-N, and then they can discuss it as a particle.
which is another perturbation in the ether, can not be discussed unless they have a corresponding particle.
So, they invent protons and electrons and things like that. I constantly make fun of them by
repeating experiments that I've done where I've cut an electrical wire with a dust pan and magnifying glass and hand to see the electrons pouring out.
I've never seen that happen. This, let's just say starting off the Vatican when I say the Vatican, it's a political institution.
It has its sovereignty from, I guess, the turn of the century from Mussolini, I guess, that was his job and no one's contended it since.
It is just a pariah in humanity, just like any other aspect of, you know, mind control would be.
You could look at what the intelligence agencies have been doing through years or corner quote certain, you know, despotic governments, despotic religions or whatever, but it is a negative, whatever the negative thing that has been established on the earth.
And this is not what I'm saying is not has nothing to do with what people believe in or their faith has to do with objectivity as if you were to come and visit this planet.
I'm not saying that the Vatican is the sole malevolent force or dictatorial force in within the context of what is real and what is not or the unseen versus the scene there are many others.
But it's the easiest one to show historically and geographically in a way that it is a political body and most people just focus on, you know, what's called politically correct.
So it is not politically correct to actually even ensue that the Vatican is wrong makes it wrong in itself.
So you contrasted a bit the material versus the immaterial and I think that we can say that we live in a world where people are conditioned to place the most faced and the things that they can rationalize by way of their senses.
And so the physical world creates the boundaries for most people's perception. What would you say is the reason behind the disparity between the physical world where academia says that natural processes run on autopilot and the unseen realm where those processes are powered by an invisible sentient component.
Well, that's difficult to answer directly because what is actually the source of the power, the power is the exhibition of work and manifestation of movement in the material world is always an immaterial world.
And as always, an immaterial aspect. You know, let's take a heat, light, electricity, magnetism, those are not material components solely material components in the material world.
These are things that are put in motion and affect the material world whose source of energy, let's just use that point or that term is immaterial.
So let's just discuss what fields are if you want to discuss space versus counter space, which is a negative space. There tends to be a lot of allusion to that in science fiction.
You can understand when you say the mind, right, and are more advanced, let's say discussion.
One can delve into neuropathy, neurology, and the study of the brain. And it's ultimately been concluded that the brain is just a sensory organ that mediates thought and mediates mind power or mediates what we'll find out later or maybe in this discussion.
What we say, spirit is actually mind. It's the character of when we impose it upon a living being and then just like putting a ladle or a bucket into an ocean, removing some water, there is a larger body, a spiritual realm where all of these minds would be tapping into.
It will be perhaps developing that in the future, but I don't see that there are people are perceiving to be purely physical to be so at all because you often hear people saying, those are photons.
And again, when I say people, I'm not the commoners. I'm talking about the professor scientist, philosophers, leaders in those fields when they say photons, their experiments tend to work out.
The actual photon itself doesn't exist, you see.
I do think that that's a point of incredulity for a lot of people that, well, you're saying that these things are fake, that they don't exist, but we have material benefits from what these scientists claim to be doing and in their labs.
So that the finality of that result is clearly a testament to its validity as opposed to what you're saying, which is really what can't be proven.
People again have the perception of we're actually benefiting from what they're doing and that's maybe another discussion, but if you objectify it, I haven't seen many many benefits.
I've seen slight improvements and applications of certain technologies, but essentially it's a they are still producing and and purveying in tropic systems, which is the opposite of life giving.
So even if we stick with the matter of light, it's not it is forms of light that require power sources, power sources that decay and degrade, give off heat where, you know, things that are living, even if you were to expand that things that are living statement into the motion of the planets and the stars, they tend to be in a harmonic balance that do not seem to be expending themselves and maintain their accuracy of movement where what they're purveying does not.
Yeah, that I understand, but to the human being who doesn't sort of understand the back end of his own technology and is only looking at the utilitarian sort of function of it, they would say that their smartphones and their cars and their whatever are performing a function that is usable and that that is certainly an advantage over what existed say 100, 200 years ago, and we should thank the scientists for that.
So what are you on about with your photons or fake stuff when clearly we have our goods and services?
Sure, you can you can go into many aspects of that, you know, what caused the footprint in the sand on the beach or what caused the tree to fall.
You can there's many, you know, there are many ways you could say, you know, causality.
Yeah, so ultimately the products that they're that we let's say, quote unquote, the let's say in this case, the society at large receives from them, they perceive them as as being beneficial because they offer more comfort than the previous technology did.
So it's very relative in that sense.
Okay, I hear what you're saying.
Well, let's say that you're on a train somewhere and the driver announces that you'll be stuck in place for the next 20 minutes because of an accident.
And so to pass time, the guy sitting next to you asks if you're religious, you say no, and then that starts a conversation on what each of your convictions are concerning the non-material existence.
How would you in a situation like that expound on the supernatural to somebody with no direct knowledge of it, but wants to learn?
Wow, that would be a big question. And the first thing I would address that is wants to learn.
Then the wants to learn needs to be held almost separate from the category in the subject matter itself.
Because it would not just be around, let's say, quote unquote, spirituality or religion, but it would be about anything.
And at that point, let's say, I was in a situation like you just mentioned that setting that first of all, let's let's let's be real.
The chances of running into someone like that in the society is in the one and a million to one and 10 million.
So let's just say for we could skip this question because that wouldn't happen.
It's so slim.
But let's say we don't skip the question and we stick with it. I would give him a standard load of Greek speak.
Basically, no one is paying attention to the obvious. And if you can perceive the obvious, which is an astounding feat on its own, then we could probably have a palpable discussion in the in the
quote unquote, spirituality, non-proceivable, ultimately called religious discussion.
Okay. I guess my thought behind the question is that most people can relate to some sensibility that indicates that the supernatural exists.
They just aren't able to rationalize it or create a usable framework around it. So it just remains in the category of who and you know stays in limbo and they can't really form a proper conclusion about it.
So in that case, is there anything that a person could say to offer up, you know, some kind of advice to point people in the right direction?
High level of discernment. You're going to have to look at the source and see if the source can be objectified.
What I mean by that is in any field of study, whatever a subject or object you want to study, the reality of that can be replaced with a fiction that appears to be or a counterfeit situation or
or you know a contrive situation or a contrived object that might be like the original.
So you're going to have to pretty much put on some objectivity glasses and see if that source is known not whether 50% is true, 50% is not because in this day and age, meaning the past 150 years, when you hear of an untrusted,
source, it's all of their stuff is not to be trusted. It's that bad right now. Like if you hear anything from a, let's say what's called a multinational corporation or a government or a religious authority, it's about 99.99999% false.
Everything that they're saying is kind of like the earth is known to be a purveyor of BS. One can say that being very critical, if you can get past the hurdle of perceiving the obvious, you could probably move further on that.
Okay, let's break down some of the aspects of how people interact with the unseen world. I think the most notable way is through religion so we can start with that.
As someone who wasn't indoctrinated into any religion, what notions of the unseen realm did you carry about in your early life and how did those play, how did those ideas play out as you got older?
Okay, well that's a very large question because how does the unseen world interact with anyone is if anyone can structure a thought and walk across the room at the same time, that is because you're multilateral feedback, you know, you're actually transmitting and receiving from your environment, meaning the unseen environment.
That's what consciousness is. You're not self-contained. Your thoughts are attached to a large network, let's say.
This has already been established, but it's not as acknowledged as it could be or should be.
And myself personally, I had to, I grew up in a Greek Orthodox Christian setting and I knew there was something just downright wrong with it. It was not only wrong, but it was dirty, it was dark.
I wouldn't say evil because they did give away food to the poor, but in essence, I had to be bribed with jelly donuts to go to church, right, until I just said no more and I would actually run away on Saturday night and I'd come back till Sunday night to avoid that.
After enough familial embarrassment of that, they said, okay, you don't have to go anymore and that was just really a good way. So actionable protest does work, I guess, when you're about six or seven.
No, that's smart. I wish I had thought of that. Well, no, I wouldn't have been allowed to get away with it. So I guess you're people more accepting 50, 40 years ago.
Not really. I mean, I had a broomstick broken on me several times, so no, it was, I accepted that over the other. Yes. No, I say, okay.
Well, I mean, in the absence of religion, it leaves some people wondering how they can affirm the existence of the unseen realm because even though we can talk about your thoughts and how they're powered, most people aren't aware of that sort of thing.
They take it for granted that the brain is the is the seat of the mind. So without religion, they're sort of left in limbo. So what is your average person to do other than join a religion or the occult if you want to understand the supernatural.
The average person is just that they're just door stops. They have no, they have no play, believe it or not, in the larger scheme of things until the larger scheme of things changes to accept them, which is not in this life.
So again, most of this conversation when we say people will be focused towards the leadership of these of these door stops, I should say.
One thing I do agree with the power brokers of the world and those that control the world, they call them useful theaters or whatever, I fully agree with that.
So the average people are just, I've defined in other sonics of space heaters. They take up space and give off heat.
And I'm not just saying this again to just skirt around the question, but they're just space heaters. They're just pawns, let's just say.
But what happens with this disposable mass is the leadership can guide them. So it's like you're swimming in a lake and here comes these senseless logs down the lake and they're going to crush you. Right? Not one you can avoid.
But if you have a barrage of a major log jam that just led through the lake, it will destroy you. They do have, they are formidable in when they're in a mass together to work in a particular direction.
But for them to function individually, it's negligible.
That's why for example, you have the quote unquote, intelligence here in this in this society. It's always just a handful. You have the spiritual people just a handful and so on and so forth.
But you know what, the real ones are not known. They always prop, there will always be a time period when there is a resurgence of intelligence or spirituality or romance in art or whatever.
And very often the ones that are genuinely with authentic creativity and genuine drive to advance those areas are hidden and the fakes and you know like your Einstein's and the Osama bin Laden's and the Oswald's and all the fake stuff that you see George Washington's all these things that are put in front of you as being notable are not actually at all.
And the real ones are kept back. So if you are amongst the average, whatever space heaters and you one day are turned on to do great things because it might be later on in your life, if not early in your life, you must understand that notoriety and fame is not what real people quote unquote or genuine performers get.
They always put in front of the faux aspect.
Yeah, I don't mean, you know, I'm obviously going to assist from referring to much to the average person because it's clearly a point of distaste.
But I'm just talking about to whomever it may concern that qualifies. So if there's some princess somewhere, the princess of Spain or whatever that decides that she wants to understand the supernatural because she realizes that the whole monarchy is just full of videos.
Okay, what are you going to do?
Okay, and even then she there are if she really was the princess of Spain, she would have been eliminated and they would put a fake in her place.
This is just the real reality. It's how it works. But let's say there she is in that position, even if she is not really the princess of Spain, the heir apparent.
What is she to do?
Back in the days when you lied to nobility, your head was cut off. I think for her to go to all of the academics and have their most of their heads cut off would be a little too drastic.
So short of that, it would be that she would have to have a her own personal revelation of observing the obvious before she embarks on any study of any subject, whether it's medical her body.
Or the natural world at large, the study of the gods or spirituality or religion, the study of history, she would have to see what learned to discern what's being put in front and see what's false and what's not and begin to acknowledge the obvious and ask the proper questions.
So the subject matter again is irrelevant.
I have noticed that a number of Abrahamic religions place quite a lot of emphasis on belief as a key component in their doctrines or at least in their traditions.
I'd say evangelical Christianity takes a lot of blame pie for that today because their refrain is just believe in your saved and it's all done by Grace Blahblah.
But the further back in history you go, the more you see that what is called religion was about a way of life and rituals. So if you do ABC, then your god accepts you if you don't, then there's consequences.
Can you elaborate on how tenuous this idea of belief is and the sort of distorting effect? It's how to help people interact with the supernatural?
Well, if someone just tells you you have to believe it's a scam because even if you study the famous New Testament documents that are put out that people say this concept is based on, it doesn't say anything like that at all in its entirety.
One big popular thing is they say is the law has been done away with it you find in the Old Testament, but the most prominent day that the quote unquote,
the disciples and apostles experience was what's what they call the day of Pentecost. If they weren't following the law, they would not have been in one place to receive what they call the Holy Spirit.
You see, so also there is no I wouldn't I would probably will be repeating myself very often on this.
I'm not saying you shouldn't use it because it's a good target phrase in the phrase is Abrahamic religions.
There's no such thing that is another sign of guiding the mind down a path that isn't so.
What I mean by that is if you read the, let's say when you say Abraham, that's a biblical text also in the Quran, but if you understand the text and you read it with comprehension, you have man society on the earth interacting with gods,
there's one God that doesn't have any people that really have an allegiance to him as if from a familial to a national level.
So he chooses Abraham to be the man that will start the genealogy of a group of people from a familial tribal to national and then worldwide level that will have allegiance to this particular God who is the God of God in the Bible.
So there is no religious aspect there as much as it's a particular people have a allegiance to a particular God and I don't see that really as being a religious thing as much as it is a hereditary thing and more of establishing a nation that is known to have an allegiance to a certain God just like for example people have an allegiance to a certain leader.
Or a monarchy it was it's always known that people even today have an allegiance to a certain deity and this particular deity did not have a group of people so he created them through Abraham.
So when I when you say Abrahamic religion, I don't see it in the way that people use religion in religious studies in what they call.
Theocracy or theology or whatever in that sense at all.
I understand and I do occasionally make myself guilty to sort of common place phrases that most people understand.
We are talking about Christianity, Islam and Judaism.
Yes. Well belief is you'll see colloquially means like lunch times over get back to work. That's all it means.
In other words, yeah just say you believe and get back to what you were doing because if you were to do the opposite to know well how much time does it take to gain knowledge versus how much time does it take to vow your belief into something.
For example, it's very easy to if you have a fake diamond that looks like the real thing you want to find someone who's looking to buy a diamond because you could purvey the sale quicker than convincing just some pedestrian who doesn't think about buying diamonds to buy one you see.
So you have to find a willing victim.
But also the consequences which are coming in the future in the society is when you find a willing victim and you victimize them and through the corruption of the sale of a corrupt item.
The penalties and the fervor and the pursuit of getting the assailant is much higher than just a common pedestrian who was not interested in it who would have a higher chance of chalking it off as a mis just a misfortune and incident.
So yes you are saying there so you mean the consequences are going to be quite dire in the future.
Sure so what I'm trying to say indirectly I'll be more direct as as we progress as a well along this path it's not just the Greek or the God speak that we're doing society at large is going to start looking for spiritual answers.
And that is the biggest threat to the current theocracies you know with every religion so every religion has its central point of focus you know you might say Judaism would be out of Israel the Roman Catholic side of the Vatican you know the Mormons out of Utah whatever whatever you'll see you know mecca for you know these other guys and you know this shrine here for these other.
Okay the people are just casually going along because if you don't have a religion will something wrong with you you know so when the people start to develop a desire to learn more about it that is the biggest enemy in the biggest threat model to these leaders of all of these different groups that I mentioned geographically because they're not very difficult to be found out as frauds.
Right I mean anyone that wants to see what Judaism is doing is a fraud can just spend 15 minutes researching on the internet if anyone wants to see what Christianity is purveying as a fraud you can just spend five minutes on the internet.
The same with Islam the same with Hinduism the same with any of these religions so again going back to the people just being worthless is that they're not even spending 15 minutes of their in their life to see that the religion that they actually
are like a profess to believe in is a complete fraud. So what will happen in the near future meaning the next few years beginning is people's genuine desire to gain knowledge and shed not completely shed belief but shed leaning on belief as the only causality for them to profess that they are a particular religious group.
So if you have a desire to gain knowledge all of the current systems will be shown to be complete you know hoaxes and frauds and that will be this is actually prophetic and all of the prophetic rites of every culture.
There will be a short time when there's a turnaround in people's minds so so all of these you know rabbis ministers, the moms or whatever yeah if you hear this you only have a few years you should have an alternative occupation prepared.
Well if we presume that with three major religions at least fall apart under scrutiny then why not give preference to some of the eastern ones like Taoism or Confucianism or Buddhism that are noticeably branded as more sublime and philosophical.
The same the same they're the same frauds in other words it's it's it's as if I took went and got a chicken and wrapped it with a rapper that said bubble gum on it and everyone's passing it around
as bubble gum for a few days until it starts to really stink and they open the rapper and they see that it's a rotten piece of chicken inside right.
So and even if someone wanted to open the rapper it says bubble gum but it's a piece of chicken this is not bubble gum and it's just chicken right it's very easy to do.
The rapping and the superficial aspect of it is very easy. That's what you see in other words if you make something so obviously fraudulent and put it in front of people and they accept it what does that say about those that accepted.
If you have beings that are so obviously susceptible to such superficial deception you don't have a quality being or quality mindset that you're dealing with.
And after thousands of years of this it's like shooting fish in the barrel it gets pretty boring and they just continue doing it anyway meaning the leadership.
Well I mean we're definitely going to take some time to look more narrowly at certain of these religions in the future episodes but for now let's move on to talk about what supposedly underpins the power of these religions and also secret societies and cults which is namely the gods.
I think it's arguably the least understood notion in any language or culture with perhaps an exception of some indigenous ones.
What are we to make of that word and its origins.
Oh if you were let's say in northern Europe 500 years ago and you said that word they point at the sun. God gee let's say you'd spell it.
Go to the or go to the it's an English word many other languages like let's say the other common one that the prefix is used academically is theos where you get we get theosophy theocracy theology from.
Other languages all law in Arabic all law Elohim in Hebrew.
Yeah Brahma in Hindu it's just a point of reference it usually in every culture if you use the corresponding term for that they usually point up.
Why do they tend to point upwards because I mean they you can identify gods even on the ground level.
Yes but generally that's the consensus of of where everything comes from even for even from the scientism this religion of modern science.
They tell you everything came from the stars.
Yeah now not evolution where you form the slime in the water and then developed legs and crawled on the surface that's still the pro the pregenesis to that is astral meaning up high.
Okay you've often talked about how the physical world is subordinate to the spiritual world and the quality and quantity of things here can be used to infer a lot about the other side.
So what can we surmise about the gods in their society by drawing parallels between the physical and the spiritual domains.
If you look at it from an industrial manufacturing point of view the sheer simulality of all things biological.
You know how you hear for example of DNA right you notice as time goes on there's less talk about that because it's such an inaccurate science is 111 comparisons you can have a long discussion or study on your own.
And of course like the study of DNA now just ends up in the legal society which is all presumption and fiction anyway in you always hear about someone being.
Convicted or acquitted based on DNA and if you look at how they're using it it's completely against the accepted methods because you know the I think I've discussed before you know again the attorneys are you know represents certain forces.
But if you look at what they call DNA broccoli as about 70 or 80% of human DNA a house fly is about 90% human DNA.
So what we're looking at several let's say aspects of the biological code that all share the same thing almost identical when you're looking at the percentages of how similar they are.
Things that living things most living things require light most living things require aspiration to breathe and food.
So you look at the mechanism of nature itself from the law of the jungle all the way to the finest scrutiny and objectifying what to be alive is.
And then seeing that there's actually a consciousness behind it that's driving it right and what even plants the secret life of plants anyone could look that up.
Fellow wrote a book about how plants were set up to electrical sensing devices and they reacted to human emotion and movement.
There's also this aspect of the gods having become a very sparse field of expertise and I want to look at that also and I don't mean knowledge of ancient religions which I think there's just still quite a bit of information about.
I mean the equivalent of what we see in indigenous cultures where in places like Vietnam or Cambodia when the witch doctor says don't go into the house over there because there's an evil spirit inside and if you go anyway as soon as you step into the living room you feel someone punched you in the head and knock you out even though the house was empty.
I mean that kind of cause an effect that's closer to how technology operates.
Where did that knowledge of the gods disappear to?
The overarching could what I call contractual discoveries that were made after the Renaissance when you hear about contractual discovery that is when you hear the explorers that were sent out throughout the world that were also followed by the by the let's say special forces to get gathering acquire all this information like the witch doctors don't go into this house or the forest or what have you.
When these discoverers went out you hear of all the explorers Magellan Vaskodagama Columbus all the soon to follow were the special forces of the Vatican and other groups that wanted that new of this existence as part of the normalcy of the society acquired the information and not only of of the happenings but also how to control and manipulate and interact with these forces and then of course eliminate the people that did have control and then take control of it and.
If you go to places in the Congo Somalia parts of Afghanistan parts of southern Libya where you don't have this contractual overarching you know corn coat the modern system that you see on the planet.
If people are quite familiar with this and it's still quite active with it especially in many of the jungle regions.
Okay I mean that's a good segue into sort of the next question if if to some extent indigenous cultures were able to retain that knowledge then I wonder why those people have been so ineffective in shaping world events and not only that but even in deciding their own fate as nations I mean if you look at the Native Americans as an example here we have a group of people who occupied probably one of the most covered land areas that I've seen outside of Syria Palestine maybe they had access to a cult of knowledge such as incantations and conjurations.
It could have easily wiped out the Europeans that invaded yet they lost their land and now they're almost extinct and so now the story is that the supremacy of Western European culture and weaponry triumph over backwater Indians who wasted their time praying to a totem pole can you impact that a bit.
Yeah why yeah in other words what are the benefits of that let's say they were doing more than the totem pole the totem pole would be more like the like a divine geographical more car just like you would have.
A marker just like you would have a marker for any other purpose on the on the earth itself I wouldn't say they were just a praying to anything it was more of a marker like a survey point but I would suggest that there were enough wisdom within those cultures to understand that an evil force was going to come to their society and that evil force was not a monolithic evil force acting on its own volition but part of the great grand cycle.
And cycle where an evil force has to come or it's inevitable that will come in order for this cycle to end and go to the next cycle meaning cosmic cycle.
Okay I mean that does carry a sense of resignation though I mean they did fight yes they did fight though.
And the fact wisdom mostly did yes and there were conscientious objectors by the way let's just say about fighting it was just submit because in other words the ones that had wisdom and really had true spiritual knowledge did not mind perishing because they understood that the the overarching force and never to build overarching and
the ability of the end of the age happening a certain way cannot be changed so why fight it. Okay I've never heard much about that I'm after looking for those accounts because I don't see much about it I mean obviously the Native Americans a lot of them are mixed race now so you don't find that knowledge base being what it used to be but there was much written about this in the 19th century but by the turn of the 20th century up until the 1930s what was written about it was sequestered and taken away all that remains.
Are things that you might find in some library or some reference that you can you know digital or not that is a second earth let's say tertiary account of their existing at one point of body of knowledge recording these things but we don't know where it is or it's not available anymore.
There's going to be a revival of this by the way and there's an attempted revival albeit by the visually impaired when I mean visually impaired meaning spiritually because you know having.
So I used to see means the spiritual things most of the people that are trying to revive quote unquote through the new age in many other aspects of every culture by the way whether it's the indigenous people or the westerners they're trying to revive some kind of spirituality but they're they're impaired they don't understand the fundamentals so they're not going to succeed until the time allows them to.
Other realm in which the supernatural is often invoked is that of the occult which oddly has remained something that people metal with at night in a basement or an attic or a forest or parking lot rather than out in the open.
Why do you think none of the occult societies have been able to pierce the veil of secular culture to take charge of man society if the power behind them is real.
I know they have they have completely when you see something on television and event whether it's an assassination a terrorist event or a pandemic or whatever that is completely fabricated and everyone believes that wholeheartedly that that there was a tremendous amount of ritual that had gone on before that to put out enough influence in that realm to influence the individuals.
Pharmaceutical companies do it if you know any one that's in not low level but higher level pharmaceutical business all of it is done by a called ritual.
Yeah that there's not much to hide on that you can this is right now current events there's something about a vaccine being put out and they're waiting until a certain time when the stars are in place they're telling you this is in the current events right now.
Yeah I guess I'm referring to more this idea that even within the secret societies if you want to talk free mason's or Jesuits or whatever the more forward facing ones.
They there's a sense in which it doesn't seem like they really know what they're doing because you can run into people who belong to those societies and they don't really know what the future holds.
They they know that there's something that the higher ups are doing right now perhaps but it almost feels like they're fumbling around in the dark still.
Well the current when you say any of these societies that you might do find on let's say a map quest or Google maps where you see they have a building or a society or a website those are the common morons that get together do fancy handshakes get photographs you know eating pork and wearing an apron or whatever.
It doesn't matter which culture you're talking about by the way all cultures have a free masonic order of some sort or a templer order or some kind of rights and I say rights RITES is the spelling.
But those are the common morons and the the only reason those exist openly is because years ago when the population was smaller and those those organizations were still of it publicly.
Visible there were more hard core but as populations expanded so let's say we go back a thousand years and we see that there's a group of free masons in a particular country there's 500 of them the population expands and grows and descendants of those free masons of decide to be in free masonry now the population instead of being just 500 or so free masons is 20,000 right well there's still only 500 that know what's going on in the other.
And the other 19,500 are just filler it's the same with the military and the same with the police.
You know when you look at the military they're grunts you know if there's a million people in the military there's fewer than a thousand or two thousand of them and know what they're doing the rest are just filler bodies you know masses like I said earlier.
The label is still valid in in other words the free the secret societies their labels are still valid if you go look at for example the Facebook logo is a free masonic logo that's been used for a long time it means a certain thing.
The Google the Gmail is a free masonic apron there's still that would you say well this is the free no they're just putting this the symbolism is showing you that it's still is still as viability is just that you can't put your hand on it.
And that I guess is also a good sort of segue into another question because there's this odd cat and mouse game that these societies in a cold groups play with the public where corporate names of logos clearly indicate that the corporation is operating in honor of or.
Under the auspices of a deity to the point where for example anybody can see that the Mazda cars named after a who are Mazda the chiefs or Austrian deity or that night he's named after a Greek goddess but if you ask the CEO they'll just deny it.
And so my question is why such a seemingly spineless way of ruling the world where you have to hide behind possible deniability when we know that high level corporations and governments utilize a cold practices.
Oh well there the CEOs are just a ceremonial figure heads again I mentioned recently when the mob got into white collar crime they needed shell corporations you know corporations to achieve a certain thing commercial or trade and then collapse it and they're like well we need a CEO I say well just get that homeless guy there to sign get him a new suit shave send him to a spa and have him signed papers doesn't matter.
You'd have to be insane to be a rational if you had this slightest amount of honor dignity lawfulness and morality to be a CEO one of these big companies.
They don't pick people that are and those companies come before so before the people so when you hear about like Jeff Boso did Amazon he didn't do or that guy that did Facebook or whatever he didn't do anything they just put some clown there they just guy they're guided.
It's very simple it's it's to do it's just that you don't get the story because it's obvious I mean at you but you know people don't get it because it's just so obvious you're the pays good though.
It's well bank numbers yeah I have from a good source the guy the the Boso guy when when he's given a certain agenda and he has to think he's reports back he's not sure about it he may not want to do it well the next time he goes and checks his bank balance it's zero point zero zero.
And they know he just checked his bank balance so he gets the phone call again and he says would you would reconsider and he says I'll reconsider so he goes back and checks his bank balance and it's 50 billion so you really want and all of these people that you hear that are wealthy or not.
In Hollywood and music and industry the moment they say I want to get out of this the moment they see that he's purchasing.
Survival equipment or a place enough of that's not on Google maps let's say or a travel to a nut to bug out or appointment with plastic surgeons and all that he gets a phone call he says your funds are taken away from you again what do you think you're doing you're in this for life they have no money he's so when you see these these people in the music industry in Hollywood they they allude to this is plenty of YouTube videos of Jim Carrey saying I don't know what I didn't you know
another actors publicly saying this is not what you think it is you know Jim Carrey wants to get away from being nearly raped or whatever by Hollywood you know people control Hollywood he can't well he could do it he'd be homeless he would be penniless
and the moment he asked someone for money they put him in a sainis silent the the Kanye West guy that went crazy out of concert talking about a luminaughty he's hospitalized for three days and comes out he's totally fine.
These people have no money princess tried it to get away from it and you can't nobody can get away from it once you get into it that deep meaning on a worldwide fame level.
Any of these guys Bill Gates wants to get away with his husband or I'm sorry his wife Melinda when Bill Gates wants to get away and washes hands of it he'll be a popper or put an insane a silent he has no money at all they have no money so bank numbers.
This is the biggest fallacy you know if you understand the collar you guys is in the end people will only listen to people who are wealthy and they're not even wealthy it's just a double irony here.
By the way if you're if you're a real wealthy person you don't put your money in the bank is only in short for a hundred thousand quid or whatever right more dollars that's you don't have to go to Harvard business school to know that you can only get a hundred thousand dollar return on your billion dollar.
Parking a billion dollars somewhere you can only come back and get a hundred thousand out of it that's you don't have to go to Harvard business school to know that's a bad move.
The wealthy people don't have the put their money in these institutions but I wanted to go back to like the the Hollywood people and the famous people Bill Gates and the Jeff Bozo and Kanye West and Prince and whatever Jay Z they could go out and buy an airplane.
And Jim Carrey they could go on by a ten for our is because that fits the role that they're playing they could go out and buy a big house.
How many times have you heard some actor especially this happened some basketball sports people recently they wanted to sell their five million dollar mansion but then it gets foreclosed on how's that possible because it's like stop your movements you know if you keep persisting your your car will explode because it crashed into a gum wrapper.
You know you crashed into a paper cup in the car exploded or your helicopter goes down or you drown.
This is not what people think it is none of these people that you know or here have any power they're all just a show it's very efficient for the the powers that are behind the scenes meaning the secret societies and the spirits that they deal with to put the charade in front of society it's very efficient.
Because right now even had someone's is Greek I want to live with honor lawfulness and dignity I want to go after these powers who were you going to aim who you can't identify them they spent the past thousand years cloaking themselves.
You can't find them.
There is no way to revolt or repel this this is the goes back to the wisdom of those native people that allow themselves to be exterminated because they knew that this had to happen anyway no matter what you did it was going to happen.
Because it was the end the ages the progression of the cosmic ages is far more significant than you living another day to wipe your bummer get hungry or have more children.
And the the essence of your spirit and the true the true motive for you existing is beyond what you see in this current age.
Yeah well we're going to get into more of that as things go on I think that'll be a pleasure because there's a lot to learn in that realm of things.
But let's wrap up the podcast by looking at the topic of ancient culture although we've touched on it a little bit already.
So what we know about the gods comes to us from memorialize the counts over the past four to five thousand years but since the middle ages the volume of those writings either declined or became very occultic and hidden.
So the most direct literature about the gods is from classical antiquity most of it.
What can this period teach us about the gods and ways that seem to vanish once the dark ages arrive?
Well there were no dark ages until the middle ages everything was just fine.
It was just a redefine that's dark because not because it was dark in any way other than we don't know much the information has been sequestered.
And the information just lets you know that you're getting closer to the end of the age every culture has in and its own prophetic writings that as we get closer to the end of this age meaning grand age not just cycle of ages where you have let's see cycles of two thousand or consecutive series of let's say thousand or two thousand years but a grand age which could be seven or twenty or twenty four thousand or fourteen thousand years.
But most likely let's just say in the multiple thousands of years the all the cultures have in their similarity is that they will be an unprecedented peak in a malevolency lack of honor lack of dignity lack of lawfulness in the end of the grand age.
You know very much described as you see now and this could be said in an objective way or it could be said in a subjective way where I like to say that if you preach doom and gloom and evil and malevolency anytime in human history it sounds about right.
But never has it been on a as we know a dark ages aside on such a level where it's all it's pretty much the entire world.
You and I would have a conversation some time back is probably some years ago and you said something interesting about ancient rites you asked me why do you have to pick ancient literature as a reference point for understanding reality.
And naturally I couldn't answer at the time so you just answered it yourself and you said because why would you refer to a book that came into existence only a few hundred years ago when you have books from thousands of years ago.
And books from the 18th century probably won't have much to offer about 6000 years of human civilization. Could you elaborate on that more about this idea first and time first in line and the primacy of ancient recordings.
Sure the the the the the primacy meaning taking it in his from a point of hysteresis where the older the better when you focus on what's you know older what came first.
It's not necessarily that it's in a book it could be something that's scribbled on the side of of of a stone it's a communication it's memorializing in communication.
For example we have the goal the gods have an active role with humanity via communication.
If you were just to narrow it down as a phenomenon why do we have people imagining things about another race of beings known as the gods.
And that they received script from them or directions to write script from them and rites from them is it purely imaginative.
And even if it was purely imaginative let's say from a romantic fictional point of you why are they also similar.
And even that becomes the notion that it's just people's imagination becomes self-defeated because the accuracy and the similarity and the causality you know that we see in history in other words when you read about Sodom and Gomorrah it's a real place when you read about temple of Solomon it's a real place when you read about you see.
Or other things these are real places how can the imagination be stretched so far it must be there must be a concurrent line of fact underneath all of it.
So all we have from the gods other than the the substantial reality that all things seem to be made by them or a similar manufacture or similar creation and formation that there is a separate aspect to the gods interacting with us through communications.
You want to call them prophets, sages, messiahs, angels you know when you get into demons when you get into the non-corporal again that there's so much of it that just because there's so much quantity doesn't mean it's valid but the quality of the information makes it valid not just the quantity.
So in other words everywhere you look there is some reference to some God everywhere somewhere and everywhere and if we take those either as valid or invalid from being from the gods you always end up at the same place qualitatively that they're all higher order dictates memorializations higher order memorializations of higher order communications.
Not just to the people at the time but to be sent through the future the most viable ones obviously are the ones written in stone because they don't decay even for example finding ancient scrolls there are many challenges let's say in the cumeron Dead Sea Scrolls right major challenges I don't need to discuss with finding 2000 year old scrolls.
They don't seem to be very durable when you have something carved into the side of a stone tends to have more durability and whether it's on a more recent find let's say the scrolls in cumeron or stale ancient stale that have been carved or even oral tradition folklore that is survived to a certain degree it all needs to be looked at and when it's looked at it has the same qualitative meaning.
Which I think validates the existence of the gods in itself the communication that's been memorialized okay but we can't overlook that among ancient text we have the Greek text competing with the Egyptian text competing with the Parthians competing with the Israelites competing with the Samarians Babylonians blah blah blah and they all claim preeminent or at least most of them do so what do we make of that order.
They do and they don't even if you look at the lowest level interpretations of whether it's the Catholic what the Catholics tell you you go through when you die the ancient Greeks tell you what you go through when you die or the Parthians or so forth they're all similar and almost identical when you look at the technique not identical in technique but identical in process.
Like for example the man on the street thinks you're good you go to heaven you're bad you go to hell forever but if you study Catholic purgatory you go there until you have worked through all of your bad stuff and then you go to the next level you come out of it and what the man on the street the typical Catholic doesn't know that because he works on belief he hasn't spent 15 minutes studying what the doctrine that the institution that he's pledged allegiance to is prevailing.
And it's not encouraged of course it's just like if you meet an attorney and not a paralegal does all the work but he go to his house or his office you look at all the law books they're all brand new they're 40 years old and they never been touched he doesn't go by those and the moment you suggest that we look there he they get very offended because his job is to manage your stupidity right same with the doctor
his job is to manage your stupidity a priest or minister or pastor and he moments to manage your stupidity they're not there to educate you educate themselves.
And if you got rid of them the people would say well we don't have any more attorneys let's make some more let's put some more in there they don't have to do anything they just have to give us the perception that they do we we don't have any more ministers or priests or pastors or rabbis or he moms let's make some more you right here yeah put this in the way.
You right here yeah put this on your priest go just tell people this right here is a little crib sheet five things and you're done they feel like these things giving example like if you understand I don't know if you know any one in the secret service.
And they have their opinions about you know the United States who's president but even the secret service itself the training that they put their agents through to protect the president is you're not protecting the man itself you're protecting the office of the presidency.
You see it's the office of the rabbi the office of the attorney the office of the doctor right the office of this it's not the so now we've lost it's all become just hollow shells right hollow it's just someone has to fill it it doesn't matter it's kind of like when you read about the post macabee and or macabee in the era in the temple in Jerusalem you know they were such a defeated people they just
took some young Syrian boy and put him in priestly garments as you are the high priest. Yeah you can just get somebody anyone you know give him you know say that he can went to whatever seminary and did a couple good things you're the pope just get up there you're the pope everybody bows down you're the pope.
It's just the offices they're hollow they're the people that are in those all offices even your local you know attorney doctor priest rabbi whatever they're just filling a position people like them or don't like them it doesn't matter it's the position is there it's all vanity you know there's no substance behind the and the characters the people that take these
professional again professors attorneys doctors whatever so on probes maybe they're all of poor character by the way if you you know get to know them judges whatever captains whatever they're all poor character.
And that and that goes to the supply message this society is such a poor state who would want to rule over them who would want to be a priest or minister or a pastor of such a poor quality society of course another well it
have to be an individual it's even poorer than them to put up with them you see any man of quality or woman of quality would never take up a leadership position in this society ever it wouldn't last even if they tried.
So you're always going to have within the past 150 years inferior people in superior positions and superior people in inferior positions this is a given as another sign of you know it's just vanity it's just the time has to be
just the time has to go through it's like being in a dunk tank for you know you agree to be in the dunk tank for one minute but you can only hold your breath for 40 seconds that's okay you said a minute so you got to deal with the last 20 seconds right.
Yes I was painful.
It is painful if you and if you're not in pain you're not paying attention but it doesn't mean you can deal you can't deal with it.
Okay so yeah I think we've looked at a variety of topics and I think that sets the table to expand on things in subsequent episodes I don't feel a need to over expand on anything since we'll have more things to cover in the future.
Are there any other generalities you'd like to mention on the subject of the supernatural before we wrap up.
Well just to find supernatural by itself you know for what people can perceive perceive to be natural if something is extraordinary it's supernatural but if you have a pretty good perception of what is possible in the natural world you may not perceive certain things as being supernatural because it's just being of the one you know the the understanding of how subtle energies you know can manifest as big powerful forces.
But generally what we consider supernatural quote unquote we meaning the society at large loosely there is stuff that's been put in front of us as being as such you know through religious doctrine and Hollywood and media and whatever but as we progress in time the next half a decade or so I think the there'll be some solidity to the term supernatural paranormal.
Miraculous meaning it will be experienced publicly it will be more more active in the world.
Cool then I think we've covered everything that we need to cover in this introductory episode and similar to the Greek speed podcast I'll be trying to do an episode a month we'll see how the timeline plays out the last one took a year.
I wouldn't be surprised if we had a similar timeline but I'll shoot for less and we'll see how it goes and so thank you to everybody who turned into this one and we look forward to seeing you at the next episode.
[Music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]