[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening and thank you for tuning into another episode of the God
Speak podcast where we examine the history and characteristics of the unseen realm. We spent
the last few episodes talking about mainstream religions and since that's what most people
used to make sense of the supernatural. We've covered Judaism and Christianity and Islam is a
predictable next choice so that's what we'll be looking at today. As per the usual disclaimer,
GodSpeak.com still has no political religious or commercial affiliations and is completely
managed by myself although anyone is free to make donations by way of my sister site
greaksbeak.com. So I hope you enjoy the upcoming conversation and thanks again for listening.
So, Greek normally I ask how you're doing but I suspect that binol questions will only
entice binol answers but I hope you've been doing well. Yes, thank you. So I think the
proper starting point when talking about Muslims is to talk about their main predecessors the
Nabateans who were at their height during Josephus' time. He described them as being descended from
Nebalev, the eldest son of Ishmael, and they appeared to have been a mercantile nation who influenced
most of the Near East and parts of Europe as well like Italy. From the information you've come across,
what do you know about the Nabateans? Very sparse. I haven't looked into what I call Arabic
and Eastern Orientalism. For example, I haven't really read the Quran in 15 years
or studied any of that specifically but it is a popular culture. You do come across them.
I would say there were more of the, if you go outside of what's called the Persian realm,
they would probably, one of the more developed culturally and traditional societies of the time.
Also being that they would keep their heritage intact so they would, you know,
tout lineage from Abraham and also have adherences to the kin of such. Yeah, I found some similar things.
So just to give some additional context, you have this vast desert area in the Middle East thanks
to the Syrian desert and the Nafoot desert which makes traveling difficult and so the Nabateans were
the ones who bridge that gap by settling outside most of the major cities of the Middle East and
building up a trade network and so kingdoms would rise and fall but the Nabateans just got more
and more wealthy by being on the sidelines and eventually gain some political power based on
the developments in certain regions. For example, when Damascus was having political problems in 85 BC,
they put a Nabatean governor in charge to rule the city. They also had a lot of interactions with
Judea and the Hezmoneans and later on hered the Great before they finally got absorbed into the Roman
empire. I don't know if you know much about those interactions. Somewhat, those would be what I
consider the more traditional movers and shakers of that period. Indeed, they did have quite a lot of
influence on the Hezmonean revolution. They supported them against the solicits and then had some
issues with hered which contributed quite a lot to Pompeii invading Judea later on. So one of the
reasons I wanted to mention in Nabateans is because when you go back and examine how most of the powerful
traditions today got started, you'll find that their origins are very different from what their
current followers proclaim. So Christianity doesn't take its root from the Christ. Judeism is
actually rabbinic Judeism and Islam also has some question marks. So I want us to look at one of those
Muslims will tell you that Muhammad came from Mecca which is in southern Arabia but when
Middle Eastern construction companies want to dig to put up a building the government requires
that someone from the Ministry of Antiquities is always present because they might run into an
ancient site which will get exposed during the digging. And so in Mecca, developers are digging
all the time to put up skyscrapers and hotels but they aren't finding any ruins of ancient cities
and in fact there's no archaeological record in Mecca that predates 800 AD even though Muhammad's
birthplace was said to be called the Mother of all cities in the Quran. Have you heard about this
aberration in Mecca's original origins? Sure, it's kind of enigmatic just like if you've heard
any other Greek speaker God speak, there's not much difference between these religions. There are
cultural mechanisms of political control. They also control every aspect of the society,
the morality and the finance and all that. So once you understand if you fast forward,
you said if you ask any Muslims, what they consider to be Islam is less than 150 years old, the same
with Christians or Judean to some extent you can go back to the 1500s but when we start discussing
the origin of these cultures it's basically another world of days that have gone by and has been
and completely different ideologies and narratives spoken and considered by the people that
supposedly subscribe to those fates. I didn't want to quote from an actual source regarding the Mecca issue.
So yes, yes and just to answer just a preface and an answer and that's very dubious and somewhat
enigmatic and very similar to the same way that if they dig at the current temple mountain
Jerusalem they're not going to find any relics because that's not the temple mount. I'm not saying that
Mecca or Medina or all these other places didn't exist, they do exist geographically but what people
acclaim for it to be is not just like for example just a bounce round a little bit. The recent discoveries
of Oar forgot his name who uncovered the real Sodom and Gomorrah east of the Jordan river versus the
one that that Hyatt Moron said was downed in the southern part right so anyone could look at
Collins I believe Dr. Stefan Collins I think is his name. They uncovered the real location of Sodom
and Gomorrah which is far no more north than traditionally believed and it doesn't want to be looked
at because it actually has proof so again even with this conversation if we start to bring up proofs
we're going to find a very stark contrast between what people think it is and what it actually can
be found out about it. Yes indeed yeah anybody can look up Steven Collins what he's done on Sodom and
Gomorrah. Just a quote about a YouTube videos on that. So just a quote from an actual source Ibn
Hisham is the one who edited the official biography of Muhammad and he wrote about Mecca having
fields and trees and water. Albukhari is one of the most prominent night century scholars he wrote
that Mecca and prisoners could be seen eating grapes but the strange thing of course is that Mecca is
surrounded by rocks and desert. Average is less than 10 centimeters of rain per year so hardly any
vegetation grows there and anyone can look at the ancient record of trees and plants by testing
the spores and the soil and it's already been revealed that Mecca had no trees but more importantly
Mecca is absent from ancient maps of Arabia that predate Islam which is odd given that it's supposed
to be a merchant city but it's interesting how these facts are actually known by islamists and
scholars but they've just ignored them for either convenience or fear of reprisal. I had come across
some information that pointed to Petra the city in Jordan there was a book written by Thomas
Artsruuni he is an Armenian historian from the ninth century and if you quote from his book on page
165 he said at the time there were some despotic brothers in the region of Arabia Petra which is now
called Mecca and then additionally ibn Hisham also says that one of Islam's first converts was a man
from Mecca who after he converted told his wife to go cleanse himself herself near the temple of
Dushara which is located in Petra so there's some evidence that points to that as well and I think
there's a documentary that's been put out about that. Sure and around that time for for
Smolania there would have been a massive exodus of anything resembling Judea culture a tradition
I think by that time there was already the major division and I think it was occupied
that whole entire area of Judea was already occupied whether it was the Eastern Orthodox
movement and the Ottoman movement you know at the time I think the row that's one of the division
with the Rome I'll actually will well into it I want to throw something around the
six century mid-sixth century I think there was a worldwide catastrophe I think it was volcanic
and there was earthquakes that subsumed most of normal life into a nightmare-ish
hellish condition on this planet you know whether wise climate wise atmospheric wise commerce
and everything was affected so you have a worldwide calamity happening roughly a hundred years before
I suppose Islam emerged so look at that look you must keep that political and geological
atmosphere you know condition in in in sight as well yes I've read a bit about that as well
because I mean how did these Arabian sort of Ragtag group just suddenly emerge in conquer
huge areas unless the politics there had been disrupted by some event right it was a mad max scenario
for about a century at that time mad max meaning the destruction of formal society conventional society
correct so I also want to talk about you know the gods themselves and that aspect of the religion
as it pertains to the Nabateen ones and also the god of Islam you've remarked in past episodes
about how Allah is not a proper name it's just a generic title meaning the god what are the implications
of that because it seems to be a reoccurring theme the names of deities are removed from the major
religions except maybe Hinduism that isn't really a religion well it is a religion Hindu well it's
a Hinduism is so broad with a two million possible gods right and all that it's more of a naturalism
like the ancient religion of bomb let's say pre-bludist or looking a lot of the Native American
observances but I would suggest that it's Allah all means the Allah like you see in the book of Daniel
it's sort of like an aramaic right like you won't see Yahweh or Allah heim really in Daniel it's always
L Allah or the ancient ones the ancient one which is sort of a tradition that you find in the orient
about referring to high deities when you do see names eliminated like for example in the parlance of
the king James and all the modern bibles that means that that writing or text has been fully
subsumed as a political tool because when you include the name like what's in a name there's a lot of
power in it if you let's say I don't like to use these examples but because of people's culture they
can see it if you watch a movie on someone casting a spell or revoking a demon they must be very
precise about the name right and this is what's always put in front of you in Hollywood and media
but they also but people aren't so smart to say well what about on the light side should we know the name
right and they just accept some loose adjective as a name and it's not so when you see lack of specifics
especially if you watch mainstream media there's never you know whenever they state something as a
fact there's nothing to back you up and there's never any specifics so and you could even take that
even further if you regarding what we just brought up in terms of mecca right it's so obscure
but I would suggest that it's all a lie and there are other many phonetically similar gods
referring to it as the moon god of a certain group in that part of the world and there are other
deity supposedly that sounds similar so again this is an enigmatic aspect of it just like when one
argues the name J.E.S.U.S it means some say it's just the Greek phonetic spelling some say it's a
transliteration because you know of this others say it means Zeus right so but the thing that you
could say is it's not correct indeed and just to address the moon god aspect it says both in the
writings of ibn Hisham and al-Tabari that Muhammad's grandfather took him to the temple of the god
Hubal to be dedicated to him and it's become popular to now say that Hubal was a moon god or that
he's related to the goddess a lot and therefore Allah is a moon god or the male version of a lot
that idea was popularized mainly in 1994 by Robert Mori and his book The Moon God Al-Alai in archaeology
of the Middle East and then different people ran with that notion in mainstream media but according
to the Islamic historian Al-Azakari the statue of Hubal was actually brought from Mesopotamia
from the city of Hitt pride that it had been in Damascus and personally I'm not surprised that
we find a Mesopotamian connection to Islam in this way because it always seems to be with these
symmetric religions that there's some linkage back to Mesopotamia or even less than that I think
the main linkage I foward to anchor the the movement of Islam it would be I pull it's a political
movement that would organize a group of people through tradition and also be as a defense against
other movements geographic movements like it would be a defense against Christian missionaries
Judean convention and religion and way of life was not considered a threat at all because it was
they were already downtrodden and scattered other than some small you know in other words every any
place that had more than a thousand people in any village or city or town in Arabia or Middle
East to eat all the way to India in parts of Europe had quote unquote Jews or Judeans living there
already right but them to form a group to impose tradition and all that would have never happened the
only thing that was around other than the far oriental philosophies and Hinduism and all that
that could pose a controlling let's say an overarching controlling effect on the culture would be
Christianity and the spread of that right so if you're going to develop a political system of
that includes religion tradition and all these other things it would have to be very stark
very plain and simple for people to understand it would have to be um stoic meaning you are who you
relate with right um actually that's not what stoic means but that's part of their edicts
which I agree with by the way so that's why you find in Islam for example you know you you should
associate with your own people and if you don't they're not viewed as equals and they should be
not considered equal it says i'm paraphrasing here from the actual what could be found in the
tradition until they convert to Islam you see so you are who you associate with so it actually
provided a defense against the movement uh the spread of Christianity which from judeian scholars
and leaders at the time again they were downtrodden had viewed it as being an abominable thing
for mankind and was very easy to convince people of that region of the same so we needed some kind of
it's a uniform code of tradition or religion to to block that and Islam was perfect for that
yeah there's been quite a lot of things written about the messianic streak that the Arabs had and how
that sort of came into interaction with the Jews or at least the Jewish sects that exist and
certainly will look at that but yeah but all cultures have that even the Native Americans have a
messianic streak it may not necessarily be the same Messiah but a superhuman or someone someone
that's going to come in first mop up clean up society and then rule it righteously indeed but if we
look at the you know the folks have been on Muhammad this founder figure i found that it's it's
legitimate to say that Muhammad was an actual historical figure despite people's occasional attempts
to deny that um i believe it's just somewhat to some degree yeah i believe there's a green telly
personally i'm sitting on the fence what is he only mentioned four five times in the correct it's
just the name i think it's a derivation of something else but but that's where i left off with it
because it for me the the actual um virility of the of the whole thing is is it's a political it's
purely a political movement which is completely understood yes or we don't need you don't need a real
person to do that but if he seems to exist that's fine but i would suggest he has nothing to do with
any of it um uh maybe posthumously i have seen and i'm trying to find it but i have seen that
there was this figure that actually had a different name not Muhammad that the Muhammad name came
after the fact but in other case there are there is a Greek text written during the Arab invasion of
Syria around 633 AD that mentions quote a false prophet has appeared among the sarsans the sarsans
was the name for the Arabs at the time so there was some kind of figure that was leading something
whether his name was Muhammad or something else is can be disputed i'm going to see if i can find
the name as we progress but in terms of starting points at least the story goes that this figure
will call in Muhammad was in a cave in 610 AD in angel visits him squeezes him so that he can't move
and tells him to recite what he was told about Islam after which he becomes suicidal and and
thinks that he's being possessed but eventually he obeys and then spends the next 12 years trying to
convert the people in his hometown by being mostly peaceful but an inefficient religious leader
and changing his tactics after that when he realized stuff wasn't working there's a lot more
that can be said but you know what have you seen about this figure at least in your studies about
his origins i had a hard problem a hard issue with understanding that anything that could be
salvaged from that time period did not have vowels in the text the vowels were put in later
so is it mahmud? mahmamid? mahmad? yes i've seen this also
yeah so the mahmud mahmad, mahmamid, sound can be attached to many things and should be put to the
side and look at the meat of the text what is it conveying and is it conveying enough that you
can build a religion on it and those that have influenced and used the text right because many don't
really use the Quran they just talk about the philosophy and what mahmamid said right later on
that's why for example if you go back you won't find any evidence of Islam until 800 there's no coin
age there's no writings there's no you know there's no evidence of it right so it's
most of it is poshimous and by the way personally my personal view on is i'm all for it
anything that could stop you know the law the stuff that the Christians are putting out in general
is a good thing another way to balance it right because it you know with Christians say they have
no law and they say you know love your neighbor but they never define love so that's why you have all
this they just it just helps people continue along what they're good at doing which is basically kill
each other so i would suggest that getting hung up on the mahmud mahmad mahmad mahmad aspect of it
for me in my studies was was very very minimal hey for example if you eliminated all of the names of
the prophets and the bible and just read what was said prophetically critically and what was
supposed to be you know verbally disposed to the people you'll get more out of it than getting hung
up on whether it was Isaiah or Jeremiah or you're right you see indeed to piggyback just off what you
mentioned about the the lack of vowels so the earliest Quran really only has consonants
but even then there's not even any diacritical marks which means that the consonants can be read in
any number of ways right it could be it could be a mixture of in other words of another cognate especially
if you've had influence from let's say Judeic authors they would be bringing their cognate and you
know their words it's very easy to just like in english you have you have words that are from other
languages like chandelier right that's French and whatever medical terms are Greek
so to me the actual individual the actual even the term jinn for example to jinn is not as important
as the what they do in their description right and what traditions and think what effect is it
going to have if it's adhered to in other words the if the text is subscribed to as the basis of a
religion or a way of life or tradition ultimately we know that no one in any religion follows what's in
the text pretty much but if they were to what would what structure cultural structure would emerge
from that that's what my main interest was yeah I mean as far as the Christian or possible Christian
derivations there was a german scholar Christoph Luxenberg although that's a pseudonym but he wrote in
2007 that parts of the Quran seemed to be derived from pre-existing Christian-era make texts that
were misinterpreted by later scholars so even like for example the virgins and paradise who are
supposedly waiting Islamic martyrs is actually should be rendered as white raisins which is very
anti-climatic well this song a lot of part many parts of it especially the prophetic parts
and the criticism of society reads like the song of songs or parts of the songs or
lamentations you know I mean it's very simple to to see the the origin based on the the ideology of
the writer the author you know and again there is no you're going to be hard pressed to find anything
prior to the year 900 you know pender otherwise right so we're talking about a pretty long stretch
between the origin and so forth it's my my whole point on it was if it came if Islam were
supposedly originally around that time and we know that all religions that are known as religions
now because by the way the real truth of anything that's supposed to be held or known in the religion
is still secret even if you read Genesis that is a in the bible that is just a recap that Moses
gave in the pentuitalk to israel after Egypt there's very partly very little information about
jet you know the creation or early man there so it's still secret right so you have all of these
things that are mentioned in the Quran are again just kind of glossed over it's the commentaries
and the dictates there are again you know how to run a society these we don't have over at
any knowledge regarding technical knowledge true you know a technical or let's say detailed
origin information that is public at all so I just want to throw that in there so if you're putting
together a text like the Quran or the the bible or anything like that it's going to be an overview
now it's it's it's it's also known actually there there it's very well known that there is technical
information and detailed information about our origin that does exist it's just never been made public
so you have to keep that in mind when you're looking at the veracity of a document you know how important a document is
yes that's correct and we will be looking a little bit at some of the other
Islamic documents just to conclude on the Muhammad bit and and to give some sort of a wrap-up
on his profile so he starts off by preaching in mecca could be petra makes about 70 converts in 12
years which is kind of bad averages up to about two people a month gets frustrated at the lack of
progress becomes confrontational with the local population once his uncle dies who's taken care of
him the locals chase him out of town for disturbing the peace so he flees to Medina where half the
population are Jews and they let him in he starts pressuring the Jews into making political
concessions towards a minute followers eventually by the way sounds like sounds like Joe
who is a Joseph Smith of of Mormonism but anyway just try to throw that in there I was laughing
while you're reading all that but could yeah I'm not surprised that these things repeat themselves
but so yeah they attack even though the Jews let them in they attack the smallest or the weakest Jewish
tribe the Banu Kanuka and drive them out of town the same happens to the second tribe the Banu Al-Nader
and then the third tribe as well the Banu Kareza are destroyed and enslaved
Muhammad then goes on to conduct about 66 raids and battles as a military leader within five years
of entering Medina he's killed or enslaved all the Jews and within five years of his death his
armies have killed off most other religions in Arabia so yeah I mean the notion of Islam
opposing Christianity you know certainly we'll get into that but from the point of view of this
Muhammad figure it seems like he was more about being manipulated by a spirit and then becoming a war
lord to advance this cause to compete I think with the Jews and the Christians who were dominance in
Arabia at least in the beginning that's how it seems I would say it's less competition than more than
making a geographical stake in establishing a geographical territory and it would have been done
all of this attributed posthumously and of course it makes sense that after you know about 30 percent
of the world's population is died from famine and hunger it's a good time to attack right I don't
see any of this as being noble on any account I mean look even if you read the book of Exodus you know
you know if you're the highest god why would you play around with the Pharaoh and play around
with this and that I don't think any of it is noble it just is that's just my you know how I view it
we're in a pretty bad spot as humans so in other words you're not going to find anything that
no matter what text you look at that supposedly teaches and preaches and demonstrates higher
morality you'll be hard to find it in the text it's just a matter of if you have allegiance to me you
do this right almost like just do as I say not as I do so it comes very natural I mean what people
ultimately want to do when you look at a history in terms of 50 and 100 year
pieces at a time is what they're good at and guess what that is killing each other right anyway that
was maybe a little general comet thrown in just to remind the listeners that they're not going to
hear anything very different if we discuss Islam or anything else because it's actually a political
you know it's but ultimately it's going to reflect all the political machinations and historical
machinations that we see and it all comes down to who you have allegiance to yeah you certainly
can't separate the the violence from what the religion is defined as but the sure so from if you
were talking about a higher level being in any religion you would never God that would act this way
because it's his desire and then have and then say that's a higher level of morality no
like someone recently asked me you know who's your god you have allegiance to and I say it's
Yahweh the god of war and they were laughing because I'm not going to mince words right is he god of war
right so you don't like it too bad right so that's why I like it running into people like one guy
you know he worships thought Thor I said okay cool you know just stick with him you know don't
start bouncing around you know um oh just to wrap up on the Muhammad a bit I did find this and who
ever wants to look into it really has to do it on their own because there's not much information but
it was said that his real name was Kathan Ibn Abdullah lot and somehow it gets changed to Muhammad later
but yeah sure I just want to again repeat it doesn't matter uh look for example if you look at the
Mormons that I consider the Muslims of the North America because they're they're almost exactly
the same you know I'm not well they're parallel so much that to see that they're not the Muslims
of Northern America means you haven't done any homework at all so it's it's just it doesn't matter
who who's ahead of it it's what is the outcome what kind of a structure does it set up uh right
what what how are the what is the religious aspect of it mean the stuff that people are told to do
regular regularly even if it's not adherent to the text which no one does by the way um
the social outcome and the political outcome again is is important you know like I've been in the
presence of uh let's say uh Muslim higher ups let's say and if you bring up the Quran they all kind
of like you know I don't want to talk about that there's nothing to do with that right just like I've
been in the presence of Christian higher ups and you bring up the Bible well what we do has nothing
to do with that I've been in the presence of quote-unquote Jewish higher ups you bring up the Torah or the
Bible again well what we do is nothing to do with that do you see my point so there's many ways to go
we can we can dig in pedantically into historians and texts and all that and it really has nothing
I mean look at the government the government has nothing to do with you know the way it's being run
with what's in their laws so there's many ways to discuss the topic and again just uh I would say
that they're all the same the only reason they're different is because of geography and culture
and that's changing with the internet and the new world order which is the new new new world order
which is going to fail and by the way just to throw this in all of your religions will not exist in
a little bit over a decade none of them will exist anymore no one will care no one will mention them
or anything so it's interesting we did God speak around this time so could you yeah the hope is that
it will be a resource that people can turn to even if only later but just to um let's talk from the
subject of the Quran a little bit because I think it's interesting when you look at the Islamic holy books
as a whole um the Quran is the most well-known but it's really only the size of the New Testament
it's not a comprehensive book like the biblical text is something important like the the procedure
for the five daily prayers isn't even mentioned in the Quran so according to mainstream Islam you
also need the Hadith and the Syrah which covers the sayings deeds and life of Muhammad there's also
the top seer which are the scholarly commentaries on Islam and if you're a Muslim who ignores those
other books and only lived by the Quran then you're called a Quranist which is actually an apostate
category did you find it to be difficult at all in your studies about Islam when the canon is so
fragmented across these multiple separate books no not at all I was expecting it just like the
various sects of Christianity like in the Eastern Orthodox Church you have to have a creed
which is an allegiance to the Eastern Orthodox Church right and yes it overtakes um
if you speak to not overtakes what's in the text or what's considered to be important whether
it's that text or not if you run into someone and use a devout Eastern Orthodox I said how do you know
if someone else is devout as you are they say they pull out an icon of the Virgin Mary and have them
kiss it if they don't kiss it they're not devout and it's like you got to shake your head and
do a double face palm and walk away you can't you can't work with that you know there's nothing to
work there you know it's kind of like give them a reflective vest and a plastic broom and go
that's what you do on this world nothing you can't form a higher society with that right and that
so when you have that kind of deviation or it's a new development
right I mean go look at the Muslim world right if it wasn't for what the the mahamadi and
Anglo treaties and all that was done in the 19th century you would you would you'd go to the Middle East
and it would be like the people in the Polynesian islands with that still wear banana leaves and go
spearfishing right but it would be the desert version of that time time would never
in other words if there wasn't an influence in the 19th century time would not have moved for
for two thousand years you would go to the Middle East and it would look just like it did three thousand
years ago and not well kept so you know when we talk about should they be doing this or be doing that
like when you get captured by ISIS for example or al-Qaeda you know the the radical ones
they the first thing they ask you you know if you find out if you're a Muslim they ask you
how many times did you pray today right and if you didn't pray at least five times you they shoot
you that's what that's their excuse for shooting you right I don't know if you've ever met anyone
who's captured by one of those groups there but that's first thing they always ask I haven't had
the pleasure but I'll take your word for it yeah I haven't been here but I know someone who has
and that's their excuse for shooting you we say it's good enough and it's not in the correct
it the whole thing is bizarre ultimately if we look at this in 50 year 100 year 200 year swaths of time
people will resort to do what they're good at doing which is killing each other so this is just another
excuse for killing someone ultimately but there is a lot of merit in the Quran itself if you
you know I think we had a discussion it refers to Moses many times you know as the law giver you know
indirectly and legitimizes the prophets and neighbor ham and all that too so you know it's kind of like
the origin who was Christopher Columbus well if we look at anything surviving that is direct evidence
of him he always signed his name in Greek and if you go to the island of heos there's always an argument
where who he was and where he was from there's a very modest house there and there's a little tiny
plaque no one knows about it you could find it this is the birthplace of the man known as Christopher
Columbus later he changed his name but if you could look this up all of the documents he ever signed
was in Greek because of course he was Spanish or Italian that's normal of course right you see my point
I'm being facetious we look at these things the same way you know yes this is what everyone thinks
it is and what we're told about it but what do we see and what do we hear about it you know actually
won't we do the research right it's lies upon lies upon lies so people can do what they're good at
doing which is kill each other which which you know can be glossed over in many ways why or whatever
but once you see a deviation like why bother writing it down why bother starting a religion why
bother adhering to anything if you're not going to follow it because humans have the innate
idea taught and epigenetically somehow that they need that structure right and they really do what
happens is if someone were brought up on an island with the Quran or anything and they read it they
would they would be a good life to adhere to it generally but then you would find other people
that were if you called yourself a Muslim you would see they're acting radically different so now
you have a choice do I act like they do or do I act like I'm supposed to other way I learned
and usually it's the the first one I'm going to act like everyone else I also found that
Quran wise one of the reasons it's so hard to discern the changes that took place in Islam's
history is because of how they look at their literature so it's interesting in western scholarly
thought older is better which is why older biblical manuscripts are given more weight than the
recent ones but in Islam it's actually the reverse newer is considered better because to them that
indicates continued divine revelation so it gets hard to establish what the original material
said and the religion ends up being very dualistic because you always have one verse that contradicts
another older verse and depending on the situation you can use any of them so it's tricky to study
in terms of that right but but the obvious thing there is let's talk about divine revelation
but the gods left all the higher gods left it's the lower demons that are here the lower the the higher
gods sent the lower demons first the higher gods came and they said screw this from out of here they
left if you look at the ancient greed gods they left one by one the gods of the bible left
right if they didn't leave there wouldn't be a promise of their return oh I'm promising that I'm
returned because I never left yeah sure that's crazy talk the reason there is you read about all the
messionic figures in the godlike figures returning is because they're not here the reason you call
it a return is because you're not present so if you know anything or anyone that's getting divine
revelation I'd like to know and show me proof of it because the gods are not here yes they could do
it telepathically and from a distance but I don't think you're that special jack that's what I tell
people when they say they have divine revelation because that's not the way the higher gods work
when the higher gods come and they give divine revelation everybody knows or at least
geographically everybody knows yes that's a very good point sounds very intuitive when it's express
that way right so when you're dealing with spiritual entities giving you revelation and there were
a lower class ultimately we're made in a different way that we are promised to be higher than them so
why would you do that either way there's it's a terrible mix to discuss a religion and its history
because the it's like discussing a tennis and baseball you know two different sports almost I
mean they're both sports but completely different things the reason anyone another was here you
can start a religion without ever writing anything down you know like a loose cult that would
it grow into whatever right it's very simple look at like American patriots not one of them know
any of the laws or the constitution they just they got everything from watching Superman comics
and watching TV or some civics class right so you can start a religion without any holy writ
you just you just it's by word of mouth oral right and you you put your you put everything in place
that you need you know your houses of worship and your magistrates and your priests and your followers
you can organize all that without a writ now imagine a religion set up that way and then go
ahead and look at Christianity that's exactly how it functions Islam functions that way so does
Judaism it doesn't matter how much like for example in Judaism they've already gotten away from the
Tanakh or the Torah and they do the Talmud and other things right so hard whatever but they can't
even they can't even rationalize that they can't they just talk about little excerpts of it they
can't see it holistically indeed no as far as just creating an ad hoc religion we saw that in
the two thousands with the what is it religion of the flying spaghetti monster or whatever that the new
atheist just made up to poke fun at their Christians it's not based on any oh you don't you don't
need to poke fun at a Christian just put a mirror in front of them or just record them and let them
just listen I mean they do it's like do you need poke fun at a clown I mean but anyway
yes one wants to be harsh one could say it that way okay so the the last thing that I'll touch
on as it relates to the Quran is just what some scholars had to say about the older Arabic manate
scripture which I thought was very interesting I can't validate any of it because I don't read
Arabic but it's worth taking note of because multiple people have pointed it out which is that when
you read the older stuff the writing is barely readable I'm going to quote from what a German
Quranic scholar called Jard Puyin said when the Yemeni government put him in charge of a restoration
project for possibly the oldest Quranic text called the Sunnah it's from a 1999 article in the Atlantic
called what is the Quran which you can still read online so quote my idea is that the Quran is a kind
of cocktail of text that were not at all understood even at the time of Muhammad many of them may even
be a hundred years older than Islam itself even within the Islamic tradition there is a huge
body of contradictory information including a significant Christian substrate the Quran claims
for itself that it's clear but if you look at it you will notice that every fifth sentence or so
simply doesn't make sense many Muslims will tell you otherwise of course but the fact is that a
fifth of the Quranic text is just incomprehensible this is what has caused the traditional
anxiety regarding translation if the Quran is not comprehensible even in Arabic then it's not
translatable end quote which is very interesting yeah that just supports the comment I made before
you don't need any of that it would here's the thing the the way that humans are taught and the human
society is set up that if you had an adherent group let's say adherent to the text they would only
last maybe three-quarters of a generation before they die most of them would give it up
it said always we don't need to live by that it's just this interesting thing I see that all the time
you see it in the corporate culture you know they have corporate rules working in a big company
and very you know they always think about how to get around them or how to find quote-unquote
loopholes so when you already have that mentality and the higher up so the leaders of a religion
it's you know they don't have to say that they've deviated from anything understood or not understood
again it doesn't matter if it's understood or not because the purpose of it was never to
be any delivery of any revelation or anything anyway you see
it's purpose was there because it's like let's say you started a religion right we have a checklist
okay we need a text check we need a priesthood check we need a geography check we need
global people that we can convince the global people that want to think they want to be better people
and if they do this they'll be better check we need an enemy check so if you have that checklist
you can make any you can create a religion around anything any concept you know even science right
science has all of that by the way and science doesn't follow their texts and quote-unquote scientists
said then you have the the enemy is the anti-scientific or the religious people you
yeah this is there's an undercurrent there is a spiritual mental very strong undercurrent
that has been controlling the planet or the inhabitants where
giving example i had a call yesterday with some people haven't spoken to in a very long time and
i said look get over there were many questions about what's happening society in the earth all
so get over it this is a garden planet and when you make it a garden as big as covering most
of the planet and with full flora and fauna you what what what could you imagine going on you're
not going to it's not designed it's not a put together to be a high-tech you know central race running
the galaxy type thing it's a garden it's a garden planet what do you know about making garden small
and large you have creatures you have plants and then then you have okay these bipedal you know
hairless you know whatever's and they think they run the planet yes they have more advantages for
many reasons than all the other creatures in this garden but do you expect it to be any more than
just that you'd be a fool right so it's a garden planet and we just happen to be part of the flora
and we're fauna and we're unique and ill prepared you know we're born naked right hairless
we don't have claws in our teeth are too small to defend and what do you expect look it's so
easy to come to come through fly through here and influence these morons and that's what you're
living under and it's a garden you're not living in some part of the galaxy that is set up was set
up to be anything special it's well a garden you know by the way people take their gardens very seriously
if someone is a high net worth let's say wealthy and they have a comfortable life they take their
gardens very seriously by the way but it's still a garden it's not their living room it's not
their library it's not you see what I mean it's a garden planet so don't it's whatever you expect from
it keep in mind that you're living in a garden and you're just one of the fauna it's very simple
so again so if you're looking at Islam and its history for example you can go back in historical
texts and accounts all the way back till post-flood and find many accounts even in the bible in other
places in history that do parallel what's in the Quran and the way of life that's taught in Islam
right very parallel i like going forward mormans are the muslims of North America
they're not muslim obviously but it's almost identical it's it's scary how similar it is right
how many wives can a morman have right how do they view their right to a place on the planet how do
they view non-mormans how do they you see the only thing is they don't really have food laws that's
because they're they're a hybrid of christian you know they got the Christianity and they're actually
they use the the christian symbology as well so they're not you know diametrically opposed like Islam is
but they are very much the same formula it's a formula like for a Christianity has a formula
modern Judaism has a formula it's the Babylonian based right the Christianity is a very
lax formula it pretty much takes everything in there was a saturday live back in the 70s
they were doing the juice blender a parody commercial you put anything in there you know you make it
a nutritious juice right that's Christianity Islam retains some law and a lot of dogma because it needs
to have a stoic view because it's there to protect the geography and culture of of the people
yes and i think on that note we'll take a look a bit at this connection between Islam and
historically Christianity and Judaism because it's well known that the Quran contains a reference
system more than 50 people in events found in the bible a number of scholars have also commented on
how Muhammad was influenced by Jews and Christians so i want to start by quoting the Iranian scholar
al-Dashdi who wrote a book in the mid 70s called 23 years about Islam so quote for those who consider
the Quran to be a miracle because of its contents the difficulty is rather that it contains nothing
new in the sense of ideas not already expressed by others all the moral precepts of the Quran
or self-evidence in general acknowledge the stories in it are taken in in identical or slightly modified
forms from the lore of the Jews and the Christians whose rabbis and monks Muhammad had met and
consulted on his journeys to Syria and quote and i've also come across professors of Islamic history
like doctor Sami Aldeib from Switzerland who claimed similar to you that the Quran was written by
rabbis what more can you say about that particular point the rabbis influence well uh let's say
rabbis would be like a lawyer when you go into a partnership or an office they don't do much they have
paralegals that do all the work like the scribes so when you say was written by rabbis is it entirely
correct no but it is a rabbinical school that did that yes for sure not for sure meaning that i that
there's any first hand account or testimony to that but you can just see it right like for example
you can look at artifacts of any sort non-written artifacts you know furniture toys
cars or whatever and if you have a a discerning mind you could see what who made that right where it
came from the origin right you can always see for example an Italian sports car versus a German sports
car versus an American sports car down to any detail right yeah i mean you could show me one
square foot of a car supercar and i could tell you if it's an Italian supercar an American supercar
a German supercar just from a small detail because i know how to discern that so if you know how to
discern how things are written uh and uh in other words you know how you have like i am big pentameter
which was popularized popularized by the ancient Greeks to it has an effect you know you have
limericks in other forms of grammatical tools right literary tools the literary tools that the
rabbinical scholars used meaning dictates the way they outlined and also the storyline and the
ideology is 100% of judeian influence 100% now the leeway that i give it there is that this is not some
nefarious conspiracy of some quote unquote Jews to get together and write and create a new religion
because if you go back and look at the judeians and their extraction and the people of the arabia
because remember the the non-Arab's the the Persians are also Islam now in mass right and it's not
there it's not their native religion anyway but if you there is no conspiracy there i the only place
i see islam being conspiratorial is when it's it's thrust into asia and the Persia right
afghanistan those because those people are really nothing to do with the direct lineage as
the people of arabia the southern part of middle east and the judeians they're all extracted from
Abraham you see so it's not nefarious in that sense for them to do it like there's a saying in
new york if you want a good lawyer get a jewish lawyer what what does that mean you know so it's
it's a hundred percent natural and plausible that it was done that way from any scholarly point
and it's evident once you understand one another way to see it is read the Quran and read the
Talmud the Babylonian Talmud Sephardic other Syrian Talmud other parts of the world Talmud that
were written and you know if you if you the ideology even the way it's written even though it's a
different language if you hold it up to the light i mean it's exactly the same you know source
and there are arabic writings by the way much later uh uh that include like if you study the
history of algebra the medical sciences and just general sciences some alchemic texts these are
things that various mathematical models and scientific models that came from the arabic world
right that were let's say followed the dictate of the arabic world are very dissimilar in the way
they're written from what is written in the Quran but if you look at obviously the biblical
characters but the way that not the bible itself but Talmudic
character writing style and let's say the book of Enoch writing style the book of jash or the book of
jubilee's writing style and the Quran it's exactly the same writing style
but there are other arabic writings obviously when you study algebra in medical practice you see
you know how many even i remember in grade school we were told these particular sciences were
attributed of arabic origin right i mean this is still commonly known i think you've heard of it right
certain things came from arabic culture that we use today in science math and other things medical
and there are writings that are still preserved from and it's very very different
than anything you'd find in an Islamic text this is not a put down or a nefarious conspiracy this is
natural this is not attacking or trying to what is the call when you reduce something revise anything
because it's not going to be around in a decade anyway either it's Christianity or Judaism as you
know it or any of it so and again just to to restate this is an apropos time to discuss these things
and as far as the the christian or the jewish connection goes we do have evidence that the
the Muhammad character had a history with the jews in the christian sex he was familiar with the apocryphal
stories of Christianity whether from the ebonite or other christian sex and obviously the Islamic
version of the christ in the virgin Mary appeared to be taken from infancy gospels of tomas and
in james also one of the earliest commentaries on the Quran was written by someone called mucatil
ibn sulayman in the eighth century and he had an interesting quote he said quote the apostle used to
sit at al-marwa at the booth of a young christian called jabber and they used to say the one who teach
is Muhammad most of what he brings is jabber the christian um and quote and so it does seem that
Muhammad was partaking in these theological discussions of Judaism and Christianity and Islam
convenantly insert itself into that by appropriating the material.
well you have to realize that the the divine gods the higher white gods left of
i'd say four five hundred bc and then they sent the biblical Messiah of uh uh you know two thousand
years ago four five hundred years later to do his dissertation beginning dissertation on his
graduate thesis right and then he left after he was killed executed so
there's nothing left to do there's you're not going to you it's all um if you're getting anything
it's uh oral history and study there is no divine revelation since then i hate to tell people
i it doesn't mean you can't get a spirit talking to you but not the higher ones no they left a long
time ago so you're talking about most of the higher gods left twenty five hundred years ago the
highest god and five hundred years after that we have the biblical Messiah doing his graduate
dissertation and that's it i mean so the rest of it have fun you know knock yourself out
indeed the last thing i want to touch on regarding the submitted connection to Islam is this period
of the crusades that you mentioned we briefly touched on earlier the more popular revisionist work
around this stuff was done in the seventies about Islamic history and basically you had scholars at
the time who came out and said that the accepted picture of Islam's origins wasn't based on actual
seventh century documents but rather on various narrative sources that were compiled decades
afterwards and Muhammad was not perceived as the founder of a new religion at the time but rather
like more like a preacher in the Old Testament tradition who talks about messianism similar to the
Jews plus you have many of the documents that actually refer to the followers of Muhammad as
quote unquote children of hey guy and the tribe of ishmail and that was their main identity as Arabs at
the time not Islam which would have come later and since the Byzantine empire was ruling over
Jerusalem the Arabs would have been in unison with the Jews at least about invading and reclaiming
their birthright by joining forces and then later on due to theological and political differences
they would have split apart in the Arabs forming Islam after the fact so yeah yeah we're talking about
hard times you see there were hard times physically because of the natural disasters then you
had hard times where you had traditions falling apart and culture falling apart just like you see
it right now with the quote unquote pandemic and all this other stuff right and by the way if anyone's
listened to Greek speak or other stuff before I've discussed everything that's happening and will be
happening so it not because I'm you know have any special knowledge or anything it's just because I
know how to discern information that works in information that doesn't and hopefully others will also
yes and certainly this material will help with that okay so to conclude this episode I think we'd be
negligent not to cover the current day situation in the Middle East and how that came to be
obviously the Ottoman Empire covered most of that region for a long time until the 18th century
in france britain italy and russia conquered much of the territory followed by the levantine
aridian territory is going to the allies after world war one can you talk about the real reason behind
the western nations fighting the Ottomans and finding them to be a problem so much so that war
was necessary to break up the empire well that's world war one yes and it was also germany flexing
its muscle which who didn't lose the war by the way world war one never really there were no
winners or losers it just stopped because of the plague that the americans brought over right so
they were sensible enough to stop the war and take advantage of breaking up the austrian
huggarian empire let's say the kaiser and all that and the same who was allied by the way with the
Ottomans right so as far as my history that of that my knowledge is yes they were I think i
allied so you look at the posh gemis again and hypothetical presumption that germany lost world war one
it makes it natural that we have to now turn our focus and beat up on the Ottoman empire and
break it up and give them ultimatums most of the harshaledimatums that were given to the Ottoman
empire were done by the vatican Jesuits right all your people have to take surnames use a romanized
script and you use our calendar or will wipe you out completely so and i would have been easy for
them to have mustard up favor because they had already committed the Armenian and Greek genocides
and all of that they were known to be extremely harsh and they sort of retained the bays family
the b-e-y-s those are like the sultans they sort of retained enough of their wealth that they said
okay we're not going to be eating out of garbage cans okay let's break it up you see
so it's kind of like if you're going to break up Microsoft when Bill Gates was there I said well
I'm a billionaire but make please keep me a hundred millionaire right i don't want to right so
have to shop at Walmart or something and they agreed and um I would say that most of the way the
middle east was carved up was done at least 50 years prior to that the the actual way was done I mean
you could research it there's not direct especially on the internet you're not going to find much
direct information unless you really really start digging under you know pass the undertow
you know you know when you go into something in an undertow and the water takes you in another direction
now the undertow is on the surface so anything you try to research on the internet that's true
immediately you're shown the undertow the stuff that carries you away so just beware
that's why for example if you look at the all of the countries in the middle east have
red white and green flags you ever noticed that they also have a British monarch a British parliamentary
type governments they also have the least favorable class of people ruling over them
they in other words if you went back into the 19th century and you saw the history of the people
that are the rulers in the middle east now the families and all that those were the people that
everyone hated and the reason you you put such people in power is to maintain your power
because if they if you put a puppet government of people that are hated by their own people
the government could be ruthless at a drop of a hat they'll do anything to hold that power and be
your puppet because if they go against you then you feed them you send them back to the people
and they never want to do that so you have all of these traits right that are basically
the handiwork of 19th century European colonialism and imperialism but not from one particular empire
it's it was everyone had their hand in structuring the middle east of the 19th century meaning the
Germans the French and the British predominantly the Americans had their hand in there as well
but the Americans were already they were on the other end of the stick also because you have 50
states to deal with and they they fixed the Americans they had the Americans squared away
by the 1890s when that's when they went from having England as an enemy to an ally where
Germany was an ally and then became the enemy so when you see the Americans switch from
English being an enemy and Germans being an ally switching it to English being an ally
and Germans being an enemy that's when the Americans were defeated by the way by the British again
I don't think I've ever discussed this but
so that colonial power was done with also so that's pretty much what you've got I mean if you
really want to know more about it you could research individual each country like for example
Jordan will be very adherent to English parliamentary style of rule where if you go to Egypt
let's say you get arrested in Egypt they use Napoleonic law on you right I don't know if you're
familiar with that I know someone who was arrested in Egypt and they use Napoleonic law on them as
there is an Napoleonic law here in Egypt right you so you see the different variances
how else would you explain other than it's a post-imperial post-colonial grouping
not not dissimilar to what a lot of the African countries right where you have the Dutch the belge
the Belgium governments English French right when in there and now they're they're still puppet
governments there and most of their laws stem from you German also influence you see
what's going to be very unique about what's coming now and what it's here is just that it's not
evident is a group of superpowers emerging in the Middle East with southern euro
and parts of Africa satellite powers so this is already happening it's just not
not evident yet and it will be mostly in place in the next five years
which will be a unique perspective on on the times themselves because
but not so unique because if you go back to the early days of of known civilization where was the
super power base right Middle East or that part of the world yes correct I will be asking about that
a bit shortly but just to go back to the current situation or at least the recent history
in the Middle East parts of Arabia there were certain parts that didn't belong to the Ottomans
a large part was also controlled by the first Saudi state since the 1700s which was founded by
Ivansod eventually his dynasty ends up ruling over all of Arabia but what exactly is the story behind
that dynasty and their role not only in promoting Wahabism today but just seeming to be tied
to the west in this almost interdependent way I would say again it's all English they would not have
been able to do anything without the gunpowder and the politics of the British or that European
influence they had a very poor reputation way even today they do but you know by the way if you
see there was an article recently public from the government there and they said we are no longer
an oil producing nation but it didn't make the mainstream news of you are you familiar with it maybe
you can research it so then so what are they what are they doing then I don't think they're running
a harrowing on camels are they so what are they up to think about it well in context of you know
the future superpowers how how are they a superpower right how are they going to become a superpower
I don't think they ever will intuitively you know what I mean because they're not going to get
a global respect as such but other countries north of them would give an example if you
dress the way they do they can't even get on a bicycle they're going to go five feet and they'll
get caught in the chain and they'll fly head over handlebars bust their chin open on the sidewalk
you see the metaphor yes I do see that yeah they would have to abandon that at the very least yeah
yeah and they will eventually but you know yeah it's just uh what it is it's it's pretty sad it's a
garden planet dude and they're definitely not small and like roses I'll tell you that
but it seems as if they also have a very interesting relationship with the US as far as
ties to them that seem almost counterintuitive yeah world war two FDR did that they ran out of oil
here I think the US now is the largest oil producing nation
uh in other words it jockey's between place number one and two for the world but you don't hear
about that anymore or now I think it's mostly in the region of Montana like Montana can
in in parts of that world you call a rato can provide the entire world's oil petroleum and they are
you know there's a lot of it coming out of Venezuela in other places but um no I don't see any
significance with the wahabi other than being a distraction they're not they're they're not in there
if they're in there prophetically and what's coming they're going to be a satellite not any more
important than the Greeks or the Turks let's say it doesn't matter how many gold plated
Lamborghini's they have in their parking lot you know now that I understand Iran is another
muslim nation with its own non-automine history so they were never conquered by the Turks
became muslims and they're not and they're not Arabic that as well they're the same bloodline as the
people in Afghanistan and parts of India right we obviously don't have time to cover the history but
if we focus on the Iranian revolution you have Reza Khan the military leader who became Shah after
the 1921 coup he was backed by the US and Britain his son Muhammad takes over after world war two
also backed by the west they put in place programs to westernize the country eventually
Mausadek becomes prime minister but's heads with the western agenda allegedly because he wants to
nationalize the oil industry among other things so the CIA have been removed by a coup and
Muhammad Reza is able to rule more firmly as the Shah eventually he also loses power thanks to the
1979 revolution which is sort of cast as a pro western authoritarian monarchy being replaced with
an anti-western Islamic theocracy what do you know about those events and why were the Islam
is able to remove the monarchy well the thing was to redo the Middle East and you redo something by
having a crisis you know if it's too if you want to change the way your house looks or a house that
you have let's say vacation house and it's too expensive to do and too much work to redo you just burn
it down make sure you have enough insurance that's the way it works you know like for example the in
2002 the NATO the North Atlantic terrorist organization I'm sorry North Atlantic treaty organization
put out a report that 9/11 was insurance fraud not terrorism and then they raised that right
so that's all it is just an insurance game so you want to you want to have an enemy
so there was a period where they they did let it happen but then they took control of it they're the
the I told that first was part of the rainy and revolution was sort of adherent and more lawful
and then they got subverted again right no different than Krushchev you know was in the middle of
the communist era in 1952 it was in the UN saying that Soviet Union is no longer communist 1952
you see so what was he saying we're we're finished with that we're going to join the rest of the world
but we have to say we are a certain way because we need to have that that dip bipolar you know
black and white good and bad right so the people in Iran say the west is bad and the people in the
west of Iran is bad that's good for business so and it doesn't make any sense
it when you when you when you live in a country like Iran the way it is now and the way it has been
for the past you know whenever 30 40 years it doesn't make any sense at all right same with Russia
unfortunately they opened Russia was redone the Soviet Union just fell because the IMF says
where your money is no good anymore very simple is that they're going to do that to the US also
but too many countries are pinned to the US dollar so they have to figure out how they're going to
deal with that cascade but I think the people of of Persia or Iran are are going to play a major
major major role in what's coming in the next few years obviously their their government's going to
change it's it's not going to last very long and when I say superpower in the Middle East they
are going to be one of them and I've gone out on the limb and said this many times I'm quite
confident say it again is that what you call the ranger Persia is going to be very close allies with
modern day israel I know it doesn't seem that way but I know someone in Tokyo the other than the
Yakuza the largest underworld body in Tokyo is the Persian Iranian Mafia and the Israeli Mafia
from the Masad and their best friends so if the underworld intelligence agencies and the you know
the black market people are the best friends are Persians and Israelis that's going to bubble to the
surface soon you see so they're you know the the best thing for marketing the old culture of the
planet is for Israel to threaten Iran for with war and Iran to threaten Israel with war
while those who control both of those countries in the back know that they're best of friends
right and that will surface that will come to a surface as well because no matter how much
let's say shift over israel for a moment difference there is between the Arab world and Israel
you know if you remember the the narrative in the 70s oh we're gonna all the Arab nations
and we're gonna push israel out into the ocean right onto the sea was one of most common narratives
right for all of that considered the Persians are not Arabs so just keep that in your hat
so when israel starts to make major alliances even though they are now like for example there are a lot
of countries in in Middle East that are opening airport flights back and forth to israel in the past
year that never have before would have considered it i think there's over three or four countries now
that we're banning flights from israel in the Middle East keep in mind those are still Arabic countries
where Persian Persia or modern day Iran is not
so it would be super easy for them to join based on that old narrative that the Arab countries wanted
to push israel into the sea not just solely but just saying so keep these things in mind
and because when these things start happening it's not going to make any sense but if you know
it's going to happen it makes lots of sense you know indeed it's very interesting
well wrapping up i mean a lot has been said about the growth of radical islam in the last four decades
whether it's usbakt mujahideen forces in the Soviet afghan war in the 80s al-Qaeda in the 90s muslim
brotherhood in the 2000s or ISIS most recently who seem to be oddly vanishing and reappearing in
the last four years what do you know about you know the origins of these radical islamist movements
particularly recently in what their ties are to sort of government conspiracies so to speak
sure well it's it's more than a conspiracy it's a constructive reality a lot of people talk about
the CIA backing them up which is true but this it's the state department that flips the bill so when
ISIS shows up with 2000 brand new toyota is made in Texas because they have the larger radiators which
do better in desert environments people queried toyota why does ISIS have all these new trucks and
like well i don't know ask the u_s_ state department are the ones that ordered it now of course most
people don't know this but the CIA has its own satellites in space it has its own spy planes it
has even has its own attack carrier group most people don't know that right maybe you can fathom
that they have satellites and other and spy planes but most people don't know they have their own
aircraft carrier group it's not talked about but it exists uh they still have the state the
u_s_ state department flip the bill so it's just a proxy army just like it's good for business you know
it's not a big deal i mean i was showing someone just bought a used cars just a segue here for a second
Volkswagen put out a two passenger i mean a two door car that got 248 miles per gallon
and back in 2014 the only made 250 of them those would have been and of course because they only made
250 of them they cost about a hundred grand uh and they never went into production well the CEO got
you know a few phone calls and he's not to do it at all he just made 250 i think he suffered a stroke
or something you know very easy to do uh so it's the same same stuff man you know we should all be
driving cars i get 250 miles per gallon or you know 120 a hundred and let's say 200 150 kilometers per
liter that's a that would be the standard but why isn't that happening you see because it's bad for
business not because you're not going to be burning oil but because now you can travel much
cheaply the whole thing is to not travel so how many times if you ever heard of a state department
warning not to travel to this country because of terrorism right i i read that stuff like for
example like with this the pandemic of 2020 i didn't care what the media was saying i went to the
federal registry every government has its own registry that it puts out a remanter every few weeks
on you know its policies and business i didn't see much mentioned in there about any kind of pandemic
he just said covid 19 and associated and related other related things like what maybe we all
have to get a digital ID and digital currency like that's related so you don't look at the media every
government has its own registry federal registry you go read that so yeah that that whole thing is
i heard a lot of ISIS stop fighting a lot of them did because they got stimulus checks from the
U.S. Treasury too you know it's true yeah apparently you can buy anything including peace
well that we're not made uh it's a garden planet but we're not i think i gave the metaphor where
let's say uh one day everyone wakes up on the planet and they see these huge independence day style
UFO motherships in the sky and everyone gets scared all the governments capitulate into the fear and
say let's make world peace and after the world peace is formed all the motherships open up and kill
everyone on earth and there's a few survivors and the one of the survivors asks why did you kill us
and he says well we created you to be a war like race to take you out here into the universe to help
us fight our wars but since you wanted peace we don't need you anymore so they destroyed you
how difficult is that to understand the the klingons and the romulists in Star Trek
actually when you watch the Star Trek the humans in the Federation are there
where not when you look at these other races those other races are metaphors of human society
not the humans everyone thinks we're they look at the humans in Star Trek as being the humans know
that humans are some idealistic race not us we are like there was one old Star Trek
where the the race war the slave two guys the guy played the riddler in the Batman he was
their white on one side and black on the other side and one wants to kill the other one and
slave the other and he says well you're both the same and he says no we're not I'm white on the left
and black on the right he's black on the left and white on the right you remember that episode
just to show how ridiculous it was that that's so every time you see a race in Star Trek
that is an aspect of the human race here now and the actual humans in Star Trek are some idealistic
golden age fictional thing that many aspire to I don't think I've ever discussed the Greek
commentary on Star Trek but there you go no very interesting so yeah I think as a very last
question I'll you know you've already touched on what the future holds for that region
obviously they can't continue in a religious delusion forever can you talk about the actual
machinations that will take place to resolve the tensions there yeah the easiest way to resolve
tensions is with crisis and the promise of a better life that's all so what you're going to see
in the Middle East is the formation for example of not necessarily because it is going to be a world
center it won't flush out the western influence it's actually going to invite it in but one of the
the let's say how do you call it a road marker you know when you're traveling on the highway it
tells you five miles ahead to the next exit about a mile away from the exit you know you're going to
the exit that brings you to the new world order being in the Middle East would be a civil war
in what you what's called Iraq al-Araq a civil war it would be very mild in other words it won't be
like any of the wars that you've seen there recently and it will split the country in half politically
and culturally not just politically culturally meaning the northern part of the country north
western part of the of Iraq will become the new Assyria and when that happens it's also going to
take land from Turkey and modern day Syria as well and I've explained over a decade ago that you're
going to have wars in Syria and places like that because that to soften them up because of this
reason and then you had the wars in Syria starting in 2014 right so you will see a mild civil war
as such you're going to see the the unification of Iran from right now Iran has Persia has two
governments Iran has two governments they have the religious side and the administrative secular side
right they're going to unify they're also going to unify with the needs which are the the people that
they think they're the modern they live across Iraq oh man Kurdish people they're going to unify
because they're really Persian even though they have a slightly different language the the Kurdish people
think they have about 27 different states spread out and they're considered to be radical terrorists by
the Turks you know the pkk or something so that that will happen there Israel is going to purge
Palestinian jurisdictions out of the main West Bank and Gaza will expand it will become much
larger than it is now and it will become a state and also ally of Israel so these are things you're
going to see unification of Cyprus and Turkey right now Cyprus is split in half they're going to work
with the Turks Greece is going to work with the Turks very closely and they're going to be satellite
nations further on you will have another another civil war type political civil war in Israel
where they will put a more spiritual government in there instead of these labor parties
or this or that or the other it'll be going towards more of a quote unquote religious but not
Orthodox religious like you see now as is like in Jerusalem is ruled by let's say Orthodox
to Jewish but it won't be Jewish it'll be more towards the older today in principle
and that civil war in Israel is going to be political one and it will stress the significance of
having a monarch instead of just a prime minister and a president by the way wherever you see a
government that has a prime minister that's their head judge a minister is a judge they also have a
president Israel has a president also because that's who signs the executive order for the administration
so that's what you're going to see coming in the least in the next five years I would say the
mile marker that or kilometer marker that lets you know this is going to be happening would be the
the second or first thing that I mentioned which was a civil war in Iraq that's going to yield a
a country a new country in the Middle East new Assyria I call it and there are plenty of Assyrians
to go back home they haven't been there as a country in 2500 years I'd say
so there you go in a nutshell there's a lot more detail I can get into but I think those are
that's a thousand times more than you'll hear anywhere else I should say about what's coming
and I don't give dates but I know the times because the dates are fictional I think I've gone over
the fictional calendar and I don't say that the January through December Monday through Friday is
fictional Monday through Sunday or whatever is fictional they say it the people that provided to you
say it's fictional what better you know like for example when you talk about attorneys you know
they based you know they say oh yeah we're respectful and we do justice and I was like what are you
talking about dude it's fiction your whole thing is based on fiction and internally publicly the
attorneys defend like they're on some noble quest right but if you look at if you speak to them
individually and show them their documentation everything is a fiction look up legal fiction
for even on the basic google search it tells your legal fiction is that something that everyone
knows is false but it's presumed to be legitimate legally or to be litigated on right like if you're
arrested for charge you know charged with stealing rocks from the moon that's why if you look at
people that are in federal prison 70% are in prison on conspiracy charges it's like what's it's
totally intangible it's all based on plea bargaining so in the future also you won't have any attorneys
and you won't have alipathic doctors either fortunately for example the medicine that you have has
nothing to do with health it's alipathic look up alipathic medicine or alapathy
ALOPA THY it has to do with offering some kind of treatment that reverses symptoms has nothing
to do with health none of that will be around in the future fortunately you cannot you cannot
move forward with this types of religions science medicine and law that you have your stuck this is it
you're you're finished this is the end of it and if if it wasn't the end of it
everyone should go into a panic and make sure that it is because you cannot move forward in a
positive direction with all of the systems in place it doesn't matter it's not political right it's
every part of your culture is a f'dop big time but here's the thing you don't have to do anything
and even if you try to do anything you would be stopped by the forces that are in control now
and by the divine forces the divine forces are going to be sending a mop up crew
right so so it's still a long and arduous road yes and we will be looking at some of those
details more closely in subsequent episodes but yeah i think that we've covered quite a lot of ground
and we should be able to wrap up on on that note yes and in conclusion i do consider
Islam to be one of the more noble religions if not one of the most noble because simply not
because i'm an adherent or believer but because they have rules and laws that can be beneficial
where the Christians have no rules the Judeans shame on them or the Jewish people they do have
rules but shame on them they're convoluted and are not biblical but at least they have rules too
well i think okay i think that brings our conversation to an end we'll be continuing in
subsequent episodes wrapping up probably by looking at the Buddhist and Hindu religious leanings
and see what we can extract from those thank you Greek for today
great welcome i think we had a good talk and thank you to the listeners for tuning in
and we will catch you at the next episode
[music fades out]
(dramatic music)