Greetings to everyone and welcome to the seventh episode of the Godspeak podcast.
I'm the Archon and I'll be joined in a second by the Greek as we continue our talks
about religion and the supernatural.
We're moving on from Western and Central Asian belief systems to the Eastern ones and
I hope people continue to find our talks informative.
So let's get into it.
Godspeak.com has no political, religious or corporate affiliations and is completely
managed by myself.
Nothing has changed there.
So thank you again for tuning in and I hope you enjoyed the conversation.
Hello, Greek.
Yeah, greetings.
Are there?
Yes.
It's been a while.
Yeah, it's been a while since we did the last one but I trust you've been keeping
well.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, as expected.
So yeah, I'm happy that we're resuming the podcast.
It would be a shame not to conclude the last few episodes.
I planned for us to talk about Eastern religions today, which is something that's become
very adulterated in the West.
I guess it's because Europeans and North Americans are content with the microwave versions
of those belief systems.
Is that an observance that you've come across in your studies of these subjects that it's
a bit watered down?
Well, it's worse than watered down.
It's just an Eastern religion in name only but if we look at what the, let's say, the
indigenous Easterners are doing with it, it's almost the same but they have a little more
history or actually being their history, a culture and basically ethos of those people.
So I always have saying it's just like these, like in parentheses, these white people are
not happy with Judaism and Christianity.
They either go to Islam or Buddhism typically, you know.
And what's offered, the gates that they go through are pretty poor.
In other words, what they go through is the, let's say, without being too conspiratorial,
premeditated, the intelligence agencies are very concerned about people's belief systems,
right?
So basically hijacked and filtered through intelligence agencies or financial systems
or what's called surface government, right?
So they're getting that watered down version of it.
Yeah, I never really looked into that much as far as the historicity in the 20th century,
you saw a lot of swamis and Buddhist leaders that came over to the West and found a lot
of popularity with celebrities and stuff.
But I never quite did look into the intelligence aspect of that.
Yes.
I say, there's no intelligence there anyway in the intelligence agencies and they know
that, give you a short little quirk, someone that has a lot of Greek speak downloads.
It's not one you know actually.
X spouse was intelligence agency, not US.
And the first day thought it was subversive.
And then they found out actually it was so enlightening that they made duplicates of it
to bring it to their colleagues and to show them how much they really are in the dark.
And this is an intelligence agency person, right?
So I thought that was quite funny.
Yeah, perhaps a bit of an indictment on who they think they are or what they think they're
doing.
Oh, if I'm making a comment, that column, the panties and ifors.
I'm sure they appreciate it.
Yeah.
But in any case, I guess a good starting point in talking about modern Eastern religions
is to mention that they were largely formed during the Axial period when the world's belief
systems were changing.
So maybe we can start by looking at the groups that were active in those regions leading
up to that period.
So we have the nomadic Indo-Iranians who are set to have migrated south from the Eurasian
steps with the Iranian group moving into current date, Iran and Iraq and the other group
going into India.
Self-desegnated themselves as Arya, which means or said to me in the noble ones and the oldest
texts for them are the Rigveda and the Avesta.
Obviously the Aryan designation became known in the 20th century for reasons connected to
the Nazis, but Greek as your research turned up, anything notable about them as a people
group.
Those terms are more of a philosophy because in an ideology, because the peoples have been
so intermixed from all the various invasions of, like for example, the Greeks, you know,
they've been so intermixed, right?
So yeah, so the people themselves, I'm sure there's a little bit of a smattering of quote
unquote those bloodlines left somewhat, but it's more of an ideology or philosophy that's
been brought down, you know, to what's left of it today.
Their chief God though, the Indo-Iranians, they had an overarching sky god called Diaoș
or Diaoș Pitfer as the academics have put it, who later became sideline in favor of other
gods like the Davas, which meant shining ones or the Asuras, which were the oath gods.
And there seems to be this common occurrence that the chief sky god around this period
of the third millennium BC was known by everybody, but then he becomes irrelevant to everybody
all over the world.
Have you ever looked into that?
I tend to be biased, let's say in my narrative, towards the biblical text.
In other words, I just see what happened, maybe they said, look what happened to the poor
Hebrews, we should probably leave that one alone, right?
So when you deal with very high levels of manifest power, it's not for the public.
Like if you see high power, high tension, you know, power lines going through the countryside,
and that everybody wants to go and mess around with that, right?
You call it a specialist, right?
High voltage, right?
So what I did was focus on that biblical text specifically, as many would know, because
it's the only text, and only, well besides its universal acceptance is the only text that
has so much information about so many specific things, including history.
That does not exclude the Eastern culture from its involvement in that, but it's not mentioned
in what's called the biblical text, you see.
I believe they were on the periphery, just like anything that happens in the world today
is known everywhere through what's called media.
They had their form of media as well back then, it was a little slower perhaps, but everyone
on the planet pretty much knew what was going on with everyone else on the planet, right?
And let's just harken back to the timelines here.
So we're looking at major events around 2000 BC, based on what civilizations left today,
1000 BC, and then around 2000 years ago, major events that were known.
It might have put some people off because of its direct involvement with only a certain
group known as the Hebrews or the Judeans and such is real.
And they probably wanted to just leave it alone.
And for good reason, because it was not directed to them directly anyway, even though it would
involve them indirectly or directly if they decided it to, you see, by legions.
So there's more of a universal aspect to the biblical text, even though it doesn't directly
mention any other peoples as being directly involved.
And just like the Skygods are the balls, right?
So just to add, to talk about a particular Skygod is just rehashing what's in the biblical
text anyway.
Indeed.
I guess my suspicion is that perhaps that Skygod might intersect with the chief god in
the biblical text, but there's no way to know because the names are different, but just
because it ends up at the top of the hierarchy.
But I guess he could also be the ball storm god.
I don't know.
But to scrounge out whatever we can from looking specifically at the Eastern stuff.
So we know that the group that ends up in Pakistan and later India are the Indo-Aryans
and that they ran into the Indus civilization there.
We don't know a ton about because their writing hasn't been deciphered and they didn't have
any temples.
But the Vedas are the oldest Aryan texts.
I believe there's four of them with the Rigveda being the oldest, which also predates the
axial age from what I can tell.
Have you looked into the Vedas at all at any point in your studies?
Yeah.
What happens with any group that's formed on this planet because of the, with people are
taught to desire when they're here is to gain power and control.
And just a caveat and a replay note, footnote.
The earth has been controlled by malevolent entities.
In other words, the gods of the world are malevolent or indifferent.
We're not talking about, you know, higher gods are talking about the ones that are involved
here.
So there is no benevolence in any of these, in other words, what's active in the culture.
You know, it's all a product of the malevolent ones, quote unquote.
Just to tangentially address that, if anyone wants to do some side reading just to get a
flavor of what I've gotten out of it, there's a book called Darkness Over Tibet by something
Ilyan.
Ilyan is the author like million without the M.
And he, it's written in 1930s, it reads like fiction, but it's not, and you'll get an idea of
what happens to any culture.
You know, and I could just basically tell you he was so journey there disguises Tibetan
and basically found out that anyone in Tibet in 1930s was told that white people were evil
in carnation of the devil.
He ends up finding a secret city where it's run by magic and cannibalism and pretty much
zombie-like people.
And evidence of that is still, you know, today available.
You could go online.
There's not much of it about it.
Some people say it's a fictional work.
He did not write it as a fictional work.
So parallel stories to the Vatican.
If you go, let's, which is Western, if you go to the Vatican, physically go there and
you run into anyone there on a one-to-one, ask them what they practice in the Vatican.
They'll say it's Satanism.
It doesn't matter who you ask, as long as it's a one-on-one honest, you know, you could run
into the any of the bishops.
You spend more than 15 minutes with him if you see zero-okay, it's Satanism.
He'll tell you that.
He won't use that term, but indirectly.
The people who use that term would be like the guys who are hired to clean the toilets
in the Vatican.
He'll tell you, oh yeah, these guys are satanic.
For sure.
Right?
So very, very similar to what I just brought up with the darkness over Tibet.
Very, very similar to what you'll see with the Mormons, for example, or the Judeans,
right?
And what goes on in the large synagogues, which are sort of less centralized.
They don't have a centralized authority.
Same thing goes on with the Buddhist.
Same thing goes on, right?
So what I'm trying to sum up here is the earth is the worst, just imagine how bad you think
it could be, it's much worse than that, even, right?
But things are still functioning for now.
So there's no positive side to any of these religions, not a one.
No, I follow.
And that book is by Theodore Ilyan.
It's still quite talked about online, so people can check that out.
Okay.
Yeah, do the audio book.
Yeah.
I had phones, I think someone did a pretty poor reading of it.
It's about four or five hour listening.
Listen, I have it here somewhere in hard copy.
Just to give some context to the Vedas, it's worth noting that they aren't a unified volume
of writing like the Bible or seemingly like the Quran.
So written over several centuries, sometimes, well, oftentimes contradicts itself when it
comes to topics that later evolved because of sectarianism.
So an example is the subject of death where the Rigveda offers various accounts of vague,
but not painful after life that's ruled over by the God of death called Yama.
It doesn't say anything about reincarnation from what I can see in terms of being reborn
as a mortal.
That seems to be an axial development that grew out of Hinduism.
But we do see talk of a resurrection with a new body that's possibly made of fire and
the old body disperses back to nature.
I just wanted to read a few short verses that illustrate that.
You have a funeral hymn that addresses the deceased, go forth on those ancient paths on which
our ancient fathers have passed beyond, unite with Yama in the highest heaven, go back home
again, merge with the glorious body.
Rigveda 10, 14 verse 7, "Another hymn is addressed to the funeral fire, Agni, do not burn
him entirely, Agni, do not consume his skin or his flesh, when you have cooked him perfectly
only then send him forth to the fathers."
So yeah, in studying the Vedas, have you at any point Greek noticed that they have this
contradictory element, especially with the Upanishads, like the Upanishads are not the
Vedas and they very much seem opposed, or have you found anything illuminating about what
it has to say?
Again, I was using the Biblical text as a reference, as a central point to see what can be harmonized
and much can be harmonized.
A year ago, I had a lot to say about the Vedatex and then all leading all the way, the Mahapuratas
and all the various Paranas and things like that, much to say about it, but now I'm sort
of drawing a blank.
I'm pretty much thinking it's trying to define the body, the spirit, the mind and the soul,
and give people some kind of awareness of those things.
It does delineate the way I just said.
And it's basically a philosophy, and as time goes on, here's the thing, the more I look
into it, the less interest I have.
Well, yeah, I mean, from my end, I found it to be a bit complex because of all the contradictions
and how long it is, and the ancient languages are not as well addressed as with the Semetic
Riding, so if you don't read ancient Polly, you can't really get into the Buddhist stuff.
Right.
There's a bit of a learning curve there as well.
That seems to keep people from getting to the truth unless you really want to be an academic
or a hardcore devotee.
I think it toys around with our reality, in our concept of reality more than most people
realize.
What it does is it shows that reality is sort of liquid or flexible, or it's not real in
a sense as we see it, but because we're experiencing what we're experiencing, it's real in that
sense.
It's real if it's happening to you.
In other words, if you're good or bad, it's real good or bad, but there really is no good
or bad if people are not in a state where they are subject to it.
Well, here's the thing.
I think I've summed up the entire scripture very simply also.
It has a lot to do with perseverance in patience and being careful and understanding and
being responsible, but it has a lot to do with patience.
There's no fast way.
As if there almost is no way, it just is, and it's trying to give understanding.
You have to see that even before it was formalized, if you read a lot of the ancient, what are
known as the ancient Greek philosophers, they were on a similar path as well in terms of
their narrative.
Yes, I have seen that comparison drawn, particularly between the ancient Indians and the ancient
Greeks as being at the forefront of that sort of philosophic or monistic contemplation.
Well, here's the way to sum up everything.
If you're here on earth, you did something that was pretty screwed up or someone pretty screwed
up, sent you here to be screwed up.
It's not a good thing.
It doesn't mean it's terminal, meaning it'll come to an end.
That's why I recently have been saying life is too long, right?
Because once you figure out what's going on here, in a very collective objective way,
not what is truly objective, but in a collective way, if you start looking at many, many things
in what they're supposed to be and what they are, that's what I call objectivity, right?
You can see that contrast is that there's something wrong.
If you're here, this is a temporal zone in our cosmic history that things have gone
wrong and you're here.
It's not a good thing.
I give as a metaphor to young people in the future, quote unquote, whatever after life you
feel is designed for your belief.
You'll have a conversation somewhere and saying that you once were on earth if you do recall
that and everyone will stop and look at you and say, you are on earth.
Wow, tell us about how fucked up it was.
That's how I would sum things up.
And these ideologies, whether it's the ancient Greek, even the Hindu, trying to explain it
by the force of these major gods, let's say, the Buddhist philosophy of it, the biblical
text or whatever is trying to somehow just move us along until we don't have to be moved
along this way anymore.
Well, I mean, wrapping up on the sort of the Vedic strain of things.
So I mean, once classical Hinduism comes along, the focus moves from the Vedas to the Upanishads,
which were also composed by multiple people, I guess, 800 to 400 BC-ish.
They aren't as systematic or internally consistent as you would expect, but they do represent
a very different view to the Vedas.
They're more contemplative and thoughtful and seem to be more towards the sort of
philosophical or ascetic end of things rather than the priestly stuff that the Vedas talks
about.
And I think that's how the notion of samsara/reincarnation starts to come into play.
But again, the Upanishads say different things about it.
One of them says that samsara takes place in the mind.
Another one says that human cremation converts the corpse into smoke that becomes food for
the gods.
So there's no real consensus.
The older one, I think, say you get a new body.
That's like a god.
Well, the whole god, I'm going to stop you.
I'm going to stop you there just to save you some labor on that.
Just back to the biblical idea.
Once you're a resurrected body, you have a body that is spiritual, which is the mind.
So that little thing you just said about the resurrection is in the mind is, yes, it is
of the spirit.
So that is, it's just a matter of translation and how you want to grab that, right?
So that's why it's important to understand the fundamental narrative.
They're really all the same.
There's no physical domain that you are limited to when you are reincarnated or resurrected.
Right?
And this is very clear in what's called the New Testament as well.
Yeah, I think there's a scene where the Christ is trying to explain that's an ecodemist.
He's like, you don't understand when you're born of the spirit.
It's like the wind, right?
So there's no physical.
So if the resurrection doesn't exist in the mind, there's something wrong with that translation
because that is along the proper line.
It doesn't mean you will solely be a spirit.
You can take on a physical form, if you like.
There are many accounts in ancient times of these demons that do take on physical form,
whether it's attracting enough moisture in the air to form what's a ghost-like figure
or take a possession or actually forming or manifesting through something else.
Those are the lower forms.
But on a higher level, when you're reborn or redone, you will be an animated spirit versus
a disanimated spirit.
That's what we would be now.
If you don't have a body, you're disanimated, just like being asleep.
This is a type or quality of spirit we have now, meaning humans.
I follow.
Yeah, and I guess that's where the uponish had suffered from the contradictions because
as time goes on, they start to say that it does, you know, you could be reborn as a dog,
right?
So somewhere along the line, I guess a new generation takes place and they just start
to write whatever that doesn't.
And up with the older material.
Right.
And that's like Christianity.
Or you have an evangelistic Christian and a Baptist or a Mormon or whatever, they'll have
their own little line, but you won't find it in the fundamental text, right?
That's a typical thing.
That's what it is.
It's my reality is better than your reality.
So if you want to be better, you have to follow my reality.
It's all business.
It's just business.
It's hard to talk about religion without talking about the business aspect, great.
It's like if you want to sell meat to people, you have to learn about, let's say, keeping
chickens or hurting cattle.
But if you're keeping chickens and hurting cattle, you have to think about the meat industry.
See, it goes both ways, right?
So if you're going to have religion pro-out to the masses, it's not kept in secret.
It's the same thing.
You heard the masses for their meat, right?
So.
And just to piggyback off the mind aspect that you mentioned before we go into Buddhism,
so one of the key Sanskrit words that seemed to have undergone a change in the actual age
was the Atman, which is said to mean, you know, solar spirits.
We won't nitpick.
And what I can tell almost all of the, at least the Upanishad exages were reluctant to identify
the Atman with the mind because they thought the mind was unsettled or capricious.
One of them said, "It's not the mind we should want to know, but the thinker."
So there's this idea that the thing behind the mind was of interest and the consensus
seems to be that there's a lower self that comprises the body and at least the mind
in this dimension.
And then there's a higher self that consists of the Atman, which is apparently something
immortal.
That's in the end.
Okay, there's little children have toy fire trucks because they can't have a real one,
right?
Full scale one.
So once humans are aware of a higher existence, let's say, what they're left with actually
toying with is a toy.
So that's what they're trying to make sense of.
Right.
And I think, I think if you pay more attention to the original Polly, text of Buddhism, they
get into that a bit more.
So to move on to that, we have the historical Buddha whose teachings, I guess, were preserved
orally about three to four hundred years after his death.
And then you have the religious Buddha that develops out of myth and sectarianism.
So just to be brief, on the historical side, you have Siddhartha Gautama, which is said
to have been born for 90 to 563 BC into a privileged family, allegedly near the current
border of India and Nepal.
And then around the age of 30, he goes through a life changing experience that leads to a
new spiritual understanding, teaches it to his followers for several decades, lives
until around 80 and then beyond that, we don't really know much.
You have to look at the Polly Canon if you want anymore, historical dependable stuff.
Have you looked at the Polly Canon all yourself?
Yeah, I have.
And again, why am I reading this?
How it, you know, it sounds good.
It sounds good.
It's fairly understandable if you settle into it, you know, if you don't try to bring
what you've been raised with, you know, when you have to have a loose understanding of
the culture, right?
To appreciate it.
But it doesn't give me what I find in the biblical text.
Even though the biblical text again is, I keep going back and use it as a reference, about
a narrow group of people, right?
And they're happenings, but the underlying story in the narrative is pretty much the same
without being about a narrow group of people, but it airs on the philosophy side.
So, and also you have to understand the naturalistic religions too.
They don't directly reference nature as much as the other, you know, the idea of worshiping
nature, but you know, finding balance, yeah.
Yeah, those religions tend to be less elaborated.
I mean, well, we can touch briefly on things like Shinto, which does try to do that a bit
more.
But just to give a brief overview of the central Buddhist teachings, so the guy allegedly
had two teachers who fell short in showing him how to achieve this liberation from samsara.
So he eventually attended himself and went to teach what came to be called the four noble
truths to his disciples.
Being that I'm not able to delve into the original poly, I have to, I can only talk about
the conventional understandings of those ideas, but I do know that some people like Ken Wheeler
who understand the original languages will tell you that those notions are inaccurately
rendered in the modern teachings.
Right, but here is a comment on Ken Wheeler and that's a harp on him.
He doesn't discern between the spirit and the soul.
It has like the first fundamental, you can have guys like that that sound smart, right?
And our crafty, but there really, there's a difference between someone who is smart
and someone who sounds smart.
It's kind of like if you are talking about biblical stuff, we brought up without bringing up
people like Michael Heiser, you're not academic and you're supposedly providing something,
but you're not telling people that they've been fooled, that there's no crucifixion, it's
right there in the text, you know, it's just because it says it in the official King James
doesn't mean that, right, logically and reasonably is there.
So you have all these people out there with an agenda and it's not like they're saying
Ken Wheeler and Michael Heiser really, I don't know about Michael Heiser, but on the Christian
side, but because he knows if he tells, if he knows the truth, he would be eating out of a garbage
can.
Ken Wheeler seems to be a little more independent, but I think he's just, he had a mentor,
all these people, they have mentors in their lives or someone that sparked them on, and they're
just basically seeing it through their eyes, they don't have the ability to objectify
them, good stuff with magnetism.
I'm not being harsh in him.
I'm just telling you what I think is going on, but you got to lay down in any spiritual
discussion or any kind of body of work, the differences, you know, it's kind of like jumping
into literature class without knowing the alphabet, and the alphabet of spirituality is you have
the mind, the body and the soul, which is the metabolism.
The mind is the spirit, the body is the carnal aspect, and the soul is the metabolism.
The soul is interchangeable with anything else that's alive, typically even in the insect world,
you know, insect breeds, plants are different, but they breed as well.
So you know, it's very interesting that this particular incarnation of most things, you
need that soul and the body to animate the spirit, and nobody gets into that, it's fascinating.
Here's the thing, I'm going to pat myself on the back and send myself some flowers for
saying, we've been saying this for years and years and years, if you don't have the fundamentals
down right, the ABCs or the one, two, three, the three R's writing, arithmetic, right?
In reason, you're not going to get far, you're just spinning wheels and it's all a bunch
of BS out there.
Otherwise, you know, if there wasn't, we wouldn't be doing this, right?
Well, in terms of the Buddhism aspect, so we have these, you know, noble truths, I'll
just run through them very quickly.
The first being that human existence is duke, which is often translated as suffering, or
some people have said to mean, you know, disappointment, but, you know, the failure of reality to
conform to our expectations where even if you get what you want, it doesn't satisfy because
desires only begin more desires.
And then you have to say, you shouldn't be, you shouldn't be desiring what you shouldn't
be doing anyway.
In other words, if you, if you were raised in a family that did this and you don't do
that, you're a bad boy, right?
So you should be doing what everybody else is doing in a broader sense, right?
If you, it's a perfect slave system ideology.
That's why, for example, you know, the, the, the, the, the castles, you know, they would
build modes and protect, things to protect themselves in Europe from the peasant's until
they started investing in Christianity, which says, ah, you're a miserable slob here,
you'll have you'll be in heaven in the afterlife and they stopped attacking the castles, right?
Castles stop being built with modes and protective things until they, the wealthy people said,
this we need to invest in this Christian stuff, which is not biblical, by the way, and to calm
the masses.
But the idea of karma and all these other things, and yeah, escaping, yeah, yeah, if you, it's
as simple as something like if you come from a family of fishermen, you have to be a fisherman,
right?
If you, if you end up, if becoming, let's say, um, something else, and even though you're
good at it, you, you basically screwed up.
Even if you're good at it.
So it's very interesting, uh, how, how you could see through the, the, the, the aspects of
it.
Right.
And so the second noble truth is what is said to cause suffering, which is tahnha, which
is commonly translated as desire, some people have said thirst, uh, but basically that, um,
cravings turn into compulsions and cause people to miss apprehend the nature of the world
and themselves.
Um, and then the third truth is that suffering can only end by the abolition of craving through
nirvana, which I guess is misconceived as a place that one goes, but it's actually said
to be the point where one stops craving for reality to be other than what it is, uh, where
you comprehend that there's a reality beyond the carnal existence and you're able to fuse
yourself with that absolute.
And then the fourth noble truth, which is basically that the way to end suffering is through
a certain eight, eightfold methodology, which I'm not gonna outline all of them because it
be a slog, but anybody can read up on them.
So yeah, again, it's hard to really present an accurate view of what, you know, this thing
is if you don't look at the original languages, but well, you can, it's echoed again, you
know how they say the biblical Christ was free of sin.
Well, sin is when you miss the mark.
All right.
So, uh, if you're, if you say you're going to climb a flight of stairs and you don't, you
just sinned, right?
It's, it's, there's no moral attachment to it, right?
If you say I'm going to go out and kill 100 people today and you killed 99, you sinned,
right?
You see, whether you're, the moral, you know, basically you're following the law or
something is different.
But people don't understand that.
So if you have no desire, the Christ was without sin because he had no desires.
He's not like when I grow up, I'm going to play it be a rock star, right?
He had no desires here.
This is, it's very clear if you read the text, right?
He came to, he knew what he had to do here.
So that's why he's without sin because he achieved everything that he set out to do, meaning
on a micro and macro scale.
You see, very simple if you understand that.
So if you have no desires, you can't sin.
I'm not saying do nothing.
But if you were actually in the position where you would do nothing, you would be without
sin.
If you did nothing and had no desire because if you do nothing, you, let's say you do the
minimal amount, you're confined to a room, you might say, well, I'm going to walk across
the room and touch the wall.
If you don't, you just sinned.
You see, it's very simple.
The biblical aspect of sinning only applies to those who are in certain covenant, right?
To agree to follow, live this way.
And when they didn't, that was falling short.
You see, it's very simple as nothing to do with what people think it is.
And not to say, I guess, that the Christ didn't have any ambitions, but all, he allowed all
of his ambitions to be fed to him from, you know, the source.
The ambition that he had was fulfilled.
So he was without sin.
So in other words, you can sin if you say in the next five seconds, I'm going to walk
across the room and touch the wall.
If you don't do that, you sinned.
Or, or if you say in 30 years, I'm going to do this.
Well, when that time comes, it's all about timing also, right?
So you can have a one day, one week, one year, ten year plan as long as you make the mark
on each one, there's no sin.
And the ambition is fine.
It's okay to have the ambition as long as when the time comes, then ambition is fulfilled.
And so one of the last things I want to touch on regarding Buddhism is the notion of
the self, which seems to be quite misapprehended.
So even though the word self might be used linguistically or for linguistic convenience,
like the reflexive myself, the Buddha seems to convey that it's an unskilled way to think
of things, you know, because you're conceiving of reality as having substance when actually
the universe is more made up of energy modalities.
And this leads to the notion of anautmon, which is in the conventional understanding is
said to mean that there isn't a soul or spirit, but, you know, again, to reference Kenweiler,
he's exposited that anautmon doesn't mean that you don't have a spirit, but simply that
humans are not their carnal incarnations and the spirit is non-local somewhere else in
the unseen realm.
Or you can further on say it is spirit that does not require a body or a soul to be anemone,
but that would free Kenweiler out.
So you could say that also.
Actually, jump on his livestream one day and ask, see what he says, but yeah, another way
that I've sort of heard of it conceptualizes is that the self can be thought of like the
rainbow and that the rainbow is in a substantial reality in the way that it appears.
It's more of an optical illusion that's created by factors, you know, like sunlight and rain
and the position of the observer.
So nobody ever reaches the end of the rainbow because once the observer moves his position,
the rainbow starts to fade away.
I'm an interject.
These are not optical illusions because they're optical.
So in the optical realm, they're real.
That's why we say optical illusion, which is kind of an oxymoron.
There is no such thing as an optical illusion.
Yeah, that's another oxymoron that we use.
There's no such thing as an optical illusion because we say optical means it's only perceivable.
Right, it's a phenomenal, it's phenomenal versus nominal, you know, nominal, immeasurable
as we understand the measure things.
We can't be managed like we, I formed rainbows by the way using a very fine mist when the
sun is out.
You can see it with a garden hose if you set it on a fine mist.
But you, so anything that's optical is not an illusion because it's in the optical realm.
It's supposed to be that way, right?
Not supposed to be real in any other way.
So but if it is optical, it's not an illusion because it's optical, you see?
I hope that grounded people.
No, of course.
By the way, I wouldn't go on any live stream because I'll tell you why and I'll give this
advice to most people.
These people that are well known, what happens if you go look in the comments and any of
these people on the internet or whatever.
And this is also before the internet I noticed.
They sound smart, they're really not that smart.
And they surround themselves with NPCs, I call them Sims, you know, people that are not,
you know, NPCs, whatever.
That's a meme.
You know, people that, you know, fair, normal, you know, they have nothing going on.
And because they follow all these people around them or around them, you know, they're great,
right?
So it's a, so yeah, if you, any of these people, if you go into the live, you'll see they're
just NPCs around them.
So when, if you, if you start in trying to interact with them and you're not an NPC, that's
outside of his, what he's used to having, you see?
If that makes any sense.
Yes, the non-player character phenomenon is quite widespread and I have tried interacting
with a few people on social media to no success.
Although if you tip them, they're more likely to talk to you if you throw in $5.
Well, that's what they do.
That's what they do.
What else are they good for?
But they're meat, they're pound of flesh.
I mean, I don't, I have not pursued any more public or even private group calls because
I didn't find people that were, you know, how would you say, productive enough, you know?
I'm looking for people to jam with to, to, as equals, not people to repeat what I'm saying
and not contribute anything beyond what is brought forward, right?
So even a, even a stupid potluck, you can bring your macaroni salad with mini marshmallows
or jello with mini whatever you bring, just bring something and I, yeah.
So yes, it is a dire prospects in that regard, but it may change.
So yeah, the Buddha didn't leave any successors and his teachings were kept in oral tradition
for some centuries until the Polycanon.
So what we have today are the orange-robed Theravadins as the oldest extant school and in
the first century AD another school called Mayana emerged, which was exported to China
and it's the most popular variety today.
Out of that came the Vajrayana, which is the religion of the Dalai Lama.
So I mean, Greek, how would you, you know, sum up the Buddhist situation today?
Is there anything useful that we can derive from it at all?
No, it's ritual.
Just like let's say you went to, you mentioned his popular in China, a Chinese farmer.
He spent a week with him doing what he does and you asked him why he does this and he'll
just say, "Oh, that's just what I will show and I just do it.
It's ritual, right?"
Most of what people do is ritual.
They don't know why they're doing it.
Just ask them, right?
I was shown this way.
This is how it's done.
It's bothering me.
So people are raised and groomed to perform these rituals, right?
You know, a lady in an expensive car doesn't know much about cars, right?
Automobiles motorized wagons.
She knows that if she pushes this pedal, it goes.
If she pushes this pedal, it stops and she turns this wheel, it goes left.
Turns this way out wheel, it goes right.
That's all she knows.
It's a ritual, right?
That whatever they do in their religious life, their personal life, their work life is
a ritual.
They basically NPCs, again, in that sense.
So it's all ritual.
So what the modern, all the modern religions look at the people that go to church on Sunday,
it's a ritual.
They don't know anything.
They did it when be there.
They burned the place down if they knew what it was about.
So the whole thing, it's all basically down to ritual.
Again, in the Asians are just as human as the rest.
Yes, unfortunately so.
But we can look at a few other things which have derived their popularity from the Asian
region.
Confucianism is one of them.
So we have Confucius who was born between 551 and 479 BC.
Of course, his name is not Confucius.
That's a Latinized term created by 17th century Jesuit missionaries.
His real name was said to be something like Kansa and he was born into poverty but later
wanted to attain political power or at least serve as an advisor to a king.
He was unable to gain that position.
So ultimately his life is mostly about teaching his followers.
He claimed no originality for his own ideas and preferred to convey wisdom from antiquity
similar to the Buddha.
And he's also reported as having told the students to those who are not eager to learn.
I do not explain anything.
Greek, do you know anything about Confucianism?
Yeah, I love his stuff.
I love his attitude.
I just don't want to be Confucius.
But I totally, in other words, there's the idealistic way of being and then there's the Confucian
way which is the way here.
I mean, if you understood, again, this for private, not public consumption, what really goes
on, you'd be like, oh crap, this is some really bad stuff.
But what's shown in public is absolutely correct for you.
It fits the people.
You do what you're told.
The noble men is the noble men and you're the servant.
Be thankful.
Right?
Shut up and whatever, right?
Because it was already Confucianism shows to me that even back then, they knew they had
figured out what people like and how people want to be, which is not good.
And it has a simple order.
But again, most of Confucianism, I had gone, there's Confucius Square in Chinatown, in New
York City.
And I remember congregating with some people at some other meeting places.
And it was like, wow, what a bunch of morons.
But they were so well disciplined and so well ordered and fairly content in their lives.
And I said, this is great.
And anyone could look up what Confuciusism is about.
Just keep it in light of most people, like the followers of Michael Heiser or Ken Wheeler
or whatever, or any popular person.
You'll notice that whatever religion, like Michael Heiser being Christian, Ken Wheeler,
being whatever Buddhism, you the Confucius.
Or actually the rules and guidelines of Confuciusism applied to both.
Yes.
And in part, because he didn't seem to have much to say about the spirit world or the gods
or anything like that, it was more about conduct.
And so yeah, the official book for Confucianism is the Analyx, which is a blessing of saying.
Yeah, I want to interject again.
Why would you say anything about the spirit world, as I said earlier, if you were here, it's
because something went wrong.
It's kind of like, what are you doing here?
You must have taken a wrong turn somewhere.
So why would he talk about the spirit world?
It would be non-productive.
It would unwind people, right?
Because even in any text, once you start understanding contemplating what is going on and collectively
objectify it, meaning that the more you try to be objective, the more you can see, you'll
say, holy crap, what am I doing here?
No one should be in this state.
From a central point of view about myself, something went wrong.
I must to easy.
So why would he talk about the spirit world?
I think it's senseless.
I think for most people, again, it's senseless and unless you give them something to do, you
know?
If you ask people why they're free-masons, it's because they like showing up to the ceremonies
because they're a bunch of losers, right?
And they're whatever jobs they have.
They know that.
It doesn't matter if he's a neurosurgeon making two million a year.
He knows he's a loser.
He knows that he's in a track.
The money's fake and it's all bullshit, right?
So I don't mean someone pan-landling, which actually has more freedom.
But the aspect of knowing that you're here, something is wrong and it's wrong that you're
here, why would you talk about the divine in any way that I just starts identifying more
than Confucius does?
Okay, so, yeah, information on Confucius has to be gleaned from the Anilex, which is a collection
of sayings compiled by his followers after his death, probably reflects them more than him
because I think only the first half of the book reportedly comes from him.
Have you looked into any Confucian writings at all?
No, I have not.
Like I said in the mid '80s, I had been around people who were professed to follow that.
And I noticed that it was not merely...
It was a ritual that they did because their parents did and they were not well-versed in
most of it.
And I did, to cursory investigation of what it was about.
I always had it in the back of my head, but I've not read the Anilex or anything like that.
But as I investigated more and more through life, I'm like, oh Confucius, I did write it.
You know, these people are like on this planet or want to be treated like cattle.
How do I know?
Well, look at them.
And he has a perfect outline for them.
The king is the king, you're the slave is the slave or the servant or whatever.
Office you have in life, be happy with it and be honored about the ones that are higher
than you.
Happy with them, whether they're good or bad, doesn't quite say that directly, but yeah.
And don't abuse the ones below you, advice for us out.
When concerning them, what you said earlier about, you know, we were talking about the gods,
yeah, he had very little to say about that.
And one of his students said that he didn't, you know, speak about miracles or gods.
And then another student asked, you know, how do you serve the gods?
And Confucius is like, well, you can't even serve your fellow humans.
Why are you asking about the gods?
Mm-hmm.
So he had this notion of keeping them at a distance.
I think he did say you should give them reverence, but that people shouldn't expect
rewards from them.
I think one of his quotes were, those who are humane rest content with their humane-ness,
so in other words, being good as its own reward.
But yeah, I mean, it's interesting how you have these figures like Confucius and also
the Buddha who had no interest in the gods and didn't seek to deify themselves yet they
ended up as religious figures centuries after they died.
Well, yeah, that's the business part.
You want to sell meat to people?
What do you know about herding cattle?
And vice versa.
Once you heard enough cattle, then you got to sell their meat.
That's religion.
But don't misunderstand what I say just because I focus on the biblical narrative and the
gods there.
Yes, plural.
There are gods in the biblical narrative.
It's not for everyone.
I never even suggest anyone should even read the biblical text because they're going to
get lost after the word "the."
So it's only those who really have a strong desire to be objective should do it.
And all the gods, even the more apathetic to humans, unless it involves humans in their
plan.
So indeed.
Also touching on another thing that you'd mentioned, Confucius had conceived of several different
ideal types of humans.
So the highest was the sage who was the complete embodiment of Confucian values.
Although Confucius would later say that he never met a sage and had given up hope of doing
so and he didn't consider himself one, although his followers did.
And then I think, you know, in order to have a category that people could attain to, he
derived the idea of the gentleman, the respectable gentleman or the nobleman, which denotes
somebody who's attained a noble character and superior status in society.
And then one of the defining traits of the gentleman is the ren often translated as humaneness
or virtuous benevolence.
He doesn't really define it in the intellect, but he discusses people who have it and, you
know, basically it involves following his version of the golden rule, which is do not impose
on, on to others, which you don't want them to oppose on to yourself.
Right.
Now the reason he, you don't define it is very simple.
The reason you don't define it is because there might be an upcoming industry that might
partake in something that you might have shed some negative light on.
And then once that new industry develops and has the monetary capability and the power
behind it, it will eliminate your philosophy and eliminate you, cancel you out, right?
It's very, it's very wise from a business perspective, not to really say what's good or bad.
Right.
And then ironically, you have to be ambiguous.
Yeah.
And ironically, that is exactly what happens when Mao comes to power, they suppress confusion
as him.
But like this idea of the golden rule, you know, you find some version of it in every major
civilization, which I guess if you date the Exodus to around 14 or 1500 BC, that would
be the earliest source in Leviticus 1918.
But, you know, confusion seems to have his own version of that, which is interesting.
Well, look, if whether you're in a subservient, servant or noble position, you want everyone
to do well because if you're the guy who's at the bottom shoveling shit for a living, his
interest, his wellbeing is in the interest of the nobleman.
That's obvious, right?
Because the nobleman shits.
And if there is in a shits shoveler, he's going to be drowning in his own.
You see, so you want, it's only logical and reasonable beyond the development of the
vine, you don't need the divine to understand that you want everyone to be happy and content
in what they're doing and to not be, you know, infirm you want the guy who's removing trash
and or burying dead bodies to be well enabled to do so.
Because if you're very wealthy and there isn't anyone to do that job, you're going to, your
life will be miserable too, you see?
An example is, you know, everyone's like, oh, look at Dubai, look at all the seven star
hotels, right?
Now it's beyond five star, right?
Those are shit towers, man.
There's no sewer, do you know there's no sewer system in those megaplex hotels that are
like ultra luxury?
There's no sewer system.
So if the trucks, there's a line of trucks that shows up at four in the morning every day
to pick up all the waste, right?
So if those trucks don't show up, there'll be these guys with the gold plated Rolls
Royces will be drowning in their own feces.
Do you see?
I'm using this is true.
You can look, well, it's kind of hard to find it, but, right?
Yeah, I mean, for the first three, four thousand years of civilization, people are just either
dead broke in peasants or rich in aristocrats or monarchs.
And now in the last 50, 60, maybe 70 years, you have this middle class that rises and it's
like, why does it behoove the elites to have them?
But then when you explain that, well, it actually behoves them because, you know, we all
serve a purpose of keeping a system alive that benefits everybody, then it makes sense.
You know, what they did was they eliminated things that are possible to be scarce, like money.
So they eliminated money, great, you know, they're basically drawing all the money from people's
signatures, right?
So those unlimited money.
And once the people accepted that without questioning it, they created a Disneyland, a
Disney world for about 80 years.
Well, let's say 100 years, but it's not fair to say 100 years because of the depression
that's when they pulled, you know, because people didn't have credit cards or checking accounts
before the 1930s, it was just bank notes.
So the way they did the depression in all countries is they people go to the bank, if you
had a business, you go to the bank and you have to take notes from the bank to pay the
workers while you got the business owners went to the bank.
That's why if you look at old movies, in every business office is a big ass safe, if you
watch old movies, right?
You can be shopper, factory, whatever, you see the bosses room, you know, the bosses office
and it's a big, huge safe in there.
That's for payday.
So these people, businesses would go to the banks to get notes to pay their workers because
they don't give you, give it work or check, the hell is this?
You know, he called the police on you.
There was no, the bank said, sorry, we don't have any notes.
So they know what could pay their workers and the workers didn't get paid.
So how are they going to, right?
So that's how you make a depression, right?
So that's why on O'Cellia and the Greek, you can't crash the system because it's already
been crashed.
What you can do is withhold, you have to physically stop people from doing anything, thus the
lockdowns, right?
Because money is unlimited.
There's no scarcity in money.
There is no money.
It's credit.
So this was, all these mass donations went on until the 40s.
So if you go in 1940s to 20, it's about 80 years.
So you've been living in a Disneyland because of this credit system, right?
Everyone, you know, can seemingly afford anything if they work hard.
And 80 years is a pretty long run to be a Disneyland or Disney World or a fictional, you know,
reality.
Talk about simulation.
This is a simulation within the simulation.
So that's why I was so content to see the lockdowns in the pandemic and all this stuff
even though there's no pandemic, you know, a biological one, because it's a great, finally,
80 years worth of Disney World is coming to an end, you know, going back to how humans
are control.
And the reason, by the way, you do credits, they don't tell people, they don't emphasize
that there is no money and it comes from your signature is to control misery, right?
So you give a loose outlet to those that you want to be wealthy and you restrict and punish
those that you don't want to be wealthy by restrict by their own ignorance, right?
That's the only reason there's fiat currency is to control misery.
It's not a Star Trek world where they bring someone on the Star Trek series, they bring
someone from the past, where's your money?
Oh, we don't use money anymore.
Well, that means we don't control people's misery if they're miserable, it's because they
brought it upon themselves and over mismanagement or lack of responsibility, not because there's
an overarching part of society that can do that, known as bankers or surface government
or whatever.
And it's a system of ignorance.
So it's over and it's great.
I mean, to see the capital, it's not really capitalism, it's capitalizing on ignorance, all
of it is.
Look at how many people, again, I gave the Dubai example, these seven star hotels, most
luxurious in the world, you have their basically shit towers.
The tanks, if the tanks aren't emptied every day, no one's going to go in there because
they have to be vented.
You know what happens if you have a 50,000 gallon tank full of feces in urine and you try
to seal it off, you know what's going to happen in a couple of days, right?
I hope you understand the idea of pressure.
Yeah, it'll blow a crater.
What have you?
We had 40 tons of crap explode in Dubai, what's all brown everywhere?
So it's not an illusion.
It's real, but it's a Disneyland is not an illusion.
There's a guy in a Mickey Mouse suit, you have the fairy castle or whatever, whatever
the, you know, whatever they have, it's not an illusionary.
It's an imposed simulation.
It's, it's, well, and it's, and they're at fault.
People don't want to take responsibility.
They're NPCs.
Again, go to all the popular YouTubers, look at their followers, look at the comments.
There's not one, not a one that is plausible in being correct.
Indeed, the state of things today.
Yeah, but I also see a parallel between Confucius' notion of the unattainable sage with Plato's
philosopher king.
Apparently you have this archetype that different people spoke about, but no one is able
to attain to and it makes me wonder, you know, if that to be taken as a red herring a
bit, because even Confucius had to deal with certain criticism, like there's a story about
a man who worked as a gatekeeper who inquired about Confucius saying, is that the guy who
is working towards the goal, the realization of which he knows to be hopeless.
End quote, you know, so I just find it interesting that you have this archetype that it's not a
god, it's not an alien, it's a person, but it's impossible to become this person that gets
this level of wisdom and conduct.
Well, it's like the Groucho Marx thing.
I would never join a club that would have me as a member, right?
In other words, if you're attained that level, you would, no one would know about it because
you would go out and live by yourself away from everyone, because you just couldn't, you
wouldn't stand, you couldn't stand them.
Think about it.
So they do, I would say indirectly, not positively, but I would suggest that those people
did exist, but they never took any prominent popularity because, I mean, look, look at the
populace.
It's not different now than it was back then.
Who would want to rule over these people?
At any time in history and anywhere in history.
And I'm being realistic.
Most people don't like what I'm saying, but they know it's true and those that like what
I'm saying and know is true, well, more to it, more power to it, really, because you're
going to need it.
I know it's, that is probably one of the more less elaborated aspects of that that, oh,
if I became a philosopher king, I wouldn't want to be a king because my subjects love it.
Right.
I get away all the time in public.
Well, I don't know, I'd be at the shops and if something political or philosophical conversation
comes up, say, well, there's a new society coming and they'll say, yeah, we know, it's a, but
none of you are suitable for it.
The people that are here now are not suitable for the next society.
They got to go.
Sorry.
I'm not making this stuff up.
So yeah, and they were like, yeah, I guess so.
And I'm like, that means you, Jack, you know, so yeah, so who, what is it a rule over?
There's nothing to rule over.
Well more on that later, when we cover that in later episodes, to wrap up on the confusion
is a bit his answer to the social and political problems of his day seem to be this idea of
cultivating people of virtue.
I think he felt that the problems facing China were too entrenched to be legislated away
or policed away.
And the real issue was that you have people of poor character and callousness, especially
those in power.
So if only they could practice the art of good moral self cultivation, then the more virtuous
rulers would have that trickle down to the people, which is why I think Confucius said,
quote, keep them in line with punishments and the common people will stay out of trouble
but will have no sense of shame, guide them by virtue and they will besides having a sense
of shame reform themselves and quote, so yeah, that was his idea of getting human beings
to obey the unenforceable by teaching them the right thing.
What are your thoughts on this methodology?
Exactly.
Well here's a small example.
You have a family with young children and before they go to school, the children do get
an idea of language, morality, rules and things like that.
They go to school and the school teaches something contrary to that and they come home.
So that puts the child in a schizophrenic position, meaning a torn mind.
Do I do what they tell me in school?
I do what they parents say.
So you have to have uniform consciousness in order for that to work.
And it could be malevolent and benevolent.
And unless the only way to judge what's malevolent or benevolent is to have a firm baseline.
So if you don't have a firm baseline or allegiance to any covenant, there is no good or bad.
It's like the guy who robs the bank gets away with it is good.
He almost got away with it.
The police busted him so the police are bad.
But people watching that saying, "Oh, the guy who robbed the bank is getting away with it is
bad and the police are good."
So which one is it?
I'm just saying forget about you.
You were never taught it was wrong to steal.
You see, once your taught was wrong to steal, then it becomes more clear.
So you have to have a baseline.
So to conclude, Confucianism ended up being suppressed during the Chen dynasty, but then
during the Han dynasty of 200 BC to 200 AD, it became state religion and was required by
officials to pass civil service exams.
Eventually in the first century AD, they started building temples too Confucius and I think
he was actually defied in 1906.
And then Mao came and took over and suppressed it because it was said to be backwards or anti-revolutionary.
And then it flourished again in the 80s and the 90s.
By the way, there is no revolution.
That's another oxymoron.
There's no such thing.
Now it was that the rock and roll band who meet the new boss, same as the old bosses.
No.
The overarching forces that are behind what goes on on the surface do not accept revolution.
In other words, you have to be more powerful than them to have real revolution.
And that's coming.
You need a cosmic police.
So yeah, we'll wrap up the podcast by looking at Taoism, I guess, which is it said that there's
two primary types.
You have the philosophical Taoism, which was associated with the Tao Day Jing and practiced
by the intellectual class.
And then you have religious Taoism that was more around rituals and temples and meant
for the common people.
But in either case, Taoism was seen as a response to the same social political problems that Confucius
addressed, but the Taoists had the opposite solutions for a lot of those things.
How learned are you in the Taoist works?
Pretty well.
Okay.
I think that provided a natural philosophy or a real science that's usable that I use in
my life every day.
The concept of eating and young.
The workings, the reason you should understand eating and young is you have the ability of
accurate predictability.
So if you have, for example, from a chemical point of view, if you understand the young or
eating qualities of one element and the young and the young elements of another, you can predict
what will happen when you put them together before you do so.
It's very simple.
And it works pretty much across the perceivable universe.
And I've used that with great success in any project that I've done through, since the mid-80s.
So I'll give an example.
My wife, she, it's cold here.
And I like it when she's barefoot and she'll walk on a ceramic floor because she does yoga.
She's very athletic.
And I'll say, put something on your feet.
She goes, "My feet are hot."
I don't feel cold.
I say, "But I know you don't feel cold right now, but what'll happen is the cold on the hot
feet will tell the body to release some yeen."
And the way the body does that is by trying to increase vacuum, developing mucus.
And what people call ket, you feel like you have a cold.
And it doesn't happen immediately.
It's because right now your body is readjusting to this yeen and yang influence in the next
day or two, you're going to feel like you're coming down with the cold.
It's kind of like little children they go out and play in the rain and the parents
are like, "No, you can't do that.
Come in a way.
I feel fine."
The rain will tell the body that it needs to release some yeen energy or yeen product.
And in order to do that, you have to develop mucus and maybe rise in temperature when people
interpret that as a cold.
It doesn't happen right away.
If you go out underdressed in a cold climate, you'll catch a cold is what they typically
say, right?
You don't catch it.
It's just the body releasing yeen product because of the excess yeen from the cold.
You see, so you have this great predictability with this.
I'm just using the health aspect as an example, right?
No, that's very useful.
It makes it practically accessible for people.
Yeah, I mean, if we look at the philosophical side of dauism, which is often dated to,
you know, 3rd or 4th century BC, you have this character, Lauzer, who's said to have written
the Dau-Day-Jing around the 6th century BC.
We don't know much about him.
His alleged biography was written in the Han Dynasty, it says he worked in the government archives.
And then as he got older, he became more frustrated with the government and city life and decided
to retire into solitude.
So as he was leaving the city on a buffalo, the keeper of the Jade Gate asked him to leave a
remembrance of his wisdom and so Lauzer wrote this text of about 5,000 characters that became
the Dau-Day-Jing.
Of course, none of this has any historical basis since the academics consider him to be a
fictional character that was just created to oppose Confucius.
But again, you know, you have this sage archetype.
Right.
And the thing is about the historical basis or not, which in many cases can be validated
if people were honest or the authorities were honest, which they're not.
Because the authorities, again, the surface authorities, not speaking against them, I'm just
telling you what's going on, are merely a shell.
If you've ever heard of them historically or seen an image or whatever, they have no power,
period.
That's why, for example, when you go into the biblical text, everything is misrepresented.
Everything is misidentified because those that have the power that are spoken of in the
biblical texts are not represented in the world.
It has to be hidden, that's just how it is, and this particular era or run of ages.
So the main point then is whether it can be historically verified or not as irrelevant
is what is trying to be communicated and is that communication useful.
It doesn't matter.
You can have that in fiction.
I mean, how many fictional films are made that are very relevant as criticism to the
present-day society, but they're fictional films?
It doesn't matter.
What is being communicated is relevant, you see.
No, I follow.
Well in the interest of time, I won't expound too much on Taoism.
I'll just touch on the notion of the Tao.
Sure.
So you have this concept used in many forms of Chinese philosophy, and it's actually a topic
of debate amongst the various schools, the Tao.
It's not really defined in the Tao-daging, exactly like Confucius.
They don't seem to want to define these things, but it's been translated as the way or more
likely the proper way.
Confucius talked about it.
It's been said to mean the steps towards becoming a sage or the path to social harmony.
For the Taoists themselves, it seems to mean the way of nature, suggesting that it's the
source of all things.
The Tao-daging does say to not try to comprehend the Tao too concretely and that it's not amenable
to complete understanding, which seems to suggest that maybe it's made up of two parts,
things that can be discussed and things that can't, you know, canceluding to the ineffable
aspect of reality that's beyond grasping.
I think it does also say in chapter 56, "Those who know don't talk about it and those who
talk about it don't know."
End quote.
Right.
That's right.
That's why I always stress that learning the enignong, so you have good predictability,
accurate predictability in any situation.
That's a bit of a funny thing.
I guess you have to contemplate it a lot to really get to it because it can't...
Right.
For example, if you contemplate it and you understand it again from a chemical side,
you will say we're nitrogen-brithers, not oxygen-brithers.
Yes, we require oxygen in the body, but we're not oxygen-brithers.
We're nitrogen-brithers.
And then once you understand how nitrogen becomes oxygen and it's byproducts, in that
process, we'll now you understand the soul from a chemical perspective, right?
And we don't have to talk about shintoism because if you're not Japanese, it's not relevant.
Well, I was going to mention just very briefly that when it comes to that, you know, you
have this poly...
Let's just say polytheistic religion that revolves around the kami or supernatural entities that
are believed to inhabit all things, which I guess makes it a bit animistic.
Well, it's less...
I think it's less than supernatural.
It would be the divine, like, something great is...
Just like someone leaves a footprint on the beach.
You know, they're not the footprint, but it's the result of them walking on the beach.
There's a lot of different things that you see, like we call the Seven Wonders of the World,
the Shintoism, they wouldn't be called Wonders, they would be called Kami, those things
have great kami.
In other words, divine inspiration, divine influence, or direct divine influence, or direct divine
manifestation.
But you know, see the divine, you see what it manifests.
Famous terms are like the kami-causi, "causi" means "wind" and "kami" means "divine,"
right?
And those people were sacrifices.
They had sacrificed to the wind god, so might as well sacrifice them by crashing into the enemy
ship.
But nothing to do with...
Well, eventually, then they put rockets under them and broke the sound barrier and done
stuff like that, crashing into ships.
If you look at some photographs of Kami-causi ship, you'll see the water protrude for half
a mile around the ship.
You know, like that vaporization that happens on the surface when you have a supersonic explosion.
Anyway, those men had gone through ritual.
It wasn't...
It wasn't really a weapon, but it was to target the ship if you're going to sacrifice someone
anyway, but it was to sacrifice the wind god, which they wanted to take control of anyway.
So which they used later on, which is not in history too much.
If you could deal with the randings of a guy called Douglas Dietrich, he talks about it a
lot.
If you could deal with him as randings, not a very sane individual, but nonetheless, his
information is pretty good.
But who is sane anyway?
Shintoism again, I think, just to emphasize, is for only for Japanese people.
That's why most people think that Japanese are Buddhists, it's for the non-Japanese.
I guess that's still fairly rigid.
Yeah, I mean, it's a bit hard of a thing to grasp.
It's not...
It's a religion that's not said to have a founder.
No official sacred texts in the strict sense, no fixed dogmas.
So it's been incorporated into their culture and way of life to the point where it's hard
to pinpoint where the central points of power originate from.
Oh, you can.
I just mentioned earlier that the people of power, you can call them people, are not known.
So once they put something out, the author is unknown.
That's how you know it came from a place of power.
Okay.
Like, the primary example is like, for example, Christianity.
A fundamental Christian will only accept an authorized version of King James, so that
you see, which is crap.
Right?
There's no one out there that can interpret or talk about what's held in the hebraic scriptures
or what's...
Mishmash is left of the New Testament.
It's not a one.
No one can talk about what's in there with accuracy.
They have to make stuff up around it and religions around it and divert people.
Because there's true power there.
In terms of the knowledge.
I mean, I believe you've said before that many Asian religions have this...
They have the characteristic of not really worshipping God's per se, but just as certain spirits
or entities or manifestations would shinto fall into that category.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
The divine power of heaven.
Rightly so, because you're just going to confuse the cattle.
You know, you don't want enough of these people on this planet through history and now
realizing that they're here because something went wrong.
They took a wrong turn and ended up here.
That's the last thing.
Everything will fall apart.
I mean, it's okay if a few thousand people know that.
I don't believe it, but know it.
But when millions start knowing that, I think society will civilization.
That's it.
It will fall apart.
Yeah, certainly that would be a pivotal turning point, presumably to the negative, as you
say.
It would be like, do a film with a bus or an airplane that goes somewhere it's not supposed
to be.
And people know they're not supposed to be.
How would you form a movie around that?
Pretty easy, right?
The theme is, you know, you'll have the short tempered guy.
You'll have the guy who tries to stay happy.
You'll have the one that panics.
You'll have the one that takes advantage.
Eventually they all form a murderous group and kill someone.
It's the same story, like Lord of the Flies over and over and over.
That's what the whole planet will become like if people figured out what's really going
on.
Do you want that?
I don't.
No, I'd rather live in a living piece for now until...
Yeah, you want to keep them diluted, yeah.
Like going to a hospital ward where a full of gunshot victims, do you want to take their
morphine away or fentanyl?
They'll be screaming and biting their tongues and jumping out of windows and you see,
you got to keep them.
Who is it?
The opiate of the people.
They'll provide these people and they love being misinformed and being lied to and I'm
putting that together because I'm just seeing society and it's not going to change until
the society is wiped, reset, not the reset that these idiots are talking about, but the real
one that's going to involve cosmic forces.
Yes, there's a lot coming that we'll be talking about in probably the next episode or
two.
But to conclude on this one, the last ancient religion I wanted to mention was that of the
bond or the bond, the indigenous religion of Tibet that was, I think, absorbed into the Buddhist
stuff.
It's still distinct, I think, if you go to that region, but it's lost some of its contours.
You've mentioned in the past that it retained some worthwhile aspects of truth.
Can you elaborate on that a bit?
I was just thinking about that, nothing I can elaborate on at the moment without really
getting into a long-winded explanation of that because it has to do a lot with geography,
who the Tibetans are, their culture and how their culture was formed.
If you understand Tibet, reading that Theodore Ilyan book might give some insight to what
happens with any society on Earth and ultimately leads to some really nasty stuff because all
it does on the bond is create a hopefulness that the predatory aspects of being here are
abstained from you, but how to cope with them and deal with them as they follow through.
In other words, this part of the universe that we are in is ruled and run by some extremely
nasty beings and they have a very organized way of manifesting their nastiness that's
acceptable to humanity.
I should say that.
And that book, "Balnik's Incompuses" is that.
You'll see a little bit more of it if you folks read that darkness over to Tibet.
Well, I think we've said as much as we can about the eastern stuff, so we can probably
conclude things.
Much of the book is about the nature of the world.
So thank you to everybody who tuned in for this episode.
It's been a pleasure to talk, as usual, and we'll probably be back for two or three more
before we wrap this up.