Greetings to everyone and welcome to episode 4 of the Godspeak podcast.
The Greek and I will be convening to talk about things pertaining to religion and supernatural,
so I hope you enjoy today's conversation.
I'm just going to keep the introduction brief.
Godspeak.com has no political religious or corporate affiliations and is completely managed
by myself, although the possibility of offering donations is open to whomever wishes to
do that on my other site, GreekSpeak.com.
So thank you again for tuning in and let's get the conversation started.
Hello there, Greek.
How has life been treating you since the last time we spoke?
Oh, this is the usual treatment.
That's a very open to the answer, but no worries.
Okay, so we've previously covered some broader topics about the supernatural which will allow
us to talk further about things like religion or the metaphysical.
And so I'd like to start with looking at the mainstream religions because nearly all
the talk about the gods in the last few thousand years has been filtered through the
prism of either so-called Judaism, Christianity, Islam, or Buddhism.
And so for this episode we'll be looking at what they call Judaism to see how that developed
into what it is today and how it snowballed into something quite different than where it
came from.
But let's start with the idea of what they call monotheism and how that acts as a backdrop
for everything else.
So from what I see, it wasn't until around the 1600s that terms like monotheism and polytheism
were first used as we understand them today.
Apparently it was weaponized by academia and religious writers to sort of discriminate
between societies that were quote unquote civilized because they believed in one god and others
in the third world were permitted because they acknowledged multiple gods.
Can you talk about the role of academia and westernism in general in shaping the idea
of monotheism?
No, actually there's nothing I can say about academia other than people aspire to it and
when they do aspire to academia meaning to study in it they have to become literate.
So other than the drive for people to have a certain level of literacy, communication,
written word and such, and other study forms, academia serves no purpose other than it's
one of the institutions that is befallen to those that control the earth which are malevolent
forces.
So that's it.
That's the entire sonic right there where we're done.
I'm joking.
Okay, well there's several things we can backtrack on.
The filter of the mainstream religions that you mentioned are all and object can be
objectified as forms of paganism as well.
So not to leave out paganism because there are large pagan communities and it's kind of
hard to speak on that.
You could look up what paganism means or whatever and you'll find that even that is adulterated.
But if one were to say those mainstream religions you mentioned earlier are steeped in pagan
ritual that would be very accurate to say that and it would be very difficult to refute
that.
The second thing is regarding monotheism it's a confusing term meaning most people think
there is only one God and I guess the term is supposed to mean belief in one God and most
people that have multiple gods do that anyway because each God is attribute have different
have different attributes which one would regard that God for.
You see, so I think what we've done here with the sonic events is when you ask a question
or we come up with a subject matter.
I like to steer clear from the anyone listening to Greek speak also will know that steer clear
from the typical ideology narratives that are out there because they're confusing and
they're designed to be so and it's actually a form of politics.
So just to almost want to bypass your question because it's complex the narratives that have
been put forward from those religions are complex and least stupid if I can say that right
and are designed to make the individuals insane if you know what I mean if they're examined
because they're completely diametric within themselves divided opposing contradictory
completely just like academia.
So how's that for an answer?
It certainly is an answer.
I agree with you in the sense that I don't think that there's any gain to be had to overly
dissect things that are inherently distasteful but I think that there is some measure of gain
that could be had by at least looking at the history of certain things to better understand
the present.
When you look at the history of monotheism you do find ancient references to the idea of
a supreme or preeminent deity in things like the zor-assurinism even in the late Bronze
Age with Akhenotans reverence of the god at 10 but I do believe that that kind of reverence
is actually what they call heenotheism where you have one god that you place above all others
as the most important.
But the you know meaning you know meaning primary Greek like you know is the first number in
Greek you know deal tria right?
Where monon means soul or one where you know means prime.
Correct.
And so this notion of only one god existing and then all other spirit beings being peripheral
isn't really something that pops up until after 500 BC you start to see references in Greek
philosophy to things like Aristotle's prime mover the stoics talk about their cosmic
god and then later on certain Judean sex eventually starts saying that their god is the
only one.
What are some of the developments that you've seen historically where things moved towards
this only recognizing one god is being relevant or legitimate?
Okay when anything is moved forward in a culture it's done by those that control the culture
and it's usually those that you never heard of so I've said before if you've ever heard
of someone or seen them or their name they're not the ones in power they are figureheads
all of them going back in history as far as you want to go.
And 99% of the time the only time you do find those that say their in power are in power
have some divine influence right and that's a whole other discussion.
So in other words the political science of it right when they put forward monotheism what
they are telling you if you translate that that they are god over you and they can enforce
it because if you don't agree with what they say they'll send someone over to kill you
and your children and take all your stuff or wipe you out or genocide you.
So that's a code basically.
Actually there's even passages in scripture where men will certain men will elevate themselves
to that point in the end overtly but when you look at let's say in god we trust on the
dollar bill whenever a name of a god is not given the people that are promoting that behind
the scenes are the gods they consider themselves to be god whenever the information is obscured
anyone who in other words a quote unquote gatekeeper is in control of and after a while they
they so so the monotheism when you examine it very closely the power based that promotes
that culturally academically however politically they are putting themselves in that position
and they rely on an ignorant populace and the populace of course is very reliable so that's
a very simple point though that aspect because anyone at all that has any even cursory you
know literacy or even is not a literate that asks someone else to read any primary fundamental
document ancient document regarding the gods you'll see that monotheism is not a good point.
That's very interesting also quite novel even in the esoteric things that I've written
I've never quite seen them you know hint to that because at least in the esoteric writings
they'll say we're propping up this nonsense and we're the ones who are the gods but I
don't think I've come across that position.
No you won't because because it's it's overly objectifying.
A simple point is this you go to let's say any major religious institution.
Once you get into the deeper inner battles you'll find that they worship Satan and if you
ask them why they'll say because he's the ruler of the earth Vatican Judean Islam Hindu all
the world religions do that when you get into the battles of you go into the Vatican into
whatever you know their satanists and they're not they're not public about it but they're
not that private about it either in other words if you're cleaning toilets in the Vatican you
will know that you don't have to be a high bishop you know right just cleaning toilets or
you know the Swiss guard there knows that everybody knows that anybody that's part of the
administrative faculty if you're there as a window washer you know that their satanists
they're not they're not shy about it but it doesn't get publicly disclosed actually it is disclosed
it's just not confirmed.
Hate that word disclosure because disclosure just means to reveal and but confirmation
means you get the seal of you know approval from an authority so again this can be debated
on a juvenile level but on a mature objectifying level yeah all the real all the main religion
administrative bodies are satanists and if you have they they won't hide it you won't see
it in you know in the press and they won't say it on the pulpit but they'll tell you yeah
well the the Satan runs the earth why so of course we worship him he's he's the God of this
world which is also in scripture by the way the Freemasons who are no sticks also worship
that kind of stuff when I say Satan I'm saying that in a in a in a very general sense they
actually have very specific deities you know like ancient demons and things like that is
what I mean but when I say Satanism it's a broad brush to make people think you know
of the opposite the adversary versus what they're told and by the way when you hear about
no sticks just remind them that you know how the the Vatican has the Jesuits and you know each
you know each religious group has sort of like its own army well the army of the no sticks is
the are the Freemasons Freemasons are no sticks by the way they do use the term but not they don't
want to be associated with it just like for example I don't want to be associated with Christians
I will never say I'm a Christian but if you look at what I profess to you know my statement of
faith yes of course it lies in the biblical Messiah biblical Christ oh so it means your Christian no I'm
not you see that's how the Freemasons do with the no sticks yeah yeah and although by the way a
a fundamentalist meaning based not you know they tell your fundamentals a bad term fundamental means
just fundamentals right like the word a is pronounced are the word b is pronounced bae you know
it's it's not you know it's fundamentalism a fundamentalist Muslim is a Torah believer actually
they did teach that while that the law is in the Torah right so does that make them a closet Jew no does
that make them Jewish no do you see how it's not that simple but you can find the truth of the
matter pretty simply yes absolutely and just not to shock people the way you find out that a fundamentalist
Muslim or a Islamic culture is it it uses the Torah is because there are I'd say about a school would say
a score but but a dozen or so passages that tell you if you want law you have to go to Moses
what Moses wrote it's in the current various Syria I think Syria 28 Syria 31 you can you know look it up
yeah yeah look it up on your own so let's move on to specifically look at what they call Judaism when
you talk about that I found that you have to differentiate between the ethnic and territorial denotation
versus the religious one we have the modern word Jew which more or less means member of the modern
Israeli state or religion and that word is not the same as Judean which means ethnically descended from
the people who once inhabited the region of Judah in what ways have you found that that distinction is relevant
eschatologically because when you read about the supernatural ultra natural events and let's say
prophetic dictates it's what runs through your blood and what allegiances you have so it's mainly
genealogical and then also it's allegiance so you can have someone who is not of the line of Judah
right because if you just a short interjection if you read the Bible there are no Jews prior to Abraham
and there really no Jews prior to Judah and technically all of the scripture I think the original
King James didn't have well maybe they did they changed it several times in 1611 revisions but it's
never Jew it's Judean so Judean then connotates a very specific line from one of the 12 or 13 sons
right so technically before Judah was born there are no Jews if you the word Jew equals Judean but
allegiance is also important because in the what's called the Torah so generous strangers that come in
and commit themselves to the the the economy of the Torah meaning the culture of the Torah to
be considered as equals so there's no racism and there's no prejudicing once someone takes an
allegiance to Yahweh like that and and there's no conversion also there's no ministry you want you
want to be with us you learn we don't go out and tell people what they should do right and when
you read about ministry and the New Testament it's about go tell those who were know about the
possibility of the Christ coming let them know that he came and was resurrected it's not to create some
ridiculous religion or something you know and so is there a sense in which there's a fallacy
in the language between Jew and Judean where when the Jews talking about themselves they're talking
about a fictitious group well yes it's it's a ideology it's a political group just like Christian is
political right there's no right when you think about it that way like when you hear church for
here's a good example church means circus no matter how you slice it right a kid is a baby goat
no matter how you slice it no matter how you want to look at it when words like that take on
different meaning it's based on the ideology of that culture and these cultures come and go
and when they go they're typically criticized harshly they're never criticized when they're still around
is it known out of what culture the Jewish group emerged out of no no it's hard to say but there's
a lot of mucking about in Europe after the first millennia of this Europe like I heard someone say
well Jewish means Yahweh's wish I'm high I got a good laugh out of that it's like history it's his story
or television is telling lies on your vision so it goes from stuff like that all the way to the
the invention of the letter J which was the letter i in the 1500s with a comma next to it a little
hook they use the letter i with a little hook a comma and then they say why don't we connect the
comma that little hook in the letter i and make a J you see that's how the letter J came about around
the 16th century 1500s it's just I'm oversimplifying there but it's pretty accurate these are things like
L-L-L like you know how the different technology with the computers you have all these acronyms i-m-h-o or
L-o-l or all that are they are they useful tools to communicate yes are they profoundly trivial yes
and here's the interesting part let's let's just cut to the chase if you're going to be
today and quote unquote an adherent and fundamental you would follow the Torah and none of them do
they don't know it it's not taught you can't blame them for being blind
right they don't even know what day it is right good luckily and they don't understand how to manage
the economy of the food laws they don't understand you know they yeah which leads to who's leading them
so if you really want to get down to it there are it's basically what which era are we discussing
and which culture but in terms of if you again to cut to the chase a lot of the quote unquote
Judeans know who they are and all the other like the Levites and the Benjaminites so they know who
they are the world doesn't really know who they are and the world doesn't even know what it means
but again let's harken back to I said earlier in the Torah you'll find that if a stranger or so
jr or a foreigner comes into the camp into the into the the culture and decides to make
an allegiance to Yahweh and follow his laws he is now included do you see how it works it would be
the same as a you know any club right once you take an oath or whatever so there that's those are
the two levels but you have to understand the the fundamental aspect of the genealogy also you
know the meaning the descendants of Abraham and the descendants of Judah Isaac but you see there
are just as many descendants of Abraham that are in quote unquote non-Jewish right through Ishmael
and others then there are right because he had three wives I think three women that he
and then Isaac had four women in one of them Judah comes out so it's interesting the three in the four
and the four and the Judah is the fourth of the fourth woman the oldest woman yeah fun with numbers huh
yeah what's that called Gematria yeah there's a lot to it but there does seem there there seems to be
a break between ancient israelite religion and the Judaism of the second temple period so prior to
the Babylonian exile Israel seemed very clear in their understanding about the diversity and the
hierarchy among the gods in which nations you know had a god ruling over them etc but then after
the fifth century BC a lot of that seems to fall apart once the temple is destroyed in Greece and
Persia become dominant it's almost like these relax created a new system led by groups like the
Pharisees and the Sadducees or Dynasties like the Hezmoneans and it becomes a lot more political
and nationalistic and overly zealous and almost delusional can you talk about those developments
well the Hezmonean was the was the post Greek Hellenism I mean they really lost their culture
they actually lost their culture big time to the Babylonians I should say which came after the Assyrians
the Assyrians were too practical that's another discussion the Babylonians were more
all-encompassing it not just practical you know in other words the Babylonian stuff will permeate every
aspect of your life where the Assyrians are more like the blue collar you know conquerors but anyway
how many times can you can your culture be modified let's just go let's use the American culture as a
an example back in the 17th and 16th centuries the colonies were here in America and they were
settled the colonies the states were colonies they were corporations mostly British English Scottish
settlers so when you came here let's say to what's called New York New Amsterdam or the Virginia
colonies or the Carolinas or Pennsylvania you essentially met Scots Germans Brits
essentially but if you look at it now it's essentially American isn't it very different
well what happened well 200 years and more more foreign influence right right hmm so when we look
at some of the other ways that the religious and the cultural practices of the Judeans changed
during the Babylonian exile we see changes in the time-keeping observance with the adoption of the dark
moon changes to the language and religion in the emergence of certain mystery religion undercurrents
so one could say that the Judeans who returned to Israel from the exile had a very different
calibration than the ones who went into Babylon and you could almost say that the upper classes at
least were more Babylonian than they were Judean especially since a lot of them chose to stay in
Babylon correct yes and there were a lot of them that were allowed to stay enrolled by Babylonian
governorship in Israel or in Jerusalem also I'd say the Majarr those who count right like imagine a
city of morons of a million people they're all morons except for a hundred people when you take
those hundred people out of that city there's you know 9999000 whatever left but they're not counted
right in other words you don't count you know what I mean it's kind of like a uh
when you look at a school of the thousand kindergartners and four staff you know it's the staff
that counts you don't go to the kindergartners asking about next year's budget or something
you have many conditions like that the gods by the way they do favor they do favor people who
are productive good at what they do knowledgeable they don't like the um they throw the sin all the gods
very little exception don't like the lower classes lower classes meaning those that
you know you might for example have a philosopher that decides to say screw this society I'm
going to live in the in a vase in a big tarot pot in the in the forest right that's different I'm
not talking about that I'm talking about the masses you know the the what you in America you call
the middle class they're not really middle class they're lower class right you know the hot dog
baseball apple pie wave the flag get my pension that's not middle class there's no middle class here
it's it's low class and then you have the the credit wealthy and elite and then you have the poor
but it's the poor are slightly below the low because there's no middle class in America they're
lower class but anyway I think that's never been said before all you hear is the middle class here's
no middle class where show me show me someone whose middle class I'll show you a little class human
or low class culture right uh you know Britney Spears you know who we're gonna go vote to make
things better you know go buy your microwave heat up your you know that's not middle class but they
have so yeah it still doesn't matter yeah you ever go to a redneck redneck garage sale
like a lots of stuff man but anyway it's not yeah the stuff yeah that's a simple minded way to look at it
though I'm talking about what the gods how the gods see right you have to have knowledge you have to
have where with all you have to also be very good with your surroundings right so anyway uh
it's it's not that simple the simplest way to assess anything is look at what's promised and then
look at the end result and it's never very clean cut is it right when I say what's promised is like
let's see something prophetic in scripture or something that's written historically but you look
at it later in the outcome is very different right here's another way to look at it Cyrus and others
from the Persian Empire agree that they the the Judean authorities that could rule in Jerusalem
and rebuild the temple should and they supported that action okay and with minimal influence
not like the Greeks they didn't decide to build a Zaroastrian temple right like the Greeks want
to build the temple of Zeus or things like that and the Romans and the others they respected so
so they go back and uh everything's uh peachy keen we're right back to where we started right wrong
right it's not like it was under David or Solomon right although technically you could say that
a big part of the reason that things couldn't go back to the way that it was because there was no king
there was no monarchy because you were operating under the auspices of the Persians well for the kind
of let them go back yeah only has monians kind of they try to fix that with the yeah the hasmonians
yeah later but they yeah we would have been known it's a political move again what happened is the
the whole thing was subsumed into you know more of a secular culture in the marty it wouldn't be
hard to find a descendant of David but they put in halfbreeds right herod for example i mean
that literally it's a breeding program you understand royalty is a breeding program yeah i mean
you can have fake royalty as well well um the first king let's say in israel there was there was no
kings before that no one he was made a king um he's a king if everyone says he's a king
and of course there's a process there because they had to get permission from the higher authority
not the time what's very hard for people to understand is um people were the angelic realm or the
gods were more interactive back then it's really hard for people to understand that's why I tell people
your prayers aren't being answered no one's listening to you it's pretty accurate
they may they might think they their prayers are being answered and listened to because you know you'll
always confabulate you know something you know i was totally broke i was destitute i prayed and
now the son is sorry getting money yeah not really there's gonna come a time when the again where
there will be listening and when they listen to your prayers the gods they were still let you know
directly and now it's called hearing voices you'll be put in a straight jacket with a cherry
lollipop but if i tell people your prayers are not being listened to they don't like to hear that right
okay why am i saying why am i being so harsh and strong about that because back then when you
prayed someone came around says yeah we heard your prayer right someone i mean physically you know
and they were there one moment physically and then they were not it sounds bizarre just like now if
you went back and you said i have a computer it's an apple or windows they're look at you like
yeah i know what you're saying but i really don't know what you're saying so if you tell people
that when people prayed and they expected you know they did sacrifice and there was a physical
manifestation and a acknowledgement it was tangible today they they don't see it because no one's
listening right now there is gonna come a time in the near future where that will change
all you hear is confabulation well i was in a tough spot i prayed and i got help but yeah okay
it's not yeah i'm not saying you did not get help but i'm not you know it did an angel come and
acknowledge well then you know you know here's an example you know put a dollar under your pillow
in the tooth fairy it's the same thing no one's listening to your prayers okay we look at okay
yeah well we'll stop crushing crushing people with the emotions for just a second
hey by the way there's a whole bunch of scripture to support that now i get it just said yeah
yeah there's a lot of scripture to support that there surely is um i don't know too much about the
language changes during that time but at some point ancient Hebrew died off because it wasn't spoken
by the second first century BC except maybe in specialized settings the lingua franca was mostly
aromatic and Greek in the region what do you know about the depth of ancient Hebrew there's a lot
that's complicated there was a whole mess of stuff going on in that uh seventh century BC
sixth century fifth century BC between the Egyptians the various mainly the Egyptians there's a
very there's very little about it uh known as like a Sinaiac writing which was a Egypt to promote you
know it you know like a lingua franca right and that influenced the ancient Hebrew a lot
which led to the Babylonian script that you see today called modern Hebrew which was fully adopted
standardized by one thousand eighty let's say but there was a lot of language uh uh
in other words efforts to standardize language back in the seventh century sixth century fifth
century fourth century BC with major Egyptian influence and you can look it's kind of like chasing
a rabbit to find out where and why things changed but um there is a passage I think in Ezra or
Nihemiah where he says now you're gonna write differently or something like that which kind of
seals it around that you know five sixty five eighty BC time period or they went to a more modern
Hebrew there's a lot of stuff happening around that period but you know I found that if a language
dies off twenty five hundred years ago ish I find it hard to understand how it resurfaces just a few
hundred years ago with modern Hebrew so that's always been a bit of an anomaly that no
much challenge is that well yeah the modern Hebrew is a hybrid but the ancient Hebrew it's not
hasn't died off because it still is translatable I've actually seen ancient Hebrew on uh for example out
in the decalogue written out on los lunus new mexico decalogue stone right and it's readable
I'm not saying I've seen ancient Hebrew anyway because in a sense I mean I've seen it on a monument
and that was supposedly done about eight hundred years ago in new mexico so one of the things
that I have heard is that modern Hebrew is very much influenced by Yiddish which emerged in the
middle ages as this language among the Ashkenashi Ashkenashi Jews in central Europe that would make
more sense since Yiddish was actually a thing and could be ported over into modern timing is off
Yiddish would be a few hundred years after but in its origin around the maseradix let's say 11
hundred's or so prior to that we're had already for a decided as a family scholarly scribe type
academic just like you have shimon and schuster today or whatever or me if they're even still around
publishing house type people sort of formalized it around a thousand eighty ten twenty eleven hundred
and was formalized middle ages as after it was you you can find that modern Hebrew writing much
earlier than that you know even around the you'll you can still find it around the time of
seven century six century when islam surfaced I would say I would lean if I were to lean anywhere to
get my stuff on where it came from would be I would lean heavily on the Babylonian influence
hence the Babylonian Talmud right but there was a major effort around that time actually you know
the seven six fifth century BC from Egypt to formalize because Egypt always saw herself as being the
the crown jewel of that culture right until you start going all the way east again to India
but the Levant up and down the Levant left and to the right if you're facing the map Egypt
always saw itself as being the cultural center of the world yeah there's I looked a while back there's
sanaiic like the Sinamon Sinaiic form of writing and if you look at it it's a not three four hundred BC
it's very similar to modern Hebrew and was put out by Egyptian and that was also the time of the
Holenicism of you know the founding of Alexandria and all that right ummm
tolamian kind of time period but I wouldn't say that the ancient Hebrew is lost or dead
it's still very tangible and readable and usable it's not like linear a or linear b of ancient Greece
with 200 you know letters in the alphabet and you have 14 letters to make the sound e right it's not
pictographic either like uh Chinese so right um I don't know there to be much information outside of
maybe Jewish literature about the internal developments during the Babylonian exile but it does
seem like the genesis of the Pharisee class came out of that period because the temple was gone the
observance of religious rituals was moved into homes and handled by elite certain elected leaders
and also I believe there were questions about the legitimacy of the second temple because it was
constructed under the auspices of Persia um partially that's partially why synagogues came about
right can you talk about these well that was the great that's part of the great assembly you know
the centhedron and all that and the pedashim and the sadrashim you know like the the names those
names imply you know piety or and you know nobleness and within you know doing the right thing or
whatever corruptible uh anacultic but uh post the around that time of the Hasmonean you know let's
get rid of this Greek or lost our culture and so much that we could say we're I know it was we're losing
our culture so much we could say we've lost its let's form an assembly but uh they're gonna they've
lost they they've already lost the ideologies and the old uh all they had to do is go back to the
text and read which no one does right so they already decidedly lost everything culturally and they
try to firm it up by forming these assemblies and the pedashim and the sadrashim and so on
and what did what did it do I mean a lot of public works you know what I mean public works like when
you see a mega church you know for Christians that's public works project isn't it there is
how big those buildings are all the seats and the parking lots and all that is that religious or
is that a public works project so what happens is they you have a group that is supposedly reinstating
you know the good old days but they're just getting involved in public works projects and various
codes and dogmas to restructure the society for their you know their power base I mean the Pharisees
as a group seem to emerge out of the scribes and the sages and they started gaining more power
around the second century BC-ish um I think an example of how the Pharisees and the Sadducees
differed in their approach to the law was their application of an eye for an eye because what I'm told
is that the Pharisee understanding was that the value of a lost eye was to be paid in currency
by the perpetrator so like silver probably but the Sadducees had a literal view that no your eye
has to be gouged out now do you know why these two camps sort of emerged this way given that they
didn't exist prior ideology very simple ideology and what people will expect because no one really
likes a monopoly right no one really likes you know they have anti-trust laws for monopolies so
you have to give people that they the idea that they have choice where you wouldn't see much of
that during the the times of Moses or David or Solomon that's more of the um easing up of you
know more of a secular way of functioning here let me just I want to interject something when you
read scripture that is a weekly newsletter how much do you expect to get out of a weekly newsletter
well as much as a weekly newsletter can give you why do I say that because the day is a thousand years
and it covers roughly well it's a 13,000 year period but in earnest it does cover a pretty solid
amount of 4,000 years and it includes a 7,000 year plan so if one day is a thousand years well that's
just what happens cosmically for a week when you read scripture right so when you hear about the
culture changing over a thousand years that's just the days worth of change cosmically and the only
reason you have all these epics changing is because man only lives for a hundred years or so I don't
think it sounds like the Greeks get into philosophy about these things but if see if people had a
normal life of a thousand years I assure you these cultural changes and discussions about what
happened to who and when and how wouldn't be happening because the you'd be alive for a thousand years
and your ideology and your your culture would be pretty much unchangeable for at least a thousand
years within your lifetime right so these changes is because your life is so short so imagine you only
live five years you wouldn't have this conquest in that conquest a few hundred years later you'd
have a conquest every year or every five years a complete turnaround of the entire planet because
you only live five years you see right that's true you live a thousand years nothing's gonna change
in a thousand years you're not gonna accept it you know so you have to factor these changes and
what happened who and how and where based on my men's life lifespan of less than a hundred years
and then it makes sense not why who why you know how and when what well it's very simple because these
beings live for a hundred years and you can screw around with them for that hundred year period but it's
easier to screw around with them when they die right their culture right no one to defend it you
influence the young so you'll notice that there's a 40 if historians have found you know 40 year
200 year 400 year cycles why it's because you only live for a hundred years if you live to a thousand
you would have 2500 3000 year cycles yeah that's good food for thought yeah I see no problem and I see
nothing to really learn from the changes of course of course every hundred years or 200 or
300 years you have an empire of course because these poor saps only live for a hundred
and you look at the influencing and of one culture and the reaffirming of another yeah it takes several
generations times you know so a hundred times two times three yeah of course look for example at
Frank Herbert who writes fiction in the dune god emperor he lives for several thousand years and the
universe is stable for that time period because he lives for that long another factor that seemed to
play a role in how different israelite sex developed in the second temple period was something called
the oral law or the oral Torah and so the israelite had the Torah that was given to them by Moses
and that was emphasized by the Sadducees but at some point prior to or during the Babylonian exile the
emphasis was also placed on a secondary set of unwritten traditions on how to apply the Torah
and that was favored by the Pharisees and then that grew eventually after Ezra you know so by the
time we get to the New Testament the Judeans are giving equal weight to both laws if not more to the
oral one can you talk about how these two observances create problems yeah animals don't like to read
and write so if you want to take control of people you push them into the animalistic realm
I once saw this one guy got ticket for not having a driver's license so walk into the court and
clearly says that you know all the states that offer driver's licenses are
have to go under the federal requirements to you know issue and require that and he brings in
all this stuff it says well unless you're driving a vehicle that weighs more than 10,000 pounds you
know your average car is only three to four thousand you know you're going to be doing this that
and the other and he shows it to the judge says well that's not what it says that's a judge actually
says that's not what it says right like you're not what you're reading is not really there you get it
and he reduced the fine from 250 to 75 do you see what I mean by that see the analogy
why you go into oral because animals don't read so if you're ruling over animals
you can you know what you say goes crack the whip of course you're going to impose oral law
in this culture it's television people when they let's say for example look at law
judicial system and all that what they know about it comes from television which is the oral
they don't know any law even police and attorney generals don't know any law supreme court judges
don't know any law I mean they might know enough to get the job but they don't know how to apply it
because if the minute they try to apply the law they're fired or they find porn on their computer
or there was a scandal to get a get a get rid of you know public you know get they're not going to
tell you regard rid of them because he's trying to apply the law regard rid of them because he was
found with you know crack in his box smoking crack here's the video you see what I mean
the same thing is that you see in corruption today it was going on back then
whenever you hear oral this or all that it's like you're being reduced out of the human realm
into the animal world heard you've heard of herd immunity right the herd the sheeple
it's pretty sad it doesn't take you don't have to be a genius to see through that but
seemingly you know you do so simple
yeah so that I bypass that whole thing the significance of it is more cultural it's psychological
and it's domination no I get it hmm that's why for example uh you know the let's go back to the subject
a little bit uh Jews quote unquote uh through history were always intermediaries between cultures
that were rival like uh like you said the medieval ages to all the way till now um you had the
Constantine type empire uh Christian empire that didn't like the Muslim empire or you know
groups so the Jews got in between as merchants you know the go between so when the Europeans wanted to
trade with the Arab world in India the Jews got in between because they were neither a third party
they were uh also they were you know they were uh they found themselves being a third party between
cultures that were um at odds with each other and uh also it's within their culture you can read
that Yahweh promotes education and literacy you'll find several verses where he says when the people
passed by you know that they should not only see the law but they should read it and they should know
what it means you know I think it's in Joshua in other places the king was supposed to make his own
copy of the five hand write his own copy of the five books of Moses you know on and on and on and on
so uh there was a the Jewish culture and the Torah promotes literacy so that made him a good
interview because you know you didn't if you're gonna rule over people it gets tricky but if you're
gonna rule over animals it's a lot easier so if you can bring the people to think like animals
right uh then you're ruling over animals because they think like animals i use a lot of animal
analogy like you know and what the the mass the public uh or you know you they go to a feeding trough
right spiritually it's a feeding trough so yeah they're the human uh in other words people
don't exist anymore there's it's very few people left on the uh lots of other beings too like it
but very few there are no more people left men and women no more very very few if not any and
you're and those that know that there are men and women um uh will not be too vocal about what it takes
to be a man or woman hmm well the last set of questions I have is about pretty much how Judaism
developed after the first century um I think it's interesting that similar to how the various forms
of Christianity that existed in the fourth century A.D. had to be suppressed by the state so that
NIC and Christianity could become dominant in that way also Judaism had different sex that
disappeared um so following the Judeo Roman wards you had the revolutionary groups like the zealots
who were crushed the Sadducees disappeared with the destruction of the temple and the Essenes
vanished after being sacked by the Romans so you only have the Pharisees remaining and their
vision of Judean religion is what became rabbinic Judaism and eventually normative Judaism that we see
today why do you think no other group has emerged in the last 2000 years to really challenge that
position of the rabbis and their religious stranglehold well here's the thing you know what like
artificial scarcity is you know like if the farmers have too much crop they burn it so the
prices stay high right that's very simple that's what's all it is they just make you just they just uh
it's a control again uh you you make people's uh life tough enough that they're not going to care
about educating themselves about things that don't put you know uh food in their belly
and when you hear about these groups being crushed i guess their god wasn't listening to them
because if he was he would go to fight he would fight for them very simple well this is always
winner than losers even if the gods fight it's really a battle between the gods but if your god is not
listening to you it's not a battle between gods for example that is scripture with Exodus the whole
Exodus thing is a battle between the gods don't get hung up about the plagues and uh whatever whatever
it's a battle between gods that's the crux of the matter you've talked a lot in the past about
today's rabbis and how they have an almost oppressive nature to them within Judaism and Israel
can you elaborate on that a bit yeah i call them the kashdapo is the kahimden stosos something in
jerman means the secret police that's what kashdapo is an act a short course kahim means secret in
jerman and stun stun stafo or something is police that's what the rabbis are you know how we
said earlier oh i said earlier that all of the mainstream religions at the very top administrative
level are satanic you know in other words they worship the god of this earth and it's not an opinion
right you could look everything i'm saying up but what they put out in the culture is what the culture
quote unquote demands loosely because remember they're too busy working to put you know feed themselves
in their children so they may not have a revolution or war or anarchy in the streets let's say
if they say we're satanists but pretty close so they want to maintain the cultural identity
right so when you say the rabbis or whatever they're maintaining cultural identity but they're given
quote-unquote liberty to use their own policies that's why a lot of people in israel they're asked
you know you're going to live here are you secular or religious well you want to say you're secular
because if you say you're religious you're assigned a rabbi district-wise any noxel you do
or any time or whatever and make sure that you're doing what he wants you to do or what is culturally
popular at the time is that how you want to live so for most people that's totally okay because they
want to they want to be good Jews they want to be good whatever you know so in order to be good i
have to accept that you see like most people that are for example the Catholics do what they do
because they want to be good people they don't know any better but in the end it doesn't matter
what they're doing is wrong and they're going to be you know they're going to pay the price
right even cosmically most Catholics they think they they're why you call it because they want to be a
good person wow it's like you just got a face palm and walk away no you're really ignorant
you don't spend five minutes in your entire life looking anything up right oh Greek that doesn't
make any sense they have bible you know whatever every wednesday a woden's day you know for woden
and they study the bible yeah i mean it shows you cosmic censorship right so it's the same thing
with with any religion the e-moms they do the same stuff you know when you hear about stonings
because someone stepped on the Quran by accident you know in Afghanistan or you know
Kuwait or whatever you know they they kill thousands of people every year for just
accrating the Quran that just doesn't you know what happens is you have the local Imam that goes
and does the little thing and based on what he thinks or should be done rouse up the crowd and
you know what i mean it's every every religion it's all the same with the Mormons the calf
yeah you just go down the you know whatever you know it's the it's that secret police mentality
and connected to what you were saying about the secret satanism stuff at the top so like out of the
rabbinic tradition came this assortment of literature that has arguably become more authoritative
than the tenak you you have the mission and then the gamara which make up the tomwood is it
because of the hidden esoteric side of things that the rabbis
tend to give more weight and attention to what they write in the tomwood and the tomah no they they're
got no if you read scripture he says i will you always says i will turn my ear i will turn my face towards
you so what's the opposite of that turn away they know they know he has turned away from them
so when they did their prayers or whatever they did they get no help so we got to do what
what's going to put food in our stomach so this esoteric knowledge is sort of esoteric knowledge
yes it kind of works with the natural world in accordance with the god of this earth
according to your human lifespan according to your desires
you form the the groups the cults that empower have power over the culture
and life goes on there's nothing special about it their god is their god my meaning
yaway is not listening and they know it because they ask them are you listening and there's no answer
so what do we do now well if this doesn't work let's go to the next one see if that works
and it works enough for them as a power base because if they were preaching and teaching and using
yaway and they asked for something and it doesn't come all the people will be like uh you're lying
to us where's the power where's the control over them then the people think you're a fraud and a
sham how are you going to control them but if you start saying well it's mystery knowledge and
this that in the other and it goes on and on and this this in the other and you get a little
carger up some things that may or may not come true and appear to be true and received is being
true now you have power over them and he starts teaching that in order to be good you have to listen
to us right that's the Catholic thing right I know whatever this is the same religious thing if
you know to be a good person you have to listen to these group of people yeah when you first come
out with that you're going to throw rotten eggs at you but you don't go after the adults that know
what you're doing you go after their children and you wait for the adults to die and then those
children then may not be wholeheartedly into that control structure but there then you go after
their children and those children then will be more than 50 50 there'll be 70 30 and then their
children will be 90% on board so it takes three generations to develop a power base like you
know like you see in the world I mean you could do maybe like four or five hours of Greek speak
and destroy any rabbi you could do four or five hours of you know Greek speak and destroy any
Catholic priest I mean why is it because of whether I'm some kind of genius or something or whatever
no this is really so it's so simple it's like it's it's just like the emperor has no clothes the
child you know everyone is amazed the child's like he's naked it's not hard it's not difficult
and in terms of the non-ribbeneic forms of Judaism we have things like carerite Judaism,
Samaritanism, Ethiopian Judaism none of which recognize the oral law or those kind of things
can we find within any of those other groups some kind of saving grace within an otherwise
wayward religious tradition tradition no those are traditions and the traditions come from what's
allowed like for example you can do even a cursory study of history of let's say that since we're
speaking of who are the Jews of the inquisitions and the lack of favorability over several
empires in in Europe and I mean empires all the way till the end of the Ottoman empire world were one
right you could look at look at the persecution of the Jews and then it was eased up and then they
were persecuted again and they go here because they're accepted but then they're persecuted right
they you know they were persecuted in Europe Spanish acquisition all that actually they were
persecuted and destroyed by Rome in the second century completely by the end of the first
beginning of the second century completely destroyed millions killed they get where do they go they
go to Spain right then they're destroyed in Spain later on right where do they go Russia and then
Russia accepts them and then who destroys them in Russia the Russians look with the program
right programs during the 17 18 19 centuries just you see now they're accepted because they're good
third parties they're they you know like if you're starting a country or you want to bring your
country into this that you missed this particular industrial revolution you bring in quote unquote
people that are raised in a Jewish culture they're very literate they have connections they bring
you up to speed uh okay well you go live in your own neighborhood and then you destroy them get rid
of them or make them you know once they give you what you right what you want and the way the reason
they're able to do that is because they were very international you know you anyone can study
quote unquote all of the sciences and medicine mathematics astronomy and all that and from the
medieval ages on that were advanced in prior advanced in the Arab world right and Eastern world
well how did it get to Europe through the Jews right this is all because you only live 100 years
yeah again if you lived five years you would see oh this empire rose and fell in 20 years conquered the
whole world in 20 years right because that would be equivalent to 200 now let's say it's very simple if
you live five seconds you would have the Roman Empire rise and fall in three minutes right here's
another another three minutes there's another empire here comes the draconian empire takes over
the whole world you know reptilians walking around you know with their spaceships let's say right
and they control the earth for two hours you only live for five seconds of course in me that's a long time
wow look at all these changes right but again if you live for a thousand years plus
and going to see much change a few thousand years all these things are once you consider the
that it's based on cosmic awareness and then lifespan and then location meaning the planet earth
you look at history and it's like of course yeah there's a curiosity about what happened when and how and
why and who but you have to consider those things there is a cosmic situation a clockwork
and then there's the lifespan of the beings that you're looking at I mean let's go look at it this way
this is maybe over-adreptifying the life of rats look at the life expectancy of a rat and their empire
and their culture and whatever look how it changes based on their life expectancy right same you'll
find that with anything so the division here not to divert but you have to keep you have to keep
that in mind the lifespan right of the beings that you're discussing and this is not a contrast but
an inclusion of the gods what's the lifespan of a god we don't know right so this is no big deal to
them but it's a big deal to us again that's why I say they're not listening no one's listening to you
they're they're there's scuttle butt yeah they're they're listening they're observing but it's not
like it used to be right and for those that are wise and understand what's coming it will change
right in the near future right so and I do want to just to ask if there's something to distinguish between
they're not listening as in the ones that you're praying to aren't listening versus perhaps there
are some low-level malevolent ones that are listening and do what they want right for each person
there could be five thousand malevolent malevolent entities waiting for that person to do the right
thing to bring them in because they have to be some brought in somehow they each have their own
characteristic on how they're brought in but I assure you the big ones the main ones are not
the listening because everything's already set it's kind of like you're getting ready you know
I don't know you're putting on tixedo to go to the the debutant ball and your neighbor you know
you got to be there in an hour your neighbor knocks on the door and says you can you help me change
a flat tire you can be like no dude I got an important place to be I got to be at soon so that's
exactly what's going on with the gods now the higher-level ones they know what has to be done at
a certain time and you're praying about this that you know that it like did shut up and the angels
like well shut it go down tell them a shut up now just leave them alone you know not worth it
we got it we got a big we got a big thing going on soon here otherwise prophecy would be
meaningless you're given more power you're actually your spirit being is in a micro
might in a microcosmic way far more powerful than you understand to manipulate your surroundings
spiritually physically and all that that's why I tell people you're praying to this god but
hi Dan I know it's not listening no no you're doing it on your own but I'm not not to take it away from
the gods because the it's at this time period that we're living and see if we live during the time of
Abraham or David or whatever yeah you pray and what did he say he says well actually got a response
they were quite busy you know like they were answering their emails you know
now they're not even turning on the computer they're just looking at the street camera
I'm not I'm not asking anyone to believe the one I'm saying or agree with me but you must hear this
and consider it file it away for later so later on at some time say this guy Greek said we weren't
listening oh yeah that's right we weren't listening there's no way to prove that right actually there
is I I know if they're listening they're gonna let you know and they let you know if why they're
delayed and when they came give your response anyway I don't know anyone getting any respogon
teaching people on scripture and y'all ain't all this no one's coming to message I got a voice
that came and told me nothing nothing they just started trippeting their lives getting better
to their prayers being answered or whatever this is the first time I'm actually saying this adamantly
like this and this ties in with quote unquote the people in Israel they're getting their land back
and all that because he says well I will turn my I will turn towards you you will be my people and
you're I will be your god if you look at what's going on there right now is any of that any of that
true nope it doesn't mean that there's if there is no influence right doesn't mean that he's not
influencing and all that and making things happen right okay the last question I want to ask
before we can oh and by the way let me interject this is what gives these these these satanic people
that they're they're they're ruled they're in the medical like your food industry I know this
firsthand not for secondhand from someone who is one of the families all your major food companies
that provide food and water to the people of the earth those families and groups are satanic
all of your major religions the high administrative are satanic all of your high political banking elite
medical elite scientific elite are satanic go on and on and on your industry people are satanic
when I say satanic they actually harvest little children
slot you know human sacrifice with all you know whatever ritual you want to get into process
you know cannibalism burning whatever whatever whatever and guess what when they do these things
guess what happens they get answers the room suddenly the temperature in the room drops 40 degrees
and a being appears I'm talking about like right now like today and tomorrow when these people
that I mentioned do these rituals the room temperature drops 30 40 50 degrees and a being appears
and talks to them is your god doing that I don't think so get real people
yes that is something to consider hmm hmm you can even go on the internet and look at what up about
it so there's plenty of testimony on it's all true when these Satanists and their medical political
related doing these ritual sacrifices they have a answer from their god maybe not every time but
85 and 95 percent of the time where you don't zero percent of the time do you see what's going on
let's get real people get your head out of the fantasy world get out of that religious dog macrab
yeah I mean within the mainstream stuff people aren't really taught to think about their religion
is practical in that way if there has to be this mystery woo thing that it happens behind a curtain
and then we say that god did something oh yeah wizard of all types of you you can do most of it
most of it there's actually technology that could move you along if you study a lot of the Hindu
culture their religion quote quote stuff is very heavy on technology you know tools actually physical
things there's some stuff like that in the biblical sense you know that the the Eiffah the
Irma Thurumim you know the the Eiffah the priest's war the workings of the inner part of the temple
the various tables in artifacts arc of the covenant those things were forms of technology
communication devices so on and so forth but anyway yeah so if you want to know which gods are
listening and acting it's the the dark forces right now and there's as I'm as we're doing this
is probably maybe a dozen the type of these rituals that are getting answers right now as we speak
where you can get on your knees and pray to whatever god you think you might have
you're not going to get an answer so what the hell is going on Greek or what's going on Arcan
right what the hell is going on well I just told you what's going on you you as an educated mature
adult have to make a decision on where you're going to put your energy and no don't I'm not saying
go ahead and put your energy with sataness if you were to I can tell you I would give you advice
on this is if if you create an intent and quote unquote a prayer even though they're not listening
that you are saved and preserved from that madness and stay away from it because you're on your own
giving an example let's say you decided to go in one of these rituals or whatever your gods
not going to stop you you're going to go right into it and just with that your ability to do that
you could stay away from it and stay away from it just as much and I'm bringing this up in a
fourth right way is because people are delusional all the people delusional it's like the computer's
not working what's the first thing the tech asks you is it plugged in right the last thing that I
will just ask before we wrap up is the position you kind of alluded to this earlier maybe like 40
minutes ago the position that the leaders within Judaism have taken towards the development of
Christianity one could see the separation between those two religious groups is somewhat odd given
how much they overlap and what they claim about their holy books and their history being similar
yet you have one camp that says that Messiah came and another camp that claims that he didn't
didn't but you've previously you know talked about how behind the scenes did Judean leaders already
knew that these differences were almost manufactured because they had to cover their tracks in the
aftermath of the Christ death yes can you talk about that I have I have a very apt yes a very apt
analogy is the 9/11 fiasco it's actually it couldn't fit any better if you took the Christian
first century development on fiasco and overlaided over the 9/11 or the JFK shooting
if you had a transparency and you laid it over you know the methodology it is exactly the same
what you do is you want a the only difference is there was a change that was external actually
both in 9/11 it was external it was the worldwide power so here's an example 9/11 19 Arab
hijackers vaporized the world trade center right and supposedly airplanes crash where there was no
evidence of the airplanes and guess what they built memorials to this right so a big airplane
goes through the Pentagon and leaves in a 10 foot diameter hole with no plane degree debris
and they have the memorial as that date then there's a plane with I don't know 50, 80,
hundred people goes down in Pennsylvania and they build this big memorial
right no such thing happened as a matter of fact the hijackers I want to call the FBI say
let go arrest the hijackers that crashed the planes into the building because they were on Egyptian
television why don't you go arrest them for flying the planes in the world trade center because they're
on TV stating that they were their identity you know what I mean this is how ridiculous it is right
so what happened was the Judean religious authorities at the time when they had already discovered
what they had done which would be deicide which to kill your god kill your basically Messiah
they needed to cover it up they couldn't get rid of the cosmic guilt the divine guilt but at least if
they get rid of it's secondarily cover it up they'll feel better about it so the biblical Christ
is stone to death on an almond tree but they cover it up by saying he was crucified by the Romans
which is very clear that Pontius Pilate you could read in the books of Mark and Luke that he says
I'm returning him back to you I find no guilt that he should be killed I'm paraphrasing here you know
I'm returning you's your law you know what about Caesar no I'm making an exception and he knew the
biblical law because he did a public hand washing which is part of the ceremony of the red heifer you
know what has to do with a unjust murder let's say right so they cover it up the location where it
happened how it happened and basically the identity of the individual by promulgating the story
of 19 Arab hijackers flew airplanes right and vaporized 200,000 tons of steel at all they
perized you get my point it's exactly the same thing or the magic bullet it was one bullet it went
through the president it hit the windshield came back around hit the senator next to him or whatever
and then came back around and people you know this is actually written the Warren commission this
goes on and on and on and on and on the through history so if you in the next big false flag if well
you have if you're living in a false flag right now with the pandemic or pandemic go study what was
done in first century is you know Judea with the story of the Christ was any anyone with any
comprehension which you're not it's very difficult to meet people that have reading comprehension
we'll read even the scripture and look at the history and see that there's no Roman crucifixion
where they say it wasn't how it was done it's very simple information is information whether it's one
or two verses it doesn't matter if it was an entire book written just about that they people would
ignore it because they lack comprehension so what you do is you cover everything up
to change it in the easiest way you cannot deny an event did not happen they would like to have
done that that it never happened at all we were never there they can't go that far
so they just change everything around the identity is completely changed
and this has been this has all been going on for on and on and on i mean you know through human history
that as far as we know the biggest false flag was the crucifixion and then you could look at all the
other false flags right that modeled after that it seems like humanity seems to deserve these false flags
have you ever found any written accounts or testimonials about the Jewish leaders knowing this
or is it just uh yeah yeah it's in the Talmud actually there's there there are plenty of what I
called like junk website research sites on the internet that have parts of the Talmud of various
Talmuds that talk about the yes yes shoe character Ben Pandora and all this other stuff you know years
ago i was in a public library actually university library and i did find writings about Pontius
pilots saying that he a mob took him away to be stoned and i have not found anything on the internet
i've never seen any deviation from the fact then the truth that Pontius pilot washed his hands of
the matter and did not proceed technically with the execution he proceeded uh as an occupational
force giving a permit permission for it to take place but not with the methodology and even the
location that people believe right and the reason the Romans were around is the same thing i give the
analogy let's say that ccp communist chinese invade the us like the red dawn movie with the russians
back in the day in the eighties and they take over the united states and all the sudden the dust settles
everyone tries to go back to normal but your post office and your police and your politicians are
all ccp chinese right so people have an idea well july forth is coming around so we want to show
to us our fireworks well they have to go to the chinese ccp and get a permit to blow off their
fireworks and when your bloat guess who's going to light the fireworks and guess who's going to be
guarding and putting up the caution barrier tape ccp police but it's an american celebration
when the christ was murdered executed it was a jadein mosaic execution under roman occupation
did you see the analogy and people are too immature see the problem is this this artificial
scarcity stuff you know like with fossil fuels and we run out of water and uh you know this
burn burn burn blow up technology kind of crap and people believe scarcity
and they live a lot not only do they it's such an ironic culture where they they taught everything is
scarce but yet they're so inefficient with what they have right they waste 90% of everything if not more
conservatively 80% of what they do is wasteful and they can't stop for a minute to consider higher order
things and that means comprehension you don't want to be the only one saying this kind of stuff by
the way publicly because you're if you ever read the old stuff uh let's say turn of the 20th century
when the bankers decided to put in their credit system they said well if anyone figures out what
we're doing we'll just discredit them and you know call them insane or right so you don't want to
be the only one and right now i think i am the only one that is saying this well thankfully you
don't have people knocking at your door calling you and saying so well because i yeah i'm not selling
memberships and getting interviews and uh you want to be public i might think of well the least we
can do is provide the information for posterity or whomever wants to take a look at it later um
well based on the posterity of a decade a little bit better than a decade you don't have that much
time left now this will be very well here's the other thing when you do get get the better society
this information will be will have no value because it's just like going through the trash
basically if the next society will if the next society wants to retrospectively look back at
this society it would be the same thing as you going into the big trash bin in your neighborhood
right it's all trash nothing that you see in the society will carry over to the next other than the
basic uh five you know the star human uh you know the configuration that we have and maybe boiling water
there's the rest of it none of it's going to go transfer over uh so but everything that i've talked
about it will be known in that society for you know with comprehension indeed well on that note i think
uh we've gone through quite a few things um nine-minute questions um i think we'll be unpacking in
later episodes some of the other mainstream religions and you know maybe over the next two or three
episodes but for now uh unless you have some concluding remarks i think we can wrap this one up
Greek not that i could think of i think uh just uh carry on and now i guess when we finish this uh
we'll we'll be finished indeed uh but we'll give it a few more episodes so um yeah thank you to
everybody tuned in for this one um it's been a fun conversation and i hope you will tune in for
the next one
you
[MUSIC]