So it is that time again on what they call a Thors day or Thursday on the Pope's work schedule,
which is an interesting thing. However, I wonder exactly what day it would be. I know you're going
to tell me it's seven days from the last time I asked you. That's right. Greek. Think about it,
though. Think about it for a minute. Why? Why would anyone want to care about that?
Is it because it's just my opinion? It's what I believe. Think about it for a moment.
Look at how these things are defined. How would you define the Pope's work schedule? Well,
it's almost not polite to say it that way. But, you know, it's just a short, you know,
it's it's the CliffsNotes version. It's called the Gregorian calendar, and it has a little bit
of a history behind it, other than the rote convention that people are used to, right?
Because no one thinks about these things, right? You don't think about, you know, many things.
Many people do many things. They don't think about why they do them. And there are
certain little bit of study that sometimes can awaken wonder why they do things, which is not
what people should do, because you will not make friends or be able to have
conventional conversation, let's say. But here's the thing, Chuck. Why would it? Why does it matter?
Right? When you think about it for a minute, what's wrong with the Pope's work schedule?
You know, you know, one, you know, what you could say about it, objectively,
is it's neither good nor bad. It's kind of worthless. And I was going to I was going to
say, actually, what does it matter? Yeah, here's here's the objective point of view,
the way I would put it. A timepiece is a timepiece. What does it matter if it's accurate or not?
It's just a timepiece. How about that? Okay, that's the one side. But let's get
even more objective when you discuss law. The meaning of law is just another actually law
has been when you're speaking in English convention, you kind of lose that what that
means. Because people have been mineshafted or screwed by the legal society. They they don't
understand what we say when we say law, who we as you could figure that out someday. But
the thing is this, what is the purpose of law? Well, see, now, what's funny to me is we've gone
into law, and I started on a timepiece. Now, why is the timepiece relatable to law?
Oh, because it's lawful timekeeping. Ah, okay. But let's go back to the Pope's work schedule.
What's it based on? Nothing. What is it based on? That is a good question. Well,
well, how do we find that out? Now, philosophically, we got to go look at the timekeeping
authorities, which would be, let's say, in the American Convention, it would be,
I think it's the Naval Observatory in Colorado Springs, they have a website,
they do the atomic clocks, okay? And then it's the Greenwich guys, right? And they've got layers,
you know, the websites get more expansive into the history and how it adopted from the Julian
date to the Gregorian. If you sift through that, now, it's not necessarily like shifting,
sifting through somebody's poop to find edible corn, because you might find something in there
anyway, it's not that foul, like most research can be, right? But what you will find is they
tell you that every weeks and months and years are arbitrary, they just count days.
Okay, so a calendar has a structure to it, you know, you've got the year, you've got the month,
you've got the, you know, and they're telling you it's arbitrary, but yet that structure exists.
So it's worthless, right? In other words, they tell you it's debased. So why would it be important
to know how to keep time based on something that's based on something?
Because it goes back to law. Now, what is law? Very simple.
Well, what it is, maybe we'll pick this up on the second hour, if anyone wants to, but don't,
okay, call in. But if you're going to give us a stock academic BS answer, or what you believe in,
without some kind of reference that we can all access, I'm going to hit the red button on you.
And Chuck might be more forgiving. But if he keeps you on for longer than a minute,
and you're stock academic BS, I'm going to mute out and go take a shower. So, so,
well, that's fair. That's fair enough. But maybe we should give them a chance to join in and have
the opportunity to get the red button hit on them. Before we go any further. What do you think?
Let's do that. Okay, so based on the convention that one might call a telephone,
you have a phone number, which is 218-339-8525. 218-339-8525. And I'm told
now that there are instructions there that will tell you to hit the 2012 extension. When you come
in, the announcement is working. The phone lines are working. So 218-339-8525. I have control of
the board. The Greek, however, has control of the Skype convention, which Oh, Charlie and the Greek,
just like it sounds. O-C-H-E-L-L-I. And the Greek, just like it, you spell it just like it sounds.
So yeah, let's, you know, the two regulations, let's say, I like using military metaphors.
Not that I like because I've mentioned what people in the military are, right? They're weaponized,
you know what, but here's the thing. But military conventions are easily recognizable.
There is a hierarchy. There is an organizing principle to them that one can almost mathematically
explain. So, well, what? Mathematics is an interesting language, which allows one to
communicate in a way which is without, well, it's without interpretation, really. You know,
if there's five, there's five, right? I mean, we know what a number is. It's very simple.
So when you take a look at the way the military is laid out, there is a hierarchy, which means that,
you know, you have an ascension of command structure and things like this. It makes sense
in a general sort of way. So I think military terminology is quite acceptable.
Yeah, or metaphor because it actually follows. It's actually a mirror of other systems.
You'll find that in the corporate structure, the God structure, and pretty much, you know,
however you want to structure something, you'll find that they all have something in common. It
has an archetype, just like all living things have archetypes. All machines have archetypes,
right? You'll find these archetypes and things that things kind of follow.
Well, universally, like the use of the word chief, for instance, it works fine. You know,
a chief executive officer, right? A chief adversary, a chief, right? All of these things,
when you talk about the chief, we know what we're talking about. It's very simple.
Good. And most people don't. Yeah. OK. So there's you got to also look at the culture.
You know, when you say when I say things like most people are we or who's we and all this stuff,
you have to consider the current convention of the current culture, what's been accepted.
And even though it seems immovable, it does change, right? What people accept and how they
do things and why. Forget about it. Any time through human history, as the conventions changed,
ask them why they did that. And they couldn't answer. Right. But they did. Those conventions
did change. And there's many conventions, social, technical, spiritual, so on and so on.
So the let's go back to the military real quick. They have a lot of regulation books. If you're
wondering how to comb the hair, polish the shoes or make the bed, you don't have you don't need
to ask for opinions. They actually have manuals on that. Right. And the hierarchy is there for
a reason also. Why are they why is there a hierarchy and why are there laws or regulations
or codes that anyone thinks? It's very simple and it's missed. Everyone's missed it. Not everyone.
I mean, but how can we do it rationally? How can we communicate that rationally?
If anyone has any ideas, please call in. No, absolutely. Now, we can now we can.
Very often I go in conversation. I'll pose a question and I'll and I'll answer it. Then
a person says, yeah, of course I knew that. No, of course you have to. I told you.
But the thing is, it's not a matter of I know and you don't or how about this or how about that or
whatever it's about. Can these pieces be put together? Here's another example. Little children,
they give them coloring books as learning tools, as primers, right, to get them started
because they're just getting activated into that kinesthetic out of, you know, more
thought based than kinesthetic. Right. You know, now they already know there are different colors
and they like shapes and they like stimulation. And now they're organizing all the stimuli
that the maturing body is developing. And while those stimuli are being matured
and put together and see how colors and shapes and speech and sound and all that start to develop,
now the organization comes in. And that's why you have the coloring book, right? Because it
gives all the like a coming together. And today, with many thoughts, only because I'm speaking to
people in technical fields and I got to shake the head and wonder, these people are like running
your society and they know nothing about what they're doing. Anyway. Okay. So, or very little,
just enough to get by. That's what everybody kind of does, it seems. It's the minimum required
daily supplement or whatever, right? So, the coloring book aspect, how about doing the Greek
speak or whatever coloring book? You know, I mean, where do you start? There's always coming together
and doing this with you once a week. And I'm like, why? Why bother? You can't get off first base.
We can't, you know, nothing is, it's not because you're supposed to change anything,
but that's not true either, because I'm getting quite a few emails of people that get it.
And people that get it, it's not because I'm saying it, it's because it's like, shit,
they never heard this before. And what the hell, you know, what the hell's going on?
And one of the key things that everyone seems to have that emails at Uncommonradio.com is that
they're trying to deal with how do you talk to other people about it when most people don't
even want to consider the subject, right? They don't want to consider it. So, I'm like, no,
you got to chill. You got to chill. Relax, man. You know, because you got to put it,
you can't just look at one aspect of what's being said here and say, well, now this, you know,
now I want to go and discuss it privately or within my sphere, or whatever of people that I have
contact, but it's not about that at all. It's do you get it? And if you get a little bit of it,
it's may not be really good. You know how they say, if a little is good, a lot is better. That's
not always true, right? No, definitely not. I mean, in fact, I mean, even considering the use
of water, if one consumes too much water, it causes a problem. Right? That's a good subject.
Let's go a little bit of a tangent here. I was discussing the body and still there's no discussion
publicly, privately on the internet mainstream or how the body really works. And it's not because
it's my theory or I want to sell some drops or whatever, or something stupid like that. It's just
you could use your own self to prove it out, right? Since you brought up water, you ever drink a whole
bunch of water and then you notice how it slushes around in the belly for a few minutes? You know,
you know, someone is people have done that at least once or twice in their lifetime,
then you remember not to do that again, because you kind of felt immobilized from it
temporarily, right? Especially if you're particularly thirsty, let's just say you've
been out in the hot sun for a while, and you really have an urge to drink a lot of water,
you might be tempted to guzzle down a lot of it really quickly. Right? Sure, sure. And you do
feel it like you're a container and there's, you know, and there's this, you got this, you know,
variable sense of what your geometry is like, and you feel it slushing around, but then it goes away
within a few minutes. Because what's interesting is when you put that liquid water in the body,
it goes into a gel state because of the vacuum and the magnetic field in the body. And an easy
way to prove that is if you look at the anatomy, from the mouth all the way to the anus, you have
something called the duodenum at the base of the stomach, right? That goes to the small intestine
that never really completely shuts. So all that water now, if you were to build a facsimile of the
body, even with soft tissue, and put that amount of water in it and lay it down, all that water will
run back out the throat and the mouth. Think about it. And even out the ears because you have vents
in the ears, okay? So why doesn't the water run out? Because it doesn't really close the
epiglottis and all these other things in the body do not seal off. Right? Even an anus will leak.
All right. Sorry about that, folks. So here's the thing.
Oh, yeah. I was thinking all the way through, why doesn't it just run straight through then?
Because the water goes into a gel state. Pure water goes into a gel state. And certain plants
exhibit that as well. So what can you do with that? Hey, how about creating machines or synthesizing
that condition? Can you imagine walking into a room and putting out a glass of water? You could
turn sideways and it kind of like, slowly moves out like jello.
Let me ask you a question about that, though, real quick, because I've observed an autopsy before.
Okay. And I've seen a stomach opened. There's no gel in there. When there's liquid, sometimes
there's just still liquid. Now, hold on, backtrack. You've observed what?
An autopsy. A living or dead cadaver or a living subject? Well, autopsy would be obviously a
dead subject. I know. Okay, dead. All right. Now, what makes the, I'm proposing
what creates the gel state. Let's go back two minutes. Well, yeah, because I mean,
the biological, the biological vacuum and the magnetic, the magnetic field that the cells have
create that. Once the body dies and it loses its vacuum and it loses its magnetism,
let's just call it magnetism. It's a form of non-ferric. Then we could get into magnetism,
man. There's ferromagnetic, paramagnetic, and diamagnetic. Oh, what did he just say?
Okay. So what's interesting, because you bring this up, the thing is, I mentioned earlier,
discussing with people about, they're supposed to be good at what they do, know nothing
comparatively to what can be known with just cursory study and observation. It's just shocking
to see that. Now, I mean, let's, yeah, I see the, yeah, you're not going to,
one thing you'll hear on Greek speak is constantly, there's a very big difference between
living and dead. Very big, very big. You can't compare. Now, most of your medical convention
is based on what you mentioned, the examination of cadavers and dead cells, right? It has nothing
to do with living people. It has a lot to do with dead people. That's why I give you an example.
Years ago, working with professional athletes, they would go to doctors and they couldn't find
anything wrong with them. And I'm like, after I heard this for a while, I was like, yeah, of course,
because the Western doctor, you know, typical doctor, he gets old people, sick people, you know,
people that are, you know, out of shape. So here comes this professional athlete
and he's glowing, right? Or she is glowing, you know, with all this energy. And of course,
you're not going to, you're like, the doctor's stunned by looking at you. Of course, he's not
going to find what's wrong with you, right? Because he's just used to looking at sick people,
you know, sedentary and whatever, right? So this is what's going on with the medical field.
The only attributes, positive attributes the medical field has is emergency medicine that
they've gotten from thousands of years of battlefield treatments, right? Otherwise,
it's all study of dead stuff. Yeah, no, I comprehend all that. The reason why I asked
the question, and I understand there's a difference between something that's alive
and something that's dead. I get it. But the reason why I asked the question is, okay,
just bear with me. You have a gel state for the water, because it's happened now. Okay,
now if you've taken in that water and then died since, why is it the gel is not still in the
belly afterwards? Because the water changed a bit. The biological vacuum of the body is gone and its
dielectric properties or its diamagnetic properties are gone. And that means it reverts back to the
liquid. Right, right. And then it starts going the other way too, it evaporates.
You can halt, all evaporation droplets must spin counterclockwise. If you understand how to put,
let's say an ultrasonic clockwise spin on water, it will not evaporate.
Oh, what did I just say? Nevermind, scratch that. I wasn't supposed to say that. Okay.
All right. Well, no, just look, and I'm already getting like weird little feedback.
I understand that there's a difference between a vivisection and a dissection. Okay, that was
precisely why I used the word autopsy, because I thought it was implied that we're talking about a
dissection. I've never observed an open stomach on a living person. True enough. Why does it have
to be open? Well, you observe it, you have one. I understand. Yes, yes, I do. But I mean that I can
observe the contents of it. With your eyes? With my eyes. Yeah. Right. Okay. Well, you could send a
little arthroscope in there or something eventually. But you've got other things that you could
document with. Do you know what the most sensitive measuring tool mankind has? It's the tongue.
It's always there. You ever been around a little child growing up? Well, let's say pre-formative,
formative, pre-formative, formative years, like between, let's say, a couple of weeks,
six months old, when you hand them something, what do they do with it? Put it in their mouth,
right? Why? Because the tongue is, they trust it, right? They don't trust the eyes. They don't trust
the ears. They get stimulation, but that they can do something with, right? If I put it on the tongue,
okay, even as an adult, you still have that super sensitive and sub-sensitive,
or I should call it, it's a super sensible and sub-sensible, meaning it's beyond what people
consider sensible in either direction. Because right now we consider, the people consider,
the tongue to be sensibly something for taste, right? Yeah, that's the sensible consideration.
The sub-sensible and the super sensible part of it is retained with the child. Why else would
they put everything on it, right? It's a measuring tool, and it still is. Now, what it does is it
actually gauges other parts of the body, actually gauges activity and behavior. Maybe we should
start a member's area on the Uncommon Sense Radio and discuss these things. I don't know, man,
this is, it's not for public consumption. But anyway, if you guys are interested about this
kind of stuff, stay tuned on Uncommon Radio. Maybe there might be some interesting features
there in the future, maybe something you click on to get some maybe tools and helps that you can
use. But the tongue is, when you become developed, let's say, it lies in the super sensible and
sub-sensible as a measuring tool. So you can also, you can't see it, right, Chuck? You said
you can't see the gel state. But guess what? You can feel it. It doesn't roll back out, right? It
just feels like you're bloated. And if someone can hang you upside down, you're not going to get
water coming out. This is an easy way to twist out. This reminds me of a conversation I was
having with someone regarding something technical today in the automotive field. And it was, they
kind of got what I was saying, but they wanted to go around in a circle because, I'm not saying you
are, but because you're also examining the convention. In other words, if you start speaking
this in public, the people are going to start throwing stock convention at you. But I've seen
this, I've seen that. How about this? How about that? And you'll notice it's about the accepted
conventions used to measure against this. And it's very difficult to, because the thing is, the less,
the simpler you can keep it, and the more direct, the better it is. Years ago, people worked with
electronic circuitry. The fewer things in the circuit, just like the plumbing, the less components
in the plumbing, the harder it is to stuff it up, right? So the less you use to determine, especially
living, things that are living, because part of the Greek speak coloring book would be the secret
page where all the secrets are. And the main one would be, you notice how heat rises and cold
goes down with artificial heating and cooling, and you've got a hot head and cold feet all year
around, right? But the secret part is when you're outside in the valley, it's hot, and up on the
mountain, it's cold. And the secret part is that your feet should be warm and your head should be
cool. And the secret part is that all living natural biological systems have a rarefied
expanding cold and a contracted, densifying, descending heat. That's the secret.
But how can it be a secret if anyone can observe it?
Well, you know, by that logic, if one considers that water would enter into the body and it ends
up in what would be a tube, in effect, and you have this cold up top and this contracting heat
toward the bottom, right? Couldn't it be that there's a clamping effect on the tube, let's just
say? And therefore, that's why you don't have water just running straight out of you, because
the warmer parts, you know, which are more internal or whatever, because they are on the descending
part of the structure, could be... Yeah, the mechanistic explanation works, but you can't
use it solely. In other words... You don't think this is a foolish question, though, right?
No, no. The thing is, you're looking for the mechanistic aspect, which you need to have also.
But there's an electrical component. When I say electricity, I'm not talking about the
type of electricity you plug a socket into, because that's the waste product of electricity.
Again, electricity is... You know, years ago, if you studied Faraday or any of those people,
Galvani, right? Back in the day, they said that electricity... They have a lot of writings.
Actually, you want to hear something funny? Over 10 or 12 years ago, you could find a lot of their
writings on the internet. Now you can't. Go figure. You know, I mean, just like stuff that's
scanned in on ScribeD and stuff like that, right? So now you've got to go to university library,
which some people are asking. They've looked up things that I've said, and they've gone down that
path, but the quality of the information online is very low. I said, yes, it is. You're going to
need to find a university library and go to the parts of the library where no one wants to go,
and you'll be probably, you know, happily surprised eventually. Now, electricity was
considered to be an attribute of living things, right? And also the electricity was considered
light, heat, and what's called voltage and current now was all the same, interchangeable,
right? You know, Chuck, for example, you can have a panel made of a certain crystalline material.
You put it in the sun, solar panel, and you get electricity from light, and electricity can make
light with a light bulb and also heat. You have heaters that are electric, and also you can have
something called the Peltier effect, P-E-L-T-I-E-R, I think, and it's a thermocouple where you put
electricity and one side gets really cold like a refrigerator, the other side gets really hot,
or you could strap a whole bunch of these to the muffler exhaust of a car, and all that wasted
heat now helps pump electricity back into the car. So heat, light, and electricity are all
interchangeable, and the body has all of that. I've had private discussions about how there's
an internal light in the body that's not visible, and that determines a lot of things
within the human body and living organisms. So a pigment, for example, and color of plants and
people and animals in here is to balance out that internal light, which is a non-visible light,
which is again electric. Which is what I contend I actually observe because of my high
alleged sensitivity to light, because I do see this emanation that comes from living things.
You know, some people say, okay, you can see auras. Well, okay, that might be one way to put it,
but it is observable depending on which part of the spectrum you're able to observe.
It is there. It is present. Right, right, and it's sub-sensible. In other words, you can't find
anything in a physics textbook that'll show you what it is. Correct. Right, and the thing,
we got on this, what is law? The same thing. Why do you want to know how to keep time?
Because let's just give it out, because I found that based on the responses that I get,
the people are almost coming here for a didactic kind of thing, which I don't want to sound pedantic
about. It's almost like a class or something. They learn stuff, and the whole thing about
doing this is not to lecture or teach or be pedantic, like really being academic, let's say.
Well, we know what academic means. This is not academic. It's the opposite of academic. This is
the anti-academic, by the way, because remember, one of the definitions or the conclusive definition
of academic means to be theoretical, impractical, and never leading to a conclusion, and for the
sake of efficiency, you want to get to a conclusion as soon as possible, don't you?
For the sake of efficiency. If you're an attorney or a doctor, you don't, right? That's why when
people are given six months to live, I just tell them, listen, don't pay the bill, and he'll give
you another six months, you know? So anyway, so you know what I mean? You're weak. Temp your
waitress, yes, sir. Yeah, okay, so all right. Well, what is law? Very simple, very simple. No
one's kicked in, and why banter about, you know, waiting for the other side or any side?
The purpose of law is very simple. It's to be in harmony with the environment.
Now, that environment could be, what do you call it, a macro or a micro environment,
and harmony means the opposite of destruction or entropy of the environment and of life in it,
right? Because you can also have an environment where you have inanimate things that break down.
That's why when you get a package delivered through the mail, for example, they put all that
soft stuff around it so it doesn't get banged up on the way, right? And you've ever had anything
shipped with someone, you know, typical or surface-dwelling earth inhabitant, like one out of
ten of them will say, it doesn't matter, just throw it in the box, and by the time it gets to you,
it's all whatever, right? It's shaking around in there, right? They call those things tumblers,
by the way. They use them to smooth out rocks, you see? Anyway, okay, so the purpose of law is
so you have harmony to preserve the environment and all the stuff in it. Simple, that's it.
For example, this is a metaphor. In the military, on a surface ship, it was probably okay to carry
a locked and loaded sidearm, but in a submarine, it's not. Because the two, well, it's both the
Navy, right? But one is an outfit, why? Because if a sidearm goes off on a surface ship, it's not
good, but it's not too catastrophic, let's say, in most cases. But if a sidearm goes off...
You're not likely to sink a battleship or to cause the death of everybody on it with a sidearm.
How about that? On a surface ship?
Right. On a surface ship, yeah.
But on a sub, right, you see? Okay, so that's why when you look at laws, they're, right,
but the problem is right now with how people encounter that word, it's so corrupted and so,
like religion is another one, very corrupt term. People don't, because this is, like I've said,
the entire planet right now is successfully, as a whole, atheist or pagan. So there's no,
there's no, there's no... And by the way, when I say pagan, I use the Pope's definition of it,
right, which also includes themselves. But anyway, and the pagans use the Pope's definition,
which is strange, but they also use the Pope's work schedule. So anyway, it's just bizarre.
This is one of those things. So it's all about laws about harmony. So let's go back to what
date is. It appears to be around the 30th day of the 12th month, right? Okay, so now here's the,
there's a crux here coming. It's always a very tight measurement. And sometimes the 13th month
is so tight that you didn't know you had it until the next moon comes. And then you can see if the
next one was really the second month, or is it really the first month because you just had the
13th? That's how tight it is, right? So unless you have a 30-foot archway with a really taut cable,
and been taking really good measurements, which I haven't lately for a while,
but I know that if I can see it as being a 13th moon, it could also be the first. I'll have to
wait for the next month, because the first moon is far more determinable than the 13th, right?
For reasons that I've explained before, and actually I've got some feedback some people are
sending. And by the way, if you really think you, a lot of people call, let me just touch on the
subject lightly, because I'm an equal opportunity hater. I hate everybody equally, right? In other
words, it's not like I'm part of any group. So when you're not part of any group, when you have
discussions with people that like to be in these groups, they view you as, they can't really
put a finger on you, because they like what you're saying, because it's in favor of them,
and not in favor of those that they're contrary to. But then again, you start saying things that
are contrary to them. So they don't know if they should like you, or hate you, or whatever. So it's
easier to say, don't like me, just hate me, because I hate everybody. That's the cleanest way to be
objective, right? So here's the interesting thing about the pagans, though. At one point,
they understood that their entire well-being, and whatever else you want to consider, that health,
agriculture, and all that, and their survival of their clan and or genealogy was dependent on
having the right laws. Think about that for a minute. The right laws, right? For agriculture,
for business, for water, for weather, for time, because if you screwed up,
and you were not in sync with the environment, the environment likes to bite you in the ass,
doesn't it? Right? So... It definitely causes you problems if you don't work with it. You work
against it, and you're not doing yourself any favors. That's really what it boils down to.
And, or you can't be apathetic either to it now, right? So here's the thing.
They were also... I said for or against it. I didn't say... See, apathetic would be...
Would be in the middle, yeah. But right now, the people are trying to be apathetic until they get
hit with a big storm or a tornado in the middle of winter. I don't know how that happens. But
anyway, the thing is also, they were... You know how you're mentioning about seeing the subtleties
of light, right? And I'm putting light in quotation marks, because it's not going to
be measured conventionally. But nonetheless, it fits. That's the best description for it.
They were also in communication with the local elementals, let's just say, or the non-corporeal
beings, right? So you can't, you know... So that is all lost now. There's some revival.
Right now, what people... There's good reason to be contrary to any mainstream religion. And
if you want to know why, just have a discussion with someone who is for five minutes. But the
problem right now is that, just like a lot of movements, it's become more of a fashion statement
to be what they call pagan or goth or whatever. They still don't know, because it's not time yet,
right? As a whole. And those that do know aren't talking about it. In terms of... They might say
they are, but they're not talking about the mechanisms that can be effective and put in
place. You know what I mean? They're not talking about it. There's no public discussion or private
discussion. You could look at... There's a lot of websites about paganism and all this other stuff,
and it's just like looking at, you know, Cinderella, whatever, you know, whatever
Walt Disney based, you know, super based stuff. There's nothing there.
I got to tell you, that's one of the most maddening things in the world,
to try and sift through what they call, you know, pagan websites. And, oh man.
Yeah, it's just, just wear glasses at night, dye your hair black, tattoo yourself,
and just say this and that, and that's it. There's nothing to do with that. Actually,
you should... What's interesting when you read certain covenants, actually read them instead
of listening to what people say about it, how most people function, is you'll find that when
you live under a certain covenant, it's like when in Rome, no one should know what you're doing. And
this is explicit in many of the ancient texts, by the way. And now, people do the opposite. You can
pretty much denote what religion, mainstream religion someone is by their dress, right? At a
distance, generally, especially the orthodox varieties. And if you look at their texts,
it actually forbids that. So, it's just the level of insanity. I mean, if you look at certain head
dresses that are given for women to be righteous in certain religions, if you look at where those
things came from, culturally and technically, you will be aghast. What it really means. So,
they've taken what the years... You're literally the only guy to ever point out the fact that
the garb of like completely covering up a woman is really the uniform of a prostitute.
Well, if anyone looks it up, they'll find it. It's just as simple as anything else.
Just look it up. You don't have a right to define these things. You see, this is the thing
that I tell people. If you're poetic or creative, you have a right to do whatever you like and
license or freedom. Those words, I guess, we could use in the same context to define something,
if it's your creation. But if you're born into something that existed a long time ago,
and you're discussing it or extracted it from a body of work, written or not, where that body
of work originally defines it, you have no right to change the definition of that.
You have no right to do that. You see my point? So, this is not dogma. This is just the way it is.
Intellectual property law in a cosmic sense, it sounds like to me.
Sure, but now these things are like gay means happy. But now it's something else. No, it's not.
You see what I mean? I mean, it's not being used properly. You see, it's not something else now.
It's improperly used. So, right? I mean, you could see this across the board.
So, law is basically finding harmony and preventing destruction,
simply put. Now, the reason I say most people have no concept of it, because
Chuck, let's say you go into a different environment, and you're given a set of laws
on how to function there. Would you reject them for safety and all that? Or would you
reject them or accept it for consideration? Well, I would have to accept it for consideration
in order to exist in the environment, wouldn't I? Right. You'd have to consider them first and
all that. And then when you consider them, and you see them to be good because they work,
you've actually lived it and tried it out, right? That makes it even better. You see,
and now you're motivated to use those laws because you're motivated to do the right thing.
But when you say law in this society, or all across the planet, it's a motivation through
penalty. People don't know what the right thing is anymore. The reason they consider law to be law
is because if they don't do that, there's a penalty. So, now the people are motivated.
You have a very different mindset if you're motivated to do something because it's the
right thing to do. And there's a very different mindset if someone is motivated to do something
because there's a penalty if they don't. Do you see? And this is why any discussion regarding law
or all these other things is not viable at this point still. Cannot be. Just look around you.
I mean, in a public forum, right? And also, when you see people defining
things that they've extracted, concepts that they've extracted out of a body of work,
whether it's fact or fiction, doesn't matter, right? That's why what I like to do often,
do you remember there's a Pulp Fiction film? I think it's Pulp Fiction.
Before, yeah, what's his name? The two guys that were rolling around
before he would shoot someone, he says, have you read the Bible? He says, I got a little verse
here in Ezekiel, whatever, right? Right? Remember that? Yeah, Jules and Vincent, right? The guy
played by Samuel L. Jackson would always recite this verse from Ezekiel. Right before he shoots
the guy. Now, I have a personal thing. I'll share it on air with everyone. This is just a private
conversation. If you ever hear me in public, I say my version of that with someone in public is,
have you ever heard of the fox Aesop's Fables? Have you ever heard of the fox and the grapes?
That's my version of it, right? Because the fox and the grapes, basically,
now Aesop's Fables is where you hear that the rabbit and the hare and the tortoise have a race,
right? The hare laps at the tortoise, falls asleep, oversleeps, the tortoise crosses the line,
right? Okay, well, the fox and the grapes is basically the fox is walking on a path,
sees some grapes it wants to eat, and it keeps jumping and jumping, can't reach them,
really wants those grapes. And then finally says, I can't really reach those grapes. But you know
what? They're probably sour. Right? So that's why when you hear people discussing many things
that they redefine, right? Whether it's scientific, biblical, cultural, law, money system,
it's the fox and the grapes. If you bring up what these things are based on that anyone can access
and see, it can't be it because that's sour. Those grapes are sour, you see?
So you cannot have a discussion in open forums like this, where that mindset is still prevalent.
This is the convention now, still. You know how I know. You could pretty much suffer the time it
takes to get all the credits for a college degree, a university degree, but they won't give you a
diploma unless you pay for it, let's say, or pay the tuition. But pretty much, most security now
has not changed, but most some of it has. You could pretty much sit in, go to any university
campus and sit in any class you want, right? In the lecture halls predominantly, not the labs so
much. Right? And you could pretty much sit in there every day for four years, sans the recess,
and have the equivalent of all the lectures and classes that it took to get a bachelor's or
whatever, right? Well, I don't know, you know, it's taken a little bit of special permission for
me to be able to sit in on certain lectures, because, you know, I've done this a few times,
actually. Sure, perhaps, yes. But in general terms, the majority of the classes are still for
the larger universities, the lecture halls are like small auditoriums. Yeah, like very, very
small auditoriums, but yeah. Yeah. So the point here is this, when you engage that, you'll see
that it's not time yet. Look at how they discuss things. Oh, okay, turn on the television.
Look at how they discuss things. And now this guy for her opinion.
Or yeah, this guy for her opinion. Yeah, there you go. That's how twisted people are these days.
Yeah, right. And alternative media, you know, mainstream. You just listen and see how the,
how it all works out or doesn't work out in terms of what we're saying here.
Well, one of the most fun things that I get to do quite often is say to somebody after they've
gone through a long discussion about something is what are you basing that on? And usually that
causes a bit of a problem. Very few people answer quickly and half the time they have a stock answer,
which quite honestly, doesn't actually lead anywhere. It's really strange.
By the way, I just got an email as we speak. I opened the Uncommon Sense. I was going to read
some of the emails, give an example, but I don't think it's necessary. Just a few minutes ago and
said, by the way, I'll be in the Uncommon Sense members area from day one. I'm tired of my own
inefficiency. Exactly. No one is immune from it. You see, you know, here's the interesting thing.
And it's happened on the show with you and I, when certain points are made. Well, like, who do you
think you are? Right. It's not who I am or what I think. It's irrelevant. I think the answer,
the correct answer on that is, well, who do you say I am? Right. But the correct thing, the reason
let me just reiterate why we why the Greek comes out and speaks about stuff like this and Chuck
can suffer it for two hours. Boldly so, I should say, is because this report is just not being
given. The last thing you want in life is to have a stockpiled information and things that can be
easily conveyed and not do it. And later on, people come and say, you knew about this. I didn't
say anything. Right. How many times do you come across stuff like that? Right. So the question
always comes up. Why didn't you say something if you knew this was happening? Right. But yeah,
but we gave all the definitions. Exactly. Try to have a conversation with someone about the
money system. They can't. It's debt. It's debt. It's debt. It's a debt. It's a debt system.
They can't. They go into a if you keep giving them information, they'll just lightly agree with
you, brush you off, just like, you know, no one's listening. They're just waiting for you to shut
up so they could say what they want to say or whoever the host or the guest is. And then it's
just like, let me say what I'm what everyone else is saying, because I know that's agreeable and
it's incorrect. Right. There is no debt. The only reason there is debt is because the legal society
has templates that you agree to and then they bundle up these templates. And when I mean a
template, it's just that and they sell them on the on the market that has where these templates are
sold, just like you have a fish market, a clothing market. You have a template market. These are
financial templates that they're selling and you have to agree to it. And just like, for example,
if you sign a piece of paper under the penalty of perjury that you're going to donate the couch
you're sitting on to the Salvation Army next week and their terms, if you don't donate it on those
terms, they can actually go to the sheriff and get a forcible entry and detainer and execute that
and kick you in the face and take the couch. Why would you sign that? Right. Why would you endorse
it? Why would you endorse anything where the possible penalty is to get you kicked in the
face? Why would you sign on to that? I don't understand. Because they don't because the
parents it's about pranking. The parents have pranked the children. There's no way the parents
cannot prank the children and then the children go into a prankster society. It would be like a
shock to them, wouldn't it? But the parents are pranking the children first from the crib so that
the children have never had a clear thought in their day without any pranking. But in fairness,
they are preparing them for the rest of the world, which is exactly the same way, wouldn't you say?
Well, they're either preparing them to be the prankster or the pranky, but they're never prank
free. But if the world itself is not prank free, and the other, you know, surface dwelling
inhabitants are also not prank free. Would you have to be prepared for that? Or should you be
unprepared? Oh, yeah, you should be prepared for all of it. But you shouldn't be of it. You could
be in it, but not of it. Well, see, and that's an interesting question. Because you said something
there about some of the feedback you get related to Well, who the hell are you? All right. Well,
here's a fair enough question. Because you're talking about these things and being separate,
and all of that, what is the difference between being in something and of it? Because obviously,
you know, you're in it, right? You know, you're in this prank world, you know, you're in this
dumbed down world where there is this censorship. But are you of it? You Well, you know, now I'm
asking you about you, which is something we don't normally do. Yeah, but that's the answer. That's
for the coloring book. If you got a job, let's say for 10,000 a day to clean out the sewer,
are you going to be of it and skinny dip and you're so happy because you're making 10 grand a
day you could retire in a year and live well for the rest of the life? Let's say, are you going to
drink the water and be so happy and gay in there, right? Like they used to say in 1930s? Or are you
going to put on protection with hazmat breathing suit and breathing tanks, regardless? You see,
now when you jump in there all naked and skinny dipping, because you know, the rats in there are
going to say this guy's nuts. Let's go eat them. Or is he competing with us? But if you once you
go in there with the hazmat suit, the rats are like, Oh, that looks kind of alien and scary.
Let's avoid leave that one alone. Well, then separating oneself is isolation, separation,
it's more like insulation. Yeah, that was my point. That's what the isolation it was an easy way to
say it to be in it or of it. Think about it. Right? Yeah. I would say I would say that this is a
air quotes, a personal choice, because most people are quite happy being of it and in it and all this
other stuff. And a lot of people you used to hear, I will fight to the death to defend your right to
say it. And I said, Don't, don't ever say I tell people, especially young people, forget about the
older people. Don't ever bring that anything to the death point, because someday you might,
someone might want to accommodate you on that, right? Stay away from that life is already too
short. Yeah, that's funny. I always say, you know, there's no reason to offer up your life,
because after all, that'll always, that'll that'll be taken eventually. Anyway, it's not,
it's not yours to offer. And it's your perception of the life. There's a saying in the ancient
Greeks, I'm paraphrasing here. Those that are afraid of dying don't know how to live.
And I think we've also defined fear. Right? We try to define life that's within the realms of the
gods. It's trying to define life is like opening up a Swiss watch, you know, the wind up kind
with all the jewels and laying it out on a table and discussing it, it doesn't really make a lot
of sense unless you've got you're sitting right over it, right? It's that's what you know what
I mean? It's really hard to define life. Death is really easy to define, because it's not it's
the opposite of life. But it's actually, if you want to just not say it's the opposite of life,
it is a termination point that is just like being asleep. If you're dead for a minute,
or 1000 years, you don't know the difference. We're not talking about if you're revived,
and all that other stuff, because that's not dying, dying, meaning that you go into chemical
decomposition, right? And you're not coming back. So So the other thing here is which is which is
very simple to to define and all this is, you've got the the fear is what the could the fear also be
what's motivating people, right? Because if you're motivated by penalty, if the penalty is harsh
enough to motivate you, you're probably afraid of it. So the definition of practical definition,
for the sake of efficiency, this is not the way that people use the term, but for because people
use terms just to pass time, I mean, you do radio, you hear radio, you look at mainstream,
you read the paper, I mean, I'm not saying you read the paper, you got your finger on what's
being said out there, right? Everything is a passing moment. All right, we're done with this,
the next thing, you know, it's the no, there's very little consideration, unless you're doing
poignant research to come to a conclusion on something, where once once you present that
conclusion, I have to show it backs it up. So that's more poignant. But for efficiency,
easily observable, if you write down exactly what seems to be the most pressing issue of the day,
on, you know, on on on your Pope's work schedule, if you write it down on a Monday as it's being
spoken, and then you return to it on a Thursday, Thursday, whatever, on that same schedule, and
go ahead and open up exactly the same sources and see where it's gone from there, you'll find that,
usually, the focus has changed one way or another, they may stick with a particular template for a
while that they work off of, but they're no longer looking at the very same exact issues,
they haven't really resolved anything, or, or defined anything sufficiently,
so that one can really understand a damn thing that's happened. That's what I observed in the
media. Yeah. Or it could be something important that becomes superficial or something superficial,
it becomes important for no reason. But the fear thing is very simple. The weak minded or weak
spirit and the lack of skill put together may make one more subject to fear. Now everyone,
no matter how skilled you are, how strong your mind or spirit is, you'll always eventually run
into something that surpasses your ability in those areas or a threshold, you know,
that that takes you to another level that you will be subjected to some form of fear.
But the way to efficiently look at it is to consider your skill level and all things and
whatever you might be considered skill in and the other thing would be how strong your spirit or
your mind is. So those that are weak minded and poor of skill are more subject to fear and that
we just defined 99.9999% of the planet. Right? And give an example like, like, Chuck, I don't
know how to operate a dishrag or a mop. And I spill over a glass of milk, and I start panicking,
because I don't know how to clean it up. And you come along with a dishrag. And you're like,
Greek man, chill. I know how to operate a mop and a dishrag. It's just spilled milk. Relax. See?
So, no, exactly. You see people panic all the time when you have to apply some sort of,
well, you know, what I would call the skills of a battlefield medic,
such as, you know, setting a bone, stopping bleeding, things like that. A lot of people
panic in situations. And it helps nothing. We're almost out of time in this hour. But this is a
good point to be made is that the fact that they are panicking is actually the impediment to solving
the situation. More than their lack of knowledge, it is their lack of knowledge that causes the
panic. But it is the panic itself that causes the problem, though, wouldn't you agree?
Sure. Like how many times you ever heard about financial collapse,
and everyone is getting engrossed in that because they're weak, and they lack skill.
Well, right. And in fact, all of the energy spent, you know, and the anxiety of it,
really outstretches even what would happen in the event of the actual thing occurring.
But anyway, we're going to continue on this discussion here on Uccelli and the Greek in
the next hour. Stay tuned to American Freedom Radio. We'll be back in a couple of minutes.
Second hour of Uccelli and the Greek here on American Freedom Radio at americanfreedomradio.com.
And I got to tell you, it's been a different sort of show this time around. Yeah, I've been a little
more vocal here. And that is strange. Usually, I don't really have to say much because well,
the Greek can do this all by himself. I just kind of put the bookends on it.
So that's the way I feel about it. Anyway, you know, before we go any further, I do want to
mention that you can join into the conversation by using a phone at 218-339-8525. 218-339-8525.
Okay, and 2012, as the recording should tell you, is the extension to dial in order to join
into the discussion. There's also a Skype convention, which the Greek has control of,
and he'll tell you what it is. Just Uccelli and the Greek and you
spell it just like it sounds O-C-H-E-L-L-I and the Greek.
Right, actually spelling out the word and by the way, just in case. Yes.
Not with an ampersand. That's that little squiggly thing that stands for the word and
in case you're unaware of that. Okay, we had someone actually just
looked at Skype. Someone did put in a contact list before the show started. I think it's one
of your associates, Daniel, I believe. So I just accepted that as well.
Okay. All right.
I have no idea what's going on over there because I'm on my usual thing, so.
Yes, okay. But also we like to hear from people that are far reaching out there somehow
and see how far we're getting. Not that it matters.
You know, it's a matter of just, I guess, for fun, right?
You got to have fun in what you do. But we were talking about fear and
you know how that's been thrown around. Before we get back into fear though,
because it does relate to it. I have been asked repeatedly and
tonight in the chat room again, I don't turn to the chat room for questions anymore.
But I have seen this repeatedly in the chat room tonight and other times.
So I have ignored it in the past because I didn't think it was a topic that fit
with what we were discussing at the time. I do go for a coherent sort of drive here.
If you don't mind, I'm going to interject this and tie it to fear. Is that all right with you?
Yeah, go for it. But by the way, let me just preface. I've been looking at chats for years
now and lately they've been getting so poor. I don't know who's going to these chats. I mean,
in golf fair, I told someone at AFR that they would make an excellent defense for Dr. Kevorkian.
But anyway, keep going. Well, the thing is, every once in a while,
a gem comes in there. And by the way, I don't disagree with you too much about that because
there's some really good people that show up in chat. But you have the general.
Yeah, exactly. Why bother? It's so true. Yeah, it's so few. And the ones that are good,
they're not really gold. So I'm not going to go panning in the beach for, you know,
for iron. But good. Well, OK, look, we can we can discuss the level of quality,
but there is quality there among the sand, let's just say. And there's a lot of sand.
OK, fair enough. That was a question. But OK, no problem.
That's fine. Just don't let the sand get in your drawers. That's all good.
Yeah, I try and avoid that as often as possible because. Well,
anyway, look, let's not go down that particular rabbit hole.
The thing is, they asked about depression and depression is one of these terms that I hear a lot.
And I've got to say that getting away from embracing fear or minimizing fear in general
in my own person, because that's what I can most easily observe. I mean,
it's hard to tell the emotions of others sometimes, but I know what mine are.
So I observe that the less fear I have, the less depression I have.
Now, that may be a wild assertion to some, but I'm wondering if these two things aren't
tied together and I wouldn't mind hearing what you have to say about depression in general.
Well, generally, you could say it's very, very simple. There's a crossover with the
Freudian convention in psychology, which is a worthless profession,
by the way, a worthless field. And it's dominated by certain very deranged people
back in the turn of the 20th century. So there's that definition. But very simple depression,
just like we're breaking down fear, not that what fear actually is, but we can define it
rationally that you can I could work with it. Right. Depression is very simple as well,
just as fear. Depression is very simply trying to mix fact with fiction. They don't mix.
For example, it's like you have a legal problem and you go get an attorney. Let's say you're
going to court and you realize that you did worse with an attorney than without one. Or you have a
health problem and you realize you're getting worse with the doctor. Wait a second. I thought
the fact was that these guys are supposed to help you. But it turns out when I go to them,
things get worse, generally speaking. Right. So that's where, you know, that is a concept
or of depression. You know, you you realize that, you know, all your parents pranked you.
So we know that the education system is is crap, but you got to do it because we did it. And then
you do it and you really find out it was crap and you wasted all your time and you should have run
away when you were four years old. But anyway, you see, so it makes sense that that both of
these things are rooted in exactly the same problem, because, look, if you have a lack of
knowledge, this is really what generates fear. OK, and weak spirit, because knowledge doesn't
always give you a strong mind or strong spirit. OK, fine. But both of those things together,
a lack of knowledge and a weak spirit. Well, really, the lack of knowledge causes one to
add fictions to their facts because they don't know the facts. Right. And a weak spirit allows
them to be driven emotionally. So doesn't fear and depression seem to really be really closely
related as as well? If you're going to go down the emotional pathway, yes. And you've got to
realize that you are physically animated. In other words, the spirit is animated through the physical
body. You remove the physical body, you go into disanimation. Sleep is a good example.
So emotion, the emotions that humans and animals and all the beings experience is because the mind
is tied into the body. So it's all emotional and it's all depression. It's all fear, you could say.
Yeah, but specifically to address it from a rational causality, they're very different. Like
here, let's just throw one more thing in the mix. You ready? You know how people say they're bored
right? I'm bored. Well, could boredom be a form of anger? And when I'm asking that question,
just like in having an itch be a form of pain. Right. It's in that same category. It's on the,
you know, on the edge of that. Right. So, you know, if someone goes to a medical practitioner
and says, hey, doctor, you got to give me something. This itching is making me crazy.
Is that because it's pleasurable or painful? Right. It's not really pain,
as we would think when we say I need something for the pain, but it's usually classified as a pain.
Can boredom be defined as a form of anger? How can you be bored? Think about it.
Now, well, I like to categorize a lot of the things. The subject matter is being in the waiting
room for humanity right now in the credits. You know, do you have to be bored at a waiting room?
You shouldn't even really be there as half the time, but.
No, but you can certainly entertain yourself if you.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Especially with these silly pods or silly phones and things. Now, I mean,
I think I've just just divert not to divert, but this all ties in together. I had one for about
a week and I got rid of it and I pretty much started critiquing the people about it. It's
too subjective. The operating system in those smartphones. See, I'm waiting for phones to
be dumb as people to be smart, but it seemed it went the other way. Anyway. So the the operating
systems in these smartphones is too subjective. It's not like a PC where, you know, you want to
do something. It's like a tool. You get a toolbox, you grab a hammer. You know, you're pretty.
It's easy to get from. It's not too subjective. You grab a pliers, grab a wrench, a screwdriver.
But when you start using the these these operating systems on the tablets and the phones,
they're too subjective. In other words, you're going too much into the mind of
the nerds that designed it. And yes, the guys that design these operating systems,
I haven't met them all, but I've met enough to give you a good universal sample.
They're not let's say you would not send them somewhere else as good representation,
representative specimens of the human race, first of all. Second of all, if you went over to their
house, they wouldn't even know how to boil water to make you a hard boiled egg. I mean,
what they're very good at, though, is their nerddom and they put all their nerdy crap and
their geeky crap in the program. And if you don't resonate with that and I mean resonate,
I mean, follow along with it. It doesn't work. It doesn't work efficiently at all. You see,
you'll end up deleting things that you wanted to save and saving things you wanted to delete
kind of thing. It's so I told this to a bunch of people and they said, no, Greek, you just
haven't. You know, you can go and change it. And they got really kind of like almost emotional
about it. So I let the subject go. But those people came back to me a week later and said,
Greek, you were correct. Is it correct about what? It's too subjective. I see the subjectivity in it
now. You see, it's not because I'm trying to convince anyone of it. You know, I think that
we're speaking. I mean, most people do have those silly things, phones, stupid phones, whatever.
And it's very different from a PC. Now, that subjectivity is the same subjectivity that
people get used to with the schools, with the religions, with the media, all media.
Right. This week, this is trending this. So it's the in crowd. Let's discuss it.
Let's bring this person to give us their opinion. It's like I don't care about anybody's opinion.
I want to know the truth. By the way, I want to share this with everyone, I think,
you know, how you get little messages. Right. And this is a personal thing. I'll make it really
short. I was replacing a part, a component. And the model number is very important. It's one of
these. It's a let's say an automotive computer. OK, and it's got to be the right one, you know,
or it's not right. So you give a model number. And they're also below that. They have a slash
and which is a serial number, which is very unique to that particular one in the series. Right.
It's for quality control or whatever. Well, I'm looking at the serial number and the first
five characters is T.R.U.T.H. What? Yes. When was the last time you saw
a serial number with the characters right in there? T.R.U.T.H.
I've never I've never I've looked at thousands of serial numbers. I've never seen anything that
that coalesces. And I've seen three letter words come together on super rare occasions. Yeah.
These numbers are nondescript. I mean, you never no one ever pays attention. PX9B1722. I mean,
it doesn't matter. It's it's just, you know, a particular order. It's nothing. It's just as
completely. Yeah. I mean, so. So how can you be bored? Do you see how I'm tying that together?
How can you be unless you're not paying attention here just for argument's sake? I just put the
camera on. Do you see where it says S.N.? Yeah, I do. What are the characters? And then
T.R.U.T.H. No kidding. No, he's showing me the serial number on his camera.
This is a car computer, basically. You can see it. There's the terminal. You know,
there's a 60 pin deal. All right. I mean, this is we don't do stuff like this. We don't break.
We don't break the, you know, the form, you know, when we're on show. But to put on was
the last time, you know what I mean? Just I just had it. I think it would add more impact
to the conversation by having you just actually see it. Right. No, that is amazing. I really
was thinking to myself, you know, for a moment there, I thought, is he making this up?
The reason why I'm saying it is, you know what the question now is, are you still bored?
How can you be bored? You never know what's coming.
Oh, this is true. I mean, you do. You know where the ship is going. But how can you be
bored on the cruise ship? It's going from London to New York. There's so much to do.
All right. So you don't want to go to New York. Well, it's a little late for that.
You can jump out, you know, so. Well, until you've seen every inch of the cruise ship
and talk to every single person on it and participate in every single activity,
which is never possible during any given trip, unless you did that, you couldn't even say
that you had experienced everything there was to experience there. Right.
Yeah. And we always have a little lascivious thing I throw in. You want to maybe see the every
inch of the partner you love, maybe objectively away from everything else or something. How can
you be bored? And here's this is why I suggest people not go on vacation. I've noticed this
the entire life. People plan on going on a vacation. It's expensive,
generally. And when they're gone, all they're doing is thinking about
what they left behind. Do they leave the stove on or they lock the house? Is this person going
to take right? And then when they get back, they're so glad they got back. So why bother
leaving in the first place? Why don't you consider Samuel Clemens or Mark Twain's advice?
He says a happy man will make his vocation his vacation. Why do you need to go on vacation
for what? Well, I understand if the climate, you know, I understand the snowbird mentality when
it's you're buried in snow in the in the northeast. It was eighty five degrees Fahrenheit in the
southwest today. Think about that for a minute. You know, why not? If you have the ability to do
that, why not spend, you know, the winters where it's warm and the summers where it's cool?
But that's not what I mean by vacation. You know, you're with me on that, Chuck. You see,
you ever notice people go on vacation and they're stressed the whole time and they're
glad to come back. Why bother going to send the postcard, you know, so we got to do the virtual
thing. So, you know, this stuff is not what I think about it. It's just a commentary that on
why people are not thinking. I don't want to share what I think about it. I want to share
a viewpoint that shows why people are not thinking. And do you want to make that choice
to be the thoughtless? Life's too short right now. This life.
Well, it doesn't matter about whatever other time period, because this is the one I'm in.
So, yeah, but you also can prepare for the next one in a certain way by not through knowledge
again. And by the way, you know, we saw this and you don't go to the gods by belief or faith.
You go to them through knowledge. And when you study the knowledge of the gods,
you'll see that there are certain things that are going to happen. And that's what you believe in.
All belief in faith is based on knowledge of something that has not yet happened,
that will happen based on a good source. So people say that they believe in something because they
have a right to or they don't have to explain it or whatever. That is the capital, the moron with
a capital R, which, by the way, it's not a pejorative term. That is a clinical term.
Moron means someone who basically stopped developing. They're too kind, let's say,
at 12 years old. I believe most people stop developing at around nine.
That was interesting. I looked at a website for some news at the earlier part of the week,
and there was a little article in there on how the people in government are behaving like children,
like 12-year-olds or nine-year-olds. So it's like that's something right out of the Greek
speaks I've been saying for over a decade. Right. So most people stop developing spiritually or
mentally. And by the way, for people who lack the definition of that term, the spirit is the mind
and the mind is the spirit. It's the PSY prefix means the spirit, like psychology, psychotic,
psychopath, psychic, anything has to do with the mind in English is PSY and Rook or Rook in the
Chaldean tongues, Hebrew, Egyptian, right, all those, it would be the Rook. And so it's the
same thing. So when you run into a shrink, a psychiatrist, he's a spiritualist, the PSY means
spirit. But you ever heard of the old, was it Golden Meyer, the film studio guy says anyone
who wants to see a psychiatrist should have their head examined. Anyway. Yeah. Right. Okay. So the
people need to have their head examined if they're going to do anything different. Now, they think
that most people on the planet think they're being different or things are changing, but they're
really not. What's the common denominator? thoughtlessness, lawlessness, lack of anything
good. Basically motivated by penalty. This is the general surface dwelling society right now.
You know, and things change when they don't have the right to change them.
So it goes on and on and on. It was nearly revolutionary to come to the conclusion that
that it wasn't the penalty that should motivate me, you know, even even the idea of the,
the the the God supposedly punishing me. I felt as though that was something to abandon as well,
that that's not the purpose by which I should write my behavior.
There is no such thing. By the way, memorialize that's in the culture, the religious culture,
but go ahead. Oh, no, I'm stating that. Look, I came to this understanding that it was not about
any of that, that the penalty has nothing to do with the motivation of my actions, or it should
not. How about that? That that this is not a way to be motivated. I shouldn't be motivated by the
penalty of what could occur if I don't do the right thing or if I don't behave according to
okay, that. But how would you know what the right thing is? You can't go by feeling an emotion
because that can be swayed, right? That's what everything is there for to sway you in that
direction, give you more choices. So the only way to know what's right or wrong is by having a deep
understanding of the environment and everything in it. And there's no better understanding than
getting it from a primary source. But anyway, see, but but to me, the primary source is the
environment, you know, and and I try and observe that and deal with it. And in that way. Now,
here's the strange part of this. In that way, could not the conventions around us that are
conducted by people be considered part of the environment in which we're existing? So it's
kind of a contradiction there, though, isn't it? Because No. Well, because we're okay, sorry, the
level of creation, the level of creation is it's in itself, is almost as dynamic and as complex
as the gods are. And I think you've heard me describe how the gods have an IQ of 2 million.
And whenever there's anything conveyed to them by man, allegedly that you can study,
it's their baby talk. And it's still very difficult to comprehend, right? They're very,
very dynamic. And the and you can see the forces in nature can be extremely dynamic, destructive,
and both constructive. And the other thing to consider is all of the gods, there are no
benevolent gods, they are all malevolent, when you are locked, you're to be animated through body.
Do you see what I mean? Because if whether you have the benevolent gods, or the malevolent gods
appear to you as they are, you're toast, they have to create a facsimile of something that you can
interact with, it would be like in the Star Trek, the matter anti matter thing, right? You just
dissolve. So So here's the thing, the dynamics of it is so dynamic, that is best to break it down
into a way that, you know, you can swallow it, let's say, right, which is through thought and
through time and through discussion. And, you know, now I'm speaking about knowledge of this
in its entirety, you can only glean so much from the environment, just like, for example,
if you were thrown into a submarine, yeah, you know, you're underwater, you know, that if some
if you have a leak, it's your ass, right? If you know all this other stuff, but you really don't
know much about about it. So you do have to, but here's the thing, again, there's many levels to
this. It's not as part of it is the the fox and the grapes. And the other part of it is you're
no longer the cool part of the in crowd. Because if it's in to not know, then you better not know
if you want to be in the in crowd. If it's in fashionable, right? It's fashionable to know,
you better know to be in fashionable. So it's really a matter of fashion. At this point,
if you look at anybody's life, including your own, how many fashions, or trends you've experienced
major ones, not the little ones, you know, you had the 60s, the 70s, the 80s, the 90s,
2000, right? You notice every decade, there's a new trend of thought, a convention that comes in,
and you get drawn into it, right? Everyone does to a certain degree. And you start considering
what that fashion statement or that convention is putting out. So you want to be popular. Right now,
it's still unpopular to be in the know. And what because of that, it always has been,
those that know even a little bit, the distance or the margin between those who don't know is
not slight, it's huge. It's might as well, you might as well be in a different planet.
It's very difficult to relate. So that's why you have to always use allegory, metaphor,
and ask questions, but not asking the question, but asking the answer. In other words,
you bring up a point. And instead of being pedantic, or didactic about it outwardly,
you kind of say, Hey, haven't you ever noticed, or whatever, and see, as you can do,
it's a double edged sword, meaning it's very efficient, it cuts in both directions.
One is you gauge the society to see, you know, who reacts. And then the other way,
if someone is ready for it, you've just helped someone out, right? That's why, you know, you hear
about the double edged sword in a lot of ancient texts, right? And people don't know what that
means. It's because it's it cuts in both directions. And sometimes, one direction,
and when you turn it and go back in the other direction could be totally unrelated. Like,
you might cut somebody's head off to the left, but to the right, you're buttering your toast.
It just, it just changes completely. You know, this is, you know, and I'm using that analogy
to show you the extreme, the extreme. That's why people don't understand things when you know,
the ancient stuff, because they want to put their spin on it. So you just got to look at how,
if you look at any ancient texts of high order, you'll notice how sometimes you'll be trying to
follow it and you can't, because all of a sudden, it's switched gears into something completely
different. So the thing here is, how much can you get from the environment is, yeah, you can get a
lot. But that's why I tried that in the beginning about water going to a gel state. You can see
that with plants, by the way. Also, that's a more, and here's another thing that people, okay,
take out a plant from the ground, clean off the roots, a healthy plant, wash, wash them up and
get a spray bottle and spray water on the roots. Does the water get absorbed directly into the
root like a sponge or does it bead up like water on a freshly waxed car? It beads up. That means
the roots are hydrophobic. And if you look at even Google images, the roots of plants are completely
sealed. So when you water plants, you're not watering the plant or the root, you're watering
the soil because the soil is acting to transmit the water in a non-physical state in the plant.
So anyway, these things, yes, you don't get that from going to university or whatever. You get that
from observation, like you were saying earlier, right? You can get a lot from observation. But
are you really observing is what I tell people, or are you trying to read into it what you think
you already know? Let go. Well, here's the other question, though, is that there's nothing
anywhere stating that there is not another language here that may not be comprehensible
to us in our current state, right? It's a tool, yeah. Language is a tool. Yeah, and there could
be a thousand languages that no one has ever heard of, been able to study, or even believes is a,
quote, dead language at this point. The organization of things in nature in and of itself
appears to me to be a language. I'm not saying I can decipher all of it. I'm saying that it appears
to be a language which has been related to me. And if one were to consider that there is a creator
or creators of this language, that they would be attempting to communicate something with it.
Well, they are. They are, but the lifespan and relativeness is different. It's not like,
for example, if you visit a place that you grew up as a child, you notice how big the tree was
as a child, and you go visit an adult, and you're like, man, that was that giant elm tree. It doesn't
seem so big now, right? And if the story takes a thousand years to tell, I will never live to
hear it all. I get that. But I'm just saying that it's not to say that the story is not being told,
though. What's happening now, it's not, but you also have to understand the timing. It's very
important. You know, like the steam engine was around 2,300 years ago, but Fulton didn't really
popularize it when they asked, what's his name, the guy who writes about all the stuff, turn of
the century, phenomenal stuff, Ford, Charles Ford. What about that? He says, well, it wasn't
steam engine time. Now it's steam engine time. It's not time yet, but also what's coming is people
don't know in terms of time is that you're being set up right now. What you're being set up for is,
imagine a car that's full of mud going to the car wash, right? And now you see it going in,
and you come out on the other side of the car wash. Instead of seeing a big, clean car, you
see a hubcap roll out and maybe the antenna, and that's it. And you're like, what happened to the
car? I thought it was supposed to just go in to get washed. It's gone. But there's enough of the
car left that you can still identify it. That's what you're being set up for. But the thing about
the communication and the language and the technology involved behind it and all that,
what the gods have shown, let's say, by conveying through man through the ancient text,
is that they get it. They know you're not going to comprehend it right now in the state.
What they're looking for is inquiry, the desire to inquire. And that's one of the things that I
harp about in public, is not only do the people not know, but they're proud of not knowing,
and neither do they want to inquire. How many times have you brought up something to someone
and they say, well, you know what? I didn't know about that. And you know what? I don't want to
know about that, and I don't care. Right? Okay. That's right. Now you know why only the hubcap
and the antenna is going to come out, but out of the car wash... Actually happens to me all the
time. Yeah. There you go. That's welcome. That's why when I tell people, everyone you've ever known,
everyone you know, and everyone you will meet is a moron. And it's pretty much the state of
affairs on this society, but it doesn't mean it's permanent. But doesn't that, by extension,
tell everybody that's even listening to you that they are indeed also a moron?
Well, the thing is, yeah. Well, it depends. I'm not telling them directly. This is a very safe
statement to make. And I've been telling this to people for a decade and no one's rebutted it. So
legally it stands. Anyway. I'm not saying you're incorrect. I'm just saying isn't that exactly...
Look, I'm listening to you right now. So someone else that I don't know is listening to me. So
as far as they're concerned, I'm a moron. As far as I'm concerned, they're a moron.
So basically everyone is a moron. Statistically, you don't know. Yeah. 99.999%. But here's why.
There's three views of the self, consider to consider. There's the way that you think
people see you. And then there's the way that people... No, there's the way that you see
yourself. There's the way that you think people see you. And then there's the way they really see
you. Yeah. I'm sorry. Oh, I don't see it. I live it. Yeah. All this. So you want to disconnect
from that. You think you're... Self-assessment. And you say, because I've assessed myself like
this, people must think I'm like this. But then there's another part where people really think
about you. And that's maybe sometimes unreliable. Avoid all of that stuff. The thing is, once you
set yourself apart, you're no longer in that. And you're okay with the psycho dab,
drabble or dribble going on. Go to any chat or listen to any radio show and it's psychobabble.
It's like, where the hell? It's like, first of all, no one's listening to each other. No one's
paying attention. And what they're saying just isn't true. So this is what... But what confuses
me is, and this is what confuses me now, maybe it's just me being a moron here. But quite honestly,
how do you... Well, I said maybe I am. How is it though, that even if one allegedly sets
themselves apart, they're not immune to this? Well, you can define immunity. Here's the thing.
Avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence. Or knowledge of existence gives you the ability
to avoid it. If you know a trap is set and you go into it, it's no longer a trap, is it? Now it's
a tragedy. That's why... But the other thing is that you can avoid a trap without ever knowing
it's there, just through ignorance as well, right? Right, Mr. Magoo. Well, there you go.
There's a nice example. But people are old enough. There's a bear trap sitting, you know,
20 feet from me right now. Now, if I never bother to go to the particular part of my yard it's in,
I won't step in it, you know? But here's the crux before, because this has been in the head for a
few minutes. I have like a little window open. I want to just say this. Imagine a high-rise on,
you know, Lexington and 53rd or a big city somewhere in Philadelphia or Chicago,
apartment building and a big high-rise and there's a goldfish or an aquarium with lots of fish in the
living room or one of the rooms in this apartment. And the fish are doing the cycle babble that you
see humans do, right? But about what's out there, who made us, what's this, what's that, what's
the aquarium flat or is it round, is it square, all the stupid stuff, you know, whatever they've
got. And they have no concept that they're an aquarium in someone's living room on the 50th
story and a building in a complex of cities on a planet, you see? So when you're okay with that,
in other words, you set yourself apart from the cycle babble, you start to look for all the hints
on that you're really an aquarium in someone's living room on the 50th story in a city instead
of all this other cycle babble, you see? And then you come back and you relax because there's no
other fish you can talk to about it, right? But it doesn't mean you can't find another fish on a
minor internet radio and anyway, you get the point, right? So... Yeah, I got you. What's the big deal?
Now here's the thing, you're a fish in an aquarium, what's the chances of you going out,
you know, down for bagels out of 10 blocks over? It ain't gonna happen right now,
right? No, not unless I figure out a way to become a fish, yeah. You're stuck in that aquarium and
you have no... and everybody around you is, you know, trying to make stuff up of what's going on
and they don't want to look at, they don't even want to inquire that you're in someone's living
room 50 stories up in a big city. I mean, you know, and sometimes you might get out and you say,
hey, let's say, theoretically, you got out, I want to go back to the aquarium, man.
Shit's crazy out here for now. So that's, again, another way to... There are some personal
messages that come in on the Skype, I mean, and on the email about what the hell do I do? I'm like,
why are you asking me? I never said you should do anything or not do anything at all. These are
things to consider. I mean, and there's many, many things to consider. There's a public speaker,
someone gave me some, remember cassette tapes, about a decade ago, and they've had them since the
70s. And there's this one guy, he was a radio, very prominent announcer, and he would do these
little minutes of wisdom every day. And one of the things in the tapes was, and I've never really
listened to them, but I got this out of it, is they never share more than 10% of what you've
discovered. Sometimes you might want to give 11, that's it, right? And the reason why is why,
why bother at this point? Because what's bantied about in the universe that man considers to be
the universe is so minimal. What they take seriously, and they've actually considered
having themselves accommodated by things that are malevolent. So you set yourself apart.
But you know, here's the thing, I think that, let's say this is, you know, 10 is the number of
judgment, let's just say, or what we're alleging, right? If you look at a, you know, 10, right? Okay.
So from a gematria point of view, now, you hear about, you know, how people use the word fear,
and we've kind of rationalized it, right? And a boredom. And what was the other one? Depression.
This is not necessarily what you might consider to be a definition. But why we discuss these things
this way is so you can have a grip on it, right? So you can rationalize it and use it, you might
have another way to do it. But you have to, you have to look at it objectively. Again,
a lot of the things that are being spoken out there, a lot of the terms, you know, the fear,
the, you know, all these, what would you say? Well, all the common terms that you hear discussed,
they're not being inquired, they're not being considered. And they're just being used. I don't
think it's just entertainment anymore. I think what's happening in media and university is
emotional laziness. So that would be another condition to consider the emotional laziness
that people, you know, have. But the thing about discussing these things like this is so it's
rational, coming together here and mentioning things does not necessarily, whether it's good
or bad for you is up to you. The point is that these things are always, let's say, up for discovery
and very obvious. One of the things I used to like to say the last thing for mankind to do is
discover the obvious. You never want to start putting out doctrines or information or thoughts
that you have to join a special group like university or something, some club to get.
That's why, you know, I see if you ever look at, there's a bunch of people talk about secret
societies, Illuminati, Freemasons, all that. It's all superficial junk. You know, why would you,
you know, if it's meant to be that way, you're not going to get it, right? You're not going to
get the secrets. So why bother? And what could they possibly have that secret that could benefit
anyone if it's a secret, because the real secrets are right in front of you, that you could work
with, right? So anyway, so the obviousness, this is how you, and going back to the term,
I actually escaped the mind for a minute, the term judgment, it's number 10. Another term,
don't be judgmental, right? You hear that all the time. Well, what are you talking about?
If anyone's conveyed themselves in a motorized wagon, if you don't exercise at least a dozen
to 1000 judgment calls, you're probably not going to be, you could probably going to be
carried home in a box. In other words, when you are conveying in a motorized wagon, what you call
an automobile, it's not an automobile, because you have to put fuel in it. When you are conveying on
the road, and you see an intersection with a red octagon that says STOP in white, what do you do?
You judge, don't you? You're constant judging. Well, here's what's weird. How do you describe
or how do you actually define or explain the word judge? Because making a judgment, see,
here's where language sucks. Making a judgment about whether to stop or which obstacle to avoid
and things like that doesn't seem the same as judging the quality. Well, that would be
condemnation then. That's where they say you're judge, jury and executioner. And then that's
what's going on in the political scene all the time with these protesters, for example,
I see these protesters or activists or whatever, they seem like they're exercising a right or
freedom. But they're actually out there to do more than that, right? Typically, so, you know,
persuading. Yeah, so, so it's not just persuading, it's just they're doing stuff that you, you know,
is outside the scope, right? So, if you, for example, or let's use the automobile analogy,
when you go to an intersection and you see the red octagon that says stop on it, you don't really
get out of the car, pull it out of the ground and throw it on the floor because it inconvenienced
you. It's there to give you discernment, right? So, most conversations are to be judged, of course.
How many times has the Greek been brought into a Skype group? And I last for 30 seconds,
because it's just stupid. And you've been you and I, I think we've been on Skype groups a while back.
And I have no qualms on telling people that obviously, you're not at work, you must have
forgot your reflective vest and plastic broom. Because that's apparently that's what you're all
you seem capable of doing. You know, I think you've actually heard me say that to people I know,
and other people are thinking that, but why do I have to say it? You see, so yeah, I usually just
cut it down to, you know, is there a point to this? You know, because there seems to be nothing
being done except a bunch of excited utterances being collected together in one particular place.
So, I don't know what the point of that is. You know, we could sit here, I could just sit here
and tell you, oh, I like ice cream. And you can tell what color, you know, your favorite color,
you know, it's dark outside, my favorite color is red. And we could continue on exchanging these
thoughts. But there really is no particular coherency to it. And I hear that happening a lot.
Well, it's been happening. But yeah, good. It's been happening. And very often, I'll bring up a
point. I used to make a saying that you need not visit an insane asylum to meet crazy people,
because the Earth is the insane asylum of the universe. And someone says, Oh, that's Goita.
And I said, Really? And I looked it up in Goita, Wolfgang Goita made that quote about 300 years
before that. And I was quite upset because I thought I was being original. But at the same
time, I was I felt like I was in good company. But then again, not because, you know, Goita
did Faust, you know, the play about the man, you know, signing a deal with the devil and all that
opera, musical piece and all that, not a discussion with someone, we were listening to some of Faust
and some of the notes you might hear in the doors. One of the doors, here is the end, right,
the end is come, right. They borrowed some of the notes out of that. But so with Faust, what's
interesting, such a man that was so aware, he still had to fall into what's called the Christian
Convention, and use things like hell and this and making the cross and all that. Because if he
stopped, he didn't study what that was, or maybe he did it to accommodate the audience,
because he lived in a time period where if you spoke out against that convention,
you were probably killed. Right? You see, well, this is the concept of the Faustian bargain,
which still survives as a literary mechanism today. Right? Right. But he used Yes, but he used
a lot of the Christian convention and culture, which is not biblical at all. It's all made up.
So even someone who seemed to be a brilliant physicist, scientist, he was even in government
and all these other things, he still had to follow that convention, which anyone could have
spent just a little bit of time to see it's all false. Right? Well, yeah, but in other words,
what I'm saying is you only have you only have so much of the language to communicate an idea.
And it's not to say that the idea of the story there is not a valid one or instructional one.
What's to say that the conventions were not adopted so that it could be relatable to the
viewer, the observer, so on and so forth. That's exactly the point. We've been saying for a long
time, you always have to accommodate the audience or you will not have one. When they I think it
was Sarah Vaughan, they asked her what makes a great jazz musician and she said, it's the audience
makes you great. Right? I mean, look at look at the popular figures in media, alternative and
mainstream. Why are they popular? Because they garner large crowds or members or attention
following, right? So and you know, there's an interesting saying about that. If man loves you,
you're hated by the gods. And if you're loved by the gods, you're hated by man. Now that's a tough
one. You want to contrast that to Faustian stuff. That's another thing to look at. Right? So, so
there's a lot of the ancient Greeks said a friend to all is a friend to none. Now a lot of these
super popular, whatever figures they seem friendly to everyone. And by the way, I used to work in
various things where I'd be exposed to people of, you know, they're of fame. And, and some of the
people actually that, you know, in TV and all that that's presented themselves as being like
wonderful, we're actually quite crappy in off camera, you know what I mean? It's like, Whoa,
this is a real, you know, you know, really sad representation of a human being, you know?
Yeah, I can tell you that. I actually knew somebody who dated one of the bozo the clowns
at one point, you know, Mr. Happy clown guy, entertaining children or whatever,
but he was actually a raging alcoholic and kind of a prick. Anyway, yeah, no, true.
Yeah. So, so, well, you know, not on all cases, but it can be that it's not what you what you
think it is. So, so the point here presentation does not necessarily represent the reality.
Let's keep that in mind. Right? Yeah, that's right. Yeah. So the presentation here has always
been get up on your hind legs and start paying attention if you so choose, because you have a
choice either way. The other thing is, haven't you ever noticed, right? And what's obvious,
you know, and the other thing is the concept of being set apart. You never hear that not,
not to say that you really never hear it. It's been heard before, but the common theme still is
making things better. What are we going to do? And I give advice and the advice is always do
absolutely nothing in that direction. Anything that you do is to set yourself apart first,
just like when the airplane is in an emergency state, they always tell people, put your oxygen
mask on first before the baby or the person next to you, because if you try to, you're right. So
help yourself first. It doesn't mean perpetually or whatever, because ultimately, the very simple
thing is this, if half the world helped just one person, that would take care of the other half,
wouldn't it? So how hard is that to do? Right? It's all these things that people are saying,
and when they have the wrong direction. And another thing, you know, money is very important.
And it says also, there's some ancient texts that do say that pretty much anything that mankind
gets involved in, he can fix with money, because it's portable land, right? You're in essence,
off of that. So if the entire direction of the alternative media, and you notice how the
mainstream doesn't talk about anything like that really, has been about a false premise of the
credit system, pretty much anything else they do will not work either. So money is a good place to
start, because it represents portability. You know, and it's the love of money that is the
root of all evil, not money itself. It's the love of it. So if you want to really get a handle on
judging society, very carefully and precisely, look at what their perception, how they discuss
money is and what it is. And you'll see that right away, they've eliminated any efficiency
and portability. So they're all stuck. Well, you know, I've always found that
interesting about the love of money also, because to me, you can't really love money,
it seems to be a fallacy built within a fallacy. Well, the thing that what love is, is, is the,
is you do it because we've never we've talked about love, I think on the older,
the highest form of love is doing the right thing, because it's the right thing to do,
even though you don't want to do it at the moment. But you're doing the right thing,
right? Then there's other forms of love, friendship, and then all the way down to
lust and all that and communal love or whatever. But what they're doing with with that sense that
it's the love of money is all is the root of all evil, is, is actually that the gods are
displaying that because they took money away, and people are still, there's no money, by the way,
what is being used as money is not even money, even though you can say it is being used as money,
it doesn't fit any definition of that. They've taken it away and no one has noticed,
there's a little bit of immature juvenile griping and quipping about it. You know,
oh, it's a node. Oh, it's just dead. Oh, it's just thin air. It's none of that. It's all credit.
But there are still people I hear that rob banks and you know, banks don't really care
about having Federal Reserve notes, they keep the Federal Reserve notes and file cabinets in the
bank. And what's kept in the safe are the promissory notes that people sign when they
allegedly get along. People don't know this, right? So anyway, and this is a very, very sad
state of affairs. And when you look at all of the world's religions, they are experts in demonology
and fictional demonology, because a lot of the things they make up as they go along,
but definitely the influence of low-level spiritual stuff. The medical system is based on
the study of cadavers and dead cells. You don't even have to discuss politics because that's who
the gods put to rule over you based on what they think of you. And then you look at the education
system, look at your teachers and scientists, look at the old people. I was discussing something
with someone the other day about older people and it's really sad to see because through convention,
human convention, when you saw someone older, you knew that based on experience, they could share
things with you, right? Not wisdom, because wisdom is something that's granted. It's actually,
there's a deity that is wisdom. It's an entity, it's a female god, by the way, and that's another
subject, but that's something different. But the older people now are reduced to fools,
and I was telling this person that when you read about it on certain ways, it's talking about those
inclusive within those rules, but those that have no rules or whatever, they're just, it's actually,
they're sad. And to show, you know how you were saying you could read out of the environment what's
going on? You don't need, let's say, not that need, but you don't necessarily have to go directly to
something that's been memorialized. Literally, you can look at the environment. When you look
at the statement that I just made about the old people being reduced to basic worthlessness
as a general whole, if you look at the environment, that will tell you it backs that statement up
because typically, they're pretty much jammed into nursing homes and with drugs and rejected
generally in most western cultures, and they're not regarded very highly. So, the environment will
show you that because if they did have any sense, they wouldn't have been there. Just like, for
example, here's another way to look at it. When you talk about certain forms, let's say, in America,
there was a republic, now it's a democracy. What happened? Well, you know what? If the republic
was so good, it wouldn't have changed into what it is now. So, stop romanticizing stuff. You see what
I mean? If you had such a great form of government before, if it was so great, how come it didn't
notice that it was... You see? Stop romanticizing this stuff is what the other practical side of it
is. Well, there you go. I think stop romanticizing might actually be the way to tie a bow on this
because we're just about out of time during this particular interlude of this particular Sonic
presentation. Well, it's the 10% that we keep... It's the coloring book, you know.
You keep kicking it around the same stuff. I've got no problems saying the same stuff for over a
decade. I run into people I haven't seen in a while. I said, Greek, you're saying the same
stuff you did 10 years ago or 8 years ago. I said, yeah. There's no progress. You know, when the cart
is stuck in the mud, you're stuck in the mud. You got to get it out of the mud first is the metaphor
here. You're not going down the road when the wheels are stuck in the mud. You got to clear
the mud first, right? So, you know, and there's no reason to keep pointing out that you're stuck
in the mud, but you can point out that we've got to get out of the mud because we got other things
we got to do. You see, that's more optimistic, right? Let's get out of this situation. But the
thing is that when you're set apart, it doesn't matter whether the people around you are doing
well or poorly because you're going to set yourself apart from them whether there's prosperity
or whether there's depression. The only thing is difficult to set yourself apart from is when
there's extreme violence. That's why in the wisdom side of what's been memorialized, the thing that
you should pray for is what? Peace. Everything else, you know, you can maneuver. If you don't
have peace, how are you, you know, okay. So as long as there's peace, lack of violence, right,
affecting you directly and those around you, you're okay. Well, my prayer is not for peace
because peace can be achieved if all things are dead. I seek to have a world in which domination
is not the primary concern. That is my prayer. Peace can be achieved through some pretty bloody
means, but to remove domination from the equation would be the thing that I would wish.
Yeah, but that's okay, but that's altruistic. But what's really happening is not really
domination. It's pranksterism is going on. The pranksters are dominating. Domination is no
problem. That'll always happen. But pranking people is a form of domination because to keep
them ignorant is to keep them easily controlled is to keep them easily destroying themselves,
don't you think? Yeah, but they're being pranked into domination because if you heard the saying
that no more has a society been enslaved at that that professes that it's free.
That's a pranking thing, right? So as long as you've got the legal society functioning the way
it is, you're going to be pranked. I mean, they are the ones running the show, by the way,
the legal society from the top to the bottom, and they are the pranksters. And then you have
everyone else is controlled by them. And if you don't know that, as the truth of the fact on this
planet right now, you're not paying attention at all. Right? So the way it functions now,
as the adversary is the stem of all of this. Well, that's for sure. And by the adversary,
we're not talking about a living embodiment of one particular thing. But that is a subject for
another show. This one is done. This is episode 10 of Ocelli and the Greek finishing out. What
do you think, Greg? Did we do some interesting time passage here, regardless of whether you
utilized a windup toy or not? Sure, I'd say so. Either way, set yourself apart from it. How can
you set yourself apart from the show you just did? Let's think about that. There you go. So
take care next time. Yep. Thank you. I think I heard the music. See you folks.