Well, now that I'm done wringing my hands for the day, we are on live here on American Freedom
Radio. As the bumper did tell you, this is Ocelli in the Greek, and of course it is,
according to the Pope's work schedule, a Thursday, the 12th day of the first month.
Yeah, that would be January 12th, but not using, not utilizing, excuse me, the Pope's work schedule,
it would be, oh, I do believe the Greek said before we went to air, and I'm not going to
take credit for it, the second day of the first month. Well, I shouldn't, because...
Second day of the 12th month. Go ahead.
Oh, I'm sorry. Second day of the 12th month. My mistake.
See, I got it wrong, even though I just heard it.
It's all right. This is something called censorship. But anyway,
here's the thing. Have you been outside lately? Those things that twinkle or shine or light up,
like that big round thing that rises in the east once a month, it's not made out of cheese. But
anyway, yeah, yeah, yeah. What else do we... You see there's a lot of conventions that have been
abandoned. Would you say the weather forecast maybe has not been abandoned, where it relies
on still visible clues from the natural environment? I think the weather forecasters still rely on
visible clues, where the time convention has abandoned visible clues, meaning something
lawful. So there are not many things that... I guess, I don't know, train bridge inspectors,
food inspectors, they rely on visible clues, I guess. Car inspectors, I don't know. Inspection,
quality inspection requires visible clues or visible cues, maybe. But how come it's...
Visible clues and cues also based on particular standards. Interesting. So there are standards
that govern the situation. See, a brown spot on one particular type of item might be a good thing.
A brown spot on another type of item might not, as far as the quality of said item, correct?
Right. Sure, sure. Things change as you go forward. But look, before we get too deep in
the conversation, I want to give people the opportunity to join into the conversation.
We've had some... Well, you received some emails, that's for sure. I received some messages. We
have those locked and loaded, if you will. But there's other ways to participate in the show,
isn't there, Greg? Yeah, let's give out the number. Go ahead, Chuck. Well, first thing is,
yep, we'll give out the telephone number, if you will, for callers 218-339-8525. Once again,
that is 218-339-8525. That is the number to dial and we will add you into the conversation as you
appear. I will only identify you by your area code if one comes up. So that's one way, but there's
another way, isn't there, Greg? Yes. On Skype, if you like Skype, it would be Ocelli and the Greek,
just like it sounds. O-C-H-E-L-L-I and the Greek. You spell it just like it sounds. And that would
be the Skype convention. And go ahead. Let's hear from you. Now, we do have the guidelines. I don't
think we need to keep bringing them up, but real quick, we could. Like, you remember Mr. Rogers
put on his sweater, it's a beautiful day in the neighborhood, right? Well, he always did sing that
song at the beginning of the show, right? Right, yeah. So, well, yeah, well, there goes the
neighborhood because he got Ocelli and the Greek. But anyway, the simple rules of this, don't talk
about yourself because people act like they care, but they really don't. They're just waiting for
you to finish and they're thinking, when is he going to shut up so I can get the microphone and
say what I want to say? So let's just be helpful. Let's share. Let's give some good testimonials or
accounts or reports. And no one cares about what you particularly like. We're not at an ice cream
shop. And the second rule is basically, if you're under the influence, and that's a big word,
but if you think you might be under the influence, you think you might sound clear and concise,
but everyone else knows you're not because it does quite sound like you're under the influence.
So those are the two simple things. So yeah, simple guidelines. Go ahead.
Well, there we go. And I wish people would take that into consideration, although sometimes
the lack of coherent or cohesive discourse is not necessarily limited to just those under the
influence. It does seem as though people are having completely disconnected conversations,
asking questions that have already been answered. I know I've made this observation elsewhere,
but I want to make it to you. Asking questions that have already been answered in a previous
statement, literally responding to a question or a statement with something completely unrelated.
I'm noticing this much, much more often lately, Greek. What's going on?
Well, let's cut to the chase. Most people on this planet right now take up space
and they give off heat. So you can define them as such. Now, if they speak and communicate,
that's quite a space heater if you ask me. But at this point, don't expect much and you won't
be disappointed. How's that? Here's the one thing about it. I was having a discussion
regarding – I actually got some emails regarding what's the point of this all?
These really big questions, they're very simple to answer. They're not easy. Just because something
is simple doesn't mean it's easy, right? But the thing is the human lifespan, let's just,
for lack of a better term, are you surface-dwelling earth inhabitants? I don't know.
You want to say 60, 70, most people 70, 75, 80, some over 100 is really, really short when you
compare it to the scheme of things. The scheme of things is the universal scheme. Something that is
put in place that needs to run its course. An analogy of that would be, you know, Chuck,
you got somebody that lives in the city and they commute or lives in the suburbs and they commute
to the city and they got a 20-minute commute every day. It's a short commute on a train,
let's say, right? And they're doing this 20 minutes a day. They really don't have
much appreciation typically or knowledge of what it took to build that entire train line,
the thousands of man hours, the time and even how to build a train, right? That would be the
general scheme. They just get on and ride. So basically, people, the surface-dwelling earth
inhabitants, they come here, they're born, they die, the lifespan we just mentioned.
But the scheme is really big. It's one big infrastructure that took a long time to put
together and now when you say, what is the meaning of this? It's not just a simple commute,
meaning your life, right? It's the actual infrastructure, everything around you. That's why
you brought up time in the beginning and we do bring up time every time when we start the show.
What day is it lawfully? And the whole thing is, that is attaching to a different scheme,
which is the sun, the moon and the stars versus the Pope's work schedule, which is this little
fiddly thing that everyone just takes for granted and it actually rules and controls their lives.
Right. Now, along those lines, really quickly, I want to interject because a question and I'm not
going to pander to the chat room here the whole time, but I thought this was a fair question.
How is it the second day of the 12th month? It's a full moon. Doesn't the full moon represent the
day in between months? Yes, yes. It appears that the sighting in the western part of the world was
last night. Now, technically, it came very early this morning, according to some observational,
you know, academic observational, but it fit the bill to be full last night, not tonight.
Now, the thing is, it appears to be, right? Yeah. Now, here's the thing. In order to make a decree,
okay, why do we keep time to memorialize events, right? So, later on, when you have, let's say,
a block or a chunk of data or information, it's dated, right? It's important, right? What's the
date on that thing, right? Okay. So, these things are monumental, literally. You know, what's a
monument? It sets a place, right? And it's immovable. So, when you, let's say, pull up a
document, you know, and it's dated or it has this day that it was drafted or whatever, that is a
monumental thing, meaning you can't change that, right? It's set in stone almost. Now, this type
of monumental decree or officiation, let's say, of what day it is, is a priestly function of someone
of great authority to do that. It was typically reserved for the courts of the kings or the high
priest. And you still have high priests. They're just not called that because it would just scare
the living panties out of you. But I'll tell you, the Greek is not in any position like that. Are you?
Do you know anyone in that kind of position? I don't. And the ones that are in those positions,
this is as far from them as anything. So, if you want to start, you know, it's kind of elusive to
a point, you know, how do you cite the full moon? But I would call the citing was last night. Also,
astronomically, the way you call the moon full is that it is completely round geometrically,
you know, and it is mostly illuminated for its surface area. So, for example, you know, the
first moon and the seventh moon appear to be the largest. You know, they call it the harvest moon,
you know, the seventh moon. And typically, now, what you'll see, the 8th, 9th, 10th and 11th and
12th moon and 13th, let's say, sometimes, which we might have this year, apparently, tend to get
smaller. And then it just booms up and just becomes really large again on the first. So,
that's how you recognize the moons. And the way that a moon is considered astronomically full,
that it is as close to a perfect circle. Like, for example, the night before,
it looks full. It looks round. But if you really look at it, it's a little truncated. It's got a
little flat spot, let's say, between 7 and 9 o'clock, you know. It's not fully, fully round,
right? And also, for its surface area, it's giving off the most light. And typically, in the ancient
way of, let's say, in the ancient Chaldean tongue, it would be Yadach Kodesh, which means the set
apart yellow. That's literally what it's called, meaning it's a separate yellow. So, when it first
rises, it's very yellowish, not orangish, but yellowish. And then it goes very bright white,
almost like a bluish white, you know, like on that full moon, bluish white hue.
So, that's the simple way. Now, the other way to do it is when you get really close to the
first and seventh month or what's called the equinox, the shadow of the moon lines up with
the shadow of the sun very, very closely, almost exactly. Because the equinox means equinox,
equi-night. Nox means night, equi means to divide or equal, and equinox means something that is done
at night. If it was equinox actually meant equal day and night, it wouldn't be called equinox,
it would be called equidiemnox, because diem in Latin, right? I don't know, I really don't like
Latin. But I understand, because quite honestly, this is exactly what is taught to those of us who
have been granted a, well, the title of a priest in the pagan discipline. You're speaking exactly
about the observations of the moon and all of it that we're supposed to use in order to count time,
by the way. So, interesting there. Well, yeah, from the, well, there really is,
here's the thing that we've gone through this many times before I even shouted out,
we got to figure out something else. I don't like that word pagan. Pagano, it's a Latin term. It
just means country bumpkin. And look, you go to any society and you see how they operate in the
urban environment, then you go out where the country bumpkins are, man, I find those people
to have a lot of wisdom and skill even more than, I mean, they're less dependent on conveniences.
So, whatever. But I don't really see, pagan to what, right? You know, we bring up a lot of biblical
discussion but we don't discuss it because it's not time yet. Because no one really will understand
what the hell you're saying because the actual translation has not been made offered yet. That's
why I dropped a link in the chat. An academic actually wrote 15 myths about the biblical text
people are not aware of. And one of the first things is that there is no translation of it.
And he proves it right there. I think we had someone in chat a couple of weeks ago say,
King James is word for word and it's not. And here you have an academic showing that as well.
Well, right. And really that was spurned by the fact that during the previous show,
I had mentioned that in a literary sense, and Carmine had mentioned in a literary sense that
that which they called the Bible, the Bibles that were printed and distributed, contained a verse
and a handful of verses, which absolutely justified slavery, which we may get into in the
second hour. I'd like to do that. That's really short. We could even do it now. But the mindset,
you see, the thing is, the problem with, you know, we come around every seven days and you
know, you got to shake the dummy load out, you know, that people have been dummy loaded for seven
days and then it takes about an hour to get them out of the dummy load mode back into something
that's, you know, more bait, you know, something that's got some basis to it versus opinion and
heresies, you know, what people like to hear or not. So the aspect of the biblical text will bring
up references to it, but we won't really discuss it because, you know, there's really nothing to
discuss because no one really has access to what it really says. You have all these erroneous
versions. It's kind of like if we're discussing JFK and we do, you know, we're constantly bringing
up the Warren Commission. I mean, yeah, it exists, but, you know, is it, you know, is it worth
discussing? No, you know, or whatever. Or you see these things are official. What would you say
things that the officials put out, you know, for for their benefit, not for your benefit.
They don't have your interests and benefits. So so I'm not saying that that officials are bad.
It just just so happens they're not good anymore, you know, because where do they come from? Do they
come from Alpha Centauri or do they come from the basic gene pool that you see on the planet? You
see, anyway, that's we've discussed that again. So so where we're going with this is we probably
suggested last time this is the sixth chapter. And what's important about that, you know,
and we're going to get into all those other things, because when we talk about slavery,
we're not talking about donkeys and horses and trains. That word slavery usually elicits
someone meaning a man or a woman rendered as property. And usually, you know, there's a
certain stigma behind that, right? When you say that word, and it's we're not talking about,
you know, we're talking about people when we say slavery. And also, when we brought up keeping
time and what's lawful or not, does that really regard much to the animal kingdom? No, because
they have a pre downloaded operating system. If we harken back to the very first time you and I did
in the Greek, all 100% external input. Let's just recap real quick. If you got a newborn puppy dog
and submitted it to a family of gorillas, and it was raised to adulthood to a dog, and you then
retrieve the dog and had it in your house, would you know it was raised by gorillas, it was still
chase a stick, bark at squirrels and pee and lift its leg and do all the things just like is if you
raised it, right? Now, it might eat a little differently, though. Maybe, maybe it may not.
Yeah, well, still, generally, you cannot tell the difference. But if you had a young, young,
young infant raised by gorillas to adulthood, and you had them come over for dinner, what do you
think they're going to act like? Just like a gorilla? Yeah, because you see, the dog hasn't
is a downloaded operating system, firmware, or whatever you want to call it, you know, it's all
pre pre downloaded. Excuse me, people do not. That's the thing we're a blank slate. We're not
animals, by the way, we, that's the thing we even though we share the hardware, similar hardware,
we are not animal in that regard. So this is what we might call the sixth time coming around. So
let's look at the number six for a moment. Let's just do some basic counting two arms,
two legs, a torso and a head. That's six, isn't it? Right? five fingers on a hand, that's six,
six feet tall, six feet under, right? You know, three plus three. So that six is the number that
denotes man, man was made on what day? In what they call Genesis six, six, they Yeah, obviously,
I mean, this is the recurrent number of men. Much like you said, the six compartments,
it all makes sense. In fact, the the pentacle, which people point to a lot and say, well,
it's a five pointed star, but it actually has a sixth compartment. Much like, you know, if you
only look at the head, arms and legs of the human body, that's fine. But what about that middle
compartment? If you put it all together, it's actually a fairly solid geometric representation
of a man. Yeah, there's a Pentagon, I believe, well, or a man. Yes. Now, the interesting part
is also the Da Vinci shows in his the man, you know, drawings, the symmetry and proportions of
it. Also, our spines are vertical and most other creatures are horizontal on all fours
that are similar warm blooded furry, you know, that share similar organs. You know, we, you know,
so there's an opposition there. Now, what comes, what's five? Five is animal, animalistic,
earth based. Five would be the maximum, let's say evolution, which means to unravel or show
or evolvement, manifestation of the earth, what the earth can give. And then comes man,
which is six, which is to steward it, right, which is to master it. And master doesn't
necessarily mean suppress when you say, you know, when you say like, someone is a master violinist,
it sounds pretty good. But when you say, you're going here to master the situation,
it sounds like you're going to bring oppression or suppression, doesn't it? It doesn't have to
be that way, right? So that's these, there's connotations that are being there's emotional
stigma and emotional stimuli that are evoked when you say certain words based on what, you know,
people's heresy, what they think it means, right? So we're supposed to make him we have,
okay, forget about the mankind is supposed to steward.
Caught you there. Caught you there. Yeah, we part of that we,
yeah, because if you're going to separate yourself, you can no longer say we but
yeah, but let's just be, you know, speak quote, unquote, kind, kind also means related, by the
way, like kind, kinder, right? So, so we all are really, fortunately, or unfortunately, right?
Because what I mean by fortunately, and unfortunately, is fortunately, we're all
related, because you know, the common base, and the and the reference point, but unfortunately,
because it hurts a lot more to have a brother and a sister misbehave than a total stranger,
doesn't it? Yes, it does. So and there's no if you understand humanity, there is no such thing
as a total stranger. So that's all DNA testing shows, by the way, that everyone has the same
mother, by the way, and all you shame on all you scientists out there that work with DNA,
they don't come out and tell the people really what's going on with that. But so anyway, that's
why the legal community has embraced it, because it's such a presumptuous field. So so this is the
number. You have you heard of the 666? Another thing that I mean, I call it the inane net,
you know, inanity, whatever, how many times have you heard 666 come up, and they're like Satanism
or Satan? That's the number of men. And it's the number of the beast. I mean, I look, I said on this
on the show with you, I said, it looks to me like three guys standing next to each other.
You know, well, simply the reason the reason why you have three sixes, because it's six, and then
you need lawfully you need from the mouth of two or three witnesses to make it so. So it's really
six. And then the other two sixes are the witnessing thereof that it is really six, six,
you know, they really is the system of man. Now, here's the thing, a lot of people use references
that they take out of a body of work, and they redefine it, you're not allowed to do that, by
the way, if you have a reference that is found in a body of work, and it's defined in that body
of work, you do not have the freedom, liberty or right to redefine it. You must use the reference,
the definition from the body of work that that reference was extracted from. Right? No paraphrasing.
Yeah, you can't. Well, you can't paraphrase as long as the the direction is correct. Right? You
know, so obviously, obviously, look, you can speak the same words in a different language, if you
maintain the integrity of the statement. Okay. Can't come out, right, right and change it.
One example would be kid, you know, that's a really poor example of because a kid is a baby
goat, no matter what you think, what you like, how you use it is irrelevant. If one person calls
a child, if one person uses the word kid, or 7 billion use the word kid, it means a baby goat,
no, no matter what you think it means. Right? And so so that's an example of the problem when
you bring up the 666. Right? Now, now you can see you can be sort of lenient or forgiving of the
matter. Because not erroneously, but not only use the word subconsciously, but intuitively,
what makes it so important is that beast. Right? Individual, let's say that is also a corporation,
a corporate individual, I mean, not corporation, but there's many around him that support him
is the only man that has ever been possessed by Satan, all the when you hear of demonic possession,
that is not the chief adversary. Those are minor imps and demons. You know, so you know,
like the movie, The Exorcist, and all these other things that the what they call the Catholic Church
or that's very fishy, all that stuff. It's like it's the devil or Satan. There's no, no, Satan
has never possessed anyone yet. The minor, you know, the lower corporal sergeants and whatever
have you see, but you can't discuss this right now. It's not time yet. Because right now the people,
the people's concept of this subject matter is alphabet block level. It's like you're,
let's say you want to discuss astrophysics with five year olds, you could do it for an hour,
they'll be quiet. And the moment you you ask, Okay, you know, does anyone have any questions,
all of a sudden, they all raise their hand. And you say, What's the question? And they all say,
you got any candy? Yeah, well, you can't discuss these things yet. If the way you have just
described most of the discourse that I see that that I can report to you Greek is occurring,
you know, on television in in face to face interactions, this is what I'm watching happen,
actually, is somebody stands there and looks at someone else and listens to what they said or
appears to, you know, based on all appearances, I would say they were listening, waits to have
appropriate time to respond, and then responds with something that you just characterized real
well. Right now, what is that now? Is it? Can you say it's stupidity, arrogance, not listening,
whatever way? Yeah, yeah, yeah. But you know, that gets into like the degrading, derogatory aspect
of it. But one thing I would advise people, yes, I do give advice, folks, is that just consider it
a level of immaturity or juvenile tendency. Because, you know, when someone when you have
a creature that is juvenile, you know, like a puppy, and they pee in your bed, you know, it's,
it's, it's a puppy, but you know, a mature dog doing it. Now he's giving you a statement, right?
So when people are doing this type of stuff, like you just brought up,
the best way to deal with it, I suggest if any folks out there also experiencing this,
is just consider the the one that is doing it as being juvenile and immature, even though they're
80 years old. I've actually had conversation recently with someone who was around 80 plus,
and they were actually captain of industry. And I was like, shaking my head, I was like,
I really feel sorry for young people. But anyway. So you just, you know, the thing is to just
consider them immature, it's more forgiving to the heart, let's say you'll help preserve your
own heart about it, you see. Otherwise, you get frustrated, you get tense, tense, you get this,
these things built up, and they have psychosomatic repercussions. Sometimes, you know,
this is what I'm dealing with right now. Thank you. Yeah, right. So So the thing is, you know,
just to remind everyone, we got about four or five listeners that really tune in and tune in,
meaning not just to the chat group and whatever. And by the way, folks, call in if you hear us
right now, we're live on what you call January 12, somewhere in the early PMs or so. So call in,
we want to kind of want to hear what you have to say for the sake of everyone else. But nonetheless,
the subject we were kind of this because this is the number six time we're coming around this time
around on the reloaded aspect of it. And what is man about and you notice we've been hinting
it from the beginning. The main situation I was going to read some emails. And by the way,
I want to thank everyone who's emailed at uncommon radio.com. There's, there's about 10 scores of
emails. And everyone, everyone is thoughtful and mindful of what has been said, they're actually
really listening. Now, I don't know if it's the same four people that have done it 50 times.
But I'm just joking. But yeah, either way. But there's some good questions there. Now many times
there are requests about discussing things. And typically, I just answer back on the email,
because I don't think it's fit for radio, meaning very specific questions regarding eschatology,
spirituality, discernment of technical things, biblical questions that I don't think are fit
for the public at large at this time. Now, that's my call. Right? Now, you might think otherwise,
Chuck, I think that this being a minor internet radio station and a very minor internet radio show,
we can pretty we have no limitations, we can say anything we want. And how we want it is from what
I understand from AFR. Oh, yeah. But, but in general, at large, I think that we best is not
necessarily stay reserved, but at least to understand that this is still a public open
venue. And I would consider speaking with you, let's say tonight as if we were on regular terrestrial
FM or AM or something, consider it within that bound also, right? Whether there's four people
listening or 5 million, pretty much going to say the same thing. But there's there's some really
behind the scenes a little bit, at least that I'm getting on the email side and some private messaging,
some really deep, profound questions that are very pertinent. Now, there are also some questions that
have been answered already. And I suggest people go back and listen. And then they do come back and
say, you know what, I went back and listened to it another five times. And I got it. And that's fine.
So, you know, it's all good that way. But you know, we're coming together now, this is the sixth time
we're coming together. And by the way, folks, when you do a little bit of research, you'll find that
any message that is given to men, whether it's the Magna Carta, the Constitution, Shakespeare,
Greek philosophers, they were very careful whether it was known or not to divide it by six parts,
you'll see many divisions of six, when man communicates to man, it's usually divisions of six,
when the gods communicate to man, it's divisions of seven. That's why, for example, it's really easy
to knock the King James Version, which is all the other versions are based on it. How do you know
you're looking at a biblical text that's King James Version, you go to the first chapter of the first
book, if it says in the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth, that's King James. And they
all say that. So that's very simple. It's this is not dogma. This is just reality and objectivity.
Now, what they've done is they tell you all these quote unquote, Christians and others will tell
you that there are 66 books when they shout that out all the time. Constantly. It's 66 books. Yes.
Well, there are not 66 books that was devised by division to be this such because for the reason I
said before, whenever you're creating something for man, now, what would a group of powerful
people create for the rest of the people? They're not so powerful, diversion, deceit,
entertainment, make sure they say, stay in shallow thinking, so it's easy to pull them into
the deep end, right? And, you know, being being pulled into the deep end, if you know what that
is, if you ever dealt with the legal society or the medical society, the academic society,
the religious society, they're just sitting there watching you and see how shallow you are.
So they could pull you into their end when they want to. And it's easy to beat up on you because
they make sure they have deep crevices to pull you in. So those that are not shallow thinkers,
avoid them completely. So so let's go back to the King James. They devised it to be 66 books.
Let's just cut to the chase. There are really 49 books in the biblical text, seven times seven,
seven divisions of seven books. Actually, one whole division is one book, which is the last
book, which is actually the first book called Revelation. But there are 49 books in the
biblical text. And the reason they tell you they're 66 is they took certain books and they
divided them like first and second Peter, first and second Samuel, first and second Chronicles,
first and second Kings. You've seen that, right? Those divisions did not exist prior and they kept
dividing until they got the 66 that they wanted, because whenever you're going to deliver a crock
of shit, sorry, to mankind, you got to have it divisible by six. So did I just say that? But
anyway, OK, so the point here is this. When man delivers to man, it's typically six. When the
earth delivers to man, it's typically five. And when the gods deliver to man, it's typically
through sevens. Now, what's interesting is what's what's the highest star ranking general you have
in stars? Usually five stars. You notice that? OK, yeah. Now, why not six? Why not seven?
The reason is because five is an earth number. It's a number that is of the animalistic. Now,
when you're going to war, I assure you, folks, every war that was ever waged is using nature.
And the reason I bring this up is because when the gods come, you know, when they send the mop up
crew to take what you guys think is sacred and mop it up and put it in the rinse bucket, yes,
they're going to use nature to do that. And like I mentioned last time, I think Chuck
is having a discussion with someone on this and they got a little befuddled. And I said,
when man goes to do war, they use nature. If you want to build a rifle or an airplane or bullets,
you have to go and mine the material from nature. And even when you're processing it,
the energy that you're heating the furnace with is coal or gas or wood. You know,
the rifle is made from refined iron and the stock is made from wood that you cut from a tree
or plastic that you get. You see, so mankind wages war, you know,
arrows, flint arrows, right? Spears, anything. You wage war using nature, right? So isn't it
interesting that you've got the highest form goes up to five, which is nature. So because remember,
all the animals and all that were complete by the fifth day and then here comes man.
Now, this is nothing to do with faith. It has to do with the faith, by the way.
It's funny how they leave that out. When you hear this thing called faith, you don't want to have
faith because that just means you're ready to be shafted. But anyway, you want to have the faith.
The faith means you have to have specifics. So the problem with the specifics is man's life is too
short because the scheme and the apparatus that has been put in place is too big. Just like we
said earlier, the commuter train ride that, you know, I shouldn't say from suburb to city because
some of those rides could be an hour long, but, you know, a short commuter ride, a few minutes
a day, the people don't think of the infrastructure much, do they? All the tracks and the train and the
infrastructure, that's thousands if not millions of man hours sometimes to go in to build these
things and no one thinks twice about it. They just appreciate or not appreciate that little 10 minute
ride they get on the train or bus or whatever. They're not really contemplating or understand
the engineering behind it. How many people ride, let's say, the LIRR or the Metro North or whatever
back east and actually understand the civil engineering behind all that? Very few, unless
you're an engineer. And even then they don't understand it because they're so compartmentalized.
You know, if you talk to an engineer, he says, I only did the tracks. I don't know anything about
the wiring. Yeah, because there's an electrical engineer, there's a geological engineer, there's
a guy who's got to figure out, you know, how the train is going to resist when it travels up a hill
or whatever, blah, blah, blah, blah. Yeah. And it's an entire army of engineers that are using nature
again. So anyways, it all just goes, it's just, this is like a whirlwind of stuff. So this, I would
say, this time coming around, we need to address mankind. This is the sixth number. It would be
apropos. And the way you address mankind is, what are the three things, I guess, that appeal to
people? One is their personal gain. You have to appeal to them, you know, gaining something. You
ever watch TV shows? If you, you know, oh, you do this, start this business and you'll make lots of
money, or you do this, your eggs won't stick to the pan anymore, right? Personal gain, right? The second
thing is fear. Oh, you don't want to be caught in the dark. You need this flashlight, right? You don't
want to, you don't want to have a leaky roof, get this, or the fear. The third thing is greed.
You know, your greed, which is, which is different, which is, you know, you want to be better all the
time, don't you? You want to be better than this guy or whatever, you know, don't you want, right? Okay, so
you've got the personal gain, the greed and the fear are the things, basically, that are, and if you
look at the biblical version that's put out, you have notions of hell, and heaven, and the Pope's
work schedule, and all these things of fear and greed, and all that, and if you actually find out
what's in the biblical text, you will be astounded, if you can understand it. Now, you've heard me speak
very often on the biblical stuff I give references, because it's first-class information, but did you
ever talk, think about this, I'm going to say it real slow, have you ever heard me recommend that anyone
go and read it? No, never, never. Do you know why? Because you're not going to understand a dang thing
in it anyway, so why would I send you on a futile path? You see? No, I, I understand, you know what the,
the, the, the objection to that, when you say that is, well, why are you special? Why do you
understand it? You know, if they say wrong, that's, well, that's, well, here's the thing. It's kind of
like, if you go into a five-star restaurant, and then the chef says, well, you know, can I make that
at home? No, I'm not even going to give you the recipe, because you can't cook like this. What makes
you special? I don't know. Everyone's got their own personal history, right? If you go to, let's say,
Michelin three-star or American five-star restaurants, there's a, there's a bunch of them, not so many,
not as many as there are regular restaurants, and each chef has his own story, doesn't he? But they
all put out great food, don't they? What makes them so special? Let's just look at it real short.
They're men. They didn't come from Alpha Centauri. They, they decided that they're going to really
focus on it. They decided to invest their, and dedicate their lives to it, all their work. In
other words, when people were out doing vacations, they were not, right? No, they cultivated a skill
through the acquisition of knowledge and the application of that knowledge, you know, and,
and constantly expanding it to refine it to a degree in which the presentation is represented.
I mean, it's a lot of work. It's a lot of work. It's a lot of work to do it. Yeah. They've
sacrificed a lot of their time, you know, where other people had to do other things. And that,
you know, that goes to the voluntary involuntary aspect, which might go to back to slavery. But,
but the thing is, the reason when I was saying that wasn't directing at you, it was just generally at
people. And I still, here's the other thing. I get a lot, quite a few emails about, you know,
you're correct. I've been looking at the Hebrew and the Greek interlinear, and it really is very
different from what they're giving us on the version. You know, should I learn Hebrew? Should
I learn Greek? Should I do all this? I said, you know, there are, here's the answer to that,
you know, like a video game, there's level one, level two, level three. So, you know, you work
on level one, you get blasted, you figure out how to not get blasted, you go to level two,
you think you're okay, but it gets harder, doesn't it? Right? And then you get to level
three, it gets harder even yet, but now you're, you have more finesse, because you've sort of
been exposed more, right? So when I get a lot of questions about people, which Hebrew, which Greek,
how should I, should I learn? Here's the thing, folks, and I'm just going to go really fast
forward to the next level and bypass that level. And the answer is this, there are plenty of
scholars that can read Greek and Hebrew, and they still don't, cannot explain what the message is.
And ultimately, it doesn't matter what language it is, are you getting the information? So the
purpose of going back to the languages of preservation, which are Hebrew and Greek,
is to getting more source material. And then once you have the source material,
it's still this big, giant jigsaw puzzle you have to put together. When you look at the versions,
it's like putting a jigsaw puzzle together in complete darkness with missing parts.
It ain't going to happen, period. I mean, if it does happen, it's a miracle.
The second part, if you go to the languages of preservation, the Hebrew and Greek,
now you've got the lights on and you've got all the pieces, but what? You still have to put it
together. And you can't put a jigsaw puzzle together unless you have a picture as a reference,
right? You ever notice a jigsaw puzzle when you buy it, it's got the what it should look like on
the box. And you start fielding all the pieces based on the image, the image that you see on
the box, right? You know, it would be 10 times harder, if not more, if you had a jigsaw puzzle
with no image to piece it together with, right? Odd you say that, because generally speaking,
when I was a kid, and I played with jigsaw puzzles, I would work without the picture all the time.
Good. Well, good. That's the mindset. Well, if you remember the skill and finesse that was
acquired after you had some positive achievement, or moved along, right? And if that didn't bother
you, you would probably be a good candidate for putting this together. And ultimately,
the big picture is this. There is a scheme that is put in place. Yes, mankind's life is really
short to appreciate it right now. But the scheme is not that very long. It's the entire scripture
is about life and death, period. It's about life and death. And now if you talk about life,
you've heard of good quality or poor quality, right? Well, if you want poor quality, you do
these things, you'll have poor quality. If you do these things, you'll have good quality.
Then there's death. Well, there's the question of what happens after death? What happens,
you know, why do we die, right? What's the reason? That is all there. And that's what it's all about.
And the purpose, this is the part that really in the future, this is going to hit many main
religions really across the teeth real hard, is the purpose of the biblical Christ is to show that
you are not bound by death anymore that to show what happened, what happens when you are released
from death, you know, so it has nothing to do with starting a religion or any kind of philosophy is
very cryptic. By the way, the most hateful character outwardly to the public in the biblical text was
the Christ. If you look at the New Testament, which I don't suggest people look at it, because
that is a series of private letters that were written amongst people to themselves. Right?
If you want to know who the Christ was, you have to be fully aware of the biblical text. In other
words, that what they call the New Testament is not the biblical text. This is a hard thing for
to explain to people, I think it's blasphemous, what they call all of the prophets, the Psalms,
and writings of Moses is the biblical text. The New Testament is after the fact.
But it is also to address those that knew what was going to happen. So, but the most hateful
character in there is the Christ. I mean, when I say hateful, meaning I just keep me away from these
people, you know, when they said, Why do you speak to these people in parable? And he says, because
the truth is not given to them, it's given to you. And not you religious people, but you like the
guys that were standing there. Oh, boy, you know. So, and I mean, how many times did he say,
you know, he go went to a city where they weren't really accepted. And he says, better off to been
in Sodom and Gomorrah. And what's going to happen to your ass? Right, and other stuff that they came
to him in one of them, and they said, Would you please tell us, Master, you know, addressing the
Christ, you know, the these men were gathering to do a feast, and the Romans came and killed them.
And what's the reason? And then these other men went to the build a tower and the tower fell and
killed them. What Why did those things happen? Why did those terrible things happen to these people?
What did the Christ say? There's no reason, no reason for it. Right? Because you got to understand
this is anyway, this is a numbers game. And it's not it really is, I wouldn't say a game, but it
isn't. Okay. You know, I've said before, we really don't know what a bear is. But we know enough
about a bear that we can say we know about bears, right? I mean, the only way you could really
find out what a bear is, is if you have a one on one conversation for about 20 hours, right? Well,
that ain't gonna happen, really. So, you know, we, we really don't know. I'm sorry, I just pictured
a conversation with a bear, you know, like Allah smoky, but sorry, go ahead. Yeah, but we see this
is how we discern things. We at this point, we don't really know what many things are, but we
know enough about them. Like electricity is perfect. You know, we really don't know what
electricity is. I mean, you know, forget about the theories and stuff they put up, but we use it.
Right? Okay, so we really don't know who exactly the gods are and what they do. But we know enough
about their characteristics that we can we can know about them. One of their characteristics is
when they create things, when they make things, when they emanate things, they do it in great
numbers, whether it's the stars in the heavens, the sand on the beach, the number of people,
the number of species, the number, you ever notice that everything in creation is massive
numbers. If you get yourself a microscope and take a blade of grass apart and start counting
all the plant cells on there, you get into the millions pretty quick. Right? Everything that
they do, one of their characteristics is they deal with very large numbers. There's one statement
that says that they have an accounting department that is so detailed that every time you lose a
hair, everyone loses or gains a hair on their head, it's accounted for. Now, how many times have
you ever thought people actually doing accounting when they brush their hair? You know, they take
the extra hair out of the comb and do a bookkeeping on that. You see, please. Yeah, this is the level
of this is a level of of rationale or painful detail that the gods engage in. Well, if you can
see all things and you can know all things, because you have access to the information,
there's no reason not to have it really accounted for to the nth degree. I don't know how else to
put it, but to have every single scrap of everything accounted for. I mean, isn't that
actually the goal when it comes to, you know, taking inventory over something that you have
control over, like a store or something? I mean, same kind of deal, right? Right, right. It would
be inventory control. Right. But it's on a level that we can't even perceive at this point, even
even, you know, even with the information mechanized age and all these supercomputers
or whatever still have not reached that level of processing. So so that is one of the characteristics
of the gods and what they actually if you ever read any of the holy writs of the world of any
culture, a lot of people don't like getting into them and the priests and the leader religious
leaders don't want you to look at them because they don't speak well of mankind, do they?
Whether it's the Rig Vedas, the Mahabharata, the Koran, the biblical text, even even all the little
offshoot little poetic things or whatever, none of them speak very well of mankind at all. So
it seems sort of discouraging, but it shouldn't be it. You know,
people want the truth, but they are they just saying that they want the truth because what
happens when they get it? You know, just like they say they want an answer to a question,
but they don't acknowledge it when they get it or anyway, I'm sorry. It's the same thing, isn't it?
Yeah, they shouldn't be asking the question. They should be asking the answer.
Right. But that's another thing. So this is to address mankind is very simple.
Well, should we say fortunately or unfortunately, your lifespan is short and most people do not
appreciate the scheme that's in front of them, the things that are in front of them. We've discussed
that over and over and over and over. And that's all I've been doing for over a decade and a half.
Now, the other aspect of it is I do this little YouTube thing with it's called the waiting room,
Rodrigo and the Greek. It's so you could get it on the on the Uncommon Radio site. Just click on
where it says YouTube. And those are just basically a impromptu Skype conversation that's recorded and
thrown up on YouTube. I don't mind. So one of the things that we've discussed there is that in order
to be to start gaining mastership, and this is also defined in scripture loosely, there are three
qualities that mankind should have or a person should have or a man or a woman should have
in order to actually function as we were intended. Right. You know what I mean by function as we
are intended, you know, like, you know, kitchen utensils are for the kitchen, but you could use
I've seen guys trying to work on a VW bug with kitchen utensils. I mean, you might get a job
done, but it's not really intended for that. Right. So look, you know, you know, I have a very
severe discipline when it comes to the intended use of items and things like that. And the intention
of the creation based on its nature, this is, this is one of the most extreme things that I
adhere to personally. So yes, please go ahead. Well, for sake of efficiency and optimization,
and just the aesthetic, it's just beautiful, you know, right, you know, a good set of tools on,
you know, on whatever is, you know, that are made for a certain thing used for that thing is just
beautiful. It's an aesthetic in itself. So, right. And I explained this in a slightly different way.
But the message is still sound no matter what language I'm speaking here. So go ahead.
So let's say there are three qualities that mankind should consider. One is to be able to
have good recall to bring all things to remembrance. The other thing is knowledge into all things. And
that would also mean that field of mastery. And the third thing is knowledge of things to come.
So it would be bringing things to remembrance, number one, which would be memory.
The second one would be knowledge into all things. And the third thing would be knowledge
of things to come. Now let's let's tie it in with the we talked about the civil engineer,
a really good engineer when it regarding a bridge, for example, when he is either in the
design process, or the the drafting process or the building process of the bridge, the really
good engineers got real good recall, they remember all the reference materials, everything they
learned in their training about it, and everything they heard about that thing. And they were able
to accumulate all that in one place with good recall, right good memory. Okay, the second thing
a good engineer has is knowledge into all things, not just the bridge, the structural steel, the
rivets and all that. But knowledge of the earth, the wind, the weather that has an effect on the
bridge, who's going to be traveling across the bridge, you know, as it trains cars, people,
the weather, you know, all these other things, right. And then the third thing that he has to
have is knowledge of things to come. If it's built well, that means like, what kind of a maintenance
schedule do we have to put into we have to paint the thing every five years or every three years,
that's, you know, it's brand new bridge now. But you have to have knowledge of things to come,
you have to have a maintenance schedule for the future. Or let's say he finds out there's some
bad rivets on a certain section, he says, well, according to what I heard that may that needs to
be changed within six months, because they're going to fail in a year that still hasn't happened. It's
things to come, you see. So anyone mastering in any fields, again, the first part is really good
memory, good recall of what you've taken in, whether it's in general or within that specific
field. The second thing is knowledge of all things that affect that thing. And the third thing is
knowledge of things to come. Now, from a biblical point of view, let's say the first part would be
good recall is when you study your remember, the second part would be knowledge into all things
is what you study, you can compare to the physical world around you. And also all things about the
gods, the characteristics of the gods. And the third thing, knowledge of things to come is what
how to keep time and prophecy. And I'll tell you that most people that subscribe to mainstream
religions have none of those things. Well, yeah, I was gonna say that the majority of what I have
observed, do not seem to be in high quality on any of the three components you just discussed.
So no, and those three components are critical for any mastership. Okay, let's go let's say a
kung fu master that applies to him also, right? He remembers all of his disciplines very well.
Right? He has knowledge of every time he's going to apply them everything around him is the floor
hard or the floor soft? Is this guy big? Is he short? And then knowledge of things to come if I
do this, this is going to happen before he does it, right? This is doesn't do something and expect
a random effect, right? Right. The same thing with a chef. He remembers all the techniques,
right? He has knowledge of all the things. Oh, this is a stainless steel thin pot, or this is a heavy
clay pot. He knows and then he and then he is knowledge of things to come. If he does all these
things, it should come out this way. This is the equipment. This is the ingredients. If I do this
particular act, this this reaction will have knowledge of things to come, right? And therefore,
so in order to be a good steward, that's what we're here for to steward all of this natural stuff.
That's the thing. Mankind started, stopped, he abandoned the general post of stewardship
and became a processor. Nature processes on her own. You're not supposed to process like that.
You're supposed to steward, right? And I don't need to explain that. That's pretty much,
you know, that's self-explanatory. What's processing, right? And what's stewardship,
right? So these things happen, you know, a lot of, in other words, let me just get into the
stewardship, just for an inkling, small, minute amount, is that many of the things that are better
left at nature do, you know, like the decomposition of things or the growing of things, or the,
let's say, the enrichment of soils and other things best left for nature to do it. But man says,
no, no, no, no, not only are we going to manage it, we're going to get in there and artificially
start processing and controlling these natural reactions, right? It's biting him in the butt
because he's going outside of his scope of work, right? So that's the aspect of
mastership. And why not? One thing that I always like, I like the finer things in life. I may not
be able to want to afford everything that's the finer thing, but I always seek things that are
finer, right? And if I'm in a situation where the things are not fine or good, I like still to make
the best choice. Like, for example, you know, traveling, I was doing some very long traveling
and you're on the highway, you know, you stop at a rest stop and what do they got to eat, right?
I don't need to say, you know, the brand names, you start with an M and ends with an S, but,
you know, and, you know, it's like, oh, I'm not going to start. Well, you go in there. It's just,
you know, what they call crap food, but you could still make a better decision. You don't get the
quadruple patty special sauce with everything. You might want to get, let's say, an apple pie
and a fish sandwich, make a better choice. Even in the worst situations, you could make a better
choice, right? I mean, let me throw a dig in. Internet radio is garbage, man. It's just junk,
but, you know, this is the best of the choice. I mean, I got Chuck O'Chelley. He's got a great voice.
I mean, you know, there's no way we could talk right now about anything because look at what's
going on. Mainstream radio is garbage. University is garbage. It's all junk right there. People are
inclined, but, you know, when I do radio, I'm ordering the apple pie maybe and the fish,
you know, I'm not going for the, you know, you'll never hear us talk about the dollar is going to
collapse or Fukushima or Fukushima is going to kill us all and all the stupid stuff that people
are just engaging in, you know, or what we are intent matters or humankind is going to end in
two years and all this stuff. I mean, where are you people getting this from, you know?
So, you know, the whole thing right now is, you know, why, you know, why come together? Why do
the show? Why do it? Why not? Why not? Why the hell not? Right. Because first of all, you know,
here's the thing, Chuck, you do radio all week long or whatever, you know, and I do what I do
and we show up and we do this thing. But I'll tell you, I assure you, folks out there, not for
whatever, but the stuff that's said here with Chuck and I, you're not going to hear anywhere
else. Sorry. I mean, and I wish you could because then I could take a break. But, you know, the
reason to come here and do this is not to really put a dig and I like not like to dig and then
whatever, but it is junk, folks. If you guys are really paying attention, there's really nothing
out there. And I'm sorry for you at this point. But at the same time, I shouldn't be because you
really, really have access to everything. All you need is a little bit of a prime or a kickstart or
a look in the right, you know, look, look at it this way a little bit. But the thing is, you don't
want to tell people how to think either, you see, because, you know, we'll get into that about what
slavery is, you know, because when you bring up these these terms like slavery, oh, it's bad. Oh,
you know, because you've been so propagandized on what this is, you know, when you hear the same
thing about radioactivity, oh, it's gonna kill us or whatever, you know, or anything, you know,
or whatever issue is discussed right now, it you notice it has an impulse, it has something on the
mind. And it's usually incorrect. Well, that it does. And you definitely will not hear me called
a fish sandwich on any other show. That's for sure. Not not no matter how many hours I do.
Ocelli in the Greek is just getting warmed up. Really, we have one more hour to go here on
American Freedom Radio. I advise you stay tuned. Because well, we are going to actually get into
that topic of slavery in the next hour. And I think it will be something that most of you have
not heard before. So stay tuned. Our number two begins here on Ocelli in the Greek, which is
broadcast from American Freedom Radio at American freedom radio.com. By the way, I want to remind
you real quickly that you can actually go to American freedom radio.com and click the donate
banner. That is a way to keep shows like this or actually, no, this is the only show like this. So
to keep this show on AFR, you can, because it's the only one like it, you can contribute there
to help with that cause. And of course, go to Uncommon Radio. If you want to write to the Greek
directly, he does read your emails and has been receiving them. And and before we kick back into
the conversation, join into the discussion, if you like. First, let's give the Skype information.
Sure. Ocelli and the Greek. It spells just like it sounds. So it would be O-C-H-E-L-L-I and the
Greek on Skype. And the phone number, Chuck, is 2 1 8 3 3 9 8 5 2 5 2 1 8 3 3 9 8 5 2 5. And we'll
add you right on in. Now, I did during the break mentioned to the Greek just before we get into
slavery as a concept. A lot of questions about Nazis, Nazis, Nazis. I've seen Nazis in the
chat room and all that. So. Oh, yeah. That term is not it's it's a it's a pejorative. It is a
negative term. It should never be used unless you are using it to degrade someone. And we're not
going to use degrading terms. Every every culture pretty much has gotten one. You know, what is it?
The N-word, greasers, spics, wops, guineas, chinks, gooks. So, I mean, those are those are
pejorative. Those are negative terms that are used against certain people based on their political
belief or race, creed or color. Right. Yeah. And that's what an N-A-Z-I is. If you're using that
term, you might as well be using all the rest when you're referring to other groups of people. And I
said groups because it doesn't necessarily have to be something you can't change. You know, the color
of your skin. It could be a political belief. So what is the sickening part about the N-A-Z-I word
is that the way it's being used, it's been accepted by academia. You will actually find
it in textbooks. They are the National Socialist Party. Sorry, folks. I'm not a sympathizer in any
way. I don't sympathize with anything that mankind does at this point or ever have seen anything worth
sympathizing with. I'm just stating a fact. Now, if you folks are still calling children baby goats
and kids, well, then, you know, it's rational that you'd be using terms like that anyway. Right. So,
I mean, that's the nature of humanity at this point. Sure. And of course, the question,
did they win or did they lose World War Two? There's a strange thing. But well, there's a
fellow that pontificates a lot about that and his information most of the time is vettable. And the
summation that this person has done is that they're in exile. And I would say that's pretty
close. I'd say that the American Intelligence Services accommodated a lot of the, let's say,
characters that were in the National Socialist Party. And that could be vetted. Right. And it
wasn't just Project Paperclip. There were other projects as well. As a matter of fact, there's
some pretty good resources that show that Adolf Hitler himself died near Bethesda, Maryland,
at the age of 106 or 107. And he was listed as the or maybe 112 listed as the oldest man in America.
But when they kind of like figured out who was it, they changed the record. But anyway,
there's many aspects to it. But the thing is, we're in a point of history right now that you
be forward thinking that the stuff. Yeah, you're still, let's say, quote unquote,
suffering conditions that were laid out in the past century. But, you know, who's who's paying
attention? You know, I mean, you have no money. Money was taken away. You have a credit based
economy. Still, people don't care to investigate that you all of your government. The only way
anyone can interact with their government now is through agency or agencies, which is not government.
There are private groups that perform government services and functions, and no one notices still
you have in America, something called the Constitution that within the first 17 words,
establishes justice, which is the revived goddess religion. And people still not aware that everyone
was leaving Europe to escape justice because it was destroying them. And what do they do?
They instill it here. And everyone says it's great. I mean, this is sick, you know.
So forget about all that stuff. The thing right now, you are engrossed in a period right now
where another seven year period is going to be starting here and roughly another year that is
going to be taking you to the next level, which is the preparation of what you folks have been
screaming about, who you folks are. You know who you are about the new world order, but it's not
the new world order that you think it'll be a new world order that you will walk right into and love
it. So how do you get into these kinds of topics? I don't know, but we try. Yeah, absolutely. And
look, I just I just passed it along because it was, you know, repetitious and seemed to be
something of curiosity. And I knew you had something to say about it. So therefore, I addressed it.
Yeah. Anyway, a couple of other odd things I'm going to get into, because I think slavery you'll
be able to dispose of rather quickly. So if you don't mind, I want to go into some other
odd communications that I found interesting, if that's OK with you. Yeah, rock it, man. Go ahead.
OK. I had somebody send me a message and I'm going to condense it regarding the drinking of one's
urine. Now they're asking this because of the vitamins that can be reproduced in this kind
of thing. And do you have any sort of viewpoint on that? Yeah. So you mentioned that that if it's in
a Shaw burger. Excuse me one second. If it's in a Shaw burger vortex, I think. Let's see.
Notice. OK, let's let's just stop. Yeah, sorry. Go ahead. No, let's stop it right there,
because all the all the Shaw burger and of vortexing and the motion does is it attaches
lines of force to enhance it or degrade it and things like that. But before we get to there,
what is it? The bladder meridian is one of the largest meridians in the body and the body
experiences what we call polarization, you know, positive, negative, good and bad,
up and down, hot and cold. Those are polar opposites, let's say. Right. Typically,
the rule with urine is very simple. If you are in a healthy state, that is because your body is
passing all the bad stuff out through the bladder. You don't you want to let it go.
If you're in a sick state, in order for you to be in balance, the stuff that could make you better,
it could be produced in the bladder. The antidote, like an example, is most people that have been
ever bitten by a venomous creature, you know, from whatever in the first few seconds to minute
or so. The antidote that is very dear and costly if they fly you with a helicopter,
if you make it right. But a similar antidote that your own body produces in the bladder urine.
So I know for a fact that that certain snake bites can be not necessarily completely nullified,
but can be treated on the scene immediately with one's own urine. I know that that's a physical
fact. Yeah, right. And that is before the actual manifestation of the venom. Well,
yeah, before it really like sets in when you have a very fresh. Right. That's what I was going to
say. Look, I'm trying to just add in here. I know you probably already know all this, but the fact
is, I don't know. It's a matter of reporting something that others can use. Yeah. And that's
why we know it, because we know that if we say it, they do it. It'll get the same result.
Right. I'm just reporting that. That in a practical sense, I know that this applies
that effectively, if you urinate on your own snake bite within the first 30 seconds,
60 seconds, I'll accept as an answer. I know if you do it pretty much right away,
you have a very good chance of not having the venom set in and do a lot of damage.
It actually either slows it down or stops it, depending on or consuming it, consuming a little
drop. It's not the quantity, it's that it actually makes contact with the front end of the
tunnel. Right. The face. Yeah. But the thing, you don't want to be a piss drinker, folks. The
ancient Greeks back in the day, if they saw people with really bright white teeth, they called them
piss drinkers, because the way you bleached your teeth back in the day is you reserved a small cup
of urine when you first woke up and rinsed your mouth with it. It gave you really pearly whites.
And people haven't really gone back that far to see that people, and I see people with really
bleached teeth, I call them piss drinkers. But anyway, you don't want to be a piss drinker,
but you got to understand it's very subtle. It's like homeopathy. When you look at homeopathic
remedies, there's nothing there, but they're very powerful because they're actually polarizing.
So yeah, I would avoid the entire, look, the state of mind in humanity today, it's really hard to
get into the details of things, but just tell them what works because you really want to help
people, right? So if you're sick, a little bit of the urine consuming it might actually flip you
around because the state of you being sick is let's say electrical or polarizing. But if you're
really healthy, I would avoid it because it means you're working right and all of the toxins that
are produced in the body are being expelled properly. And also if you are rapidly polarized,
like a venomous bite, the antidote is produced in the urine. So there you go. And there was a
fad a few years ago about being a piss drinker and that stuff just made me just want to not even talk
about the subject. All right, what else you got, Chuck? Yeah. Well, no, I just thought that would
be an interesting thing because I know it does have a practical purpose. If it's considered
properly, right, considered properly, right. Right now, which most things are not so we want
to jump into slavery. Well, yeah, last last thing. Last thing is that I have questions about hollow
earth. They're all hollow. All everything is hollow because show me anything that the gods
create that is inefficient. Every molecule, every so-called atom, every little bit of matter is in
a very high efficient state. Can you show me any one little molecule of anything on a plant that is
not doing something? Even you know, everything is everything. Yeah. So if you're going to build
something structurally strong, you ever heard of an exoskeleton? Right? It's much more efficient
than filling it solid, isn't it? Just almost just as strong without the mass, right? Without the
so all that. Yeah. How many times have you heard of a large earthquake ringing the earth like a
seismically proven? Right. How can you assume? Yeah. Yeah. So in other words, there are cavernous
areas of the earth. That's for sure. Yeah. Think of the earth in scale like this. Imagine a clay
pot. You know, you people have experienced clay pots and gardens and whatever. Imagine a clay
pot about a little bit over a foot and a half in diameter, about an inch and a half thick.
Now, if you kick that, even with a steel toe boot, you're not going to damage it, right? It's pretty
strong. You need a big sledgehammer to break that. Right. Yeah. OK. Yeah, that's that's fine.
That's for sure. Yeah. Yeah. And I just wanted to dispose of those couple of questions really
quickly because we haven't gotten any phone callers to one eight three three nine eight five
two five two one eight three three nine eight five two five. And like I said, I will add you in.
You know the rules. That's that. Also, Ocelli and the Greek on Skype, if you message over there,
the Greek will handle adding you in. I have control of the phone lines. So now back to the topic at
hand, which I don't think will take too long. The concept of slavery, it's more than a concept,
it's a practice, but go ahead. Well, yes, true. But for me, it's a concept because,
well, you know, I don't feel as though I'm actively participating in this at the moment,
although I would say that by surrogacy, this happens in a lot of instances. I think people
are kind of enslaved by a lot of different conventions, if you will. But let's get into
what's the lawful understanding of slavery is. Well, you said you don't feel like you're
slaving. What happens if someone hurts your feelings and changes it? Right. You know,
there's an interesting concept there that being a concept of what we feel and what we know.
Let's go more what people can know. You know, earlier we spoke about man's post as really
being a steward. Right now, if you're going to steward anything, you have to provide for it. But
based on what you know, remember what you and all your knowledge of it and also things to come.
Right. Like if you, for example, one of the great things of the advent of what I call the
engine driven wagon, it's not an automobile because you have to put fuel in it. Auto
means that it just keeps going on and on. But you see, if you, let's say, use the horse for
transportation, let's say you left it in the stall for a month because you weren't going anywhere,
Chuck. You know, you got to go out and brush it and feed it and water it every day, don't you?
Even though you're not using it where something that's a machine, you know, you might want to
just stay home for a month and the car could just be, you know, stationary. It's fine. You don't have
to really do much for it. Right. Yeah. As long as it was in decent condition to begin with. It's
not an issue. It's just a little dusty. Yeah. And maybe air in the tires. So there's a convenience
aspect there. You have to consider what it takes to steward something. Now, the aspect of slavery
and people being property. Let me just I haven't really discussed this much, but there's no such
thing as ownership. Why? Because in order to own something, you have to create it.
And the best you're going to do is baking some chocolate chip cookies and say you own them
only in the form of a chocolate chip cookie. But you really didn't make the flour and the butter
and the milk, did you? So there's a concept there of ownership which just doesn't exist.
And by the way, folks, those of you who have a little bit of reading comprehension,
if ever you're ever given anything called a title or certificate of title or deed that says you're
an owner, go ahead and read it. It doesn't say you're an owner. It says you're you're holding
it in tenancy. What's a tenant? Oh, boy. So you're a tenant when you're handed the certificate of
deed. You're not the owner. Yeah. And also it's a certificate of deed, not the deed, by the way.
That's right. That's right. Same with corporations. You get a package back says,
congratulations. You know, thanks for registering with us. Thanks for giving it to us. Now you're
the owner operator, you know. OK, so now anyway. So the whole thing is about you forget about it.
You're just using stuff and there is no ownership. It's a it's a concept that is flawed.
And but it's that satisfy the fear, greed and and personal gain amongst other people.
So the basic point is this. When we look at the stewardship aspect, there is a very dynamic
aspect of humanity where you have conflict and war and subjugation. Right. And by the way,
in order to this, this is going to lead into slavery, because if you actually one aspect of
slavery, many of the slaves or servants were acquired through postwar manifests, you know,
like when one country conquered another, it subjugated and enslaved the other. You've
probably read or heard this in the past more than the future. Now they do it doing democracy.
And I give you a story about that, too, in Afghanistan. But so typically there's something
called lawfulness, which is very, very difficult to discuss because most people have no concept of
it when we and I think that part of you and I getting together and doing these sonic events
is to not only hint, but be redundant about pursuing it, you know, it whatever it is being
lawful and it comes from your God. So, you know, if you look at certain ancient writs, right,
the certain one, let's say it actually has very specific rules. It says that if you conquer a
people and you you take them on, don't oppress them because you've already oppressed them by
conquering them, treat them well. Right. So, you know, the thing that people are saying, let's say
regarding biblical text, you know, they haven't read it. One of the things is, for example, if
you conquer a people and you can take a woman for your wife, but you should not oppress her,
you shave her head and trim her nails. And for 30 days, you're to leave her alone and do not
oppress her, do not subdue her because you already have by because you've killed off most of the
males in her family, you know, the men, you know, and you've actually taken her away from her nation.
So so do not do that. So another thing in regarding warfare in that ancient text is that if you're
going to do warfare against someone, you do not cut down fruit trees or trees that provide food.
Do not do that. You know, the no scorched earth kind of thing. You know what I mean? Like you've
heard about what the unlawful. The other thing is, if you if there's a you have a border with
what's considered an enemy, if their animals come over to your side, you are to return the animals
unharmed. Now, even if you look at like the Hatfields and McCoys, you know, the famous,
I guess maybe it's myth, infamous or myth, mythological. I don't know. American feuding
families. They took pop shots at each other's animals and things. You're not supposed to do
that. These are. Yeah. Yeah. Well, no, look, I'm fairly familiar with that. I'm satisfied it was
a real situation. And part of the accounts apply to, you know, one one faction slaughtering another
faction's pig and things like that. That's unlawful. You know, and if you look at what
they were probably they had probably subscribed to one of those mainstream religions. We're not
going to use its name. So that's why they're unlawful. Yeah. So it's very easy. These are
proofs that we discuss here. You know, there's there's there's there's no liking or disliking.
It's just a proofing out of what's going on. When I mentioned the reality of the Hatfields
and McCoys, I'm stating that the record appears sound in the account that that's all I'm telling
you is that the report appears logical and appears to have been preserved regarding the
events. Let's jump back for the sake of time. I'll step on you for a second here, because I
noticed we have 40 minutes or less. So the one when I brought up the concept of war, because
through even any part, any discussion, you'll see that subjugation after war led to slavery.
And I'm giving here the lawful side, which people are not familiar with. You are not supposed to
mistreat or abuse or oppress. And I just gave you several references, which I don't like to do,
but anyone can look it up. It's not what you think it is. And the reason I brought that up
is because it's a preface. You see, most most societies have fallen or people fall into slavery
as a result of some kind of conflict. Right. So even during the conflict, which is life and death
in a lawful manner, there is no suppression, oppression, destruction of property, harm or
injury after the battle, which is what most people think there is. So right here, I'm setting
the stage to talk about lawful slavery. Slavery is both a lawful and legal condition. Now we're
covering the lawful side. Now, from a lawful perspective, a slave is someone who is not
necessarily stewarding his own household or himself. Right. In other words, he is under or
she is under a master that provides a roof over their head, let's say, keeps them warm when it's
cold, cool when they're hot and food in their belly and clothing. Right. Where if it wasn't
provided for them, they would have to get it on their own through some form of commerce or
production on their own. Right. So slavery is an essence of of of stewardship again. Now,
let's just go back to the lawful side of it. Typically, people didn't get have slaves unless
you needed them because you needed their production value. Right. Whether it was agriculture,
industrial or whatever. And by the way, I still hear a lot of some, quote unquote, factually minded
people talk about ridiculous crap like like everything before the 20th century was primitive.
The Romans had very heavy industry. As a matter of fact, one of the largest bakeries in the world up
until the turn of the 19th century was in Rome. They produced millions of loaves of bread every
day. You know, people are not aware of these things, you know, so so there's much industry
that was needed. And here's the thing, folks. Now, you when you hear about industry and production
of items, you typically think things being punched out a la Henry Ford on a conveyor belt with
machines. The ancients were quite well capable of doing that. But the reason why they suggested it
was possibly best to have people doing it is because they always found the quality,
the outcome, almost an indescribable quality of the product to be better when you had machines
that that were that had a soul, meaning breathing and blood flowing through their veins than a
machine made of wood or metal. Right. So they preferred that. So so back to the stewardship
part, you have the slave to produce. Right. Because it's also for commercial reasons. Right.
If it costs you X amount to keep the slaves, you need to make, you know,
one point something X on the end. Right. You don't want to be losing. Right. Right. To create more
gain. And just like now, you know, there's with mass production, you make a small amount on a
large number. Right. There was some mass production going on back then to undoing value of volume.
And even today, you know, there's some things that are expensive that if you ever notice,
a lot of luxury items don't have a high markup. But a lot of the things you get at more of a
discount commercial level or big market level have a very big markup. Like, for example,
you go to a big supermarket. Sometimes those things are marked up 10 times,
where if you go by, let's say, a very elite product, there's only maybe a 30 percent markup
or 10 percent markup. So there's a whole market structure and how things were done.
And slaves were used for all of those things, for things that were mass produced
and also for things that were considered fine luxury items. So I'm just covering the whole
awful gamut, because when you say the word slave, you think of someone living on the floor in
chains and being whipped every day. Still, it's amazing how ignorant people are. Now,
you see how we tied it into the production value and also the stewardship value.
Now, here's the other thing. Let's say let's denigrate the slave from being human to being
just something that produces something. If you have a farmer, just for a moment,
if you have a farmer that goes out and spends 150,000 on a tractor to work on his farm,
does he abuse that tractor? Generally not. Or does he take care of it and act sometimes
even more than the other things because of its high value? So lawfully, slaves were people that
did not provide the stewardship and maintenance to be autonomous or self-sufficient, but they were
part of a collective group for some reason of profit or whatever. They were not typically
abused or oppressed like most people think they were today. During harsh economic times,
for example, when the manager or let's say plantation owner or the master had the slaves
and the slaves were costing him more than he was producing, he might have been in a really bad spot
and he deprived them of food and things in hoping that the times would get better.
Let's say whatever industry he was in or estate he was trying to maintain did not recover,
then everything went to shit and everybody went to shit and you got a really bad
happening there. There were many cases like that. How many times have you heard of a corporation
going under and they're not telling the workers why they're being mistreated
because you're right and then they finally go under and they leave everyone flat on their face?
So this was very much how things were going. For every piece of bad news, it travels further than
the good news. You never hear about the slaves that were held in opulence. There were, I would
say, many times in world history where slaves were held in splendor and people that were more
sovereign or independent were in squalor. So being a slave in ancient Rome and ancient Greece,
you probably had running water, clean streets and all that where if you're more independent,
let's say in the Gaelic part of the world, let's say the northwestern part of Europe,
you're probably living in squalor. You probably lived in a straw hut and you wore animal skins
where if you were a slave in ancient Greece, you probably lived with marble floors and
you had running water and all this stuff. So we're trying to objectify the lawful reasoning
and giving some examples that are more subjective, well-rounded, I hope. Now, this is the lawful
aspect. The lawful aspect of slavery is you have a living, breathing man or woman that is
voluntarily there even when they're subjugated as spoils of war because if you go back to that
ancient text, you had a slave for seven years and by the way, what they call the Book of Leviticus
or the Shefer Vayikra in Hebrew, at the very last chapter around there, it actually gives you
a chart which is a price list or a value list of people in silver based on their age and gender.
Are you aware of that, Chuck? Yeah, I put it in the chat earlier. If you go to the last chapter
of what they call Leviticus, they do give you a menu or what would you call it, a price sheet
or an index of what people should be worth. By the way, after seven years, you were let go but
if you really liked the household and you wanted to stay because the mastership was good and you
were well taken care of, you stood at the threshold of the master's house and he pierced your left ear
and then you were a slave for life. Also, there were laws there if you were to hurt a slave and
break his tooth, you set him free and all these things. You weren't to abuse if you look at the
laws of slavery in ancient days. If you beat a slave and you hurt him, he lost an eye or broke
a tooth from the beating or whatever he was to be granted. So, anyone could look this up, the laws
of slavery. Now, we're talking about law now. Now, legal is different. Legal slavery, now legal is
what you agree, legal is the legal system, legal society as you folks know it came together in
ancient Greece and I think we gave the history on that. Do you remember the history we gave on that,
or should I reiterate it real quick? I think you should go over it again real quick. I do recall
it. I mean, I know what it boils down to but we also have a caller by the way. So, let's bring him
in. Okay, let's do that. Apparently, it's an anonymous caller but and you know, I go to unmute
the anonymous caller and they're gone. Sorry. Maybe it's anonymous. Okay, all right. Well,
the thing and when I say legal, it's not a universal in a sense of pertaining the law
but the way that it's practiced in the convention today, just like the medical system, if you look
at any medical book, you're going to see a hell of a lot of Greek words in there, aren't you?
Right? They're using the Greek academic convention. Now, the legal society is using the same
convention. Now, what happened in ancient Greece was that industry, government, people like that,
when they had controversies and things they had to resolve, they called on groups of scholars
that were well-versed in those fields and could resolve rationally the conflict, right?
And they were known as the, let's say, the lawyers, right? But they were, you know,
they were just like geeks or whatever, you know. So, these guys spent their whole life studying
and they would go into these situations, let's say, where in today's, let's use today's common
parlance, there were billions involved. Here's this guy comes in, he solves it all and they
throw him like, you know, pennies, you know. And he's like, these scholars got together and said,
you notice how these real powerful and wealthy people, you know, they're always calling us,
we're solving their problems and we're like kind of living a very modest lifestyle. I think it's
time for us to get wealthy. And so, what they did was they got together and when these courts
had formed and they would go out and get some official capacity just to find anyone on the
street and accuse them of something and charge them with a crime that they didn't commit and
then run them through their court system as if they were guilty, just to show that they can do
that using parlor tricks, trickery of words, meanings and things like that, right? And they
were able to do that and they did that so much that people started paying them just to leave
them alone. It's called a retainer. So, wealthy people started coming to them and said, listen,
just don't do that. Here's X amount of money per month or every moon just to leave me alone. Or
let me give you X amount of money so you could come within my circle to prevent some of this
from happening, just like corporations have lawyers on retainer, right? And if you ever see
attorneys when you challenge, they say, we're going to do, we're going to take legal action
against you. It's like, it's just stupid stuff. This system still exists today, just like the
medical system is based on the Hippocratic Oath, allegedly, and still using the Greek
Convention. You're still under the Greek system, not the Roman system. So, this is how it's come
forward. But what's happened through time, it's always the chief goddess of that they adopted was
D.I.K.E. And she had no desire for men, by the way. That's why women that don't have desire for
men are still called D.I.K.E.s. But anyway, and then those from Mott, and then it became Justicia.
A lot of the emperors are called known as Justinians. They're very influential.
Now, it's the crown and all that. So, the purpose of the legal society is all voluntary. You have
to agree to it. But the thing is, you don't know what you're saying. You don't know what these
words mean. In English, you have two languages in English. You have legalese and then common
English. You might have classical English. But people use words they don't know what they mean
when you go into the legal environment. And by the way, the legal environment represents,
it's one of the manifestations of the chief adversary on the planet. That's how you know.
That's how they operate, meaning Satan. Right. Now, hang on just a second because
I think our anonymous caller is back. This is very fascinating, though, and I'm appreciating it.
But let's bring the anonymous caller on. And there we go. Anonymous caller,
you're on with Ocelli and the Greek. Going once, going twice.
Thank you. All right. We'll try again. I'm gone. Okay. Sorry.
All right. That's fine. So, this is the legal aspect of it. It's based on things that you don't
know that you agree to. And then once you discover it later that you were tricked, they say, well,
you agreed to it. Now, if you talk about legal slavery, what did we refer? Because it always
has a stem. Anything that's corrupted has to resemble something that's not to be accepted.
Right. Like a counterfeit note has to resemble what they call a note that's authoritatively
printed. This is also why people that make presentations often mix the truth with the
lie in order to present it as something that is truth and whole. They often mix real facts and
real things with the BS, if you will. A Trojan horse type deal, maybe sometimes.
Yeah. It'll have a covering of it. So, what you have with the legal society, and by the way,
legal society is influential. If you go to the medical society and they tell you we just do this
and if you say, well, what about this? Well, legally, I can't tell you that, right? The same
with the scientists. They will legally can't. So, basically, these guys are running the whole show,
just like they intended to run everything back in those days, right? Because when these people
of great wealth that had problems came to them, it was any field, basically, and they were able
to help. So, this is the same today, whether you're looking at the medical industry, the
religious industry, the food industry, scientific industry, they always have what? A legal department.
By the way, folks, when you hear stuff about the Federal Reserve Bank, just to throw this in there,
the Federal Reserve Bank closed down and was out of the country by 1934. What you're left with
is called the Federal Reserve System. It's a system of moving paper and if you go to any bank
or whatever, they can't make a decision unless they consult the what department? The legal department.
So, now, you know, even the president carried what they called the football, right? Where you push
the button. You know, he doesn't do that unless he consults what? The JAG, right? In the military,
right? The legal department. So, you'll see this. This is how the adversary or, you know, the
spiritual adversary controls through these people. That's why people say, you know, you have
all these problems in society. No, no. You just walk down the street. If you have a law office,
a church and a medical clinic, you got problems. It doesn't matter if it's, you know, it's a little
mainstream thing, a little main street city in the middle of nowhere or a main city. You got
these institutions. They are very rigid and very heartless and very cruel for a reason and we've
discussed the reasons why. It's because they're there to accommodate people. So, until people
don't want to be accommodated by anymore, you're going to have these problems. And I wouldn't say
that is the absolute root but it is the manifestation of the root. The first thing that
comes out of the soil, let's say. So, the legal aspect of slavery is slavery would be voluntary
or cognizant. Back in lawful slavery, if you asked anyone if you're a slave, they would clearly tell
you yes or no. And they were known as such. But now, the concept of servitude is very ambiguous,
very, very ambiguous. It's being applied constantly in the prison system,
constantly, the status. It's being applied constantly in commerce, right? And one of
the ways that they drag you into that legal status of slavery is by calling you a debtor
because a debtor or a vagabond has no right or no standing in their court.
Like, for example, this is going to be a little side note but this ties all together because
there's no simple answer to all these things. This is not like a sitcom or something, you know,
or abandon this or get rid of this thing and it fixes anything. But, you know, the White Star,
which became Cunard Lines, I believe, which was what they call the Titanic when it went down, right?
What they did was in order to shed liability from all those people, you know, because they have a
big liability, let's say, lawsuits for financial damages, right? Let's say money damages the White
Star Line. So what they did, their attorneys, was they sent a small laundry bill for a penny to all
the passengers there. Now, if you paid the penny, the family did, you admitted to being a debtor.
So you have no status to sue. If you didn't pay the penny, you were listed as a defaulter and you
had no status to sue. Think about that for a minute, how conniving this is. I think you and I,
you and I once did a private call in Australia about land grab, how the United States got land
by suing the description, right? When they sent out Daniel Boone and all the explorers and they
described everyone, you know, they're memorialized as these heroes, these adventurers. No, no, no.
They went out to come back with descriptions of the mountain ranges and the plains and the people
and the rivers and the animals. And then the attorneys went to work and they knitted it all
together and termed what's called a legal description. And then they sued the description.
And because no one came to answer, they claimed it because the description was libelous and in
default. Well, it seems like I recall that from the money topic, because money representing land,
et cetera, et cetera. I think that was affordable land. So therefore, that was the I think that was
a public presentation, actually. Yes, it was. Oh, that's right. Yeah. Either way,
there's some it was posted once on just Greek speak blog or something. The audio is not available,
but this has never been discussed as far as I know. And anyone could actually look it up. There
was a lot of stuff that's been on the Internet that I've referenced, let's say, a decade ago
that is no longer there. Like, for example, I used to have easy access to what's called the
uniform slave codes of 1750. They're no longer online. And the reason why I'm bringing that
up is because 1750, all the let's say states, if you did if you were a slave in one state and did
something, it was it was like a slap on the wrist. But another state, it was a death penalty. So all
the states said we need to have a uniform code here because, you know, what they did, that's
where if you ever heard of what's called a liquor license or a driver's license or a passport,
that's where those things were developed. If a slave were to travel 15 miles beyond the past
plantation, he needed a passport. That's why where are the international water markers set
off the coast? How many miles? Fifteen miles. Right. Yeah. If he was in a wagon by himself,
he needed a license to travel. He needed a license to get married. Have you ever heard of a marriage
license? All these things I just mentioned came out of the uniform slave codes of 1750,
and you can't find them online anymore. So isn't that interesting, by the way?
You know, one more time. We have that anonymous caller, I think, back again. Let's try.
Maybe they were having a technical issue.
Hello. A little musical break. Apparently.
All right. Thank you. That's pretty good. Okay. So that's a little comical interlude there.
So, yeah, the other thing I was saying regarding that there was a speech that I think Thomas
Jefferson made regarding the returning of these explorers, how he would make him and his posterity
wealthy beyond their belief on a national level. You know, so if anyone could find that speech,
I think it was in the late 1700s or early 1800s when these explorers came back, how they would
really expand beyond belief, wealth, and, you know, create it. So the legal aspect of it is very,
very, very, very tricky. Now, this goes into what's called most of the people that have
slave status and they don't know it have gotten it through what? Pranking. You ever heard of that
term? Yeah. A prank is a ludicrous trick. And yeah, and this is how it works. Like, you know,
a prankster offers you a chair with a thumbtack on it and you say, I don't feel like sitting.
Well, come on, you look a little tired. Why don't you sit down and you sit down and you jump up
because you've just been punctured by a thumbtack and he starts laughing and you ask him why you
did that as well. You sat down on your own. Well, you kind of convinced me a little. And why did you
put the thumbtack? Well, because it's funny. That's all. So if you ever deal with anyone in the legal
society, whether it's really small, the guys with the badges or the guns or the guys with the
suitcases or the guys with the black robes, at the end of the day, no matter what they do, they got a
kick out of it. And also they got a lot of credit out of it. Right. So and the same with the
religious authorities, the same with the medical authorities, they really got a kick out of it.
I mean, here's the thing. If you know anyone that is really functional in the medical system and I
mean, you know, where they work with people, not just prescribed. If you go to their house in their
garage or their basement, they've got boxes floor to ceiling on lawsuits against them for
for malpractice and negligence suits. And you're thinking like maybe a stack half inch high is
enough to end their career. Right. But these guys got tens and thousands of pages against them and
they're still functioning. Why? Right. Because it's pranking and you folks love it. How do. Well,
you may not love it. You may not know you love it, but it sure looks like you do. So anyway,
because you're still encouraging children to go into those fields. This is how you know you're
being set up to be, quote unquote, legally enslaved or prank drive down the street.
You see a university that's functioning perfect. They put out a big crop, a new crop every year
to be harvested, don't they? So this is this is might sound harsh and it might sound subjective,
but I assure you it's not. Anyone visiting this planet from somewhere else can see this as as
you would see the nose on your face permitted that you have one. So and by the way, I did look online
a little bit and I do see that there are some of these codes from like, say, 1740 in particular
states and provinces. But I don't see the uniform slave codes of 1750 is the doctrine that was put
together. Yeah, I see. I see one in 1740 and like North Carolina, I think it is. This is no, it
wouldn't be one state. It was called the Uniform Slave Codes of 1750. Yeah, I see South Carolina.
I see. You know, it probably is. They all came together. They had a convention. Yeah. OK, so
because you'll find blaringly that's where passports came from. Driver's license, liquor,
marriage license. Are those things? Oh, yeah. So when you talk about slavery, I mean,
what is that? You know, it's but here's the thing, folks. Is it true or is it not true that pretty
much the society on this planet right now can easily be described by understanding what cannibals,
birthdays and dolls have in common? Is it true or not true? Well, to me, that is one of the most
fascinating things that you ever said. And it is part of the reality, not just that you said it,
but as part of the reality. Right. So if you're going to describe a society like that is being
tricked into doing things that they don't like and which could be defined as slavery, legally
a surprise, you know, if they've legitimized. Would you also is it true or not true that
humanity has legitimized savagery right now? Well, see, that's my contention that by consent.
OK, that word consent by contract. Effectively, we've legitimized a whole bunch of things
that if you were asked bluntly to support them, you would not, which is a bizarre state of being
to me. Right. And this is this. Do you think abolishing the Fed or getting rid of some
international billionaire that's funding color revolutions or getting rid of vaccines or whatever
are going to change any of this? No, it's not. You know, I figure something else arise to take
its place because it has a place. Could it be that could it be that let's say there's a let's
say there is a car with five people going down a highway and it overturns and starts to go on fire.
Do you think they can help themselves or do you think it'd be best if others came in and help them
out? Because there may be two. They're all unconscious in the car upside down after it
hit a tree. There's not much they can do until one until a few of them start waking up and they
notice they can't get out of the car. Right. That's a metaphor. Imagine this car going down
the road with seven billion plus people and it's just got smacked into a tree. They can't help
themselves. That's why the gods are going to do it and they're going to send a mop up crew and
all the stuff that people consider sacred and righteous is going to end up in the rinse bucket.
And that's going to be one hell of an event to see. And even when, by the way,
Chaka, we said because this is the sixth episode addressing mankind. And yes, that's you folks.
Do you know when all these things are happening, they're still going to be, you know, that river
in Egypt, what's it called? A big river. Talking about denial. Yeah. Denial. Denial.
Yeah. Yes. No, I got you. And it seems as though that's going to be part of the natural condition
based on what it is I'm observing. This lack of communication. So even if there is someone,
strangely enough, reporting that this is happening, I fear that it may not be understood,
recognized, communicated, despite the fact that they have all the opportunities to do so. It's
just not going to happen. How about that? Let's throw. Yeah. OK. Yeah. Well,
that's more general. You want to get more specific?
Yeah. Last time we ended off with maybe talking about how Iran is going to kind of
chummy up to some other national entities that it's viewed as an opponent or adversary or enemy
of right now, which is going to be kind of a surprise. But here's the other aspect of it.
That part of the way, just by the way, one of the most often mentioned topics
inside conversations regarding this show is the Middle East Union.
Should be so. And it won't be it won't be it won't be labeled as such, but it will come together
by description as such. If you're describing what's going on, it'll always going to fight
because or have they'll eat together, work together and walk together, but they won't
be able to sleep together. That's a term in the Middle East, by the way. Sleep together means
rest together in rest. And what you're going to see is pay attention to the eastern Mediterranean
in the next two years or less. Eastern Mediterranean would be the Levant. We might
say like central like area of Israel near Jerusalem. Pay attention to more northern
Lebanon, a little more inland to Jordan. This is going to be very dynamic time period
because ever since this time period started around what you call 2003, which by the way,
you know how we say we're in the credits that started around 1998. It really didn't kick in
until five years later because there's always five points of interest or a rest period of five before
man comes on the scene. So you got to add that five and then you got to add four seven year periods
with a three and a half year period and that's how this credits roll up. Years ago, I wouldn't say
this in public, but why the hell not, right? So what you're going to see is all these events
that have been going on since let's say 2001, which is the middle of that five year period,
all the way to now and another year is going to start brewing up in what you call central
part of that eastern Mediterranean, western Levant area. You're going to have to really
see some things before they come because when they come, people are going to be really whipped
into a lather. Do you remember hearing how people got whipped into a lather when every two years or
so, the Israelis are bombing the Palestinians, right? From the flotilla to the bombing wall,
there's going to be some very serious action in that area regarding those two groups and things.
So we might discuss that a little bit more and that will lead to an edifice that will be
prepared to be put up that hasn't been up for over two millennia and a preparation of it.
And also, in order for it to be on the planet, there has to be acknowledgement of who and what
it's for and I assure you, it has absolutely nothing to do with any of the religions
until they start getting their act together and looking at what
supposedly the religion is supposed to be based on. In other words, they're going to need really
new ideas and the only way you get a new idea is by reading a really old book.
So there's going to be some interesting stuff coming. We still have this year,
what they call, which by the way, the year really doesn't start till the spring. So this
thing that the people call the New Year's that they just had, I don't know, would you say that's
a little early? Yeah, but it doesn't matter. If something happens while you're sleeping,
you don't really notice till later when you wake up anyway. But what you folks might wake up to is
that the New Year really starts around spring. I believe we've discussed how that works. A new
year starts in the spring, ends in the fall, and the winter is an intermediate time.
So yeah, you just watch what's going on around you. The change is always coming. Just like we
discussed last week, everything's got a front and a back, a left and a right, a top, a bottom,
and an inside and an out. Guess what? All those things that we mentioned, those points of view
or perspectives that you can grab and use, all those things are always in constant change.
Even just changing the location of an object changes the object because it can no longer
be defined by its location. So you have a lot of change happening and how much of it do you
want to grab? The other thing is the advice to give is to seek out information that is based
on something. When you hear words, someone using words, whether it's kid, wisdom, faith,
God or whatever, listen to them and see if they're using it how the word was meant to be used.
And if they're not, guess what they're doing? They're just dummy loading you, folks.
Or you might just have a little voice in your head saying, when are they going to shut up so
I can get the microphone and say what I want to say? But anyway, that's the way things are going
as I see. Well, there you go. And that sort of does sum things up. I mean, after all,
men have a left, a right, a top, a bottom, an inside and an outside, too, don't they?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. And mankind here, well, you got to remember the number six is vital.
And from an ethereal point of view or a cosmic point of view or divine point of view,
when you see that coming around. So, you know, I think no matter how we look at mankind from
that perspective, you'll see that is there's divisions of six typically that pronounced
themselves through it. Well, absolutely. And, you know, we are running low on time. I do see
an anonymous caller back. I'm almost ready to take it again. Yeah, I think we don't have much time
to go, but that's all right. We actually there's there's the thing is there's never it's interesting
is there's never enough time. But there but sometimes we get these little little bits at
the end or we could just take a breather, even though it's right before the end, which is good
for a short call. But then if the answer is somewhat long winded, it won't really work too
well. But the thing is, also, we spoke about last week about discernment and objective versus
subjective. So these are all cumulative. But the point here was to bring up the point of six and
being aspect of mankind and also slavery. I think we covered the slavery part.
People can go on on their own, but we're giving more of an objective point of view of what's going
on with slavery. The thing is, it's really difficult to overcome the current convention or
style or fad. Like, you know, if you're probably old enough, do you remember yourself or others
showing you photos from the early 70s when they wore those tacky polyester patterns with the big
lapels? You know, everyone, everyone thought they were so cool. It was so hip. But now it's like
you don't really it's so funky. And so I mean, funky in a bad way. It's just really just
aesthetically ugly. So many of the things that people are engaged in now seriously will find
to be such in the future. So why not just be reserved and pursue things that seem to be more
enduring than fad like, you know, I mean, there's a couple of people still online saying we should
all going to die from Fukushima or Fukushima and all these other things. So what's, you know,
still a lot of dummy loading going on. But the thing is, for people is if you hear information,
see information, just see what it's based on. And usually it's listed or somehow,
would you say exposed or divulged or to you there. So you have to pay attention.
Hmm. Yeah, that's true. Look, all things which are seen as occult end up being revealed at
some point or other. And I could categorize a lot of the information that that has
recently seemed to have come to light, although may have always been there in one way or another.
Yeah, the problem that I see, well, right now, this is the stream that we're on the internet
radio or even mainstream or even bookstores. A lot of these people that do publish and put out
occult knowledge or known as such, you know, all you got to do is get a bunch of tattoos,
a big black coat and a funky glasses in Europe. You say you're a cult and everyone's like,
yeah, or say you're a witch or say you're this or a shaman or a wizard.
And everyone's like, yeah. The thing is, most of this, it's OK to listen to that,
but check up on them and you'll find that they don't know what they're talking about
because people that are well versed in those things, guess what? They're not public.
That's the catch 22. Why? Because in order to be well versed in the powers of the occult,
let's say, or the natural things, you don't make yourself public because you look at the audience
and you're like, I can't share this with anybody. And the reason we come on here and say these
things to some extent is to help the mindset and how to discern what's out there. I'm not an occult
practitioner of anything. I pretty much if you want to know, excuse me, what I'm and what I do
and what I think, just listen to what I'm saying. You don't have to read into it much. You could
read out of it. It's just about separating yourself from all of it and that mean all of it
and finding out what's lawful. Which is not that hard. Well, there you have it. I mean,
and after all, nobody is going to really speak profoundly on any of these sort of practices,
which you've kind of described in a general sense in public anyway, because my understanding is
the rule always prevails that you do not share this information with the uninitiated.
That's right. The principles of all these things are still underlining everywhere anyway. So
all right, everybody. Thank you. Absolutely. That puts a fine point on the end of chapter six
of Ocelli and the Greek here on American Freedom Radio. We do appreciate your time.
And hopefully you have figured out what your number is. Take care, Greek. All right. Thank you.