So just after 10 PM, according to the wind up toy that we call a clock or
the digital representation thereof, this is Ocelli and the Greek broadcast
live on American freedom radio at American freedom, radio.com.
I didn't mention what day it is.
Generally speaking where I'm sitting, it is still called a Thor's day or a
Thursday, uh, on the Pope's work schedule.
But by observation, Greek, what day is it?
Well, you know, sometimes it's helpful to just try to guess, you know, like
everything else seems like everyone else is guessing about everything.
So, uh, right.
Uh, it, and then when, and guessing isn't good enough, you got to follow
something and there you go.
That's why the Pope's work schedule works so well.
Before we get into that, I want to suggest that, uh, calling people
morons, by the way, is, is not a pejorative.
It's an accurate term in regarding, um, certain condition, mental condition.
And the, uh, you're starting right at the gate.
Right.
But, uh, remember there's also a lascivious comment we make every week.
So anyway, uh, the, the, uh, uh, they're very, uh, uh, gracious to say it's
around 12 years old, but I've had a lot of discussions about, um, uh, uh, you
know, uh, many things this week.
And it's a maturity problem.
As you can see, really most people stop maturing at around nine and he, you know,
even these old farts that you see still around the world, they, they really have
stopped growing spiritually or mentally around nine years old.
So, you know, when we talk about the Pope's work schedule, the wind up
toil and stuff, you think it's, it's pretty fitting, don't you think?
I mean, uh, uh, anyway, but anyway, let's get back to the day that you asked.
Um, uh, things aren't lining up for the first month and we already had a 12 months.
So what do you think it's a, where it's, it's the eighth day of the 13 months.
Yeah.
I was going to say, it appears that we have a 13th month, uh, that much I can
figure out, but eighth day, you think?
Yeah.
But how'd you figure it out?
Well, as we rolled up the 12th, a month or a couple of weeks.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, yeah.
So, so that's the whole thing is, is, uh, uh, if we were told this, like tying shoe,
could you imagine you never learned how to, no one ever showed you how to tie
shoelaces that well, you know, you could figure it out, you know, but if no one
ever showed you how to tie shoelaces, can you imagine how dyslexic and retarded
you'd feel if you try to learn it at 40 or 30, you know, so this time thing is,
um, it doesn't really matter because here's the thing.
Well, for most, like, for example, let's go back to the moron thing.
When I call people morons, it's because I'm being objective, right?
Um, and on the other hand, uh, you, you actually, there's an old Swahili
proverb, when you throw a stone, the dog that it hits yelps, right?
Most people don't like it because it's fitting, but a lot of people that are
wondering like, what the hell is something wrong with me?
Or is it all these idiots around me?
Yeah.
It's all the idiots around you.
You see?
So, um, I'm speaking for the people who want to say it.
Maybe they don't got the balls to say it, right?
I like to say in fact, he's, but so anyway, the point, the point here, the
point here is the planet is full of idiots and this has been written
about thousands of years ago.
Now, why would you want to give groom a society that is raised in being
pranked, uh, no transfer of knowledge, sort of a low self-esteem, why would
you want to give them the ability to operate objectively and autonomously?
In other words, the tools that they can, in other words, impart the tools to
people within a society where they could be self-sufficient, why would you do that?
How are you, how are you going to take advantage of them?
Of them.
If you do that, if people understand what is a tree, what is a blade of grass,
the movements of the fish, how to work with metal, how to work with fiber, how
to work with, you know, chemistry and all this stuff, which doesn't take much, by
the way, um, they don't eat much.
Before we descend too much further into morons, idiots, and yes, indeed.
I think that retarded is actually a term which is, you know, describes
something in a scientific sense.
And, and these terms are quantitative, idiot and moron are quantitative.
I mean, you can actually attach them to a particular level of intelligence, uh, based
on the IQ test, which is a whole other topic before we go into that though.
Maybe we should let people know that they can join into the show.
If, uh, if they still want to do that, uh, via a couple of conventions, why don't
you start with the Skype convention?
Okay.
Well, Skype convention, it would be Ocelli and the Greek and Ocelli is O C H E L L I.
And, you know, I've been thinking about that a little bit.
Uh, the C you just, you didn't need the H really because it's Italian, but, uh, or
something like that.
So what about the phone number on the, uh, on the, what they call a proverbial
area code and seven digits would be.
Well, yeah, absolutely.
The look and, and, uh, to join that, you just got to send a request to that Skype,
which you're in control of and, uh, you will accept it and bring them on into
the show as we go further, right.
And why not?
Okay.
Now, the other way to do it is through the convention known as a telephone.
So if you are not too much of an idiot, a moron, or possibly too retarded to dial a
telephone 2 1 8 3 3 9 8 5 2 5 2 1 8 3 3 9 8 5 2 5.
And then you'll follow a direction, which will allow you to be added into the call,
which I have the board for, and I can add you right on in and I'll just identify you
by area code.
And, uh, I don't know, you want to give the guidelines or should we bother with that?
What do you think?
Yeah.
Real quick, simple.
They're basically two guidelines that would benefit anyone in any, any forum or
any conversation.
Don't talk about yourself, even though people think they say seem interested.
They really don't.
They're waiting for you to finish saying what you're saying.
And so you could shut up and they could tell you what they want to say.
So if you decide to call in, I share something worthwhile.
And the second thing is if you're under the influence, as they say of anything, you may
not think that you sound like you are under the influence or not, but everyone else
clearly can't tell.
So let's just say, be sober at this point.
If you're deciding to call it, what do you think?
That sounds fair enough.
Uh, and again, 2 1 8 3 3 9 8 5 2 5, just in case I said it too quickly the first few
times.
So back to what you were discussing.
Yeah, yeah.
The whole thing is it's not about the, again, people take it as pejorative, but most
people are quite happy, at least the ones that have messaged on the uncommon sense of
the uncommon radio sites, uh, are quite pleased with the commentary.
But on the, on the other hand, um, there are so many things to discuss that go within
the lines of, let's say lawful timekeeping.
Right.
I mean, what, what does that matter?
You know, when you think about it, most people use the windup toy in the calendar to
go to work, right?
Because they're part of some kind of organized corporate structure or corporate
culture that, uh, you have to use that.
And that's fine.
Um, but the, the, the trees, the birds, the rivers, the fish, you know, the planets and
all that don't go on that.
Right.
So if you're relating from the most common base level with all of those other things
in nature or in a professional capacity, like let's say a commercial fisherman, right?
A commercial fisherman can actually spot the, the migration and transmigration of fish
using lawful timekeeping.
But with the Pope's work schedule, it falls apart.
They need these, they need these, uh, these radar and sonar things, you know, and, uh,
then they're guessing.
So what does this do?
Okay.
There are many things regarding health, regarding law, regarding, uh, culture that
people can discuss and impart to each other that make them self-sufficient.
Would you, what's another term for self-sufficient?
I mean, they're empowered to the point where they don't feel like they are dependent on,
um, another group or anyone else, let's say at large, um, meaning like a stranger,
right, to proceed with their lives.
I mean, um, I hear people, parents pranking their children, like, Oh, the child looks
like it has a fever.
We got to go to the hospital.
I mean, what would you do if, you know, don't you know that hospitals were set up
hundreds of years ago for, there were places to send people to die, hospice,
hospital.
I mean, so anyway, um, the whole thing is there is a lot to discuss, right?
But this is a public forum.
And many times I say this is, we're having a private conversation that just happens
to be on a minor internet radio platform.
So let's just, you know, uh, continue that way.
Uh, uh, but there are so many things that can be discussed that make people feel
less dependent upon a pretty, now there's a ridiculous system.
And when I say ridiculous system, there's nothing wrong with having a legal society.
There's nothing wrong with having a medical society and education society is
scientific society, military on and on and on nothing wrong with it.
But the quality of what they're offering is so piss poor, right?
Just like a character, the character of humanity at this point is very piss poor.
It doesn't matter if you're in America, in Russia, Iraq, Afghanistan, Chad,
Columbia, it doesn't matter what Japan, the character, why?
One of the things to consider is that poor quality food and poor quality drink
or, you know, intake, nutritive intake, when it reaches a low quality, it affects
the character of the individual character, meaning their mind, right?
What, what denotes a character, right?
It's the spirit, the mind.
And, uh, and then you have, uh, the, a deliberate, you see, it's not a
dumbing down, it's a numbing down and people are not being dumbed down.
They're being dumbed up because when you, when you down something where
let's say it's diminishing, so they're being dumbed up, not dumbed down.
So even that's backwards.
So anyway, uh, coin that if you want, uh, you're tired of being dumbed up, right?
What does dumbed up mean?
You know, well, think about it when you're dumbing down, it sounds
like the dumbiness is going down, but I think the dumbiness is going up.
So they're being dumbed up and numbed up, right?
Do you get numbed up at the dentist?
You get numbed down, you get numbed up.
So the dumbing up is increasing, right?
And the numbing up is increasing, but there still is a small,
again, it's a quantitative consideration.
So if it's on its way up, it's increasing.
So if you're, if the dumbness is increasing, then you're being
dumbed up, not dumbed down.
And if you're being dumbed down, then the dumbness is decreasing.
That's right.
So it doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, no, the, the, the, the convention doesn't make sense, does it?
Cause people say, oh, everyone's so dumbed down.
I'm like, well, I'm kind of scratching my head.
I'm like, are they really, I'm going to leave that alone.
Let's just call them numbed, you know?
So there's a lot to be done.
Um, let's say in the relative short time, you know, time, meaning people
think, you know, there's all this time left when there, there is just plenty
of time left, you know, it's going to be, the perception of time is going
to be whittled down and played around with, you know, during this time period
where humanity is being set up, right.
And just like any set up people, you know, whoever's involved in the
setup, you know, the set up E doesn't know they're being set up.
So I don't even know why we're talking, but here's the telling people what's
coming down the pike in, in general or specific terms, does it make any sense?
Because what does it have to do with them?
Right.
And here's where it gets strange too, because one would wonder listening to
the speaker objectively, not even talking about you specifically, but just taking
you as a spoken word object, you know, as a sonic entity, as you like to say, um,
you know, you are, again, objectively speaking, you're within the realm of the
prevailing condition as well.
So aren't you subject to the same problems that everyone else being stupid
everywhere else, or I'm not stupid.
That wasn't the word you used, but just in general,
yeah, but, but here's the thing.
Let's go back.
You can, we can answer that very easily.
Uh, you just go back to the first rule of people calling in, you don't call in
and say, Oh, I feel so dumbed down.
Oh, I feel a part of everything else.
Oh, I'm just also subject to what you guys are.
Who cares?
The reason for the Greek speaking is because no one else is saying it.
And we're not just saying it because it's like Dada or beatnik stuff.
I don't know if you've ever heard of Marcel Duchamp, he started the Dada
movement.
Um, and yeah, actually carried his ladder, you know, he's a pretty famous artist
and a famous chess player.
The art community thought he was a chess player and the chess player thought he was
an artist.
It was strange, but he started the Dada movement where he actually put the cart in
front of the horse in the 1920s and did a really slow motion black and white film.
And, and on the, on his way to a, an art exhibit that he didn't want to go to
actually on, on his way home from grocery shopping a while back, uh, he was
reminded that he had an art exhibit that afternoon and he was like, okay, really?
Yeah.
Cause he didn't like the artists being trained.
You know, he thought it should be free forming.
Is he, why should you go to school?
If you're an artist, like a plumber or an engineer should be more free flowing.
Well, he was reminded of an art exhibit, you know, that he was made aware of, you
know, six months before he would be one of the main displays and he's like, shit,
you know, I really don't care about it.
But, so what he did is he went up to the plumbing supply on Houston street and West
Broadway and bought a urinal and screwed it to a piece of plywood and submitted it.
And it won the competition and all the art community went wild and they asked
him what inspired to do that.
He says, are you joking?
I hate these exhibits.
I just figured I'd give you a piss pot and you'll tell me it's beautiful.
Right.
So this is, this is an, this is what, what's going on right now, because you
know, we got to show, you know, we got to, what are we going to talk about?
Who are we going to interview?
Who's going to be the guest, you know, all this other stuff.
Screw that.
How about just come out and say what needs to be said.
But, you know, when, when involved in the spoken word, uh, you know,
performances in the nineties, I got to tell you that there were, uh, there were
guys that are reminiscent of this artist you're talking about because, uh, they
would literally go up there and make nonsensical statements, uh, for the sake
of making a nonsensical statement, because they despise the idea of publicly
performing their poetry, which they felt needed to be experienced in a certain way.
We don't have to get into all that, but yeah.
Jack Kerouac and on and on and on.
Yeah.
Well like that, but, uh, you know, obviously guys whose names you're never
going to hear, but the thing is, I actually witnessed people doing this on
purpose where it was like, I did it actually just to sort of, uh, urinate on
the whole situation and yet, you know, thunderous applause or snapping of
fingers or whatever it was that was, you know, the convention in that place.
Right.
Always found that interesting.
Now, the point here, Chuck, is that when you do that, you're definitely going
to say what no one else is saying, right?
I mean, that's actually what I was getting at is that it was so bizarre and random
that yes, indeed it was English language, but it was just, you know, yeah.
And the cruise ship swallowed the monkey underneath the tree with the banana
peeling, you know, and it's like, none of that made any sort of sense, but sounded
as though it did and people would applaud.
Now, here's the thing, saying that's why the thing about coming here and saying
what no one else is saying is not the point, even though it could be, it's just
reporting.
So being subject to it is irrelevant because here's the point, I've said this
many times, if anyone was saying even anything close, I wouldn't be doing, I'd
just, you know, personal contacts or whatever, say, hey, this guy spoke this
week, listen to that or whatever, check this guy out or what this website is or
this, you know, I mean, here, this is some good stuff.
It can be objectified and it's not happening.
So just, you know, here's the thing, you can actually do a show or a
presentation publicly sonically on just how to keep time and then back it up with
all of the reoccurrences and things that actually work on that to help people like
commercial fishermen, farmers, people raising children, people in any field,
even dyes, people that work with dying clothing, but believe it or not, is
affected by movement of the moon, you know, like during the full moon
processes tend to emerge and grow.
And during the dark moon processes subside, like, for example, if you have a
metal plating outfit, like let's say plating, you know, sinks and sink faucets
and doorknobs and stuff, you're, you're, you know, they got all these parts made
and they dip them in this huge bath, you know, okay, well, your highest reject
rate is always during the dark moon, right?
And they don't know that.
They see it randomly and say, oh, we got a high reject rate.
And it comes around every 30 days or something.
So, you know, so, so, I mean, this is, we can actually do presentations on the
attributes, positive attributes on just keeping time.
And the other thing, food, food and water preparation.
Anything I, I recommend anyone up your quality of intake of nutrition and your
drink, whatever you're drinking, right?
And you'll see what happens to yourself.
I mean, clearer thinking and all that, you know, simple experiments and how
nutrition affects the body.
Have a child or yourself, even unruled paper, blank paper, write your name or
write something or sign the name, right?
Or something, have a meal of whatever and wait 15 minutes to a half an hour and
then write the name again and then compare the two and you'll notice how
different it is or if it's the same.
Children have them write something and then give them some chocolate pudding or
whatever that they request, right?
And have them write something again.
And I've seen a young girl write the word cat, C-A-T, like a six year old would
write it. And after the chocolate pudding, about a half an hour or 15 minutes for a
child, the C kind of like drooped.
It almost looked like an O.
The opening was instead of being on the side of the letter was at the bottom and
the A just became like a little thin line and the T just couldn't be crossed.
It was either, you know, crossed at the very bottom.
Like I was like, write it again.
And she wrote it again and it was the same reaction and compared to how it was
before, it just looked like a pretty good penmanship for a six year old.
So you can see how, for example, with pharmaceutical companies, when they do
commercials, if you I think they still do commercials on television, they give you
the warnings and they always discuss about the effects on the kidneys, the liver, the
heart, the spleen, whatever, the blood.
But they never tell you the effect on the brain.
You ever notice on the side effects?
They never tell you how it's going to affect the brain.
Never.
Well, on occasion, they talk about things that are, you know.
Affected with the brain, but yeah, not directly.
Yeah, yeah. The brain is an organ.
I mean, then we can break it down to the components.
But so so that's for those who are mechanistic, you know, you can see how food
intake is very important.
So anyway, but it's all intake and it's all external input.
And that's been discussed.
So so anyway, let's let's kill about another hour and a half.
We're here. Is there anything anyone wants to discuss?
They could call it in or I might even turn on the chat and see what's going on in that
mess. So and by the way, back when AFR got started again, I was like, got to get a
chat, man. You got to get a chat, you know, get feedback.
And it's like, oh, man, you know.
But anyway, so let's see what's going on.
Oh, yeah. And the chat room has grown a bit, you know, certain shows seem to get a bit
more chat activity than others.
Anyway, it is what it is.
Of course, there is a chat room at American Freedom Radio dot com.
If you go to the website, the front page and you, in fact, click on a little banner that
says live chat, you can join right on in through the chat tango convention.
How about that? I'm looking at a question that has
reoccurred in the chat a few times about the question of what is the name of the chief
deity? And they bring up, you know, things like Yahweh and Elohim and translations.
Yeah. Yeah. Elohim is not a name.
It's just a plural title.
It would be El and well, that's in the Hebrew convention, convention, Aramaic, Chaldean,
you know, the El or El is a single deity means emanator or, you know, they give you all kinds
of definitions. But the letter E and the letter L means to emanate Elohim is just plural.
And the name is Yahweh, as it can be pronounced, there's a if anyone's really, really
wants to get their their brain kind of racked up, the name is actually
in code described how to pronounce in the Book of Exodus when Moses is asked, Moses
asks, who should I say sent me, you know, and there's no burning bush, by the way, it was
there was an angel that stood between Moses and a bush and the bush was not did not get
consumed by his flame. So there's no burning.
But anyway, I would think we've discussed that before.
I almost made a lascivious joke there.
But go ahead. Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, well, there you go.
We got, yeah, one lascivious comment every it's appropriate.
OK, so and the scriptures, by the way, are lascivious.
They're not I shouldn't say because lascivious means inappropriately sexual that there are
appropriate. It's been sanitized, though, you know, in the versions that you get.
Right. So, yeah, the problem, again, with discussing anything super dynamic, like the
gods or 100 kilowatt dam, 100 million kilowatt dam or whatever, or the nature of the
sun or the nature of anything super dynamic, even dragsters or whatever, right, or
fancy cars. There's a problem with dynamics when you get into very high dynamics.
It scares people, you know.
No, absolutely. I was just letting people know about the call in number again.
So now that you start, OK, you sound like John Bonham with the kid didn't mean to that.
I do pound on the keyboard.
I apologize. I usually that's right for that.
Good. That's fine. Anyway.
Yeah, so the other problem with being dynamics is that humans have a very, very low
self-esteem. Your typical surface dwelling earth inhabits and it's got a very, very low
self-esteem. So it's at least make it just low self-esteem instead of very, very low
self-esteem. But so when you discuss certain subjects of importance that are easily
related and communicated and validated, it kind of tweaks people, rubs them the wrong
way because they don't feel like they are worth being entitled to have that kind of
information. Now, with their mouth, they're going to say something different.
We're talking about reading the mentality of the individual.
When you start laying out how simple something is, it can't be that.
Oh, because if it was that, then everybody, whether that you just there's a million
reasons why it's not that.
But they never look at what can be validated.
It's just the way surface dwelling earth inhabitants are.
So the low self-esteem is that that's very difficult to get over because they'll just
throw anything, you know, that, you know, for example, if you ever are in public near
university and you have a conversation with an academic or a professor, ask him if he
knows what the word means.
And instead of telling him it has like 70 percent more punch.
I don't know why, like the word nice, you know, instead of telling people what it
means, they have these little silly phones.
Just look it up right there on the spot, you know, and it has like 70 percent more
punch when they look it up themselves, you know, and then you're telling them it's
like you can't be telling them the truth.
Right. So so anyway, I often try and tell people to look things up themselves as
opposed to laying out exactly what it is.
And, you know, occasionally I'll give a link, but I don't exactly explain where to
find it. I'd rather they discover it for themselves.
It sticks with them much better.
Sure. So I'll show you the self-esteem example.
If you show an academic or professor what the word academic means, it's funny.
What they do is they glance at it, they read it, and then they quickly shut it off and
put it away and they want to change the subject.
This happens. It's a very consistent with them.
Oh, well, I don't know who right away they're trying to just ad hominem, disqualify
the source. Right.
They never will. They'll give you a million reasons indirectly why it doesn't mean
that, but they'll never acknowledge what is right there in front of them.
Right. Well, listen, with with that, we do have one caller on the line, so I want to
add them into the discussion once again.
218-339-8525 and Ocelli and the Greek on Skype.
So let's see what the caller who is under the anonymous title here has to say.
OK, we got I'm getting some noise.
How about you? Yeah, you're you're on the air caller, not hearing any.
OK. All righty, then.
So, yeah, so what's interesting, again, one thing I did, let's go jump around here.
We're kind of like running around the seashore around here a little bit and trying to
figure out what kind of shells we could pick up, put in a bag and take home and say,
hey, let's what we got, you know, going to the beach.
Right. The treasury secretary, I saw a little bit on the what they call the news, you
know, that TV show or that website they call the news and stuff.
And they got a treasury secretary and I just I like to go and kind of see what their
initial see what's the first thing any of these people do in their professional or
official capacity is they do the acceptance speech right after they're sworn in or
whatever. And that kind of sets the tone.
You get a sense of their character, you know, and try to go beyond, you know, how well
of a speaker they are or not.
Right. And see, you know, how much of it was written by, you know, a speechwriter and
how much of it they really mean.
I mean, you can tell someone means what they say or say is what they mean, you know.
So absolutely nothing said.
Right. On the acceptance speech, you know, I mean, in terms of vision or whatever.
Right. I just did a little quick YouTube.
So you know why?
Because the people don't want to hear about what money is about.
And let me just throw this in and we do a little bit of lasciviousness and money every
week. OK, listen, folks, when when you go and you have plastic, they're not money
cards, right? They're credit cards or debit cards.
Right. Because it's credit.
OK, so let's say someone goes and does a transaction and they swipe the card and it's
let's say at whatever retail place and it's one hundred bucks.
Right. That hundred bucks did not exist anywhere until you swiped that card.
Right. It didn't exist that the provider of the card or the quote unquote bank did not
have anything to give you or create for the transact.
It is created on the spot.
And actually, if you know how to read and code, when you have the signature line, it
says that I agree to do everything in the agreement, whatever, whatever.
So, you know, that's what you're agreeing to.
OK, so, for example, the legal society has got a really good grip on this.
And by the way, also another thing I heard in the news, the alleged president was
supposedly making a decree and then an alleged judge stopped it regarding
immigration. Now, many everyone kind of missed what's going on there.
Right. In code, what they're saying is it doesn't matter who's in office, the legal
society is running the country.
You see, it's a code because it's because if you go back and look at ancient stuff,
they say this planet is being run by the adversary, the chief adversary right now.
Now, who represents?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, because what does that have to do with the
manifestation of money on the spot?
Basically, because it wasn't created until that moment.
I mean, that's a statement.
But why keep going?
Because it doesn't matter.
It's it's not all it's actually true.
Speak to someone in legal society.
They will not want to discuss it.
Anyone legal side, you cannot pay for anything.
You settle it now in advertisements.
They say that. OK, but it's a tall statement.
But this this is very easily because physically, physically people load ATM
machines with something that exists ahead of time.
And that is the Federal Reserve notes.
They load them into an ATM machine.
It's not like it magically appears out of thin air, you know, so it is being
transferred physically from one place to the other.
But and then it gets into a strange thing when you're talking about the
accounting, maybe.
But the Federal Reserve, you shouldn't be using it unless you're a Federal Reserve
agent. And so you could load any other kind of contraband into a machine.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I'm not saying that those sheets couldn't distribute anything into them.
Right, right. So it could be a it could be it's like a cigarette machine or candy
bar machine in reverse.
Instead of it giving you the candy, you're giving it the candy.
But this is OK. When you load a note in there, they don't care about the note.
They care about the transaction.
What's what the bank has in its warehouse or its inventory is a list of
transaction numbers.
Whether you look there, there's a YouTube video.
Anyone can go see it. A guy's protesting property taxes, by the way.
Right. Not one penny of any taxes, federal, state, local, city in the past 70
years has paid for anything, not even a stripe in the street for the traffic lane.
Nothing. Right.
Because it's all economic theory.
And you still hear people saying taxpayer dollars.
Well, you got to say that because it's to tell people the truth about the matter.
It's like might as well be speaking Swahili in a Japanese radio.
Right. You can't. It just doesn't work.
It's like what they just don't get it.
And they can't at this point.
And actually, here's the thing.
They never will. They will just stop using it in the future.
And here's the interesting thing about it.
Humanity missed having basically a perfect society 70 years ago when everything
went into the credit system because all you had to do is really sign the name.
But here's the thing. It sounds confusing, right?
But you can't make it any simpler.
For example, you hear a lot of people complaining about the problems with the
dollar, quote unquote, but you never hear any anyone in politics or any leader of
a country or anyone discussing that at all.
It's not a problem because it doesn't exist.
All right. It's a it's a way to just keep you playing the game.
And it's a game that you die in, just like rollerball or something like that.
You will be killed for it if you say if they think you should be doing something
and you don't do it, wherever they are, whatever level of prankster.
But let's go back to the how the money is created in thin air.
It's not created. It's in there.
It's all credit. It's already every.
OK, this is how credit works.
A potluck or stone soup.
The agreement is, Chuck, you have a room with 10 people and the only way you get
into the room is by bringing something to eat.
So every one of those 10 people has to bring something to eat into the room.
That means that if that's a requirement for being there, there's food in the room,
you see, for everyone.
And there's enough for 10 people to eat.
And what if the requirement was you have to bring in order to enter that room, you
have to bring enough food for a year so that if you have 10 people in the room,
there's enough, you see, for 10 people for a year.
Because the way the credit system works is just like the casino.
You can't go to the casino and pull something out of the pocket and go to the
blackjack table or the roulette table.
You're given a lot of credit line, not a line of credit, credit line.
That's the birth certificate.
Right, and the rest of it is just one big show because they're still trying to
operate as if things are lawful and you missed the point as a society on this
planet. No one in position of power is concerned about anything economic.
The way you judge the character of an individual and the audience is by how
concerned they are about what is going on with economic policy or the economy.
Oh, the dollar is going to clap.
You got idiots out there making their living talking about the dollar every
month. It's supposed to collapse.
It never does. And they get more listeners.
Right. Well, look, I don't I don't see any of that going on in our chat room.
We're not getting phone calls or Skype messages.
So I will posit this question, which was asked a couple of times in the room.
Does the Greek use Federal Reserve notes?
No, I don't.
If so, OK, just checking.
Fair, fair enough question, I thought.
Go ahead. Now, you have to you have to acknowledge something as something to to
use it, don't you? Generally speaking, yeah.
Yeah. How can you use them?
But it's not even.
No. OK, here's another way to think about it.
There's something called efficiency, which is the opposite of loss.
Right. In other words, high level of loss is the opposite of high waste.
The opposite of waste is efficiency.
You're stuck in a system, OK, where if you realize what's going on, there is no
way it's going to change based on your desire.
OK, so you're going to have to learn to adapt with it, just like if you got a job
working in the sewer, cleaning the sewer for really good pay and you're going to do
it because you could retire in a year.
You're not going to change the sewer.
You're not expecting that you're going to go down the hole tomorrow and it's going to
be like spring water and smell like daisies.
You're pretty.
The chances of that happening is unusually to none.
Right. So what what is like here's a simple example.
If you learn to read with comprehension and listen with comprehension, you will see
that everything that we've been saying here, well, the Chilean, the Greek is true.
Right. And that's not a plausible statement.
That is, for example, if you read any document that is regarding finance, whether
it's private or public, meaning a public official, a private bank, nowhere is the
word pay being used.
Nowhere is the word money being used.
It's settling agreements, settling transactions, liabilities, assets.
Cannot, you know, OK, let's drop it, right.
It's not fair to discuss how money is created, right, because it's really taboo.
That's why it's not good to discuss the gods in detail.
It's taboo. Right.
In other words, taboo, meaning it shouldn't be done because it just doesn't make sense.
No matter how simple it is, it's a topic of there.
There are still many topics in society, including health, that once the topic is
brought up, the people that are listening immediately want to bring forward.
They dig into the deepest recesses of their minds, all the little filing cabinets, and
they take out everything that they've stored up regarding that subject.
And then they compare what they're hearing to that.
And if the comparison starts going down low, it's rejected.
Right. That's called it is a psycho is a term for that.
It's not plausible deniability.
Cognitive dissonance.
Right. So the the elements of of of subjects that are critical and important, like, for
example, money, health, timekeeping, farming, all that, many of these subjects that even
if you start discussing it in a narrow sense within the community, right, let's say you
went to a farmer's co-op and you stood up and talked about how to make the crops grow
better. When you're speaking to them regarding, let's say, irrigation, they're all
they're comparing what you're saying to what they've stored up.
You see, and that's the advantage that the convention has.
Right. You see, so once you establish something as a convention, right, like from
public education, media, houses of worship, whatever religion, once those conventions
are established, they become a reference point.
So the listener is always going back to these conventions and comparing what they're
now hearing to that.
Right. And now here's the thing.
There are quite a few people that have accepted that these things are we're not
beneficial. They're not malevolent and we need a better way, but they still cannot
avoid comparing. You see, and that's the hardest part.
Right. Well, you know, but I'm seeing the repeated question in the chat room once
again. What currency does the Greek use?
Well, you don't need currency, it's credit.
Fair enough. It's a credit based economy.
Look, I'm just placing the questions to you.
That's all I'm doing.
Actually, yeah.
Yeah. The whole thing is this.
It's again, that's the first rule.
You see, you see there's there's there's a desire.
That's the maybe that's why people aren't calling in.
What's the first rule?
Who cares what the Greek uses?
I don't care what you use.
I really don't. Because the whole thing is about what affects everyone, what can
anyone grab objectively?
You know, if you're using a tape measure, does it matter if it's brand A or brand B?
The thing is, does it conform to the standards?
Right. You know, like they have the what is it the standards in Washington, D.C.?
Right. They have what a foot is, what an inch is on platinum rod and all that.
Right. Well, yeah, but but there are, in fact, different qualities and tape measures.
Some of them fall apart when you use them once or twice.
Sure. But the standard, the references is it's got to be spot on within a certain
tolerance. So I like that word tolerance.
It's amazing people can even tolerate the Greek anymore.
But anyway, you know, so no lascivious comments yet.
All right. Yeah. OK, so, yeah.
So the thing goes on.
And here's Chuck, I'll ask you a question.
What the hell happened this week?
I really did not.
Anything noteworthy on your end or let's say not your end about you personally, but
anything happened that you want to bring up any topic that you think could be kicked
around?
No, I just I continue to notice the very same things that communication
is getting more and more scrambled, it seems, you know, that no one answers
questions, not the leadership nor the subservient individuals
in any particular place that I observe.
Uh, it appears, you know, even though I think I'm speaking in logical
terms, it doesn't mean that I'm being understood.
So I don't know. It's it's just.
OK, here's here's a thought and you can take this personally or not, if you already
know that they're not going to take clear, concise, rational, succinct communication,
go into it as if you already know that they're not willing to accept that or perform
on that level. Then how do you go into it?
Right. Think about it.
That's that's that's that's even harder, isn't it?
Right. Well, not really, because for the most part, I would not engage
were it not for my desire to communicate in a logical
fashion and for not for my belief that eventually I'll discover someone
who can. Uh, but that that that hope is fading
quickly. This is my report of my experience, by the way.
So, yeah, well, you know, this time period, you know, you ever notice at the end of
every seven year time period, there is this little bit of tension where people get a
little more numbed out, I should say, because when the transition comes, it's
seen as a relief and not something new.
You don't really you don't really notice it when you're numbed out, you know, you
just like, OK, let's just go with it now.
You know, this is how it is now.
Be more accurately numbed in, though, because you're getting numbed into a certain
state. There you go.
See, I caught me on that, too.
Thank you. No, no problem.
I was just thinking, you know, using the numbed up, numbed out possibly.
Yeah. But numbed up or numbed in.
Just using the same logic that made perfect sense earlier.
You know, the thing the thing that I would advise people is to consistently keep
hammering. How are you going to up the quality of your intake of food, water,
mental intake information?
Right. Also, the problem with taking in information is just like food when you
compare it to what you're used to eating.
Use food for an example.
One of the things that's very difficult for people to do is improve the quality of
their food. The reason why is because let's just say, would you wouldn't you say
that people perceive the world as being insecure, right?
Like there's no nothing really too sure.
We don't know what's going to happen today.
And but they view their diet, what they like to eat consistently as being a sense
of security. Oh, no.
And now I got to change that.
It's like pulling the rug from under their feet.
Right. So so that requires a lot of discipline.
Constantly improve. You can always make a better choice.
And that affects the character and the health and also the information intake.
Again, why do I need to hear something that doesn't conform to what I've already
heard? Now, a lot of people in alternative media think that they're providing a
better platform, but all they're doing is complaining about the information that's
been shoveled down the pipes or the wires by the mainstream.
That's what I've noticed pretty much, at least when I used to listen to it.
And I don't think it's changed much.
And if it has, I would have been made aware of maybe by someone communicating it
to me. But well, unfortunately, I'm a bit more of a jerk about this because I
complain about all of the information streams because of the inherent bias and
foolishness. I'm not talking about the stream.
I'm talking about the information that the alternative media is complaining about
the subject matter that the streams are putting out.
Oh, no, it's not the complaint.
Oh, I see. You're like the anti-complainer.
You're complaining about those that are complaining.
Well, no, what's what's strange to me is that is that I point out things.
Let me see if you can wrap your mind around this one.
People that are allegedly alternative are stating constantly that they're upset
with the, I hate to bring the politics into it, but just use it as an example,
the attacks on Trump because the mainstream media is against him.
OK. Now, what I find fascinating about that is the mainstream media is his
adversary. He's the adversary of the mainstream media, but they're being paid
to run commercials on his behalf in between their alleged complaints about him,
in which case they are also making sure to broadcast his image, his words, his
every movement, his tweet, whatever, constantly.
I question the entire concept of this.
In other words, the adversarial position is false.
The complaint about it is false.
The alleged alternative to it is false.
The whole thing is just a ridiculous stage show that is there just for the sake of
the stage show, in my estimation.
Well, there's a saying, Chuck, it's like I looked high and low, but obviously I
didn't look low enough.
Well, yeah, kind of.
But what's strange to me is that nobody questions the idea behind that.
Right. Yeah.
You brought up you brought up the alternative stream and how they complain about
the mainstream. I'm telling you that that when I discuss this kind of thing, I
posit that question and nobody wants to answer it.
You know, is it not all just the same crap anyway?
It's just a bunch of noise.
Right, because we're not.
Well, OK, well, listen, look, look, here's here's the thing again.
These people are alternative media.
Did they come from Mars or Alpha Centauri or are they surface dwelling Earth
inhabitants that happen to get a computer and a microphone and a slot in a state
and some kind of radio thing or website?
It's the second, right?
All right. So say no more.
This is your typical human stuff that's been discussed.
Anyone can go there.
There's a bunch of papers written in the 1500s about the criticism of the English
society. Right.
And if you just take the author and the date out, you read it and I'll say to you,
Chuck or anyone, you know, when was this written?
It looks like it was written about a week ago.
What do you mean? It's 500 years ago.
People are exactly the same in terms of these matters.
Right. So right.
If you just simply transpose some of the points of reference that are obviously
dated, you know, you change the horse and carriage methodology to,
you know, the automobile that they, you know, whatever that is, say when you want
to call it the horse drawn carriage without the horse, now the horseless carriage,
if you will. If you do stuff like that and, you know,
if you change things, it'll virtually look the same.
Yeah. Yeah. Right. And here's the thing.
The people are inherently subjective.
The reason why is because of the level of pranking that's done on them and
reinforced by force.
Like the parents start pranking them at a very young age, as we've mentioned
before, you know, the parents will tell the child, you know, I know the education
system, you don't learn anything, but you have to do it because I did it.
Right. And so on and so forth.
So the pranking starts at home and they get set up and then the pranking
continues in the public convention.
However, it would be the public schools or private schools.
This is done in the most elite private schools.
Also, folks, unless you happen to be going to an Elizabethan grammar school,
which is where you go to school between, let's say, seven and twelve.
And if you want more school after that, you go to university and you get a
degree at around 16 or 17 or so.
But that's those days are gone.
And even in those days, it was for those that, you know, could afford it or wanted
to afford it.
So they're inherently pregnant.
In other words, this inherent subjectiveness, you know, to the group think the
crowd mentality and the pranking is inherited, meaning
from generation to generation as the child is in the crib, let's say,
and being raised in a household.
They are this all this subjectiveness is being laid on them.
They have nowhere to breathe, nowhere to go because it's being done to
them since they were weaned off whatever formula or the mother's
thing. So tell you tell you one other thing here real quick, because I'm
going to take this very last insert from the chat room,
this very last inquiry from the chat room, I should say, because
I find it to be a useful question.
But after that, I would rather that you guys call in or Skype in.
OK, that's it. I'm not going to pay attention to the chat room any longer.
And it's very simple.
Can credit be used lawfully now?
Yes.
OK, I like to explain, but I would like you to explain
how it is that credit is lawful and what we have
here is not.
Credit is lawful when you are in a position, let's say, in ancient times,
there was a major, let's say, when when
OK.
Money is portable land, right?
So, OK, now we've discussed that in the past.
So let's say silver and gold becomes a convention
where gold is stockpiled and silver is used in commerce typically.
Right. And other things.
Let's say a silver mine opens in a gold mine opens
where now there is so much silver and something potato sized nuggets everywhere.
I mean, you just, you know, imagine going inside of a mountain, you hit it with
sledgehammer and all of a sudden a million of these potato head sized pieces
of silver fall out of the mountain.
What is silver worth? Not much.
Right. So all of a sudden the silver isn't worth much
and the economy could go into trouble.
Right. Because now all the silver that you needed to buy food
for a month doesn't get you food for a day.
So you see, you see there's problems with that as well.
But that's supply side economics.
So what happens to stabilize an environment is, OK, we will have some borders
here and we'll define the inhabitants within these borders as citizens
or as inhabitants.
And we we define them by them agreeing
to the jurisdiction of the leadership.
Right. Everyone is there by acceptance of the jurisdiction.
And what we will do is create a credit system where something very much
like Rome, where if you were a Roman, you can go and get
one to three loaves of bread a day from the state bakery.
OK, so and this was just to keep people stable.
What happened in the 30s with most countries in the world is that central banks
put the government's ability to make money into receivership for six percent.
I don't know if you've ever discussed how simple that was.
But so you're in receivership, you're in bankruptcy.
And if you want to know what receivership means, you can look it up.
It's basically they let the business, you know, when there's a business
that goes bankrupt and it's been a fixture in society, they don't shut it down.
They say the creditors come in and say, look, keep the shingle up,
keep the store open, and now we're going to just pay you a salary.
At the end of the day, we take everything out of the till.
And instead of being the owner where you just get a salary, you know,
so it's receivership basically keep the business going.
Nothing has changed.
But, you know, when you walk in, you see the guy used to own it.
So how come you're not smiling anymore?
You know. OK, so anyway.
So credit can be lawful in that capacity.
But what happens when someone goes to get a loan, let's say at a bank
or swipes a credit card because it's all credit.
If you have that card, it's already given that you have all the credentials
to be a resident or a citizen or whatever.
And the signature in the transaction is validated by you by a fingerprint.
I think it's a chip now or a signature and it's paid for.
But here come the third parties, the debt collectors, the legal society.
And it's like, oh, no, you have to pay it again
because they're trying to make it seem like you actually borrowed something,
but you didn't. Now, the problem.
With this is that if people knew that all they had to do was sign.
Right. This is what they did in Libya, by the way.
If you read the little green book about Gaddafi and everyone had.
Right. Anyway, utilities paid.
And I mean, right.
Because it was from the birth certificate.
But anyway, people would not go to work
because there's a major deficiency in the morality of the human.
Basically, to comprehend that they they don't have to pay for things.
All they have to do is excel at what they're naturally talented to do.
Could you imagine a society where instead of people being told you have to get a job
and work, you were you were actually encouraged
to develop whatever natural skills you had and you just did that
and everyone did that and you maintained everything around you.
And if you needed food, you just went and signed the name or whatever and you got it.
That's you know, that's like Star Trek.
People have imagined things like that.
I was going to say, you know, Star Trek, you're living in it.
Now, here's what's going on.
There's something called forensic accounting.
And so, well, I think we'll have to touch on that in the next hour,
because there's that music and it is time to take a break here
on the 11th chapter of Ocelli in the Greek Reloaded.
Stay tuned to American Freedom Radio.
The second hour of the 11th chapter of Ocelli and the Greek,
I'm in fact, the Ocelli half of that.
And we are broadcast live on American Freedom Radio
at American Freedom Radio dot com.
You may be hearing this in the archives or through some other convention.
Either way, I'm sure you're hearing things on this show
that you're not hearing elsewhere.
You can join in to the discussion and make even more things
be heard that are not being heard elsewhere
without too much trouble through the telephone convention
at two one eight three three nine eight five two five.
That's two one eight three three nine eight five two five,
which I have control over at the moment.
Or you could use the Skype convention, which the Greek has control
over the moment.
Ocelli and the Greek send a contact request.
You spell it just like it sounds O-C-H-E-L-L-I.
Now, let's see.
The C being in the.
Well, anyway, we talked about that.
You don't need the H, but you do need the H for Skype.
So, yes.
Anyway, we were talking about forensic accounting and credit.
So there's RESPA, FISA, federal, whatever, credit laws.
You can look them up at STPA and all that other stuff.
Fair Credit Consumer or whatever acts.
And they all basically state that if someone says you
owe them money, they have to validate it.
Now, what they do is they don't validate.
They verify.
They sent you a statement.
Again, they now in order to be validated, they have to do it
in an affidavit form signed under the penalty of perjury.
And no one's going to do that.
And typically the legal society ignores that because that's their whole thing
is they are not capable of doing anything beneficial.
So they have to pretty much do that kind of stuff.
Is act as debt collectors and charge people with things and all that.
And you see, we've got into it before and we stopped from ancient days.
It's been very well known that this planet was surrendered to the chief adversary,
the legal society or the boots on the ground of the spiritual adversary.
Just right now, they've adopted the ancient revived goddess religion.
All right.
I just had to throw that in as an addendum to what you said earlier.
But basically, if anyone says that you owe them something, they have to prove it.
And that's the federal law.
And there are state laws for that as well.
But no, no one's really told that.
So, yeah.
So the credit is used.
But how are you going to pay credit with credit?
How are you going to pay a debt with a debt?
If all these idiots and talk about it's debt based, right?
No, it's debt based.
You ever try to discuss the money system with someone?
Oh, hold on. Hold on.
I know. I know. It's debt based.
That's it. It's just debt based. It's debt slavery.
You're like, well, wait a second.
I know we're going. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
See, yeah, they can't because they're comparing what you're saying
to what they've been told.
It doesn't add up.
So it can't be true.
I think. Well, the reasonable concept, though, is that when money is created,
according to the standard explanation, there is incumbents
on something called interest.
Well, right. Yeah.
What's called money?
I mean, look, I can only call it what they call it.
But that's hold on.
The interest is part of the economic theory,
just like taxation is part of economic theory.
Oh, I understand.
But you see, if you take into account the way it's collected
and the way it's exchanged and then understand that there is this invisible
amount added to it, which doesn't actually exist,
then you leverage it by the invisible amount.
So in this way, all of it becomes pushed by debt.
Well, yeah. Well, alleged.
And the reason they do that is to make it intimidating.
Oh, let me just pay this now and negotiate.
So at least I don't have to deal with more.
It's just a prank is always cloaked.
Not always, but most cases can be cloaked with intimidation.
I just think that the debt based concept is not predicated on nothing.
It's actually, you know, somewhat reasonable when one considers
how things are actually exchanged things.
Here we go. The pieces of paper are exchanged.
Yeah, it's. Yeah, but it's pranking.
It's pranking. It's just like when the child, the parent tells the child,
you got it. I know you're not going to learn anything in school,
but you got to do it because I did it.
The child's like, I can't argue with that.
Wait a second. Wait a second.
It's like indirectly, you know, because it sounds reasonable.
So, well, you know, I know everybody knows education is crap,
but I got to do it because everybody did it.
Yeah, good boy. Pat you on the back.
Well, wait a second.
You tell me I got to waste 12 years of the life on this.
OK, so we talk about debt.
Well, wait a second.
If I don't pay it or whatever, they're going to take the car or the house.
Wait a second. Right.
So all of a sudden there is this low level emotional
stuff that compares back to the pranking that was done when you were,
you know, three years old in the crib.
So it's very that's why.
Hey, let's go back. I don't know.
How far do you want to go back?
And since you and I used to meet and do these sonic events,
I know it's another way to dub surface dwelling earth inhabitants was what?
Unrehabilitable.
What does unrehabilitable mean as a group?
Unrehabilitable. Can't fix it.
So what do you how do you deal with it?
You deal with it. Right.
In other words, not deal with it like a like a deck of cards,
but you insulate yourself, you get knowledge and you learn how to navigate.
And you'll notice you'll notice that
90 percent of your waking time is how to avoid
or compensate for the idiocy around you.
And the other 10 percent is, you know, wiping your bum, maybe it's
and getting food and having a comfortable bed to sleep in. Right.
So could you know, it's just if you really did a let's say
an accounting, how much time one can spend avoiding these morons
or at least not avoiding you're going to have to make contact,
you know, whether it's the auto parts store or the grocery store.
However, however, however, you're going to have to put up with it to some degree.
And it's a tremendous amount of time.
And it's sorry.
That's why here's here's the thing.
I really feel bad.
But not not to express it directly, but indirectly.
There are people who celebrate birthdays.
I have a good time or whatever.
But you got to be a real moron to separate celebrate being born into this.
I mean, but anyway, this has also been dubbed more than once in ancient grits.
You should be crying about the day you were born into this mess.
But not because you should not have been born,
because if you're here, you should have. Right.
But what you're going through is not really how
it can be or should be. Right.
So but if you're going to do that's one reason for the another thing is
what do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common?
You can think about that a little bit.
No, we're not going to go over it again.
That's been done over too many times. Right.
So and and this is how you're going to get an idea of the level of of practice
to be on this planet with the society that's here.
Think about it. How common.
Let's just change gears a little bit.
It all ties in together with the the interest that you said,
you know, which is there for intimidation purposes and all this. Right.
And agreement also. What if you agree to it? So what?
You know, that's you got to do it now. Right.
But think about how common it was to read about human sacrifice back in the day.
Oh, but we don't do that anymore. Right.
No, we just do a parody of it.
And we, you know, meaning humans. Right.
I don't think it would have been too common to read about it
because the printing press wasn't invented until, you know, a certain time period.
So but it was where you've been reading about it.
You know, well, now if you're well, let's say, you know,
even when the printing press was put out, they said, oh, great.
All this crap that people are talking about is going to be printed.
Now, this is what they were saying 500 years ago.
Yeah. So anyway, so so if you see all of these sacred sites and all this other stuff,
you see those are places where children were sacrificed.
Even today, the majority of the world's religions still practice within their
celebratory rites, mimicking and parody of child sacrifice. Right.
So you're you're basically a society on the verge of just,
you know, a millimeter away from just reaching a sharp or blunt object
and taking the lights out of a child.
I mean, this is historically your history, you know.
OK, so how how far have you gone away from that?
Not much, because you're still I'd say it's pretty explicit
how it's being parodied in all of the rites of the people celebrating.
Right. Still pretty explicit.
Whether it's known or not is irrelevant because you have to be objective.
Now, when you look at such a base thing like that, how are you going to escape
all the concepts and the notions that hold the society or the individual back?
Very difficult, because that's a very low place to be, you know,
engaging in human sacrifice, whether it is actual human sacrifice
or basing your sacred days on a parody of it.
You're not going to pretty much.
Yeah. You see my point, Chuck?
It's you're going to be stuck on that low level until you clear that.
So so I think we lost Chuck.
So I'm going to see if I can carry this.
He just dropped. Maybe he lost Internet or something.
So we were on the let's see if he comes back.
We were on the discussion of the of the credit being lawful or not.
And yeah, it is. Credit can be lawful.
Money can be lawful.
It's just the way that it's done is not lawful.
It's being done legally.
So how are we going to we who is we going to mitigate that?
You don't. You just have to be very wise about it and then proceed,
you know, from that point on, however you want.
And typically when you try to objectify something like that,
it seems like an avalanche of information to go after.
But because it's very much like a jigsaw puzzle.
If you have a jigsaw puzzle, it's very helpful to see the whole picture first
before you try to assembling the pieces.
And what happens is people have been misled about many, many things.
Regardless, it doesn't matter if it's about the money system, the legal system.
Notice, I don't say the law system because it even
well, it's a very big discernment there
regarding on how the body works, regarding political scenarios,
natural scenarios.
What I mean by natural scenarios, tying it in with health
also is that man is agriculturally based.
So how are you going to pretty much objectify something like that
if objectivity tends to be tossed to the side?
So you need as a society and on an individual level, a picture
that is very simple, that all these, let's say, myriad of pieces
then can be thrown together much quicker and much more efficiently.
And that's just not going to happen on a major scale at this point.
And yeah, I mean, every time this show starts, we discuss
lawful timekeeping.
I mean, it's kind of neat.
It's kind of quirky, but it's really kind of sad.
Could you imagine communicating the concept
that people don't even know how to keep time lawfully?
Ah, where do you go?
How do you go from there?
I mean, discuss the body real quick.
You know, this is a seasonal change right now for depends on
whether you're going on, let's say, from a cold to warmer
season or a warm to colder season.
If you're on the other side, let's say like Australia, New Zealand
and other places like that.
The time of transition is very important
to comprehend how the environment is working and adapt to it readily.
So you don't get what's called a cold or a common cold.
Or when you're going into the warmer months, you are comfortable
because when you take the notion that people are still being told
that you are nothing more than a meat bag
and with a filter in it that you eat stuff and it's absorbed.
Yeah, it's it's yeah, right.
You absorb things like a sponge, I guess.
Perhaps not.
Anyone should really study what the intestines of animals look like.
And you will see there are hydrophobic impervious layers.
What is going on?
So, you know, looking at things objectively.
Now, here's another thing to consider.
There is a tremendous amount of work that has been done by people
by these conventional, what would you what would you say?
Constructs, whether it's the scientific society, legal society,
medical society or whatever, I'm leaving the religious society.
How do it? Because that's tends to be pretty ridiculous.
But they've done a lot of grunt labor work and producing images
and studies on things.
And then when it comes to explaining what these things do, they cannot do it.
They give you descriptions and people get lost in the sauce, so to speak,
when it comes to being overwhelmed with descriptions.
And you're just given descriptions on how the body works,
descriptions on how the economic or the legal system works,
descriptions on how nature works.
But very rarely are you given explanations.
Now, in order to be able to objectify, you need both.
You need to know what it's doing and why it's doing it.
And, you know, I'd like to also discuss many times the reciprocating motor,
you know, or the engine, you know, the way cars work, which are prevalent in society.
And people's notion of how they work with fuel is not the way they do so.
But from a descriptive point of view, it does seem to work that way.
If I run out of gas, it doesn't go.
And speaking out of getting gas and coming back, here's Chuck.
So, well, you know, sometimes electronics don't cooperate.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
No, it's mentioning that it's all the whole thing about Greek speak and O and G show is how do you,
hmm, you know, in mining, it's called a pry bar.
It's a stick of dynamite, right?
So how do you get, how do you blow off all the dust and all the stuff, right, to get people to be objective?
Not that they have to, but it's the objectivity that's sorely lacking.
What I was saying, Chuck, and I'll just reiterate real quick, is that what they're getting from all the conventional societies,
you know, the medical society, scientific society, legal society, I left out the religious society,
because that's pretty worthless across the board, is that they've done a lot of grunt work, right?
You go to a university, look at all their books, go on the internet, look at all these societies,
they've accumulated all this information, and when I say like heavy lifting, you know,
if you want to see what the body looks like inside, you don't really have to do it.
It's been done already.
Go get an anatomy book, or like you said, go watch an autopsy from the gallery or something, right?
So it's already been done.
But what they're lacking in is they only give descriptions.
They cannot explain it, right?
They cannot explain how natural things work.
They cannot explain how the body works.
They can't explain how a reciprocating engine works.
They give you descriptions only, and I shouldn't say only, but sometimes there's some explanations,
and then they brush it over, and they keep going with descriptions.
You'll be buried with descriptions if you study any of these fields in depth, right?
Now, in order to be objective, you need the description and the explanation.
You've got to know what it's doing and a little bit of why.
But that's the why's never being discussed.
Like the human body is where most people are walking around thinking that they have positive pressure
in the body and that they're a freaking filter bag.
How many times have you heard, you've got to eat that because it absorbs?
What are you talking about?
But through all the descriptions, they kind of sneak that in because they cannot.
There are people in the medical field that do know how the body works, and guess what?
Just like the legal field or the religious field or scientific field,
when you really find out how things really work, you're not going to last
because you're going to start talking to people that work in the field with you,
and it's going to get up to the higher-ups, and they're higher-ups, and they're higher-ups,
and it's going to come down on you.
It's going to rain shit on you, and they're going to tell you pretty much either shut up.
If they ask you, do you like working here, right?
And that's all they do.
They just keep asking, do you like working here?
I've had a conversation with someone before.
So they invited me into, he's a university guy.
They invited me into an office.
They had me wait there for an hour, and a guy shows up that I've never seen before.
He had two people waiting outside, and he just sat at the desk,
and he looked at me for about three minutes, and he says, do you like working here?
And I said, well, yeah, I do.
And he says, okay, and he asked me again, do you like working here?
And I said, yeah, and he got up, and he walked out, and that was it.
I said, oh, man, you're being intimidated, right?
Well, you know, you're on quite a run here.
I actually had a question of my own way back there.
If you don't mind, I want to rewind a little bit,
because you discussed positive pressure in the body.
Okay.
Now, here's something that, you know, helped me to sort this out.
You've got blood vessels, right, and blood travels through them.
These are basically like tubes in the body, aren't they?
Okay, so if you send a liquid through a hose, that would be sort of the similar kind
of action that we're seeing, right, with blood traveling through the body?
Yeah.
Okay, so by forcing a liquid through a hose,
isn't there some sort of pressure put on the hose?
Yeah, who's forcing what?
Yeah, could a straw that you drink soda out of be a tube in a hose?
Where's the pressure in that?
It's negative, isn't it?
Well, but there's probably some pressure which is put on the structure
of the straw, even though it's, you know...
Inward.
Yeah, but...
Yeah, here's the thing, a real quick way to rationalize it without even...
Well, you understand what I'm getting at, right?
Yeah, here's an even easier way, you ready?
This is a good one to do with children.
When you put your feet or your hands in water, do they shrivel up
or do they puff up like a frog?
Well, they shrivel up.
Right, right.
Okay, now, hold on.
I'm not trying to sell this or convince anyone because it's obvious.
They just got to say it.
Well, let's say you've got a flexible membrane, like a Ziploc bag, let's say.
I think that's a brand name or whatever.
So, I put a slab of meat in there.
When you put pressure in it, it blows up like a balloon.
But when you put suction on it, what happens?
It shrivels up, doesn't it?
Right.
Because the body's under a slight vacuum.
It's slightly lower than atmospheric pressure, just enough to support you.
Like, for example, you can...
This is a model of...
You know how they talk about the molten iron in the middle of the earth?
You can make a scale model with molten iron and any liquid on the surface will
evaporate within a few minutes.
You can make a model of the human body using tissue and fluid and bone,
and it will not support itself or have the features as it does,
as we recognize it, until you put a slight vacuum on it.
Okay, but one thing here...
Oh, wait a second.
Here's the lascivious part, unless you got a blow-up doll.
But anyway, okay, there we go.
You had to throw something lascivious.
Okay, no problem.
So, everybody's a blow-up doll, maybe.
I don't know, but yeah.
Well, that's an interesting thought.
Everyone wants...
Yeah, well, I mean, if you're under pressure, you know,
you're under pressure, you know?
Anyway, so that's like a Red Fox joke, but anyway, go ahead.
But here's the thing, going back to your, you know, to your plastic bag, right?
When you have it sealed and you create a vacuum, okay, fine.
So, that's the condition until the meat begins to decay or the thing in the bag
begins to decay, which does happen, right, because of a chemical reaction
that causes the bag to expand and therefore can eventually put enough
pressure on it, in fact, it'll pop.
Right, just like a dead body does, right.
Well, yeah, that's actually where I was going.
So, I'm just thinking to myself that by virtue of there being a vessel and a
chemical reaction within the vessel, couldn't that possibly cause pressure?
At the point of decomposing, but here's the thing, the whole concept of pressure
with blood pressure is an emergence of a ratio between heartbeats and it's been
discussed as colloquially, because blood pressure measurements are not really
blood pressure measurements.
It's a small fraction of time in between beats to measure the impulse of the heart,
right?
But, okay, since you mentioned the vessels, do you know that the majority of the
vessels are less than a millimeter in diameter?
Actually, a tenth of a millimeter in diameter.
The majority of the body, you've got about 2,500 miles of blood vessels in the body,
most of them are capillaries, right?
Now, have you ever heard of capillary action?
Does that force the liquid?
Does that put negative?
It's negative, right?
You put, right, capillary tube sucks, right?
You put a small capillary tube in a glass of water and you see how the level is
higher than the rest within the capillary.
Now, this is not as simple, but we're giving rational examples.
The problem with trying to discuss what people can observe without getting any
specialized knowledge, just around them, right?
Again, is they have to compare it to all these other analogies.
I don't even like to give the analogy of the plastic bag, even though it's a good
one, I think, right?
Because all you need to say is, look, when you soften the membrane of the skin
through, let's say, soaking in water, does it appear to be shriveled or expanding?
Expansive.
Well, it's shriveled.
So that's like basic physics, let's say, that we know that the area...
Let's not even use basic physics.
We know that that area that is now softened is subject of negative pressure,
slightly less than the environment, right?
So, what's interesting about this is, now, when we transfer over to how the
medical field works, how many times have we said that there's nothing wrong with
the medical field if you're dead?
Because all of their study is based on removing living cells from a living host,
which then the cells die and are preserved, or studying cadavers, right?
Isn't that pretty much the entire study of Western medicine?
Pretty much.
You see?
When you have a heart, for example, when they discuss the heart,
they hold the heart in their hand and they only discuss the part that's
one inch thick.
The part that's less than, you know, an eighth of an inch or a sixteenth
of an inch thick, they slice it off and throw it on the floor.
And that's the part that's doing all the work.
And it can't be because it's only, you know, so thin.
It's the heavy one, you see?
So, you know, Frank Chester, if anyone wants to really have fun,
and this guy, he's a master teacher.
He's very good at what he does.
Frank Chester, like Chester Drawers, C-H-E-S-T-E-R.
He has the seven-sided lawful figure.
It's a really good lesson.
You shouldn't be disappointed by any time that you spend with Frank.
He's got a bunch of YouTubes.
He's surrounded by a lot of these flaky, you know, I call them breakfast cereal
types, you know, fruits, nuts, and flakes.
But anyway, but he's done some really good work.
And he's done some...one of his early videos he shows,
he's got a two-by-four with a 15-pound weight on it, like a hammer,
just to show how 15 pounds can swing.
And he's got a hose with some liquid that mimics blood,
and it doesn't even move the blood three feet, right?
And 15 pounds of pressure would be enough to rupture the skin, you know?
So, this is very interesting, and it's been discussed.
You know, here's the interesting thing, and let's go back.
You know, we should go back, really back.
The ancient Greeks said that the fluid in the body moves like a wave, right?
And they said, oh, that can't be true because we have blood vessels.
They were not discussing blood.
Here's the other thing about looking at accumulated knowledge.
Just like we've stated, all you're getting from doctors is thousands of years
of accumulated knowledge from battlefield medicine, when you think about it.
The only thing that they have going for themselves is the emergency room,
and thereof, right?
Because you also have elective surgery, where someone walks in, and they lay them down,
they clean them up, and they use saws and knives and things, right?
All right, bandit, all right, okay.
So, basically, the majority of information that is given
in this field is predominantly about battlefield medicine.
Now, I just heard that I cut out.
I don't know if that's true or not.
But you're fine from my end.
I'm hearing you just fine, so.
Okay. All right.
So, this is pretty much how any field goes.
It's just an immediate description.
But, you know, here, Chuck, okay, forget about the plastic bags for a minute.
You know, septem means seven, octo means eight, nova means nine,
and decem means ten, doesn't it?
Sure, sure.
Yeah, okay.
Do I need to say anything more?
Do I need to explain anything?
Well, no, those are just, I mean, that's what their meaning is, yeah.
Now, how can you have D-E-C-E-M-B-E-R and write 12 next to it?
What are you, freaking blind?
Like they say back, you know, hey.
I got you, go ahead.
You know, how can you see septem and write nine?
How can you see octo and write ten?
What's wrong with you?
It's not bad of it, people, right?
You know, I mean, I got nothing to work with over here.
Because pretty much, you know, I mean, look, pretty much the entire society
is exposed to the septem, octo, novum, decem thing, right?
And they're messing it up.
Every year it comes around and everybody's, and, right, okay.
And no one's raised, you know, wait a second.
Got nothing to work, you know, what's going on, right?
You know, if you want to know the status of the society, every morning wake up
and call a heating and cooling engineer, call up the physics department
at the university and say, hey, listen, I want to talk to you guys about,
you know, have you gotten any recent queries or questions about anybody
calling and saying, why aren't you guys building machines or air conditioners
that make a rarefied rising cold and a descending, densifying heat?
You know, in other words, anybody calling you and asking you about,
you know, making, you know, climate control with rising cold and descending
heat, and they're like, no, no, no one is.
They say, hang up and say, okay, this is a planet full of idiots still, right?
I mean, do we need to explain that in all natural systems, the cold rises
and the heat descends in natural growing biological systems,
but decomposing molecular breakdown, you have a rising heat and descending cold.
I mean, you know, you make a campfire, is the wood integrating or disintegrating?
It's disintegrating, it's chemical breakdown, isn't it?
Of course, the heat is going to rise, right?
In your refrigerator, is it being powered by this entropic form of current
from a power plant that's compressing magnetic field down a copper wire?
Of course, the cold is going to go down.
Well, I do note that in a house where you have heating at the baseboard,
if one is to lay on the floor of that house, it does often feel cooler than it does
if you stand on a ladder, okay?
It does seem warmer up higher.
Well, yeah, because that heat is generated by, again, this entropic form of electricity,
it's pressurized magnetic field or oil or coal or whatever.
Here's the thing, and this is away from the first rule.
What I've noticed is when, let's say you have person A that wants to be objective and tries to,
and then you've got person B who is either on the fence or doesn't want to be objective.
They like to be just like what's been fed.
It doesn't matter if it's good or bad, right?
Well, look, I hope you're not representing me as person B here.
I'm telling you an honest observation.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is not that person.
Let's just say you're watching this now, okay?
Okay.
It's a little self-conscious there, but anyway, this is totally objective.
What's the meeting?
How do you meet the two in the middle?
The most peaceful way, especially if there's wisdom involved, the objective walks away.
How many times have you heard people say, as soon as I hear this, I walk away, right?
You've heard that coming and going in various aspects of society and people saying that.
As soon as I hear this topic, I go away, right?
I say that a lot.
As a matter of fact, as soon as I hear that, I'm done.
Yeah, that's it.
I get in the car, drive away or whatever, close the thing.
Okay, we're done.
There's no reason to go down because at least that's a form of wisdom that you know that
there's a 50-50 chance something can come out of it, but I'm not banking on the 50 that's
going to be optimistic.
I'm going to stick with the consistently that this isn't going to go anywhere, so it's worth
it to leave it alone, right?
That's generally what's been going on for years and years and years.
But now discussing this during the credits is okay because it's part of prepping people
hearing what's coming.
There is going to be a lot of it that is going to emerge again and be the new convention.
What's sustainable?
What's living?
Who are the gods?
That's the main thing.
Here's the thing.
Even with the one that wants to be objective because you really can't be truly objective
when you're animated through a physical body.
Think about it, right?
You can try to be objective as you want and a bee lands on your neck with a stinger.
Try to be objective there.
You're going to go out, right?
So you're always going to be subjective.
You know, I'm not feeling well or I got to grab something.
Something is always going to remind you that you're animated through this physical form.
But the main thing that gets really harsh where it becomes disheartening and that's
where you just have to say it because you have to say it and detach the persona from
it.
Typically, what happens is, let's say, you see someone's hungry and they don't know
what good food is.
They say, listen, man, I'm going to buy you a meal at a five-star restaurant, a really
good meal.
And as you're walking with them to the restaurant, you can't stop them from going into the
nearest garbage can and eating out of the garbage can, right?
So it's like, all right.
And after a while on the way to the restaurant, you're going to say, you know what?
I'm done with this.
Forget it.
Because you can't, you know, I mean, because the discrepancy is so huge.
Like we said here before, the difference between those who know and don't know is not a
small margin.
It's like so large.
It's, you know, it's like going to another planet almost.
There's no
Well, an example of this could be easily that, you know what?
The garbage can at the five-star restaurant is probably better than the food which is
being served at, well, XYZ, insert the name.
Right.
But yeah, but here's the other thing, you know, I think we kind of define capitalism
as being when you're done using it, you destroy it so nobody else can use it, right?
That's why when you hear we're capitalistic, right?
You know, how many times have you heard it?
You know, we're done using it.
Now break it.
Well, it's fine.
Just leave it somewhere.
No, no, no.
We got to destroy it.
That's what they do with, you know, they put locks on dumpsters now, right?
Which I don't think is lawful, by the way.
Yeah, I know.
But, you know, that's capitalism though, because when you're done using it, you got
to destroy it so nobody else can use it.
And guess what?
These people want capitalism.
How many times do you hear that?
Who are these people?
What do you mean by these people?
You know who you are.
And those of you who are not know who you are too.
Right.
That's an interesting thing, you know, when people learn how to listen with discernment,
just like we used to say, if you're pursuing the truth, you cannot be insulted, right?
Think about it, because you're not invested in dumb shit.
If you're, let's say, for example, okay, let's say, Chuck.
All right.
Let's say I'm the Greek.
Okay.
I like the truth.
All right.
So you come up to me and you say, hey, man, your shirt looks real dirty.
And I'm like, wait a second.
All right.
Let me see what he's saying.
You know what?
It is.
Thanks, man.
Or if it's not dirty, I can assess it.
I say, Chuck, you know, are you sure about that?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Well, I don't think it's accurate because you can't show me how it's dirty.
So I'm not insulted either way.
Right.
I wouldn't be an insult.
It would just be merely taking a look and observing whether the assertion is correct or not.
Well, let's go back to the 1950s thing.
Your mother wears combat boots in school, right?
This is right.
All right.
Okay.
Well, she does.
Is it comfortable?
Yeah.
So what?
You got a problem with it?
Or she does it, you know?
So what?
What's the big deal?
This is not the truth has nothing to do with these things, right?
That's why, for example, when you certain people of certain faiths,
they ask them what they believe and why they can't tell you.
So, you know, that's where you walk away.
And, you know, because they're just going to be insulted.
You know, there used to be a saying that says that you should never talk about
politics and religion because you might offend the ignorant.
If you're pursuing the truth, there is no offense.
There's only transgression based on agreement.
You see, that's why the courts, they don't go by truth.
They go by facts.
That's why they have offenses.
But, you know, but when you talk about facts, you get into another strange area.
Right.
The facts is not the truth.
You know, if you wear a pink baseball cap every Monday,
it keeps the elephants out of Chicago, right?
How do I know it's a fact?
You know, I know it's a fact.
I don't see any elephants in Chicago, do I?
Well, that's a fact.
See?
So, yeah.
So but anyway, there's a progression.
Now, here's the interesting thing.
How do you get?
How do you get objective, right?
You don't.
It's not like something you can take off the shelf.
You got to ask questions like we mentioned earlier about forensics, which just means evidence.
All right.
Well, that's why I asked the question about the blood pressure because
look, I can observe other things and make a statement based on those observations
that seem to contradict what you're talking about.
But if you examine it a different way and, you know, and understand that,
you know, examining something similar is not examining the thing itself.
Right.
Examining the thing, examining the thing itself is very important because usually when you discuss
things regarding health or the body or nature, you're dealing with things that are alive.
And I'll tell you right now, the higher up you go into the academic or conventional community,
talking about the life force, chi, prana,
Zoe in Greek, right?
All these things that the ancients talked about the life force, right?
They get, it shakes them, it rocks them to the core.
They cannot, they're afraid of it.
William Reich discussed this.
If you start discussing what makes you, allows someone to walk across the room or eat and sleep,
you know, things that are alive, what is it?
These people that are in the entitled positions are very afraid of that.
Right.
They're very armored against it.
So what happens is by default, these people are there, these entitled classes,
because not everybody wants to study the body their whole life.
They got other things to do, right?
They want to be a shoemaker or radio host or work on cars or do nothing.
They don't want to study the body.
So when they want to learn about the body, they trust that they're being given the real deal,
right?
And now if you tell them it's not the real deal now, it's not because they can't go ahead
and relearn it now.
They don't know what to trust, just like the food.
If you tell people they have to maybe improve their diet, you know, they're watching the
news and listening to radio and seeing how people, they feel a sense of insecurity around
them.
The only thing they have secure is the way they eat.
Now they got to change that.
That's like pulling the rug from under their feet.
So it takes, I think we define fear.
If you look at the concept of that being lack of skill and weak mindedness,
it starts to make sense.
You know, forget about the trust aspect.
You ever hear, for example, you can like someone and not trust them and you can trust someone
and not like them, right?
I had to explain this to someone recently.
I said, hey, when you go to the pub or the bar and you have drinks, you enjoy being three,
four hours with these guys, but would you give them the keys to the house or the car?
No, I wouldn't.
Okay, but there's a guy, kind of nerdy guy across the street.
You don't talk to him much, but you trust him with the keys.
Yes, I do.
You see?
So some people are likable and not trustable.
Other people are trustable and not likable.
Well, you may not like your bartender very much, but you do trust that he put in the
glass what you ordered most of the time.
I don't think people examine exactly what was put in the glass.
So people are not only trusting these idiots in the entitled classes, you know, the professors,
the professionals, whatever, and they want to like them also.
The thing is, if you've been screwed over with rubbish information, and by the way,
I did a quick news, one of these news things that I look at.
There was an article, I think it was Rappaport blog or something, about how they're discovering
now that thousands of scientific and medical reports have been fraudulent and deceptive,
right?
This is being compiled now, like people within that group, you know, that X amount in the
past 10 years were not dozens or not hundreds, but thousands of studies that were medical
and scientific are outright fraudulent and deceptive.
Think about that for a moment.
Where's the outrage?
I think just five or ten would be enough to shut it down, right?
So anyway.
Well, yeah, that's fascinating, too, because, you know, what happens when they discover
something in what they call science nowadays to be an inaccurate assertion is they just
change the books and move on, you know, if they even bother to change the books.
So, sure, sure.
Well, you know, even on that aspect, how many times have you heard the concept of blackmail?
You see, why not just fess up?
You know, some people say, well, the politicians are blackmailed, right?
Because how many times have you heard about, you know, people in office, official positions
or whatever, do something bad, and then it just it's like, no big deal, you know, did
they go to jail?
You know, it's stupid stuff like that.
By the way, there's no prison in a lawful society.
You do have jails, though, for temporary holding, you know, but these things like the concept
of they're blackmailed.
So what?
So let's say you cheated on the wife and they got photographs.
Fess up.
Come out and say, yeah, I had a weak moment.
The position I have is more important than this with the scumbags trying to show over
here.
So what?
You know, just keep going.
Where are these guys?
I mean, can you imagine, you know, that blackmail is actually containing these people?
You know, what happened here?
You know, where's the integrity?
You see?
Well, integrity.
You're asking for a two horned unicorn.
It's a rhetorical question because the unicorns don't even.
Yeah.
What did I just say?
A two horned unicorn.
But it's a double entendre anyway, because not even a one horned unicorn is worth it.
Right.
Exactly.
So so the whole thing here is, you know, it's on rehabilitatable.
But here's the other thing.
If you're going to be set up, you know what I mean?
Might as well be set up by the gods, because I mean, that's like the ultimate dynamic force.
Right.
So you're all being set up by the gods and you don't know it.
Well, look, you know, you want to you want to make it real simple.
Justicia, justice, the goddess religion where you remember somewhere we've discussed that your law
comes from your god, right?
And if you don't have a god, then the state becomes your default god.
And they use a god too.
And you're living under the revived goddess religion.
So what do you know about goddess religions in this specific one?
If you answered nothing, that's correct.
Most people don't want to go there.
It's too freaking scary.
Well, first of all, not only is it scary.
Second of all, how are you going to objectify the information?
Very difficult, right?
But you will find out that this particular goddess that is personified in many ways is anti-life.
Wow, Greek.
What does that mean?
Well, because life as we know it, animated from material right now is dependent upon
the Congress of male and female, whether it's man or woman or male or female animal,
even plants to some degree.
And the destruction of that union is what she is hard up on.
And that's why the distortion that's why the distortion of each of the sexes is incumbent
in order to create, you know, the what do we call that the androgynous figure?
Yes, or asexual as well.
Asexual or androgynous.
The whole thing about the tea.
This was one of the major things in the pre-flood that survived.
And it was discussed in some of the hidden stuff that the Egyptians and the Babylonians
and the Greeks discussed was that mankind was once in a godlike state.
And when mankind was in a godlike state, they were not identified as male or female or man
and woman.
They were androgynous or hermaphroditic, both or neither.
So or asexual.
So the way you accomplish a godlike society is by encouraging male with male union and
the males become effeminate and sterile and female with female union and the females
maintain their sterility and procreate without the male.
This agenda has been in place big time, full swing since the 40s and 30s.
Right to the point now where you the chemicals that are being dumped in rivers are gender
bending.
The legal society has full on taken this philosophy.
The medical society has taken full on.
The culture, the pop culture has taken it full on.
It has nothing to do with your preference.
It has to do with utter and complete human side, not genocide, but the entire human race
and all things living that come through that union.
And for a pretty minor goddess, she's accomplished quite a bit.
She's been given her 15 minutes of fame, so to speak, within a cosmic sense, which
is a long time, by the way, in there, because a thousand years is a day.
So when you think about it, you've all been duped.
And I say all you it's not to offend or condescend because those of you who know or
don't feel it, it's interesting how the insecure say, oh, that's condescending or
insulting.
You know, well, that's how you can tell right away who's pursuing what.
But in general, at large, the society at large has been duped by this goddess religion.
And when it was imposed with less technological fervor in societies, it destroyed those
societies when the Greeks accepted decay and when the Egyptians accepted Mott.
Right.
And you had the goddess religions.
Yes.
And a lot of the aboriginal cultures as well utterly destroy them.
Here's the thing that if you really want to say something to these patriots, you know,
these quote, these guys that go and protest, I don't know, whatever you really want to
get their heads or their panties in a twist because they could be wearing panties underneath
all that, even though they're from Texas, because, you know, only two things come from
Texas.
Right.
But anyway, so you just go up to me, so you know that the people left Europe for hundreds
of years to escape justice because just to come here, let's say, to the Americas.
Because justice was destroying them in Europe.
And, you know, they'll look at you like, what the hell did you say?
They don't know what you're talking about.
Right.
Because they're asking for it.
Mm hmm.
I mean, I just want justice.
What are you talking about?
So anyway, this is that's why it's very you can confidently say you've all been duped
at large.
You've been duped by this goddess religion.
Now, here's the interesting thing.
It's not that you're looking for a maternal or paternal at all.
It just so happens that this particular malevolent entity that has been given the center stage
at this point happens to be a female entity, female god.
It's not that female is bad or female gods are bad because Sophia, our wisdom, is a
female god.
And she is very highly esteemed.
Right.
You know, a lot of times when I bring up the effects of the goddess religion, they think
it's anti-feminine.
It's like saying, let's say you were carjacked with someone with a ski mask and you let him
get the car, but then you jump back in and you kick their ass.
You pull them out on the street.
You pull off the mask and it's a woman.
Are you anti-feminine because you're telling people someone a woman stole the car?
No, it just so happened that this particular malevolent deed was carried out by a right.
That's all it is.
And the thing is, that's how you can see how it can be objectified.
And not only do you think, you know, you hear all these idiots discussing the sacred
feminine and all this other stuff.
Yes, yes, okay, yes, yes, yes, but you're daydreaming.
You're not addressing what's going on right now.
You know, the people are so incredibly emerged in this malevolent goddess religion that discussing
the positive goddess aspect is, I mean, how can you do that?
You know, by ignoring the malevolency that's right in your face right now.
Take care of that first.
Well, now, hold on.
You can't take care of it.
You just set yourself apart from it.
Oh, yeah, because I was going to say, wait a minute.
Aren't you the one who says that?
Well, take care of it, meaning in the mind.
Yeah, it's like, wait a second.
You know, you see people going to the courts and we want justice.
You're like, oh, that's not going to go very well.
You can't.
You know, there's no way.
So, you know, there's many, many levels to this.
But the thing is, look, look, let's not say it again.
September means seven.
October means eight.
Nova means nine.
And Destin means ten.
Chuck, I'm going to leave it like that.
Right.
Do we need to explain that?
We used to explain that, right?
And like I did a little before.
You don't need to do that.
That's it.
Look, that's all you got to say.
December means ten.
November means nine.
October means eight.
September means seven.
That's all you got to say.
If you don't pick up the rest.
Hey, I got nothing to work with here.
And the same thing with this goddess religion.
The same thing with, come on, blood pressure.
No, come on.
You go on and on and on and on.
Anybody could go look at the intestines.
How many layers you got there?
Where's the pore?
This is not porous.
Nothing's being absorbed.
You know, this is an interesting thing.
That's why, you know, let's go back to that.
You know, we're kind of like jumping around like a grove over here.
Think about it for a moment.
How important is it that you integrate yourself into the environment?
It's everything.
That's why, you know, when they send airplanes up with jet fighters,
they have to wear pressure suits and all that.
And that's why when you go underwater, you need to accommodate that as well.
But how about, are we taking living on the surface so granted?
You know, that we think we can do anything,
you know, in terms of how we interact with the environment,
in terms of food and drink and things like that.
Maybe that could be one of the problems regarding what people consider health.
Right?
But where are they getting the information from?
You see, and also, you know, and also how are you going to come out and say,
for example, if you live in a cold climate, okay,
or a cold season, and you eat something that was grown in the tropics,
that something is going to change your body to living in the tropics,
but you're in a cold place, you're going to catch a cold.
I mean, where do you need to, do you need to explain that anymore?
Or do they, now, should they get it or not?
That depends on the individual, right?
How, if they're censored or not, or if it's meant to them,
for them to suffer that inadequacy of objectivity.
So there's many levels to it.
You know, sometimes you could just say it in passing and they get it.
And like I said, that, by the way, eating seasonally works every time.
The only time it didn't work, one person said it didn't work.
I said, well, what did you do?
Because I didn't even try it.
And so I guess, but I'm still mentioning it just to show you
or show the relationship of how communication works, you know,
with these things, you know, these, they're very, very simple.
So, and again, you want to, let's, you know, one of the most,
I think we've talked about, you know, people saying,
I'm going to do this to the death and whatever.
I suggest you don't say that because someday you might be accommodated, right?
But the concept of religious fervor and faith
and the mainstream religion and alternative religions or whatever,
if you start inquiring what these people are basing,
you know, this is regarding the gods, by the way.
That's why I used to discuss with people,
the little preacher down the street or minister
or whatever you want to call them or rabbi or whatever,
imam, a little guy that everyone likes
because he gives us some charity,
gives out cans of food, give you a blanket,
a place, you know, it's a place of worship
because you believe in it or whatever.
That guy is in deeper trouble than some of the most heinous criminals
that have ever lived.
Why? Why?
No matter how much you like them,
how happy-go-lucky they are or whatever,
or they tell you it's about love
because he is representing the gods to mankind
and everything that's coming out of their mouth is a lie.
Everything.
I don't have to meet them to know it.
Why? They're in deeper trouble
because a mass murderer or whatever out there
didn't say he was doing it in the name of whatever
or representing the gods.
Now, some of them might have been saying that,
but even then, these little guys that everyone,
oh, I like going to this church or this temple
because they really, it's a good place to meet.
Yeah, but you can go meet somewhere else.
Don't start, you know, this is demonology
you're getting involved in here right now, right?
It's big.
So people don't understand how the various degrees
of subjects regarding dynamic things can change
the veracity of the outcome.
For example, you can go and meet anywhere
and do charity anywhere,
but once you go into a building
that says to be representing the gods
and everything that they're doing is false or contrary
or actually in the list of the texts
that they allegedly subscribe to all the abominations,
you should get away from that.
This is not advice.
This is just common sense.
Just because it's not coming down on them now
doesn't mean it's not gonna come down, you see?
And I propose that we,
just as we get ready to wrap up the 11th chapter here,
maybe we should call it, this is not advice.
Yeah, well, you know what I like?
There used to be a t-shirt and it was a hammer
and it said, this is not a drill, right?
Yeah, so anyway, you've seen that?
Okay, I never saw that one, but I can imagine.
The t-shirt of a hammer, it says, this is not a drill.
Yeah, so yeah, in other words, what are you talking about?
You know, you could show up till,
you know, we could be doing this for the next 500 weeks
and it wouldn't change a thing.
Well, I don't know what it would change.
I can't imagine doing this for 500 weeks,
but who knows?
I can't exactly see the future myself.
Maybe you can, Greek.
It's, well, we like to keep everything limited
and we'll probably put a cap on it soon.
We'll see how it goes.
Exactly, but this one is done,
the 11th chapter in the book, so to speak.
Ocelli and the Greek is finished.
Stay tuned to American Freedom Radio.
We may see you next,
what they call, Thursday on the Pope's work schedule.
Take care.