Oh, well, stuck mute buttons and all here we go with Ocelli and the Greek here on American
Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com. Now, it is fascinating to note that we have
some sort of an issue at the moment, but I assume that all these things will be cleared up and we'll
be able to take your questions and get your input through the Skype convention at Ocelli and the
Greek on Skype, which the Greek has yet to join me, by the way, but we have Ocelli and the Greek
on Skype. You can call in. Also, we should have the phone lines up rather shortly at 218-339-8525,
218-339-8525, and since this is supposed to be the final broadcast of this particular sonic entity,
I advise that if you have thought about getting in on the discussion, you do so.
Anyway, let's see what happens. Well, like I say, the Greek is, I think, attempting to join me now
and we will hear from him shortly. I've got to say that this has been an interesting adventure. I
don't want to comment too much without the other half of the show with me. Let's see what's going
on. This is humorous. This is very humorous. Anyway, let's see what happens. I went to
UncommonRadio.com earlier in the week because somebody had pointed out to me that the banner
was put up there stating that this would be the final broadcast and actually the Greek was looking
for input as to what he should do next at the website, and I found that interesting. I do
have the phone lines up, by the way, at 218-339-8525, 218-339-8525, and not sure what's going
to happen here. If you want to call in, though, by all means, join in. Let's see. I'm getting
messages on the Skype already. This is kind of entertaining. All right, let's try and grab the
other Skype ID, Mr. Bordop, the one that is generally used by the Greek, and see if that
works because for some reason, we're not able to join him into the discussion. However, as I said
for you, the listener, 218-339-8525, is the available way for you to engage. I guess the Skype
Convention will not be available unless you contact Charles.Ocelli, which is my Skype ID. I
will drag you in. Here we go. Let's see what happens here. I love this, by the way, because
my stuff sabotages me every now and then. I'm wondering if the Greek in his wisdom was not able
to sort out his Skype, which I would find kind of funny. Anyhow, let's see if we can get him online
and into the conversation. Well, it has been a fascinating set of episodes, that's for sure.
We did this the first time, I think, beginning in 2015, and it was every Saturday,
you know, every Saturn day, according to the Pope's work schedule and all that kind of good
stuff, you know, that thing that allegedly they call a calendar, which is a timepiece relative to
what's happening on this surface of this particular planet, I guess.
We'd begun it then, and then, well, let's see now. This would be episode 12 this time around,
so I guess for the past 12 weeks, there was a reloaded version of this show. In between,
he did something called Uncommon Sense or Uncommon Sense Radio. I can't remember the title
exactly. I think it was Uncommon Radio with Seth Michaels. Some people have said that they don't
enjoy my commentary so much that they kind of enjoyed Seth a lot more than they did me. Who
knows? Maybe Seth will return for the next Greek Sonic project. Let's see if we can somehow get
the man in here. Maybe he'll have to call in. 218-339-8525. 218-339-8525.
That would be just too funny if he had to join in via cell phone or something.
Well, I can conduct a show that way anyway. It doesn't matter. I can sit here and talk to a
sandwich if I felt like it. I could make it somewhat interesting for you. I'm sure of that.
With some of the guests I've had on occasion, I could say that a ham sandwich would be a step up,
but we all make mistakes. Let's see what happens here, folks.
Like I say, you can join into the conversation at 218-339-8525. I don't know.
What should we do here, Mr. Bordoff? Should I do something else? What's going on?
See, I don't want to hijack the two hours because everybody was waiting for this to happen.
A bunch of people had actually expressed a bit of regret that this would be the final episode,
that this would be the final chapter, so to speak. I thought it was kind of humorous.
I'm sort of burnt out after doing this. This is usually my fourth show of the week
that I've done for myself on the Ocelli Effect going Monday through Thursday. Occasionally,
I show up on other shows and do other work as well. Generally speaking, I would have already
done four shows, and immediately after what I do with Carmine on Thursdays, I would jump into this
one and usually get pretty worn out. I know it sounds funny because it's just four hours of my
life and all that, but when you have to intellectually engage with things for more than
an hour or two and make sure that there's no dead air and sort of marshal a broadcast,
it's a skill set, I imagine. Are we here for the giggles of how awkward and silly this all is?
I'm going to go to the chat room. How about this? Let's see.
So far, I'm just going to read some of the comments here. I'm going to go back a little
bit. Let's see. The Greek is busy making perfect rice, is one comment, and examining fecal matter.
The Greek can't get on the call. He's trying, though. Comes from Greekswoman. Okay, cool.
Let's see. Oh, I see. I have done both today and still made it on time. All right. Let's see.
Greek call in, LOL. That's from Yon Matthew. Let's see. Greek forgot to call into his own call-in
show. Let's see what else we got. Let's see. Or saw the pointlessness of it. LOL, likely the latter.
Was hoping he could address the legalities of homesteading. That's because Seth was okay. Well,
that's just rude to Seth. I'm not going to be rude to Seth. He's not a bad guy.
Let's see. Oh, check that out. Yeah, virtual problems with a virtual system and a virtual
limitation. Well, after all, everything is virtually something or other, isn't it, Greek?
It can be. Yeah. All right. Go ahead. Let me just continue. You settle down for a second.
I always find this stuff funny, man. I can't help but laugh.
So the Greek has actually joined in for Ocelli and the Greek. This is the final chapter. We
still have enough time to get this to get this done the way I see it, because there's plenty
of time to say essentially the same thing that's been said over and over again. And as I said,
this would be the 12th chapter of the reloaded version. There were 18 proper episodes of the
first version, I think. And truthfully, there were a couple of other rogue episodes there that
you could count. So somewhere near 40 episodes or so, I think would be 30 to 40, depending on how
you look at it, because we did appear on, let's see, Jack Bloodstream at one point.
We did a couple of little surprise things that were done unscheduled on AFR,
plus the private show on my website. We did two of them, but only one of them was retained
by the recording. So about 80 hours of stuff, right? On average, two hours each.
Yeah. Roughly 80 hours is what will be all told here altogether. And the way I see it is pretty
much the same stuff has been said over and over again.
Right. Okay. Yeah. Well, why not? Right? I mean...
Listen, repetition is not... I'm not being insulting by saying it was repetitious. I'm just...
Oh, no, no. Here's the thing. How can you move forward? You've got to... It's like preheat.
You've got to get up to the right temperature. And obviously, this is not the society for it.
Here's the thing, Chuck. And it's easy to say objectively that the message or the reports that
are done on the ONG is not for this society at large, period. Because 99% of what's discussed
is the obvious, right? Speaking of the obvious, right? How do we start off by discussing what day
it is, right? I mean, why is that even important? Go think about that. If you're going to have to
report back to the mothership, you have to be objective. You can't come to this planet and say,
well, I like strawberry ice cream, and this, that, and the other. You have to be objective.
And when you objectify the condition, it's relatively foreign to the population at large,
relatively. Meaning that if you say, what's lawful timekeeping? Do you know what day it is?
The first thing they do, whatever aspect of society, they're going to run to the Pope's
work schedule, right? If you ask about all these things that we've discussed, they're pretty obvious
points. But I always love how people look at their wrist, even though they don't wear wrist
watches and haven't for several years. Still do that. I always appreciate that little pantomime
myself. But here's the other thing. There's Uncommonradio.com, and that's basically a
courtesy website. So if someone asks if you have a site, you don't look unprepared,
and there's just archives. Perhaps the Greek sonic emanations and reports will continue,
and that will be pretty much the hub, Uncommon Radio. And AFR pretty much had a discussion
with Danny, and he's like, just keep it going if you want. And I'm like, well, I don't know what
I want at this point. I think we have to do what we know. And that's the thing. People always do
what they know, right? That's why nothing gets done. Anyway, but yeah, there'll be more to come.
It's just the thing is, the things that are discussed are out of time and out of place
at this point. It just has no place in this society. But here's the thing. The topics and
the way things are discussed and reported on is for the next society to come. Not a political
society as people know it, and not as a... When I say political, it means like everything is
revolving around political notions and political conventions, right? This is a non-political
society that's coming, meaning it will not be based on anything that, other than being able
to turn on a pot and boil water and throw a chicken or an egg in there or bake some bread,
nothing will transfer over, because it will be based on real materialism, real spirituality,
well, versus fake. What's that, right? You know, what's interesting is when you have certain
discussions, you say, well, that sounds spiritual or religious, and I'm not that. Well, the people
that are stuck in materialism don't even know anything about materialism, because if the people
that are materialistic were really so, wouldn't they complain about all their fluids being stored
in flat-bottom containers? Yeah, you would think. Let's say, wait a second, all fluids should be in
an ovoid container. Why do we, right? Wouldn't they be calling their engineers and their academics
and saying, why don't you design heating and cooling systems that make a rarefied rising cold
and a densifying descending heat like it is in nature? So, the ones that are saying that they're
materialistic and the criticism of, you hear people, oh, they're materialistic. No, they're not,
because how well-versed or have they mastered materialism to be dubbed materialists?
So, what does that mean? It's the opposite, right? Right. Everything is the opposite. When you go,
you think you're going to get an education, you're being dumbed up. When you think you're going to
a place to get health, you're being made unhealthy. When you think you're going to a place,
you're going to learn about spirituality, you're going the opposite, or you're learning actually
about demonology, on and on and on and on. So, everything is backwards. So, how many times have
you heard, again, people being dubbed materialistic? What do they know about the material world?
Nothing. And are they paying attention at all? So, that's what I mean. These reports are for
the next society, because in the next society, if someone is dubbed as a materialist,
they will be an expert in that, you see. So, anyway. Now, can you say that people are expert
at being dumb? I don't know. I think they're not really, even though I call people morons and
idiots, which is a technical term. They're really stubborn and rebellious, is really what it is.
And they're apathetic. So, all the instruction, all the knowledge, all the imparting will not change
until the stubbornness and the apathetic or apathy goes away. So, that's how you top off
a limited sonic series, right? Because whenever we get together, we say everything should be
limited. Everything should be packaged in a container somehow. Right? So, okay.
Now, fair enough. I'm actually trying to drag someone into the conversation
on Skype. So, please continue. All right. Yeah. I can dummy load the audience for a few minutes,
maybe. I don't know. Do you want to talk about what everybody else is talking about,
maybe? I don't know. Well, why would we want to do that? I mean, after all, this is the final
chapter here of this. Do you want to use up the time doing that? Actually, it's really difficult
to do that. But here's the thing. What people are not used to is having something explained
clearly from the beginning and clearly showing an end. Do you ever notice how
things are not begun and ended neatly? Right? You sound like John Bonham on the keyboard.
Yeah. Sorry about that. But I'm trying to do what I said. Sorry.
So, either way. Yeah. So, the thing is, for example, in classrooms, they have the children
in there. I mean, anyway. And they ring the bell. Everybody gets up, goes to the next one. So,
anything maybe that isn't worth finishing isn't worth starting. Right? So, you've got to keep
things. You know, construction projects have a start date and an end date. So,
well, the interesting thing about giving objective reports is that it's very unique and it's very,
very simple. And anyone can see it. But it's just, again, the apathy and the rebelliousness
and the stubbornness not to. And one interesting way to explain the condition of humanity is
actually by reading the emails that get at Uncommon Radio by the people who are reaching out
and saying, hey, you know, I want to just message you through the email. And if you read like 99%
of the emails are very well thought out and objective. It's not like, oh, I really like what
you're saying. You know, none of that stuff. You know, it's just, hey, look, I heard I heard the
report on this. I checked it out. Holy crap. It's. Yeah. Right. Or what about you mentioned this,
but what about that? Right. Very, very objective, which which sheds a positive light on the on
the ability to get responses. In other words, it's a good thing to to have a way for people to
respond or communicate with through what's called email or call ins if they want to call in
the Ocelli and the Greek Skype is down right now. So.
Right. I'm doing my best to drag people in through my Skype. Yes, there you are.
Hi there. I dragged you right into the conversation. So you're actually on the air with us.
Just took me a minute because my Skype is muddy. Sorry about that. No worries at all.
So I know that you wanted to make sure that you added in a question or a comment to this show
because you were reaching out earlier. So by all means, go right ahead. Thank you. Well,
I wanted to ask the Greek concerning some of the things that he's talked about regarding
Christianity, what he calls Christianity and how it's called. Yeah. Yeah. How he's been
critical of certain things and talked about the questionability of certain things.
And he's talked a lot about the translations as far as the King James not being a translation
and certain things not being accurate. And I think that that's all been very well.
But he hasn't really touched on the New Testament aspect of things. And he hasn't
really expressed any thoughts or reports on things such as what they call salvation or
accepting the work of Christ or having one's name written in the book of life,
sort of the things that Christians believe are the things that actually get them to heaven or
get them saved. And I wanted to know if he had any kind of report or opinion on things like that.
I believe I gave you an email on that. And I see you have a lot of fervor
and zeal to have this discussed openly. And typically when I get together with Chuck,
nothing personal, Chuck, but Chuck shuts down when we speak about scriptural stuff. I know,
I know, I know. But that's why I like to keep it more general. And the scriptural stuff is
misunderstood. Regarding Christianity at large, nothing that's discussed
viably in Christianity is biblical. Zero. Now, in order to have a rational discussion,
if 1% of Christianity was biblical, you'd have to grant it to be rational. If a 2%, 5%, or if one
thing in Christianity was rational, you'd have to grant it. Otherwise, it sounds irrational to say
nothing in Christianity is biblical. At least in a positive sense. There are a lot of things in the
biblical text, both in the King James and in the original language of preservation, that condemn
by description, not by name, what Christianity does and its believers and followers through
their actions. So we have to establish that through research. You can't just take things
as they're said. Now, you went through a few different points. There is no such thing as a
New and Old Testament. It's all one contiguous document. Yes, that's fine. The whole thing about
new and old, all that is not in the scriptures. There's no part, there's nothing there that
delineates that. Just like there aren't 66 books, there are 49 books. It was devised,
books were devised and divided to create the 66 number. Because from a sort of an occult way,
whenever you're addressing mankind by mankind, it's usually divisible by sixes. So they did that.
Now, the other thing you said regarding salvation, I always bring this up, actually for a decade,
to quote-unquote the born-again sect when they talk about being saved. Ask them, what are you
being saved from? And they don't know. Or they cannot give you a scriptural answer.
The concept of salvation is very, very, very, very, very simple. Now, here's the other point.
I'll get back to what you're being saved from, which these people that profess faith in this
particular era don't know. If they said condemnation, would that be accurate?
No. Well, condemnation would be execution of judgment in the sense as it's reared verbally
before it's done. Condemnation, you see, that's another thing. It's like judging and
condemning, right? Now, you've got to realize that we started off earlier by discussing it's the
obvious that we like to report on, right? So what's obvious is when people talk about being saved,
what are you being saved from? And they don't know. I've gotten answers like sin or things like that.
That's a behavior. How can you be saved from a behavior? That's like, you know, you got up in
the middle of the night and you stubbed your big toe on a kitchen table. How are you going to be
saved from that? It's done. That's not where you're being saved from, right? Because sin is
not an issue until it's performed. So you're not being saved. It's very simple. Now, the other
thing I think you mentioned in one of the written correspondences is the writings of what's known as
the disciple or apostle Shaul or Paul. Shaul would be the name in preservation, let's say,
right? More of an Aramaic. The reason why I don't discuss a lot of the points and the apologetics,
apologize me to defend, of what they call the New Testament is because that is on a PhD level.
Like the Genesis and first third of the biblical text would be kindergarten to fifth grade,
and then it would be fifth grade to eighth grade and through the Psalms. And then you get to the
later prophets, which would be graduating from high school. And the New Testament would be
bachelor's degree and PhD. And who they call the apostle Paul is speaking on a PhD level.
And if you've ever listened to the recordings that we've done here, I've always brought that in mind
as a metaphor, where if you were to lecture a group of five year olds on astrophysics for an
hour, they will all be quiet. And after the hour, you ask them if they have any questions,
and they all raise their hands and the question is the same. Do you have any candy? Right? See?
So discussing now, let's just boil it down. Let's just give it away. It's like the Greek
speaking in circles now. Why don't we just give it away? What you're being saved from is death.
The entire biblical text is about three things. It's about life, it's about death,
and everything in between and after, which is the law. The law is how you deal with the
environment. Right? I've asked people, what is law? And no one can answer. It's the simplest
thing in the world. Right? Okay, so here's the thing. Who they call the Apostle Paul was writing
about was to convince those that knew. Do you remember reading somewhere and they said the Christ,
when he met some pagans, he says, I didn't come for you, I came for the lost ones of Israel. Right?
Right, right.
Right? Okay, that's not what it says. If you go look in the original language,
I didn't come for you, I came for the deceased or those that are departed from Israel,
meaning those that are dead. Because the people, he didn't come for those who didn't know what
scripture means. People that knew the promises that were given to the original man and woman
was that you're going to die. But you it will not be a terminal condition, you will be subject
to reincarnation or resurrection, meaning brought back. And this was a promise. And it went on and
on for 1000s of years. And the Christ came for one purpose only was to show that when you die,
what happens after you die that you can't be brought back physically. Right? And then you
have a new body because you can choose in that reincarnated state to be physical or non physical,
right? This is discussed in many of the prophets as well. So see, I find this I find this really
interesting, because some of the readings that I've done of what I believe to be biblical text,
okay, point to the idea that the Christ figure says, that this is the new law that he has
actually come to bring the new law, that that the old law is actually gone. That's not what it says
at some point that he is not trying to do away with the old law doesn't doesn't say that either.
Because here you ready, I'm going to drop this on both of you.
The word law is not in there. In scripture is the teaching.
Well, no, I understand that. But no, no, no, it's different. The law is brought up in there
as well. There are laws, but the teachings. Well, and this is also what is different is now what
is the teaching that if you are no longer subject to death, it's a different set of rules. Then if
you're subject, that was going to be my point is that if you're coming with a different teaching,
right, you have a different set of laws, because you're no longer sub. Well, you're no longer
subject to the old system. Let's just describe it as the system. I know that's not the word used,
but I mean, right or wrong. Okay, hold on. I think you let's not miss the point here.
What he said was irrelevant to those that don't know the purpose. In other words, if you read the
prophets talk about many will take interest in this, but it will be a stumbling block on them.
What's a stumbling block, something that makes you trick. Now, here's the interesting thing.
If you study scripture, you will find out through the prop, even the Christ after he was resurrected
said, if you want to know who I am, you have to know what Moses said, the prophets and the Psalms.
That's why modern Christianity tells you don't read the Old Testament, because
every, you know, here's the point. This is very, very simple. There are movies that have been done
like Men in Black, when he says, when you put on this suit, no one will be able to remember you,
you'll be like some form of, you know, whatever, deja vu or something, right?
The most interesting quality of the biblical Christ, which is in the text, by the way,
if you know how to read out of it, is that he was invisible, not invisible, you know,
you could see him in the room. But if he knocked on your door and came in right now where you are
and sat with you and spoke with you for three hours and left and someone asked you five minutes
later, what did he look like? You'd say, well, you know, he looked like a man. Okay, what color
was his hair? I think it was brown or black. Or how tall was he? I'm not sure. Right? He had this
ability of invisibility. In other words, he looked he mixed in with whoever was there. That's why
when you see, when the people wanted to throw him over the cliff for what he was saying,
how did he escape that? He just turned around and walked right through the crowd.
Right? When when people when his mother asked him to do something, if I do this, they'll know who I
am. He was invisible. That's why he had spoken in the what's called the New Testament, he had
directly engaged the Pharisees, at least four times. And yet when it came time to his arrest,
they didn't know how to describe him to be arrested. So they had to hire Judas to betray
him with a kiss. Right? Because even though they knew who he was, when they heard him and looked
at him a minute later, they could not recognize him. That's why he had to betray him with a kiss
to show his kit show us who he is. So So here's the interesting part of what you're being shown
this long haired thing, whatever, nailed to a cross wearing a diaper. And there's other stuff
you see in movies where he looks real dirt, you know? Yeah, that is Serapis, or a skepulous.
Right? You go look up Serapis, the cult of Serapis. Have you? If you look at the cult of a
skepulous who was a god of health? They always have you ever heard Christians say God bless you?
Yeah, not just after a sneeze, but like, Oh, God bless you. Goodbye. You know, that is a typical
saying of the cult of a skepulous. It has nothing to do is not, you will not find that in Scripture
at all. God bless. I've also heard that that character is some form of Ascension Master.
So here's the thing about all that is, there is a fascination and every Okay, this is another
thing to explain. And I never thought OMG, would be a discussion of Scripture. But let me just let
me make this point clear about 90% of the emails I get out on common radio and before was regarding
Scripture. So there is a strong desire, as I said, over a decade ago, you're going to see this topic
coming up more and more as the future comes, but none of it will be accurate, because the time to
speak on this accurately, is not now. Because desire, the desire is desire, but the knowledge,
the knowledge in an accurate fashion is not right. And it's not in the knowledge is no special thing,
you just have to do it, you just have to do the work. But the thing is, okay, do you remember
seeing photographs in the 1970s, people were polyester bell bottoms and wide lapels and real
tacky colors. Why did they do that? Because aesthetically was pleasing? Hell no. The reason
why they did it because it was fashionable. Right now, it's still fashionable to be like
the fox and the grapes. Oh, you know, who knows what knows what about Scripture? Oh, yeah, who knows?
That's no good. My idea is better. Because no one is looking because if you look, you will be very
unpopular. Now, here's the other thing regarding if you're approaching anything, even if it's the
newspaper, and you're prepared to read into it, what you think it's going to say, you will leave
there pretty happy with any body of work, but you will get nothing out of it. Now, the entire
civilization on the planet right now, when you approach any religion has already been bombarded
through Hollywood, which controls the mindset through audio and visual, and other conventions,
literary and such, that whenever you bring up Islam, Christianity, Buddhism, or whatever, you
have a preconceived notion through these other forms of media, what this is. And when you start
looking at the text that these things are allegedly subscribed to, you see certain key
phrases, and you overlay all the stuff that was overlaid on you, which is false. So in other words,
when you say that, for example, I'm not putting you on the spot here, because I do appreciate your
very well thought out, I think we did correspond written on the email as well, is that you're
bringing all the propaganda that's been going on for the past 1800 years, and trying to make it
fit into something that it's not even out of. So you're trying to get into it instead of reading
out of it, right? Right. But I do feel like some of the way that you're describing it kind of does it
does make it sound like this type, the knowledge, the true knowledge concerning what the biblical
text is talking about is very esoteric, as if there's only a very small amount of people that
could understand it within a very specialized form of studying it and context. And that kind of does
feel like it does away with a large population of people that would subscribe to that belief.
Yeah, it does. Because you're being impressed, don't be impressed by numbers. There's always
been a very few people always on the planet. There's as a matter of fact, if you do a little
bit of research, you can find the number, it's very small. It's only four figures.
Don't be impressed by quantity, the gods. Okay. Like, you've heard me say, like, we don't know
what a bear is. But we know enough of a bear that we can say we know what bears are. Because no one
sat down and had a five hour conversation with a bear. But we know they're, you know, they're furry.
And there's, you know, like this, and like that, and like this big observation. So we don't know,
really who the gods are. But we have enough information from them that we supposedly from
them, that we know about them, that one of the characteristics of the gods is anything they do,
they're doing great number when they create right cells in the body, planets, stars, grains of sand
on the beach people. But even they tell you specifically, there are certain qualities to look
for. This is the possibility of Yeah, good. Well, what you just said about the fact that the
that are not to be deceived by numbers, and that we don't exactly know who the gods are,
but then what would you write off? Yeah, but would you write off the testimonies of people that have
claimed to have firsthand experiences, as far as like revelations of heaven or hell, or
there is no parable, for example, Jesus talking about the rich man burning in hell, and then there
would be people that say that, well, I went there too. And they've read about translation, that would
be the lake of fire. There is no heaven, no one goes to heaven, and no one goes to hell, the word
that is being used as hell is the grave. And so everyone goes to the grave. And heaven, no one
goes to heaven, because heaven is coming here, like it was during the flood. And before the flood,
heaven is a realm, there are three of them. So, so some people say that they've been there.
In contrast, some people. Well, yeah, sure, sure, sure. There, I've heard someone testify that he
saw a demonic looking figure come into the room, very much Hollywood demonic looking figure. And he
calls it in the name of Jesus. And this long haired flowing thing came around and shoot the demon
away. That's just two lower low level entities having fun. So in other words, the there are low
level and entities meaning like, not elementals, because elementals are indifferent to mankind.
These are like low level angelic type elementals, that they're sitting at the bar. And they're
saying, man, we got so many people down here, I bet you that if I go out and show up as this Jesus
Christ character that they see on TV, and you show up as the devil character they see on TV,
we're going to have a field day and the sky is going to fall for it. And they do that.
The same thing with ghosts. Well, people see, you know, this house is haunted by a little girl
that died here 100 years ago, and people see the little girl walking around on the second floor.
That's, that's, that's one of these entities playing a joke on you, man. They know what's
on TV, they know what iconography you have. They can't read your mind. You have to say, you know,
so anyway, they could also there are other entities that plant dreams in the head
while you're sleeping. So once you start, here's the other thing I'm going to advise people on.
Once you start studying reality, your dreaming stops. Or if they try to bring a dream on you,
you might be like, hey, you know what, I ain't having it. They go away.
Because all benevolent gods or angels that send a dream to they identify themselves by name,
why they're coming to you, and so on and so forth.
Doesn't it say something in the Bible similar to always test the spirits as far as making
sure of who they are? So in that case, I guess they wouldn't always identify themselves,
you'd have to inquire as to who they are, make sure that they're real.
But you also have to look at the conditions that around 1960 years ago, all this was shut off.
And anything that has come until a time in the future, and any contact with the spiritual world
from 1960 years until a time here coming in the near future, is these malevolent entities.
And malevolent entities always show themselves as being good, or beneficial or just there.
The scripture is very clear, actually, I'll cite some of this is, if they say here he is at the
mountains, don't go. If they here he is at the desert, don't go. It's not me. Right? Have you
remember that? Yeah, until the time is set. So, so, you know, here, you know, if you want to learn
about how these revelations work, go study some of the, quote, unquote, Islamic reports on the,
on the jinn. I've personally met a woman who, when this topic came up, she, she froze and she says,
Listen, I really don't like talking about this, but it seems like you know about this. And she
gave me a firsthand account of a family member who was actually captured by one of these jinn,
you know, and she knew because I knew by the way I was speaking that I wouldn't be laughing at her,
right? Well, I definitely I feel like there's validity in saying that you have these malevolent
spirits that that show up and prank people continuously. But, but the idea that you have
also an omnipresent omnipotent God, let's call him supreme being that can do whatever he wants,
and that he wouldn't intervene or take a step to also show people stop, stop, let's go back
omnipresent. If scripture just because something is very a bit of information is very short,
like a verse could be four words or three words strung together, right? Doesn't mean it's not
important. Give you an example, if someone is on a cruise ship, and they fall overboard,
and he says, Help me, I'm drowning. Oh, what did he say? Oh, that was too short can't be important.
Right? So it when you say he's omnipresent and omnipotent, how does he do that? He tells you
how he does that he has another species that does that for him. There are species on that. So have
you ever heard of caribou? They're pretty freakish looking. They have four with wings and four faces
and right. Have you ever heard of angels? They appear they don't have wings, by the way,
they appear as men solely. Right? And then they have other angels that are elemental. And then
there is a particular species or a type of heavenly creature that performs the duty of
the omnipresence for the Creator. And I'm not going to say who that is right now. It's because
it is it's not a who as we it's not anthropomorphic. It is something that is made up of
seven things. And it's one body part. I'll just give you a hint. You know, here's the thing is,
they're called the seven eyes. And it looks like imagine a creature that is made up of seven eyes.
Right? And there's, look, here's the thing. I had a conversation recently with someone a few
months ago recently. And he said, Listen, I got time, I want to ask you a couple of questions,
it'll be short. And three hours later, we're still on there. You know, because he was expecting really
short pat answers, you know, like, you know, everything that people try to discuss, you know,
he thought he would hear again. And he interrupted and he says, Man, you're bursting at the seams.
You know, and I said, Yeah, I am. I've got a hold. I've got a hold back. That's why I think on this
uncommon radio thing, and I'll just say here, I'm going to do that ridiculous thing that everyone
else is doing a membership area, where, where you just join, I guess, and you, you, you look at a
menu of various topics, as, as the ones that we are discussing right now, openly. Okay, well,
that's seven, and the seven eyes are mentioned, but it's very short. Right? But But because Oh,
but wait a second, Greek, that's too short to be important. Wait a second. You know, right?
forensics, they can actually sorry, in forensics, they could build a case based on a fiber that is
microscopic, right? Hmm.
Well, I mean, I guess, I guess, in wrapping up this particular question, I just, it feels a bit
counterintuitive, this idea that, and I've always kind of wrestled with this, you have billions of
people on the planet, a few more billion historically. And there's, it just feels like
this, this idea of them being as countless as sand, and yet being completely disposable. And
then you have this tiny group of people that somehow managed to access the truth. And those
are the people that sort of pass the test, or whatever. Yeah, you don't want to be, you don't
want to be one of those people. Because if you're loved by the gods, you're hated by men. And if
you're loved by men, you're hated by the gods. And they make your life a living hell in quotation
marks. But doesn't don't the gods love men, like, why set up a system that, you know, most people
are not going to be able to pass the threshold, because waste, because all the gods all from the
lowest to the highest are malevolent to humanity right now. What I mean by malevolent is if any of
them showed up as they are, you would disintegrate painfully. So they have to shield themselves. And
their world is so dynamic, that that we cannot imagine the dynamics involved in the power
involved. So they're all malevolent at the point that we're in right now. Just like if you were a
goldfish in a bowl, all the inhabitants in the apartment that the goldfish was sitting in are
malevolent to you. Because all they have to do is reach in, pull you out of the goldfish and set you
on the coffee table and you are gasping for water. You cannot, you cannot go, you cannot interface
with them. But if you're, if you're an all powerful God, you can just turn yourself into a goldfish
and interface with them. And that's what a lot of testimonies are. Exactly. Then that's what's being
done. But you have to look at the conditions. The Christ, by the way, if you read from Genesis
all the way to Revelation, who, to Revelation, except for Revelation, that was written and
dictated to prophets by the Christ. That's why one litmus test to someone who says they know the
Bible is very simple is that when Moses was speaking, you know, at the bush, who was he
speaking to? And if they just say God and generic, they don't know. I mean, just keep walking because
that's too generic. That was the Christ that he was speaking to. Right. Everything. The only,
the only dictation that is not from the Christ is the book of Revelation. It's very clear. It was
from the father to the son to his servants. That's why if you don't fit that servant class,
you will not. I assure you, if you are religious in any of the mainstream religions or offshoots,
I assure you this, you will not understand anything in the book of Revelation at all.
Period. Other than the word the up and down or white or black or red, you will not understand
anything because it is not for the believers. It is for the servant. Like give you an example.
If you and I are roommates and you believe I'm a roommate and you, I believe you're a roommate and
you come home one day and ask me to wash your socks. I'll say a few men. But if I'm your servant
and you come home and you say, wash my socks, Greek, I'll say, yes, sir. Because that's the
position I have. Most of the people on the planet today that are, quote unquote, believers are
giving lip service. There is no law. Right. And they say, well, he's just love, but they forget
that there's four or three different types of love. So, you know, the thing is, the time is
coming. What's really exciting for everyone that's listening is starting around a year from now.
There's going to be a more discrediting of current convention, which you are seeing.
And I'll give you some I've been saying this for over a decade and what you're it's coming on right
now. Like, for example, there's right now there's the whole thing about the media being discredited,
even by the American political leader. There is a discreditation about the medical society there.
It still has not become a discreditation of the legal society and the financial society somewhat.
But what you will start seeing starting next year is a discreditation of all
mainstream religions. And it's starting right now. Right. And then what will happen is that topic,
any any mainstream religion in topical nature at its core is about the gods or gods. Right.
That's otherwise it wouldn't be dubbed mainstream religion because they all have some form of God.
They've really messed up by what they're doing. They would have been better off representing,
you know, like what Monsanto does or whatever, then what they're doing. Because when you start
misrepresenting the gods, as the mainstream religions are, all of them and the minor ones,
you are going to be in a little bit of trouble. So let me just bring this point up. In the future,
perhaps within a decade, all of your religious people right now that are famous,
you will run into them and they will deny ever being in that field.
On TV evidence. I mean, that's kind of. Yeah. But but they will still. Yeah. Or worse.
Or worse. Yeah. So this is going to be an interesting time that's coming. And I always
suggest that people it doesn't matter if it's the human body of any of the religious texts,
politics, money, physics, water, anything, go to what's been memorialized about that topic.
Right. Right. As far as start there, as far as this period that you're speaking of,
how much validity would you place on the speakings and the writings of people like
Anthony Patch, who talks about CERN and this idea that you have a portal that's going to be opened
and no, no, no. OK, hold on. This is what you're going to find out about CERN. Have you ever heard
of a TV show called Pimp My Ride where they take an old car and OK, and they throw. OK, CERN is
the pimp my ride for the physicists. They took all of the junk rubbish, mentally disturbed people,
all the junk rubbish manufacturing processes, all the junk rubbish, electrical theories and
physical theories and threw billions and gajillions or whatever credits at it to build
a model to show basically we have access to the credit system and you don't, sucka. Right. And
we got spinning rims on this CERN and all this other stuff. And we got a pop up 42 inch TV on
the trunk. Look, don't fall for it. Now, I'm not going to say don't fall for it because I've
I was going to do a Skype call with someone about a week ago and say I only got 10 minutes because
someone wants to watch a movie with me. I said, great, listen, when people sit down and want to
watch a movie, I get the chair and I sit opposite of them and I watch them watching the movie.
You learn a lot more because the movies, I mean, there hasn't been really any film worth watching
because I know the Hollywood, it's basically stupid people making entertainment for more
stupid people. Don't get sucked up into it anyway. And it's a harsh criticism, but I assure you,
it's pretty objective. Or it could be people in the know making movies for stupid people,
hoping to dumb them down. Well, yeah, it could be, but it's not. But I don't want to be harsh.
I don't want to go there right now, but watch what people do. So when you watch Pimp My Ride,
watch people watching Pimp My Ride, how excited and how into it they are. Watch people that talk
about CERN. They know nothing about physics. They know nothing about the money system. They know
nothing about the gods or spiritual systems at all. Well, we've said that you said in the past
that a lot of knowledge is suppressed and that everything that was allegedly, yeah, that was to
be known about physics and science was known in the late 19th century. Yeah. So so if we're talking
about institutions like CERN, wouldn't it stand to reason that that is a field where the suppressed
knowledge is being used for their own private purposes? No, no, because everything that was
known was abandoned with the advent of Einstein around the 1920s or so. They abandoned everything
for relativity and the elect Walt Disney's electron and proton. In the public, you mean, though,
and the private, too. Yeah, well, we don't know. Private would be university, but we don't know.
Well, let me let me assure you of one thing. Do research a little bit on J.J. Thompson in 1895.
He showed that what you call weight and momentum is not in mass. That means that it doesn't matter
if it's a lead brick or a feather. You have the illusion of him weighing different, not because
of the material, but because of electrical lines of force that attach to it. This was 1895. By the
1920s, there were elevating submarines at a rate of 10,000, 10,000, I'm sorry, 10,000 meters per
second or five. I'm sorry, 40 seconds for 10,000 meters. And they use submarines because they were
already designed for the pressure. They locked. That's why when you hear about those cigar shaped
UFOs, you can go to any of the Navy diagrams of submarines and identify it as a submarine without
the propeller and the rudder. You could actually scale it. So in private, you're not being given
anything because decisions have been made around that time period in accordance with the cosmic
censorship that was put on humanity that I've discussed that the gods put on humanity 2,500
years ago. So decisions were made, but that means that decisions were made in private by certain
elites, right? Yes. Well, aren't you one of the elites? Think about it. Well, in regard to the
institutions of this world, I mean, the elites. Yeah. So, you know, the higher, you know, the
thing about what's going on, though, if you read what the gods have memorialized,
the worst of men are put as leaders, right? They don't think if you want to know what the gods
think of you, look at who they put as your leaders. You don't vote anyone into public
office or kingship, right? The gods according to what they think of the society is what the
what leader they fashion over you. So they don't think. But here's the point. There was if you
study scripture and meditate on it means keep thinking about it, you will find out that there
was a there is a conflict in the heavenly realm, right? Where one third of the spiritual beings
sort of revolted, supposedly the term is not really revolt, but have fallen away from the
main from the main from the main course, the main course of attitude and convention in that realm.
They decided to pull themselves out and do other things, OK, based on the creation. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And I can get into that in the second hour, if you like. Otherwise, we'll
see if you want to hold on. Right. So we're going to go into the next hour. And obviously,
if you think about who has been placed in leadership above the American people, well,
I guess the gods don't think much of us anyway. No, Ocelli in the Greek
continues for the final chapter. Stay tuned to American Freedom Radio. We'll be right back.
The second hour of the final chapter of Ocelli in the Greek begins here on American Freedom
Radio and American Freedom Radio dot com. Of course, I am one half of that sonic entity.
Chuck Ocelli is my name. Don't often say it during this show, but figured I'll throw it in
just for the sake of noting it. So I am here with the Greek and we've actually held over our caller
who I didn't identify in the first hour at all. But hey, we don't necessarily need to identify him,
although I don't know Greek. What do you think? Oh, it's up to him. Go ahead and state your name
and purpose if you like. Otherwise, we continue with the conversation.
Thanks. My name is Sam. I'm a guy calling from Sweden and just recently came across the show
maybe two, three weeks ago. And I'm a big fan of it. I'm sorry that this is the last episode.
Well, yeah. And here's the thing. Like Sam, if you wish, you can join in via the convention
of the phone at 218-339-8525. That is, again, I'll slow it down. 218-339-8525. I have control
of the phone line. I also have control of the Skype because there was a little bit of a thing
that went on here. So Charles Ocelli spelled O-C-H-E-L-L-I on Skype. If you send me a request
that you want to join in or a message, if you're already on my list, I will add you into the
conversation as well. So there you go. This is the way you can join into the show, which was the
difference when we reloaded it this time. We encourage callers for every single show.
Two varying levels of success, Greg. Yeah. Now, Charles, wait a second. Charles Dotto Ocelli.
I mean, that sounds like freaking royalty, man. What's up? But anyway. Okay. I'm just done. All
right. Okay. That's okay. You know, listen, my middle name makes it even worse. It's okay.
All right. So just to finish up a thought, the conflict that there is, now here's the point.
It's very difficult to discuss this because you sound like a real nutter if you have imaginary
friends, right? Now, you sound even crazier if you start to discuss a civilization or a society that
is intangible other than the information that's been memorialized about them. Now,
any information, by the way, when it's not understood cannot be good, right? Now,
I think the Aesop's fables, the fox and the grapes, right? The fox can't get the grapes. Oh,
those grapes must be sour then. And that's all the discussion you hear about anything,
whether it's the money system, the body, the way the human body works in the medical system,
any of the ancient texts or anything. It can't be good. We can't look there because we don't
understand it. So that would mean that these things are memorialized in futility and that's
not what they are. The problem is that people want to read into them what they've been
propagandized about before the fact of approaching the information and they're trying to compare
what they've been propagandized on with what's actually memorialized and it's not a very good
conversion. So they have to walk away saying, I don't understand legal documents. I don't
understand medical documents. I don't understand this and that. It can't be any good because it's
not just the television. It's been the pranking and it's been what you might call social engineering,
which has backfired. And we'll get back to the topic here. Those that knew, I've always said this
with Chuck here. The difference between those that know and those that don't know, it's not like,
you're in another room. You're in a different universe. The margin is so big that when the
priesthood, by the way, when I say priesthood, those are the people that have knowledge in any
society. They wear certain robes and depending on the culture, they had access to this information
and they noticed that the people didn't want it and they started dividing themselves and saying
these people are savages. And instead of taking the time and showing it to them, they separated
themselves and they called them the great unwashed, savages, sheeple, whatever, whatever.
And they started looking at them as being repugnant and vile, which they are. I'm not
saying that they're not now. Objectively, people are typically repugnant and vile as a group,
majority. So the thing is not to make excuses for them because they're part of the creation.
And when the creation changes, which it is, it will change as well. And those that are in the
leadership positions are going to be in a little bit of hot water, in the hot seat,
not because they're going to be directly offended through actionable causes, but because they will
be ignored and put into irrelevancy. So with that interjected, the problem that is going on
in the other realm, right? It sounds like crazy people now talking about the gods, is that if you
read out of scripture, you will see there is constantly a metaphor that is being given.
And it's a contrast between the material, physical flesh body and the spirit, the mind body, right?
What the spirit wants is not for the body. What the body wants is not good for the spirit.
Sometimes, not always, right? And there's a lot of sayings regarding good body, good mind,
and all this other stuff. So the problem is that there was a debate to a certain extent about
the creation on whether or not a spirit can be solely animated through physical means.
And the call by a third of them was, no, because if you animate the spirit through the physical
means, it's subject to corruption. And also, the spirit will take the material to a limit,
which could not be good. So you have to separate. And they said, no, let's do it because it'll be
the ultimate, let's say, combination for starting off a new way in the universe, right?
Mm-hmm.
So the whole thing here to test the durability and the veracity of it,
those third are saying, okay, go mess with them then. You didn't want this to happen. It happened.
It's been created. So go ahead and put them through a torture test. Just like, for example,
when manufacturers build a car, they crash test it, they put it in a room, and they put high
pressure water on it for three days in a row to simulate 10 years of rain, right? You've seen,
right? That kind of stuff, where they put product like certain laboratories, right?
Right.
So we're being tested by these malevolent spirits, but not overtly. Now, this was done
overtly during the flood. If you read the book of Job, he talks, have you ever heard of the term,
the anaf? It's a Hebrew term, which is the dark cloud or the cloud, I believe, in the King James
event mentioned as that. Well, if you look at that, have you seen the film? I hate to make film
references, but this is how people communicate these days. Independence Day, where this cloud,
and the big ship comes down, and there's this dark cloud that appears, you know?
Okay. What people fail to recall or read out of scripture is the mothership, okay,
was still visible by mankind up until the flood. What mothership is that? Can I just throw in a
few extra little tidbits here? Have you ever heard of something called the Garden of Eden?
Where does it say in scripture that was on the earth? Nowhere, because it was not on the earth,
it was on the mothership, and even though the rivers flowed out of it, guess what? When the
mothership left, I'm using the term mothership, so did the Garden of Eden, and all these idiots
today are still saying, oh, the Garden of Eden's in Africa, the Garden of Eden's in Alaska,
the Garden of Eden's here. What are you talking about? Where are you getting this stuff from?
Are you reading what, at least, here's the other point. If you use a phrase, a verb,
I mean, a phrase, or a term, or a subject that is taken out of a body of work, where that is
defined in that body of work, you have no right, no freedom, and no license to redefine it, right?
So, if you read something, let's say, for example, Lucifer, or Garden of Eden, or this or that,
those terms originate in the biblical text, and they're defined there as well. You can't take a
term, let's say a medical term like nephrology, and define it as a form of making ice cream. No,
because it's defined within the body that you got it from, right? So, what's going on is people are
grabbing these catchphrases, and they're leaving the definitions that are right in the same text,
and they're redefining it, and you're not allowed to do that. That's completely corrupt,
unless you find corruption to be allowable, which it seems to be. You know, you meaning whoever,
you know, allows this type of stuff to go on and promotes it. So, you have a situation here where
the current existence is so different than anything that was, that you read about,
scripturally, that it's hard to reconcile the thought of what you see as reality today,
with what was going on back then. The other thing that's difficult is you've all been
propagandized to the point that change takes millions and billions of years,
where certain changes can happen very rapidly, like, for example, petrified trees. You know,
when a tree dies, it falls over within five years. So, if a tree is petrified in a vertical
state, that means that process happened in less than five years, or began to happen, right? So,
you know, things like the Grand Canyon took millions of years. No, they didn't. There's
something called cavitation, right? So, there are many of these processes. I'm not saying that
there's a Christian thing that says the earth is 6,000 years old. Nowhere does it say that in
scripture. It clearly states that there was a remodeling that started about 13,000 years ago.
Now, even in secular bullshit science, they tell you that in many, across the board, they say that
it appears to have been a solar system-wide catastrophe around 12,500-13,000 years ago,
right? So, the thing is, are we really looking at things? Are we really reading
out of them or reading into them? And it's really the second part. So, you know,
the questions that you brought up, so if you were to leave, let's just sum up what you've asked.
If you ask anyone what they're being saved from, they don't know. And if you go to scripture,
it's very clear that you're being saved from being in the grave, or dead,
because being dead is a state of, like, being asleep. Rest in peace. The cemetery is the Greek
word timitirion, which literally means a place where you go to sleep without dreaming, right?
Right. So, you're going to be, now, a lot of times people are confused by what I say,
because they don't, they're not listening. Is it Greek? You believe in reincarnation? I said,
well, not as it's being discussed, but yes, of course, it's for sure. Everyone will be
reincarnated or resurrected, absolutely. If the information is validatable and correct,
right? Right.
But no one has been yet, except for one, the prototype, right? Now, here's the interesting
thing. You have a lot of people also discussing the legend of the flood, the legend of the Christ,
the legend of this, the legend of that, every society, outside of whatever religion, of course.
When you have, let's say, a Christ-type figure in Egyptology, and a Christ-type figure in Hinduism,
and a Christ-type figure, you know, East, West, North, South, what does that tell you?
That there was an oral tradition that came down because everyone came from the same source,
right? You see this all the time in the military. You can have a bunch of guys in a platoon,
and after the war, they separate and they live all over the country. They're still going to tell
the story of their experience when they were all together. Even now, let's say they're all
over the country, different parts of the world, right? But they still tell the same story.
Don't they? Because it originated in the same spot. So, when you hear about people saying,
oh, well, that Christ thing, you know, that was also in Egypt, that's Osiris, and that's this,
and that, yeah, of course, all that does is proves that we all had the same origin.
And as everyone expanded and traveled away, it was kept, you know, these stories or accounts
were kept. Yeah, that's all it does, right? You see, this is very, but the thing is, who's going
to speak rationally and report rationally on these things when it's not fashionable? Right now,
it's fashionable to be Christian, by the way. So, you see rappers on stage wearing crucifixes,
right? It's a fashion statement, right? You know what I'm talking about? Yeah,
I know what you're talking about. Yeah, and there is no crucifix. The joke is on,
you know, there's no crucifixion in the biblical text, even though the Greek word Stavros is
translated as crucifix. If you look up the etymological term of crucifix, it's a botanical
term that has to do with botany, a flower blossoming in springtime. Anyway, it's very
clear that the Christ was, he was executed according to the law of Moses, right? It's very
clear Pontius Pilate knew the law. He says, I'm handing him back to you to use your law.
What law did the Judean authorities use? Roman crucifixion? Or do they use the law of Moses?
What's the method of public? What's the method of execution in the biblical text? It's death
by stoning. But high crimes you were to be stoned where you're nailed to a tree. Now,
what was the Christ accused of? What's the highest crime in the law of Moses? Blasphemy,
isn't it? That's the highest crime. And, you know, there's the whole thing. It's all just
one big fraud. But, but here's the thing. If you have an audience, you better accommodate them,
because you know what happens if you're not accommodating the audience, they dismantle,
they just go somewhere else where they will be accommodated, right? In business, that's called an
opportunity loss. Well, that I can understand that in the case of these like big mainstream
outlets that are clearly doing it doesn't matter. No, even the even the might you go to the smallest
little Bible study in someone's house, they're still pontificating the same rubbish. They're
even worse. The little groups are like little Hitler, little dictators, I shouldn't say,
how do you know, they're like little, they're, they're the worst form of terror would be go
study scripture and go to a little Bible study or a small church and watch what you want to see what
evil means. And then talk to them about it. I sort of get the image of Westboro Baptist Church at
that point, which is kind of to a different extreme, I feel, but I'm just military loves
a Baptist, by the way, because they're the easiest to convert over to certain satanic rituals. But
anyway, go ahead. You'd spoken about cosmic censorship. And I wanted to ask, you'd also
mentioned that you had these knowledge depositories in the past, like the Library of
Alexandria, that they were destroyed all over the world, not just there. Yeah. But what would you
say about current day depositories, such as the Vatican libraries or alleged satanic archives
that exist in hidden mansions? Okay, let me just throw this one thing in this entire world is ruled
by the God of this world, which is the adversary known as Hassan, which means the adversary, right?
He has a name, and I'm not going to use the name. And it's in Genesis, if you look at it,
and he's not it. And they translate it as serpent. There, you know how they show you,
by the way, in iconography, they have a naked man, a naked woman in an apple tree and a snake.
Yeah, you've ever heard of a man or a woman's name Robin,
or hawk, or does that mean that they're a bird? Because Robin could be male or female, right? A
man or a woman. If you if I said to you, I met someone named Robin, would you think of a bird or
you know, you know, someone right? No. So why are they translating a serpent when it's actually
someone's name? It was an anthropomorphic, it looked just like, like anybody else.
So this is Satan's world. So all of the universities, all the religions,
all of your sciences, all that are his. And it's based on deception. So the Vatican,
we were saying all about these depositories. Now, there are nothing more than a byproduct.
Have you ever seen a film called Idiocracy, which is supposed to be 500 years into the future,
let's say, or 300 years into the future? What kind of depository would they have?
Does it matter? Here's the thing. Whatever depositories of information exists right now
are safe. And they don't even have to be secret, because the people don't want to take the time to
understand them. There's two ways to hide something. One is to hide it physically, or
you spend 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10 generations dumbing up people to the point where you could leave it
out in plain sight, and they won't understand it. That's another way to keep a secret.
Right. You've spoken in the past also about the goddess religions.
And I want somebody who wants to look into that further. Do you know of any reference material or
books or sources that one can turn to for that? On the internet, no. But you would,
what I would suggest, this is what I would suggest. Go to a university library and ask
where this information can be in a non-textbook form. In other words, for example, if you go to
the southwest of America, that's typically a snowbird-type town. So when it's cold and snowy
in the northeast of America, people of high net worth or wealthy go and spend their winters in
warmer places. And when they die, they might have a library and they bequeath it to a university.
And, you know, books from the 17th, 18th, 19th centuries. And when these things are bequeathed
and held in the university library, they are no longer read by people who are students and
professors because it's not popular. They don't even understand it. So you want to find these,
you want to find things that were written in the 19th century particularly.
In the 20th century, there was a big clamp down on information and book burnings and things like
that. But what you will do is in your travels, you will find your own ways of researching the
goddess religion. The easiest way to research anything is to be objective within your own
surroundings. Look at the logos and look at the justice system which personifies that and start
looking at the history of those things and then you will find something and some more commentary.
Can I give you specifics? In the future, perhaps, I will get some authors and books,
but they're going to be kind of difficult to find. There used to be a site called ScribeD
or S-C-R-I-B-D that people scan a lot of stuff in, but they're hard to find on a search because
they're not named. It'll just be like a code. So that would be a good place to start.
There is much written about ancient culture, especially what's called the Chaldean Hebrew
culture, and if you study the history of these cultures, you will see the topic evoked quite a
bit, like Ashtarte and on and on and on, the Egyptian culture and all that, and the Greek
culture, and then you will see how it branched off. But essentially, not all goddesses are
malevolent, but the ones that are instilled in the culture now are, for sure, and what makes them
malevolent is that they are anti-life. Now, if you don't think anti-life is malevolent, then
I don't know how else to find a common ground for discussion. You see, some people may think that
anti-life is not malevolent, right? I mean, you might, you know, run into that.
Yeah, I'm going to bow out, but I do just want to leave with two questions that I'll try to make
them as brief as possible. Would you be able to share some of your opinions or whatever reports
you have on George Soros? He's a name that's brought up a lot in the media as being somebody
that orchestrates this and that politically. And then the second one is, what are your thoughts on
Marvel, the corporation that puts out all these superhero movies? Because it seems as if a lot
of stuff, a lot of these big movies have a lot of code and a lot of supernatural references.
Well, any code needs a perimeter to be deciphered. Let's go backwards. Marvel
would be something. Are you familiar with the Persian or religion called Zoroism or Zoroathrism?
Say that fast, twice you'll get a hernia, right? Zoroism, look it up. It's a religion out of
Persia. And what they taught was that man will be saved by someone of superhuman qualities coming
out of society. That's where you get the superheroes and the super quality stuff. That's Zoroism out
of Persia. That's all it is, right? The Marvel and the superhero, Superman, Batman, Superdog,
Wonder Woman, that's all Zoroism. Go study Zoroism and you'll see what I'm talking about.
George Soros seems to just be a contemporary Henry Morgenthau or a contemporary, you know,
Morgenthau was someone who heavily influenced FDR. Every time there is a dynamic political
condition, there is always some kind of a mogul behind the scenes that is pushing and instigating
in being the deal maker for these political things. Because ultimately you will find out
that what you're calling political or the status of governments or sovereign nations are actually
corporate entities. And any corporate entity engaging in any form of business needs a
negotiator, right? And that's why when you look at what they call that television show,
they call the news. Let's talk about the United States real quick. When they want to make a
decision on policy, they don't say it's lawful or unlawful. They say it doesn't suit the best
interests of the United States. Just like when Ford cancels a particular model car, why did you
cancel it? Because it wasn't in Ford's best interest to continue manufacturing it. You'll
never hear lawful and unlawful. It's always what's in our best interest. And every corporate entity
needs a hardcore, hardline negotiator in the background. And that's all he is. And these
guys have appeared over and over in every piece of history. They're handlers and they're negotiators.
I can only objectify it. Okay. Last question. Actually, one thing just came to mind. You've
spoken previously about the relationship between the US and the UK. And I've heard people refer
to that before as a sort of special relationship. And some people say that the US is just a colony
still. What are your thoughts on that? And if that is the case, how can it then really be a
superpower? Or does the UK still run things? No, it's a time of confusion. 20th century is the
time when the pot's ready to be poured out. The UK is an interesting thing. So is the US. And all
these things are not easily answered. No, but I wouldn't say it's a colony. But I would say that
200 and some odd years ago, a group of subjects decided to be poor subjects and take action
against their masters. And then what comes after that? But I have touched on this on describing
how all functions are based on law. And if you look at your law system in the US or the UK,
it's the same organization. So nothing much has changed. And also, don't look at the type
of government, but look at the type of religious body that's operating. Whenever you have, for
example, a revolution in a country, they might topple and change the type of governmental system.
But the type of religion is still there. So now you know where the stability is, right?
It's the quote unquote houses of worship and those that are the real government, right?
Cool. Well, yeah, I think I got a lot of my questions out. And I thank you guys for taking
the time to answer them. Greek, primarily. Okay, that's fine. And also, if I if I did a
membership area on a book, put you on the spot on uncommon radio, would you join?
Absolutely. I joined that day. Okay, interesting. All right. I'm just taking a little bit of a
poll on that. It's not that I find it distasteful. I just find that that if I if a membership area
can thrive, then it'll be a give and take situation. Then I could say, Hey, look, there's
five or 10 or 100 members. I'm going to go and do some work. And I feel like it's it's being,
you know, focused on right. And I could write papers and do audios and things that are very
specific to right. So I'm just taking an open poll on that. Sorry, Chuck, I just wanted to
see what people thought. Don't apologize to me. It's mine. Yeah, I was gonna ask like,
why not? Why not write a book? You were asking about your next project?
Well, I always people I run into people in public say we should write a book. I'm saying,
well, I wouldn't mind doing that. But you know, if I'm going to write a book and
put it out out there, I'm presuming that people know how to read.
Right. But with comprehension, I'm talking about being functionally literate, where you know what
the letter A, you know, you know how to say, D, O, G, or you know how to say N, I, C, E,
but you don't know what it means. I mean, if you start you give you an example, I had spoken to an
author a while back, I've met, I've met and he says, I want you to read the book. So he gave it
to me in an E form. And even in the first chapter, I said, Wait a second, you're using these words
incorrectly. They're not. That's not what they mean. He says, It doesn't matter. Great. Just
read the book. I'm like, Whoa, okay, so we so the thing is just to buy the book and read it and
without comprehension. This is the author himself telling me this, by the way. So, you know,
that's why I find it. Yeah. And the last thing you want to do is write a book about a book.
Right. So I think, you know, have you heard me mentioned in the past that all libraries,
you read material even at home, or in your own personal space by yourself,
you read all reading was done out loud. Right? It was not done silently. Now they're promoting
while the past few hundred years, if you went to an ancient library, like you brought up Library
of Alexandria, you would pick up your reading material, there would be hundreds of small booths
and larger booths. If it was a longer piece of material, you would, it was the birth of the
conference room, it would be passed around between person to person. So you would walk
into an ancient library, and there would be this vibration and this murmur of everyone speaking
individually in these little booths, you know, nothing was read silently, everything was read out
loud. This is a new thing to be silently reading. That's why I suggest people get audio books,
because it satisfies that. And also, when you have the written word spoken, it has a different
effect on the mind. Right? There's a frequency there. In other words, if you go to a modern day
library and lean up against put the hand on the wall, it feels like you're in the morgue.
If you went to an ancient library, and you put the hand on the wall and leaned on it,
it would be vibrating, literally, from all of the hundreds of mouths speaking.
Different, different, completely different. If you look at the ancient ancient temple structures,
accurate depictions, they had hundreds of little booths, little conference rooms from
from the individual one, all the way up to, you know, 5, 10, 15 people sitting in an area,
and they would close them off as best as they could, and everything would be spoken out loud.
And there were no secrets that way. Like, for example, let me just say one more thing,
the people that have been duped in modern democracy is that they told it go vote in secret.
They don't understand that when you do that, you're explicitly implying that now the government can
keep secrets and a lawful government does not have secrets. A lawful government is there to
serve its function and be open. So now, you go and cast your secret vote, and now you're going to
complain about secret agencies, and secret spies, and secret this, and secret that, and all these
things. It's kind of twisted. The ancient, the lawful societies did not do things in secret.
It was open. Everyone knew what was going on. And what, yeah. So, not all of them, but I'm just
saying. Sort of piggybacking off this membership idea that you spoke of, would you be open to doing
like one-on-one Skype sessions with people that had more questions? Sure, sure. I would suggest
probably doing a once-a-week group or something, yeah. That'd be cool. Yeah. Or the emails are
great. Yeah. Well, somehow, I'll put up all that information on Common Radio. And the thing is,
with, and I appreciate it. And also, can you tell us just real quick before you go, how you came
up across Ocelli and the Greek? Well, I heard you on Freeman TV. Freeman, what's it called?
Flyby or whatever, the audio podcast. So, I figured that that particular episode was really
interesting. And I'd try and figure out more about the guy who was being interviewed.
Appreciate it. Yeah. Well, let people know if you think people of good character are interested in
being objective. I think on Common Radio or listening to Greek speak. And you might have
heard me say, I wish there was other people saying this so that I could take a break.
I'm not a public person or public, you know, I just think that these things need to be discussed
openly. Yeah, I agree with you. Well, thank you guys for letting me call in. It's been good.
Well, thanks. Thank you for coming. And Chuck dropped off. Maybe we'll have him back in a
moment. All right. Cool. Okay. Thank you, Sam. Thank you. Bye then. You too. And in the meantime,
until Chuck comes back, we'll get a little bit of Greek speak. I appreciate you calling in, Sam. And
we're probably discussing things at length that normally I would avoid discussing only because
this topic, as whoever's listening now still will acknowledge that everyone has got an opinion on
it. And typically it's a very sour topic and you can't blame people for discussing, you know,
saying, oh, that sounds religious because what has happened is the mainstream religions or not
so mainstream religions have left such a bad taste in anyone trying to objectify reality
that anything that even comes close to that topic is rejected. The same with legalese, for example.
Why is it that the majority of people on the planet right now regard to what's called an
attorney as liars and deceivers, but yet when it comes to discussing something legal, they don't
want to, but they hold them in a negative light. It's like, why let it sit there and fester? Why
don't you address it, you know, at least intellectually? You know, if the population
at large just finds the legal society or those, the actors in the legal society distasteful,
why don't they spend a little bit of time studying what's been memorialized about them,
right? So they can maybe double check and see if they're doing their job right so they don't have
to despise them. You know, there was someone I had a discussion with who had a discussion with
someone at the Sturgis, I think it's the get together with the Harley Davidson's once a year.
And there was a politician speaking there and someone, you know, after the politician was
speaking, I believe it was a senator, someone approached him and says, hey, you know,
you're not following the rules in any of your, you know, committees or hearings or Constitution
or anything. And the reply of the senator was, well, we're going to keep doing what we're doing
until you stop us, right? The same thing is with the medical society. The people just don't want
to discuss how the medical society functions, they just want to discuss how they have interacted
with them and what kind of sympathy they want to get. So what's interesting, why am I saying this,
is because in the near future, there's going to be a little bit of sanity or health regarding
these subjects where people will actually invest a little bit of time and see what these things
really are, at least from what's been memorialized about them. Now, there are,
this sounds really interesting, but actually might sound distasteful, but most people hate
knowledge. Most people hate the truth. I've actually had people say to me, hey, man, I don't
need to get anything from a book. I don't need a book. Well, forget about a book. It doesn't have
to be a book. It could be just something reported. It could be audio, could be a DVD. It could be
something scribbled on a bathroom wall. But why not? I think it might be they're afraid of
inconsistency in places that they don't expect it. Think about that for a moment. Could it be
that people are just happy about inconsistency in most cases because it makes them feel better?
So either way, there's many, there's a lot of fat to chew. There's many things to discuss.
Excuse me. There's topics that need to be examined. You hear the term researcher or research.
Well, that means to go and search again. Why bother researching when it hasn't been searched
out the first time at all anyway? So I think there's going to be some searching that's going
to begin. Now, the reason I say this is because this is a time period now that is ending roughly
this seven-year cycle. And another seven-year cycle is going to be starting in what you call 2018
around that time in the spring. And by the way, just speaking of springtime, this is a time of
seasonal change. And just to maybe throw something in, this is an interesting year,
it appears to be intercalary an extra month, meaning it's the middle of the 13th
moon or month right now, but it is a seasonal change. So parts of the world will be going into
winter and the more dominating part will be going into summer or spring. And the interesting thing
to consider about that is how do we define those seasons and what happens during those seasons and
the seasonal change. So either way, we'll see if Chuck comes back. Danny, I'm going to take a pause
here for about 30 seconds. I'll be right back. We're going to have a little bit of dead air.
Sorry, folks, I'll be right back. Okay, sorry about the dead air, folks. And until Chuck comes
back, if he does, this is the final installment of the Reloaded Ocelli in the Greek, episode 12
or chapter 12 as Chuck has dubbed it. And the reason why is perhaps that putting a limitation
or a sense of construct behind any event, whether it be, I guess, like I said, any event, this is
a sonic event, a series of, and they're roughly 24 hours, two hours a piece of archived information
that could be found on American Freedom Radio or Uncommonradio.com. And also, Chuck has diligently,
I think, have somehow recorded them on his what they call ocelli.com website and various YouTube
places. And I do encourage anyone who is seeking objectivity, although it is not fashionable at the
moment, might want to inquire. The whole thing about giving inquiry or having inquiry is, are you
prepared to just leave aside anything that is, that is, you might consider prejudicial, instilled
within your personal belief, your opinion, let's say? Are you willing to put that aside and just
see what can be commonly seen by anyone yet is refused to be done so? It's very simple.
There's a concept called fashion, you know, like being fashionably laid or being fashionable,
whether it was how things are said, how you wear clothes or whatever. Fashion has become more than
just what we, how we use the term. It is also the word fashion could mean to assemble something and
put something together. And when it is, if you can discern the culture and when it is fashionable
or acceptable to be ignorant or to be, let's say, opinionated, but you don't really have your own
opinion. You really have to go along with the opinion that has been formed. I think it's called
politically correct. And by the way, folks, growing up in the 60s and 70s, we were being told that,
you know, America is a type of place where you can be yourself. And somehow that's promoted now,
but in a perverted way, but be yourself, do what you want or whatever. But what's interesting is
when you were back then and even now dealing, I say dealing, encountering any of the
quote unquote authority type figures, whether it's the legal society, medical society or religious
society and private, the authoritative figures always said you have to be like everyone else.
Yet publicly, you're being told to expand yourself, be you, be creative, be unique.
But in private, with vehement authority, you're being told to be like everyone else. So
there's a dichotomy here and a mixed message, I think, that is not helpful or sane for the
individual. In other words, what is expressed through fashion and through the culture and what
is popular at large, you will find that even though it might be fashionable to be one way,
when you're in a more of a private setting, albeit considered public as well, in some cases,
like a court or interacting with police or a medical practitioner or religious practitioner,
they will tell you, you have to be like everyone else. And so on the on an expansive point of view,
it's that you can express your individuality. I think that's a setup. I think you're being
pranked. You know, there's a concept of freedom, there's a concept of license to be yourself,
there's a concept of what you might have rights. And by the way, folks, just to throw this in,
these concepts, by the way, you know, it's part of the prank, but just to throw this in
regarding rights, in order for rights to be instilled, there has to be an establishment
of a crime that has been committed. Because in law, there are no rights, you have pretty much
you're in open, you're at large, you're what's called free to an extent. But once a crime has
been committed and alleged, and you're suspected of it, you go under what's called rights now.
So when people are, it's kind of backwards, think of it when you're claiming that you
have some bestowed rights or unalienable rights or unalienable rights or whatever,
however they want to fashion it again, there has to be some kind of misdeed that's been committed
in order for those rights to kick in. So I don't know if it's just myself, or how people have
twisted that perception, but a little bit of more homework needs to be done on that.
Because typically, when people say they're going to stand up for their rights, I usually say,
well, if they're fixing to bust people that day might be best that you just stay sitting down.
So anyway, be objective, be perceptive, and you don't need to go to any kind of specialized
source or specialized, again, source or place to be objective, you have to start with what's in
five feet or two meters reach of you. Are you paying attention to what's going on around you?
And the other thing is, always, you have to understand the concept of centrality,
where do things start from? And with mankind, if you're listening, and you're a sentient being,
you probably have a physical body, you really need to learn how the body really works and what it
really is and put aside what the medical community has put on society through the media and all the
other forms that they do have. Because if you are deceived about how the body works,
and the body is headquarters for the physical and the spiritual side, if headquarters is deceived,
and anything that comes out of it or goes into it in a resonant way will be deception.
So try to understand and comprehend how the body works. The medical society at large,
whether it's academic or in practice, they have done a tremendous amount of what I call grunt work
or field work in establishing certain aspects of what the human body is. But you also have to keep
in mind that that is nothing more than an accumulation of battlefield medicine. If you do
even cursory research, you will find that the medical system at large today is based on roughly
something that started less than 100 years ago, as if anything prior to that has been discarded
for some reason. There's a banking aspect, of course, to this. This might sound like
conspirology of some sort. But get a grip on the central location known as you, who you are.
Basically, you're a mind that's being animated through a physical form. The mind also means
the spirit. So learn how the body works. Instead of just saying it in general terms,
find out how your intake affects you, what you drink, what you eat, and how the body itself
affects you. You notice that if you don't get enough sleep, you don't feel well. If you get
too much sleep, you don't feel well. What is sleep? What is food? When you have an injury,
how is it treated? In ancient Greece, they discussed that the fluids in the body move in a
wave pattern in one general flow. That was discarded as being nonsense. They were not
discussing the blood. They were discussing the lymphatic system. So the question here is,
what do you know about the lymphatic system? Could it be that there's more lymphatic fluid
in the body than there is blood? That's more than a could it be. The answer to that would be yes.
So what do you know about the lymphatic system? Do you ever notice how when you bump
a part of the body, the head, the elbow or something, your first desire is to grab it
and squeeze it? Interesting, right? Okay, so start learning a little bit about lymphology
or lymphatics and what that is. And unfortunately, there's not a lot of information on that. But
whatever you can get on it, it would be a good place to start. Understand what a biological
vacuum is. Could it be that the body is under a slight negative pressure? It's sucking, not
pushing? Well, what can you do with that? How can you understand a little bit more about that?
I believe that Chuck and I have wrestled this discussion back and forth on the original
in the Greek. It was the container episode two, I believe. Now, why am I bringing this up? Because
the simple point is this. If you are deceived about how the body works and the body is
headquarters, if headquarters is deceived, then what can come out and go in? More deception.
So that is an interesting place or an interesting way to objectify it. You know, could you imagine
going to a car mechanic and explaining what you'd like done? And before you leave the car with him,
he asks you where the steering wheel is. How confident are you? But why is everyone confident,
apparently confident, that the body is just a meatbag with blood in it and pressure?
And it's warm. That sounds like a pretty piss poor evaluation of what's going on. So anything
you could learn about how the body really works is going to be a really good place to start
objectifying what is going on around you, and then objectifying what is going on within the
room that you're in, just the room that you're sitting in. You know, why is it that you have a
hot head and cold feet all year round indoors when outside it seems like the heat descends
and the cold rises? If you look at the mountaintops and the valley, you know, in contrast, why is it
that your head should be cool and your feet should be warm versus a hot head and cold feet?
But yet, you see, there are these contrasts that are going on, and there's a difference here
between things that are alive and things that are not alive. You know, there's an interesting
thing that Wilhelm Reich discussed, and it was armoring, emotional armoring, and how if you go
to the academics or the leaders of convention and you bring up anything that has to do with the
life force, they get very agitated. It seems like any convention does not want to discuss the life
force or where things come from. If you go to a banker, ask him where are they getting the money
to lend to you from, where they have to show it by law, and they get very, very uncomfortable.
Why? You see, ask anyone in any of the religious establishments, where are they getting what
they're saying, and watch how uncomfortable they get, right? Why? Why is that? Why is it humanity
right now is at a state where if you start discussing source aspects or source causes,
they get very uncomfortable. Think about it, because, well, if you were to objectify it,
then you might actually become uncomfortable as well. It's probably more comfortable to be
fashionable in being uncomfortable, if that makes any sense. So this is a very difficult path to
pursue, but it's what I should say, it's very simple but not easy. I would encourage anyone,
especially the young people, to start being objective, but in a mature way, because there's
always the immature aspect of a little child, when he asks you why, you tell him, and they ask why
again, and they tell them, and they ask why, and they keep going. Do it in a mature way, but the
whys should never end. Sort of questioning the answers and maybe asking the answer instead of
asking the question. So wrapping this up sort of as the 12th chapter, as Chuck has dubbed it. Now,
ironically, the Greek was not around for the beginning, and Chuck may not be around for the
end of the episode or the chapter, so there's a little bit of irony there. Maybe the first will
be last and the last will be first, but all I can say is I encourage people that do find
the information that has been imparted by the Greek, or what can be dubbed as Greek speak,
to do more than just tickle their ear, in other words, as a fanciful sonic thing.
And if it actually is thought-provoking, which by the way, thinking can get you in a lot of trouble,
so you have to be careful when and how you do that, but if it is thought-provoking in that
there are other ways, and you don't have to be running around discussing Freudian terms like
boredom and, well, I don't know if boredom is Freudian, or depression and ego and things like
that, where you can actually start putting things in terms that are practical and viable.
And basically, don't be a muppet. Don't be a puppet, in essence. You're a man or a woman,
you are, or a young man or a young woman, you are who you are when you discover
how to be objective. You will see that these things that have been thrust upon,
you know, let's say the individual or the man or the woman, young or old, are not necessarily so.
And there's nothing really wrong with it because you're not going to change it.
So the moral here is to set yourself apart. Be objective, set yourself apart from it.
This is very common, by the way, when you look at people in the emergency
fields, when they approach to render their services, they are cool as a cucumber, as they say,
and try to objectify things. It doesn't mean do it in a robotic sense, but be methodical,
be clear and be objective. And you have to also be able to discern and read the fashions that are
at large in society right now. I'm using that word a lot tonight, at large, which just means
prevalent and not necessarily under control. So this being the last episode, I want to end
chapter. I want to thank Chuck for putting up with the Greek for all this time. I'm sure
if he didn't enjoy it, he wouldn't do it. But Chuck has, I think, put himself out to do this
collaborative project, as we said, roughly 80 hours on the web, because most of the things that
he has spent his radio career on, which he is very good at, by the way, and he is a true professional
in that field. I would suggest he has, and here he is. I was just thanking Mr. Chuck Ocelli for
putting up with the Greek for about 80 hours. Yeah, well, apparently the Skype didn't want to
cooperate there. I don't know. I don't. I'm speechless. But that's fine. And so was I.
That's why I basically recapped and told people be objective and don't be deceived. And what else
are you going to say, you know? But that's all right. It's been Skype karma night. So it's ironic
how I figured I wasn't around for the beginning and you weren't going to be around for the end.
But here you go. I was able to get back on. But it is almost that time. And there you go.
It is ironic that the Skype doesn't cooperate. Yeah. Tonight was very ironic. We usually have
impeccable Skype etiquette showing up and keeping a couple of drops here and there.
The other thing ironic was I always try to avoid discussion on scripture and we had a caller that
dominated the topic. And here we go. And this is the 12th chapter. And thanks again, Chuck,
for putting up with the Greek all this time. Well, and thanks to everybody who did decide
to listen. And I think it is always advisable to think and respond to all things in as objective
a fashion as possible. Wouldn't you agree? Oh, I think that's what we've been trying
to do all this time. Thanks. All right.