Well, well, here we are once again on what they do call a Thor's Day night, apparently,
well, at least where I'm sitting on this particular rock. And this is the Ocelli and the Greek show,
which is separate, by the way, from the Ocelli Effect. There were some odd questions about that
this week. This is very much a different show. Okay. That being said, I did not give the date.
Why? Because, well, I'll do it. According to, well, here we go. According to that thing we
call a calendar, and the Pope's work schedule is really what we should be calling it. But
according to that thing that is colloquially known as a calendar, try that five times fast.
You know, it's, well, the fifth day of January, the fifth day of the first month in the year 2017.
However, what day is it actually? Well, you just gave the date, and, you know, today,
meaning the real day, you know, when the sun rises and sets and what the fish and the tigers
and the whales and the bees and the rivers are doing, don't go on that. Because if you look
at today, for example, I mean, this, you know, we could, we've got no agenda, right? So you said
it's, well, anyone can say January 5th, 2017, right? And it's what they call a Thor's Day,
depending on where you are. I don't think it's late enough on the States here to be that late
and past the next day. But if we go to 2016, let's say if we go to 2015, it's just to,
I like doing this little, it's a little demonstration, right?
Right.
Go to January 25th, what they call 2015. All right, you ready? The fifth, or the fifth,
if you're from the ghetto, is, was a moon's day. It was what they call a Monday. You know,
I got that little button on the bottom of windows, right? All right, let's go to 2018.
Can we dare to go that far forward?
We might as well, because those calendars have already been printed and all that. So
they're available and also their digital facsimile thereof. So go ahead.
So on what they call January 2018, the fifth is going to be on what they call Friar's Day or
Friday. So let me ask you, is January 5th, a Thursday, a moon's day or Friday Friar's Day?
Which one is it? It's none. It's arbitrary.
Yeah. So, and what, you know what, and no one is paying attention at all.
At all. And I wish we could do some copyrighted material because I know when we,
when this, this stuff, these seeds get scattered along the web,
they block certain content, right? You know, if you, let's say, threw in a little YouTube
or something.
Right.
Right. So George Carlin has a couple, let's see, he just lays in, you know, the voice
and no one is paying attention, you know, see it George, you know, but so, and no one at all,
you know how he says that, you know, no one. And, and when he's basically denigrating the
audience and what do they all do? They give him an applause.
They applaud.
They applaud. Yes. And he's actually talking about them to them. So
doesn't that make us getting together once a week kind of irrelevant? Oh, anyway, did I just say
that? Okay. Well, you know, irrelevant to us, but how about we just take it into another direction
and look at what, well, the objective point of view might be about, well, let's start with this
get together once a week. What would be the objective way to look at what it is we do here?
Well, you know, well, you could speak for yourself. I could speak for myself. I'm doing
Why? Because I've been going on the internet, the internet, whatever, all over the place,
print books, library, talking to folks and discovering things that no one is, it's, you
know, should be common and no one is paying attention. So later on, if it becomes kind of
normal and people start going around and saying, Hey, this guy could, you know, the Greek, he,
he knows about this stuff. You know, some, somebody might get upset and, you know,
come and pull you out of the bed where you're sleeping and say, Hey man, you knew about this
and you didn't say anything. Right. You get the point. That does go to the point of why it is I
do what I do as well. I think that if something is known, it needs to be spoken. It needs to be
shared regardless of whether people accept it or not, or take it in or not. It needs to be done.
It's just, well, seems to be the lawful thing to do, but let's not get into lawful tonight. Let's
focus on objective. How about that? Well, we are going to be lawful. We always want to be lawful
because when you pursue lawfulness, you actually end up being more impeccable instead of less
impeccable. Let's say that's like being more pregnant or less pregnant, isn't it? When you
say that, but so we, I suggest to the young ones, let's just say to the young people out there,
what would you consider young pre, like post formative years and preadolescent. So like
between let's say three and four and like 11 and 12 would be young people, right?
Well, you know, kind of dependent on, on your perspective just a bit because, you know,
to a 20 year old, they're not very young themselves. They don't think of themselves as,
you know, we, we often say children or kids or whatever, which of course kids is a, is an
abominable term, but you know, they, they don't think of themselves that way. But in my mid
forties here, I look at a 20 year old and think to myself, this is a child quite often. Yeah,
good. Well, 20 is the age of majority, by the way. And you know, when you, when you reach,
let's say you have, let's say what's called a 20th birthday, the next minute, the next day,
the next week past that birth date is taken from the 21st year. So you're actually living
in your 21st year. So there's a little hint, folks, when you're reading older documents
and they say someone is 21 or 22, and you look at their bio when they were born and say, oh,
they're, this is wrong because they're a year off. They're not. So let's say you just had,
let's say a 40th birthday. You're in your, you're 41. You see?
Which I, which I always found interesting too, because in the Middle East, that is a, there,
there is a distinction there. They actually do count. And, and I do mean people from Lebanon.
I do mean people from the place they call Syria. I do mean even Pakistanis will,
will sit there and say, well, wait a minute. When were you born? And they don't necessarily call
you 20 as you would be in the U S right. You would be 21 because you're in your 21st year,
as you just described. Right. And that's, this is just a little hint. So when, because there's
some people that like to look at information closely and they'll point out the lack of
understanding that convention as an error in some script somewhere or some writ, right? So this
needs to be understood the convention of the culture. But this is the point to the young
people. You're screwed. Why? Because conventionally for years and years, you looked up to the older
people for wisdom and for knowledge and for training. Now I noticed, especially the past
decade or so, the older people, because they've been motivated by penalty their whole life,
they can't see straight and they can't really guide young people anymore. And this is not
everyone. I'm sure there's some older people out there that can, but as a, as a generally specific
comment, meaning general, meaning pretty general, but I can tell you it's pretty specific too.
You're going to have to do it on your own because the older people have been reduced to basically
old bags and fools. And I, I've, I think I've given examples about that a couple of years ago
when we first loaded Ocelli in the Greek. Sounds like a weapon, you know, but anyway.
Well, it is, it is in fact, in my estimation, but go ahead.
Well, that's why, you know, that, you know, I have no problem if I call your typical surface
dwelling earth inhabitant a moron, because that's a technical, I mean, it's a, it's a,
it's not a put down and you can take it as such, right? But it's pretty accurate. And you could
just look at how people on this planet have been acting for so long and they wonder why
their shallow thinking always has them diving into the deep end. Right. But basically, okay.
So if most people are, oh, and by the way, if most people are morons, what do you call someone
that's in the military? There are weapons grade moron, but anyway. Okay.
Oh, nice. You know, and, and, and look, before we get too far into this, I love that though,
by the way, a weapons grade moron. That's, that's, that's, that's, that's clever. I appreciate that.
Right now, if you're, by the way, this is not denigrating when the military, but if you're like,
if you're from Alpha Centauri or Mars, or, you know, some other constellation, well,
then you can exclude yourself. But if you're pretty much from this planet,
you don't know what's going on either as a general rule.
That's true. But I'll tell you what, if you are from this planet, you possess a phone,
you can join into the conversation. Okay. At 218-339-8525. 218-339-8525. I have the phone
panel in front of me, so I have control of that. And meanwhile, you, Greek, have control of something else.
Right. Well, let's do it for a Skype convention, for the ultra high quality digital Skype stuff.
You have a good mic, or you can use a phone. Just put in your contact search, Ocelli and the Greek.
And it's spelled just like it sounds. You could just type it through, no space, or Ocelli would
be O-C-H-E-L-L-I. And there you go. And spread it on thick, spread that number on thick,
because we like some callers. So go ahead, pour it on again, that number again.
218-339-8525. That's 218-339-8525. I may announce it again, but I'm really hoping that there will
be some participation. So come on and join in. There's a couple of, well, guidelines for these
calls though, aren't there? Well, here's the thing. There are guidelines, and that's the laws of the
show, right? So if you're calling in and you don't want to follow those rules, well, does that give
us the, would you say, right or the leeway to hit the red button? Well, your conversation may be
subject to early termination. How about that? Yeah, that's right. Or we can just forward the
call to the mental health hotline. But anyway. I would never do that, but okay.
Okay. By the way, that's a little funny skit. Have you ever heard it? I wish I should play it,
but anyway. Okay. The rules are very simple. They're basically two, and they're not really
etched in stone, but they're just good for any, by the way, folks, Chuck, these are not just rules
for calling in here, but they're just good general rules if you're going to a party, going to work,
or any other conversation, wouldn't you say so? Yeah. I think they work, you know,
all the way around. I mean, I can't find too many situations. I mean, occasionally,
I guess it might be entertaining to be in a violation of these guidelines, but outside of
the entertainment factor on occasion, which would be rare, really for the best circumstances for
conversation in general, these rules do apply across the board. So go ahead. Oh, basically,
the first one is call in. Let us know what you've discovered. Give us some testimony,
some report. Share with everybody. All the other boys and girls want to hear,
but if you start talking about yourself and what you like or don't like, you know what?
People always act like they're interested, but they're really not. No one really cares about you,
and when they're talking, when you're talking, they're thinking, when is this person going to
shut up so I can get the mic and say what I want to say? And so basically, come on and give us some
clarity. Give us some objectivity. Give us a good report, something that could help.
The other thing would be if you're under some kind of chemical influence or other influence,
it could be even a spirit bothering you or a six-foot-tall dust ball in your closet with fangs
and claws or whatever, and you feel like you're under the influence of any substance other than
that, you might think you're not under the influence or you sound fine, but you really
don't. If you're drinking, smoking or shooting or popping or whatever to excess, you know what?
Usually when you speak, you kind of sound like you are, so that's the other thing.
The reason I bring that up is you would be surprised. I haven't really noticed lately
because guess what? I don't listen to internet radio, but years ago when I did,
I noticed quite a few people, what do we call it? Under the influence would call in and I'm like,
okay, this guy's toasted. Very simple and I think these are good guidelines for any public or
semi-public and even private conversations that are put on minor internet radio stations like this one.
There you go.
Before we got on, I said, what are we going to do? No agenda. The whole thing is about being
objective, right? Now, what is objectivity? Somebody could look it up or we could look
it up or whatever. It's too objectified. We're using it in a colloquial way.
Let's see. Where do we start on that? Do we start on the problems? Do we start on
how to do it? Because how to do it, this is not a technical show, but basically,
it's about being lawful. Now, have you ever taken a class on geometry or engineering or
anything that's a technical field where you're basically imparting information for others to
technically access so you don't have to make stuff up as you go along? If you're engineering
like bridge building and you're taking structures and strength of materials in various classes,
it needs to be uniform, right? You're looking for the uniformity of something. If you open a book
on geometry and you go to where it says triangle, any book in geometry anywhere would pretty much
show you the same thing, something with three sides, right? You have this uniformity that not
only is uniform across the planet, but across time, right? That is what the base of lawfulness
is from a colloquial way. Ultimately, if you've listened to the Greek speak before,
that comes from your God or someone of very high authority, right, Chuck? Don't you think
the people that are called lawmakers are considered high in authority, whether society,
whether it's whatever form they take, ministerial or political or monarchy, right?
That would be the prevailing wisdom. Generally speaking, those in authority are the lawgivers
regardless of where they are or exactly how high up they are in the food chain.
For instance, in your own home, if you have children, well, you are a lawgiver in your own
home, aren't you? Now, you're not necessarily the highest thing on the food chain or way up there
in the hierarchy, but for all intents and purposes for that- Yeah, you're the highest
perceived authority. Right, perceived authority, perfect.
Perceived, right, right, because when you're young, your parents are not only
the highest authority, but guess what? They're gods to you as well, almost on that level.
Well, they are literally the provider of all things when you're very young and vulnerable,
so that would, well, kind of qualify, yeah. So this natural system, when I say natural
because it's inherit, you notice it doesn't change much from generation to generation,
right? It's sort of inherited, this concept of rules coming from authority.
Wouldn't you say then if you try to stretch one's perception of authority in terms of power and
wisdom and keep going, wouldn't you want to block them from understanding even higher authorities
than they've already perceived, like let's say the gods and how they function? And if you actually
look at what's going on, that would be very clear, looking at all the religions and the way people
discuss the gods. And yes, I'm saying gods plural because you will never ever find anywhere,
especially in accurate lawful information where gods is a singular term. And think of it this way,
when you say the word army, do you think of a single individual, a single thing,
or is it a large grouping? So that would be a simple way to start off with a conversation of
what is lawful. Like if you, for example, are taking from understanding concepts, class and
geometry, you can construct various shapes just using a compass which is just like a string and
a ruler. You don't need to measure to make a square or a circle or a seven-sided figure or
other figures, right? You do that by called constructing, right? If you want to make a
perfect circle, you take a point and stretch out a string and as long as you keep the tension the
same, you'll get a circle going around. You don't need to measure anything, right? And from that
circle and you're constructing other things. Are you familiar with squaring the circle?
That's where you get the proportions of 7-11 which is also the proportions of the earth to
the moon. The Egyptians were big on this. You ever heard of something called 7-11 convenience store?
Yeah, so when you look at squaring the circle, all that construction is done without any
measurement. It's just using lines that intersect and forming other points, right? Why am I talking
about geometry? Because when you're taking a class or being instructed on how to do this,
you must be lawful every step of the way. In other words, when you construct the circle by
pulling a taut line around a center point to get the radius the same and get a near perfect circle,
if you don't do that right, you won't have a circle and your other constructed elements
will not be based on lawfulness or will not be constructed accurately, you see?
So you have to be lawful each step of the way and this is just geometry now, right?
And this is just the way we function because mathematics is just a language to rationalize
communication, right? That's all it is. And by the way, if you ever run into someone,
you bring up something and say, I'm not good at math. There's someone who's emotionally lazy
because you don't have to say, I'm not good at math. I'm just not into complicated math because
everyone is into math. If you just ask someone how many toes or fingers or eggs in a basket there
are, everyone can somehow apply mathematics to rational communication. It's about communicating
rationally and mathematics has to be lawful, right? When you add up a column of numbers
and you submit the total and someone says it's wrong, well, they can't just say it's wrong and
I don't know why and I don't need to know why I don't like it, right? They just say,
we'll add them up again and look, you'll see the mistake, right? Typically, right?
In a rational conversation, that's how it works, right?
Right. Well, they might not know the exact part of the equation that has been inaccurately
represented, but you can easily say and definitively say that this is the improper conclusion, right?
Right. And this is, so mathematics is a very stringent or astringent way to maybe communicate
how rational communication is had, right? But outside of that, it seems like this thing
called opinion, belief and desire and my own personal heresy, heresy is the Greek word,
heresy is your own personal liking. It's fine to be a heretic in an ice cream shop when they
have 31 flavors or so. I don't know if there are any ice cream shops that just have one flavor,
it's possible, but they offer all these flavors because whoever is being patronized
can employ some heresy, meaning do what they like, right? You know, things like that.
But in many other things that big subjects, let's say bigger subjects that move populations,
that move society, that move the way people perceive everything, have fallen apart into
this disarray because you have this group over here that likes this or believes this,
and this other group here, right, that likes or believes that, so which one do you want to join?
Neither, right? So what happens is there's a level of hypocrisy where people – if you needed
a carpenter to come and install a new door, you want it to be pretty accurate. If you have a
three-foot door opening, what are you going to tell the carpenter if he puts a two-foot door in there?
Hey, dude.
Big problem.
Yeah, right. You want it – and actually, doors, if they're an eighth of an inch off,
they may not close and the weather will come through if they're too small or leaky.
But not only that, but the dimension of thickness must be understood correctly because if you put
a paper-thin door up, it may not stand up properly also even if it is measured to cover the
gap in the door jamb, right?
Yeah, or shoe sizes. If you're a 10-and-a-half, do you settle for a 10 or an 11? No. They want
that accurate number. They want – how about bicycle tires and car tires? If you need a 215
R70 14 on your tire on the car, they're not going to – if someone gives you a 220 R16
15 tire, it's not going to work. But you want that accurate. You see, when they get – but
with things like for example who the gods are, how the law functions, how the governments function,
what money is, how the body works, what is history, are we given – all this, that doesn't
matter. Oh, that's your opinion. Okay, so you're not going to change that. But it's interesting to
be able to rationalize why it's so and I think we did earlier because actually everybody covered
your ears. Chuck, didn't I say they're all morons? But anyway, okay.
Yeah, you did.
All right. So guys, okay, come back here. You can uncover your ears now.
Which is funny right there because you told people to cover their ears and then you told them
to uncover their ears. So if they actually listen to you, I guess they'll stay that way.
But they're not listening. So what's the difference? So we have about four – actually,
I think I recently got an email recently at theuncommonradio.com and the person signed
off their message as the sixth listener. So there you go. We're now up to six listeners.
So anyway, back to the hypocrisy and all that and how to objectify and we've never really
got into discussing that and basically, you have to understand what lawfulness is.
Lawfulness is not just the law. When you bring up the topic of law because everyone's mind has
been raped really by the desire to do things because they are motivated by the penalty if
they do or don't. You know what I mean? Like how many times have you heard, oh, a little child,
I want to drive a car. Mom says, well, you need a driver's license first. He says, well,
why do I need a driver's license? If you don't get one, you go to jail.
You got to go to college. Why do I go to college? Oh, so you get a good job. Well,
I need a good job because if you get a good job, you'll be a bum.
Now, wait a minute here because I have this rebellious nature, honestly, and therefore,
it always bothers me quite a bit when people adhere to something based on the fact that
they're going to be penalized. If they don't do it and they know nothing about it. I have
actually witnessed in a pretty – it was a civil almost slash criminal case years ago
where the attorney general didn't like the – because none of them know any law. They just
whatever. If you bring up a law in a legal situation, they say, well, forget about the
law. Did you or did you not do it? It's irrelevant because the law – anyway, but I heard an
attorney general say if you continue doing the way you are, you're just going to go to jail. Why?
Well, because I'm just saying so. Even your entitled classes, I mean like all the way up.
I recently heard an interview about a year ago. I think the current attorney general for the
country, she was under scrutiny regarding something political. I don't know what she
was under fire for and there were all these congressmen drilling her and it was as if she
just picked up like the cliff notes of the cliff notes on legalism. She was just somebody,
some common person off the street that just picked up like let's say a quick handbook on what
legal America or the legal system in America is for five minutes. She basically just – these
people don't know what's going on. I've heard and read opinions of supreme court justices. I'm like,
where are you getting this? What are you talking about? This is so far off anything real.
I pointed out just a little while ago on my show that I watched a congressional hearing earlier
today. There you go. Yeah, oh boy. A congressional hearing on – it had to do with the Russian hack
and the Trump thing and all that and okay, now the intelligence, the guys who were – had a
cyber command and everything else are going to sit here and explain to these senators what's
going on. So they sat there and rather properly read their statement into the record, which I
thought was valid. Okay. Now, can you predict what I'm going to say here, Rick? No, go ahead. Sort
of. Well, they fairly adequately explained a great deal of what was being questioned here,
the purpose for this get-together, okay? Then I sat in awe and absolute astonishment
as the alleged people on the Armed Services Committee continued to ask the same questions
that had already been answered or had already been communicated to them in the earlier statements
repeatedly. Yeah, as if there's idiocracy. By the way, let me just throw a little dig in here.
If the people were objective, like 5 or 10 percent, around 9-11 you would have disbanded the
entire military and cast it out into the ocean and you would have – if you needed a military,
you would have called on what you call allies, bring the French over, the English, the Canadians,
anybody to take over because the US military should have been completely disbanded
after 9-11 because they couldn't prevent two airplanes from being hijacked and slamming into
buildings and one going here. I mean, come on. Come on now. It has nothing to do with – let's
not go to the – let's just stick to the official story, okay, on what happened. If something like
so egregious happens in terms of negligence or ineffectiveness, the entire military should have
been disbanded, all of them. I don't know how many million there are. It should have just all
been shut down, sold for scrap and bring in the French, the English, anybody, just allies,
contract them out to be the US military because I mean that's how – this is based on the official
story now and no one is following through. We would have called up the militia
because that would have been another option. Anybody else.
Eighth graders with slingshots. I mean anything. That would have been an improvement.
Right. Yes. So that right away when things like this happen and the public – there
was a terror attack. We were attacked but the military didn't do anything. That's a dog that
doesn't bark, a dog with no teeth. Actually, it's a dog that's pretty dead. So what are you still
doing? You have to – as things happen, you have a series of events that need to be followed but
because people are opinion-based and emotionally based, they get caught up in stuff and because
they're motivated by penalty, they will never see what I just said. I think this might be the
first time anyone has said what we just said that a 9-11 based on the official story, the entire
military, all branches of service should have been disbanded, disbanded, all of it and we should
have brought in allies. I don't know what they call allies. I really don't think Americans really
have allies but you see. But that needed to be done first. So you look at all these things,
the level of hypocrisy, the level of stupidity. I'm not saying by the way that the military should
be disbanded. I'm just saying that would have been the logical, rational conclusion immediately.
You're not doing your job but it's a grievous negligence. It's just like you're falling – you
fell asleep on the job so bad that you can't wake up kind of thing. So when you see all these things
going on, people – just throw one more thing before we get on to how to be objective.
If you – how many times have you heard about people discussing the money system and it's just
credit all around, right? It's just – and there's debt. Well, wait a second. Okay. Wait a second.
Well, there's a problem here. How can you be solely credit, just credit, not money and then
having credit but just credit and have a debt? That's an impossibility of the law unless you
agree to it. Again, what do you hear everyone saying? Well, I agree with that. I agree with
that so I guess it makes it true. All of this stuff about jobs and economy – here's another
comment. Let's make another comment on what they call the United States of America. About 80 years
ago or so, the ship, let's call it a ship, got the entire hull ripped open. So if you're still
discussing what movie you're going to watch on the lower deck or what you're going to have for
dinner, you're not paying attention. You should be discussing how much you're going to get for
the scrap metal or where's the life jacket because you're not paying any – I mean it's really bad,
the situation. Anybody could look up what I just said. The US has been bankrupt
since 1933 and then in 1934, it went into receivership. I'm not going to explain what
that is. You could look up what receivership after bankruptcy is and it's not what you think.
Just look it up. It's a little phrase. You could meditate on that. Also, if you look up Title 12,
Section 411 in the US Code, it says that only Federal Reserve agents are allowed to use Federal
Reserve notes and no other use is authorized. That's Title 12, USC, Section 411. It's a little
legalese paragraph but it's written in 8th grade level so anybody could read it. Now, wait a second.
Stop for a moment because if you're out there and you have any sort of what they generally refer
to as paper money in your pocket, you can take it out and read what phrase on it, Greg.
Federal Reserve note which is a check. If you look up USC Title 12, Section 411, it tells you
unless you're a Federal Reserve agent, there is no other use for using that is authorized. Now,
do you need that to be interpreted? If I see no other use or not authorized,
I don't need to have that explained to me by anyone.
Well, I found it interesting too that when I was looking at the whole voting thing over this
selection process recently that laid out right in the law is something that says if you're voting
effectively for a national leadership position, you're also acting against the state in which
you live. Kind of fascinating. It's insurrection. But the real purpose, by the way, here's the
thing. We brought up several subjects. The past few subjects we just brought up are large social
concepts, military, 9-11, money. It's a large social stuff. Let's not get into more specific
ones regarding health and whatever is more scientific. But if you regard just these subjects
that we brought up and you just look at what is really going on, it's not difficult to just spend
a few minutes looking at it. You will see that the way the common man or common moron perceives
these things is so radically different from how they're memorialized and what the laws behind them
are and the rationale behind them are that the gap is huge. In other words, right now your average
surface-toiling earth inhabitant has to go 500 steps in the opposite direction that they're going
just to get to zero. So it ain't going to happen, folks. That's why earlier, did I say their shows
may be irrelevant? Yeah, I think you did. Yeah, there's a few people here that are looking up
things. Okay, folks, we have more than four listeners. I've gotten maybe five or ten scores
of emails and everyone's been positive and the people that chime in or write in are,
I would say, pretty rational. Really, folks, there's about 200 of you out there.
How to be objective? What are these things based on? What is the true nature of the thing?
Let's go back and we'll give a lot of allegory and metaphor on how to be objective and maybe
these points were easier to remember. Okay, now, Chuck, let's just remember the point of
right after 9-11, like 24 to 72 hours after the military should have been disbanded completely,
all branches of service, all leadership, all the way down to the foot shoulder and
just replaced by eighth graders with slingshots would have been whatever.
The allegedly intelligence community, I mean, the whole apparatus, the whole thing, yes.
And apparati or apparatuses, right? Whatever they may be called, yes. Okay.
Okay, now, why? That sounds like an extreme statement. I'm very nationalist and patriarch,
we should have a military. Yeah, but look, when you look at something like the military,
it's pretty extreme. It's not like eighth graders with slingshots. I mean, they've got
really serious hardware and ordnance and a tremendous investment, right?
Hardware, ordnance, hardware, ordnance, training, uniforms, logistics.
A tremendous investment. Are they there to help an old lady cross the street or take a cat out
of a tree? No. They're there to do some real serious activity, right? Okay, so we had something,
I wouldn't say, it wasn't another, and also a military is designed to be a parody with another
military, not an eighth grader with a slingshot, let's say, from Chechnya. It would be a Chechen
military, a Russian military, an Italian military, another military. So here we have passenger
airlines, right? And guys with box cutters, okay? And they couldn't do anything with that. That is
so egregiously off. Not because I believe so or whatever, because the status of that position,
of that framework, of what we call the military, again, is it there for helping old ladies cross
the street or taking cats out of trees or whatever? No, it is there to do, to be thorough, to be
extreme, to be dynamic, to be, right? And they failed so miserably that the, well, how would
you say, the retribution of criticizing them solely for not doing their job didn't come at
all. I mean, it was, it all- Right, and to correlate this, to correlate this in an allegorical sense,
once again, you know, the box cutters versus this massive military apparatus, it is one apparatus,
I'll call it that. The fact is, it's very much like imagining that the newly walking toddler has
just knocked out a 20-year-old boy with a right cross. That is how disparate the equation is when
you think about the box cutters, which did the damage it did to the buildings and everything
else. At the end of the day, a couple of guys and a couple of dollar store box cutters, basically.
Right. And your expertise, I would call it expertise, let's just say opinion or whatever
aside, I would consider you an expert on that because you've had private conversations on,
looked at your work. Would you say it is physically impossible for Oswald to have
taken the shot where and when it happened? Yeah. The way it was told. That's a huge problem.
Yeah, not what you believe in, but physically just doesn't add up. I mean, just like,
you know, three plus three doesn't equals, you know, nine or 19, that's how far off.
Yeah, but everyone still accepts it. Why? Because they cannot be objective.
Yeah, I would love a pack of Twinkies to satisfy, you know, an entire barbecue filled with 200
people, but I'm just not going to accomplish that with that particular package of Twinkies.
It's not going to happen. In the future, you might try seven loaves of bread, but anyway.
Maybe. Yeah. So here, what's going on? Well, you know, who are we going to address here?
You know, one of the sayings that I like to put into an old Texas saying that they couldn't pour
piss out of a boot even with instructions on the heel. Now, let's think about that for a moment,
folks. If you don't know how to pour piss out of a boot and someone tells you there's instructions
on the heel and you still can't do it, you just got to scratch your head and walk away,
right? Because just looking for the instructions will get the job done. You get it?
This is how simple being objective can be. You have to look for what it's based on or what it is.
Just look. But, you know, it was written somewhere that the people will not, their eyes will be
closed so they can't see and their ears will be closed so they can't hear. That's from a spiritual
point of view. Didn't we ever come up with a term or mention a term called cosmic censorship?
Anyway. Yeah. If you want to know more about that, it's past events, sonic events. So, but this
doesn't mean that it can be, cannot be broken through. There's a Wizard of Oz book and film
where how difficult was it for Dorothy to figure out what was going on behind the curtain? Was she,
did she need the military to do that? No, I'm just joking. Oh, just a little dog.
Yeah, that's right. It was very simple. All you have to do is look around you. Now, if you remember
the scene, I don't clearly remember it, but basically they're all frightened and she's
looking off to the side and she noticed something that got her attention that no one else had seen
and she went over there and the whole thing was exposed. But right now, whether it's the
Kennedy assassination or all these other things, 9-11 or whatever, it doesn't matter. You can come
out and give all the specificities of all these things, but the people, it's, they'll say, oh,
that was then, this is now. So they've gotten to the point now where there is no more, how would
you say, hope in that department as a general society. In other words, the train, the tracks
are laid out, the train's going to go. But you either jump off the train or you stay on the
train, make sure you don't have any sharp objects around you when it takes the hit, right? That's
basically what the purpose of the Greek speaking is. Set yourself apart from it. If you want to be
politically, religiously, or whatever involved in any of these group think mentalities, activism
or whatever, do it at your own risk. But I'm telling you, it's not efficient and time better
well spent. Like you can do other things like sleeping, taking a shower, taking a windy walk,
walking a dog, but anyway. But that being said, it's interesting because we had this discussion
at the beginning here, where if you see something, you need to say something effectively.
If you see something being done, though, don't you need to do something on occasion?
Yeah, but people are held, there's many levels of that also, because again,
they're motivated by penalty. If I don't do it, will I get in trouble? Or then you have those
that actually do things that are correct, when someone needs help. But I have noticed, for
example, if you're traveling, conveying in a motorized wagon, known as an automobile, it's
not really an automobile because you have to put fuel in it. Someone will stop, the car will die
out and everyone behind them is honking. It's like, do you think he just parked at the green
light to ruin your day? The guy needs help. Have you ever seen that or heard of that?
So you do have a lot of, it's a mixed bag, there's no consistency there. But basically,
folks, all in the young ones, objectivity is very simple, but it's very difficult and complicated
when you're constantly being pounded with this motivation by penalty. The religious groups do
it a lot too. If you don't do this, you're going to hell, right? You ever heard that before, by the
way? And not just the Bible Belt, but actually the buckle of the Bible Belt, it gets pretty bad,
but all this stuff, it's all penalty, penalty, penalty, penalty. How can you think straight?
You're traumatized. It would be a form of spiritual or psychological trauma that most people are under
right now. Now, both the mainstream and the alternative take advantage of that.
Like, for example, how many times have you heard about both mainstream and alternative
commentators and guests and hosts pick the subjects we just covered and talk and talk and
talk for years and years and years and write books and do all this stuff and never address
the basic fact that we just brought up, that most simple objective thing. It's not because we're
bringing it up, because what is the purpose of the military? What was the purpose of this? What
is the purpose of that? And let's see how they did in this situation. How would you grade them?
And then go on and see what happens. You ever notice, by the way, when things are reported
they in the media, they say, well, this happened and we don't know who to blame yet.
You ever hear that? Who's to blame? I always find it. I always find it interesting, too, because
I often stop my own shows on occasion by by entering some of these more reduced thoughts
into the end of the discussion. You want me to give you an example?
OK. We talk about vaccinations and what the components are and how damaging they are.
Yes, indeed, I do believe they are. But I turn to why are you allowing someone to
utilize a piece of metal to inject something into your body unless it's absolutely necessary?
But motivation, a penalty, again, to stop disease. If you don't get that,
we'll have contagious diseases. Well, then if so, then if the vaccines work so well,
then why don't you just get it and shut up? And if everyone else doesn't, you'll be fine
because you're vaccinated. Right. Well, yeah. Another point I bring up as well.
And but that's the funny part is I bring these things up and really it makes a lot of people
who are well prepared on the subject to discuss, you know, the methylmercury, the thimerosal,
the squalene, you know, exactly what strains are being used, live viruses, everything else.
A lot of them stumble over the very simple things that I bring up like that, though.
Well, are they from planet Earth? I assume, you know, that's why we mentioned in the beginning
of the program, you know, go ahead. Well, I'm saying I cannot objectively state that I know
that with absolute certainty, but I do assume it. Everything leads to that. They were probably born
here and have inherited all the crap we're talking about. Yeah. And they're still carrying on as if
everything's OK and they're looking for someone to blame. So being objective, folks, what is it
based on, you know, how simple it is now? No, let's just bring up a point. I think since you
and I started speaking two years ago, I said this is a time period, by the way, that's going to end
around the spring of twenty eighteen. So it's getting closer because the year starts in the
spring. Right. It ends in the fall of the previous year. And the winter is an interim time. And I
think I've explained that on how to keep time, which is an old show that we did. It might still
be up on the YouTube playlist. So when this all you have from the past seven years, what you call
roughly 2011, the spring 2010, what have I been saying, folks, those who have listened to the
Greek? I'm not just to pat myself on the back, but sometimes you do because no one else does,
let's say. But just to say at this point, this seven years is going to be a time of distraction
and confusion. And all you're going to be getting is missing planes, financial crisis and political
scandal. And that's going to keep repeating missing planes. I mean, when I look at the
Internet news or whatever on a home page, I've been noticing that there's either a plane accident
or a missing plane every month. Now, have you noticed that, Chuck? Yeah, I have. And you want
I just want to interject something here really quickly. Ironically, I have been stopped from
posting in the chat room because I was spamming with one word answers to people,
according to the system. And also, I am not. Yeah, I'm not answering people on the Skype texts
any longer. If you want to join into the discussion, the number is 218-339-8525,
218-339-8525. I promise I won't interrupt you with the numbers again, Greek. But
one more thing, the Ocelli and the Greek Skype is also a way to join in. That is how you're
going to have to do it. I'm not I'm not messing around with this anymore. So there you go.
So there you go. Yeah. Tell it. Tell it like it is. OK. No, I'm poured on thick. Give the number
one more time. 218-218-339-8525. So 218-339-8525. If you are capable of operating a telephone,
it will work. All right. Now, this is this is not my opinion, by the way, folks. This is just
simple rationale. If someone gives you a list of numbers, let's say four or five numbers added up
and they say, here it is. Well, that's not correct. Let's go over it again. What is the purpose of
this? Can we quantify and qualify what we're talking about? Let's say we just came to this
planet. I just want to repeat this one point maybe for the fourth time. We're just visiting
this planet. We watch what happened on 9-11 and we look at everything that's through, put all the
apparatus put through society. We notice an apparatus called the military. And I'm not from
this planet. I would say, OK, these guys didn't do their job so poorly that why are they still
there? Not my opinion. I mean, it's just like adding up things. It just doesn't add up that
that nothing was focused in their direction. Right. And the same thing with the with the Kennedy
shooting that Chuck, I'm sure you've gone over for hundreds of hours, I'm sure, on air. And
there's lots of other evidence. And just like pretty much anything that you are shown on a social,
political, historical point of view, most of the stuff just ain't so.
But the people are just so traumatized and they just want to be liked. Remember that we were
saying one of the rules is, but anyway, no one really cares. They just want to be liked. So
all this mixed bag of stuff combined with the cosmic censorship that's going to change,
start changing here in a few. And you're in a situation where I think it would be good advice
to learn to be objective. Why? So you don't end up being inefficient. And I think I gave the
example years ago. Remember, was it two years ago or maybe three or four? There was a big movement
for what they call survivalists or what do they call those people that store food for a bad day
when there's a disaster? Preppers. Preppers. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Preppers. There was a fellow,
a local fellow, an older guy, and he said, aren't you stocking up on water?
And the other guy said, no, why? Nothing's going to happen. And he's like, well, if something
happens, I'm not going to give you anything. You're going to die. And I'm like, oh, boy,
this guy is really, really kind of extreme. I better walk away. So I saw him a couple of years
later. I mean, actually recently and maybe a year ago or so. And I said, well, how's my prepping
going? He said, oh, that was back then. And I just got up. It's all right. I don't need to do
that. I'm like, what? Are you joking? How can you be? So do you know how much he spent, let's say,
on rice and beans and gasoline and generators and all that? Wouldn't that have been better spent
somewhere else? You see? So the level of inefficiency is just- Was this like Y2K era
or was it after that? No, no, no. After that. This was when- There's been various waves.
2012, I think, around there, what they call 2012. Would you- Right.
Between 2012 and 2014, it was getting kind of thick there with the prepping.
Well, a couple of things happened. First of all, just in my lifetime,
there's been various threats that were allegedly happening where people did this in waves.
But most notably, I would say, the Y2K threat, the 2012 threat. I think there was- Well,
when it comes to guns and ammo, there was definitely an upsurge when Obama became president.
But quite often, again, it does boil right down to threat of, well, some sort of bad thing
happening. Penalty. Yeah. They were motivated by penalty. Look, if you want to do the right thing,
you should always be prepared. You don't care. You're not extreme and you're not crazy and you're
not inefficient if you're carrying a spare tire on the car. You're not a pessimist either. You're
just prepared. Right? So there's nothing wrong with having some extra food and extra water,
whatever else you think you might need if the lights just went out or if there was a major
disaster. So I'm not saying don't do that. I'm just saying what these people get wrapped up and
isn't coming. The dollar collapse is another thing that you keep over and over. I'm like,
well, that's kind of a joke because there is no dollar. The U.S. dollar is just a note for a
dollar. So anyway, there was a show called Casper the Friendly Ghost. Is it Casper the Friendly
Dollar now? Is that what it is? It's going to collapse. But anyway. Well, and we take that all
the way back. Bill Cooper was talking about this in the 1990s for sure. I was listening to it then
and we're still hearing about it today, that the dollar is not only going to collapse,
which eventually, even if you accept that it could, it has it has to at some point.
But the fact is, as I previously tell you, it's it's it's coming very soon, though.
Yeah, actually, it did collapse already. You're under you're running under receivership.
It's a note for a dollar. There is no dollar. You know, you know where they get the dollar
in the market. That is because certain Federal Reserve Bank type institutions and, you know,
the JP Morgans and the big ones, we need to mention them. They get first dibs on transactions.
That's all it is. And they're American based companies. If you look at where how these
companies you've heard of, like Delaware Corporation, New York Corporation or whatever.
Right. These are American based corporations. They get first dib on transactions. One day,
we'll talk about how the money system works. And actually, I did with someone last night.
You shouldn't say that in public because it's too extreme. Are you joking?
It might be, you know, not on planet Earth. But if I go to Alpha Centauri and say it,
they'll say maybe we should get into the mothership, go there and blow this planet up,
take them out of their misery. They're so dumb. But but here, if you say it,
no one really listens anyway. It's just really, really sad how the money system works.
Actually, the money system works in a way. So there's an unlimited supply of it. So there's
no excuse that you didn't have the money to do something. Does that make sense for the government
side? They can create all the money they'd ever wanted, but they can't tell you where it comes from
because human greed is so bad that then you won't want to do anything. It'll actually
paralyze you. You know, let me just give you the end of the story for this.
When we did talk about the money system for a couple of hours in the past,
another sonic events. But how would you think people would react? I mean,
all let's say three hundred and whatever million people here, if they got a check for about seventy
three thousand every month, what do you think they would do? Do you think they would go and
work and take care of all the stuff needs to be taken care of? And, you know, what do you think?
How much do you think a loaf of bread or a gallon of milk will cost in about a month?
You see where I'm going? And this is, you know, and every we just you don't have to ask for them.
You just the government sends it to you. And what will happen if everyone gets a check like that
every month? The debt goes down to zero because there is no debt. The debt is excess credit.
Now, funny thing is funny thing is, Greg, I think that's actually going to happen at some point.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. And this was set up to be a perfect society. Remember in Star Trek that
you guys don't have any money here? You know, when they brought someone from the past is no,
no, because everybody understands they have to do what they have to do. We don't need money.
Mm hmm. You see. So but you look at the people. It's it's not. Hmm. You really can't
blame the leadership. Oh, we got to blame somebody. But anyway, where do the leaders
come from? Alpha Centauri? Are they from Earth also? You see. So well, they certainly come.
They certainly come from Earth. And so does this particular broadcast. Ocelli in the Greek,
we have completed one hour, according to that wind up toy or the digital representation
that we call a clock. And in hour two, I'm sure we're going to get a bit deeper.
And hey, who knows, you might actually learn something. Stay tuned.
The second hour of Ocelli in the Greek begins here on American Freedom Radio from the facilities of
AmericanFreedomRadio.com. Of course, I'm Chuck Ocelli and the Greek is with me. And well,
you know, this is definitely a decidedly different show from what you will get elsewhere. I see
questions coming up here and there. And I know I said I wouldn't respond to the chat room. But
one last time I will, because I'm being asked if donations are fit and proper Greek. So I don't
know if you want to respond to that. Yeah, there's no simple answer. But if someone is asking that you
could give might as well give if you feel like giving and what is feeling have to do with it.
The thing is, are you being objective? So, you know, a cup of coffee a day, whatever, what does
that cost or whatever, right? How often do you, you know, go somewhere? I mean, I used to hear
that going to the movies was real cheap to get out of the summer heat for two hours, right?
So what do you get in here, you know, or there or whatever? What's it worth to you? But, you know,
could free mean be an acronym? Free from revenue emanated elsewhere. So there's no free lunch,
really, is it? Well, there actually are free lunches. It's been paid by someone else.
So using that term loosely pay, but by the way, Chuck, one thing we did leave out when you asked
me at the very, very beginning was what day is it? And I did not answer. I just got off and just
spun everybody off on well, you know how what you think it is, isn't. But you're exactly you're
exactly right. I did not press you on that. And we did wind up going off into another direction. So
yeah, you did not actually announce the day for the listener, right? Just like no one ever
really announced who did in JFK or what happened on 911. Let's say completely or whatever. Yes,
same thing. So it doesn't matter. It just get wrapped up. And were they telling us it's this
and I guess it's good enough. So and by the way, I'm not a conspiracy theorist and all that other
mindless earth people stuff. I'm just saying, folks, you're not paying attention. None of you
are and I see none of you 99.999999999%. So let's just say we almost didn't say it again. It
appears to be around the 23rd day of this of the 11th month. Hmm. Hmm. So I don't know. It sounds
confusing, right? Well, anyway, Decem means 10, doesn't it? You know? So and Nova means nine and
Octo means eight and septum means seven. All day and all night. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So anyway,
objective, we're trying to see what is it? What is the substance? What is the law? Because law
can bear substance as well. Because it guides one's behavior and one's thoughts, right? Remember,
we were talking about taking a class on geometry where you construct basic geometric forms without
a ruler or any measurement. You basically, the concept of construction, just using a string,
basically, and a straight, you know, a divider and a compass and a straight edge. And you can
create all these geometric forms, but they must be lawful. If you do a three sided figure, it has
to bear the qualities of a three sided figure, a four sided figure the same, a circle the same.
They have qualities and there are laws behind them. Because if you don't follow the law of a
circle, how are you going to construct the triangle properly? You won't be able to. It
just goes on and on and on. So let's just give the term objective an etymological definition.
They just basically say something objective to the mind. It's a military term, objective point.
Okay, objective, 1610, originally in the philosophical sense of considered in relation
to its object. Philosophical sense, the doctrine that knowledge is based on objective reality.
You notice how even that's not really or just in a regular dictionary,
here that the state of quality of being objective. Objectivity is a noun that means a lack of bias,
judgment or prejudice. Maintaining one's objectivity is the most important job of a judge.
The meaning of objectivity is easy to remember when you see that the word object embedded within it.
So how do we, you know, how do we? Partially sensible, partially sensible because
they did mention a judge there and a judge's job is to judge, not to prejudge or to condemn.
So prejudice should be removed from the equation as the antithesis of objectivity.
That means that you approach it without, well, judging it ahead of time, right?
Or heresy is the opposite of objectivity. If you're in a Greek speaking or Greek reading,
it would be, what do you like? So in other words, if you went to an ice cream shop,
instead of saying, what flavor do you like, what flavor is your heresy, right?
So basically, this thing about, and by the way, that's why I don't partake in any media,
even in background, I have music and other things like that. And by the way, folks,
I brought up music and let's be objective. If it sounds good, it is good. And friends don't
listen, friends don't let friends listen to bad music. So I think they asked, who's the trumpet
player, Satchmo, you know, what's your favorite music? And he says, man, if it sounds good,
it is good, right? It doesn't matter what the genre is, right? Now, that's kind of interesting
because it's like, what flavor ice cream do you like? You know, certain things are subjective,
but if strawberry gives you a rash, you can objectify that, right? You could say,
no strawberry for sure. To me, opinions and beliefs and likes give me rashes. So anyway.
Listen, I used to enjoy coconut and then it started giving me a rash,
so I don't partake in it any longer. Right, because you had to objectify it,
that it was the coconut. Yeah, you don't do, yeah. Stop putting knitting needles in your own eyes,
so this is what's going on. And basically, what is the object sense or what is the objectivity
of a thing? What is the purpose of a thing is a very simple, simple way to look at it.
You know, the purpose, you know, we're here on a minor internet radio station, just two guys
shooting the shit. It's a private conversation that's being uploaded and streamed somehow on
American Freedom Radio. That's really the reality of it, right? Now, what's perceived is, oh,
it's Ocelli and the Greek, you know, but we don't speak other than on the show. And basically,
I think I have the right to say that this is a private conversation done in public.
And essentially, you know, that's the objectivity of it. We don't have any
group or plan or producers or anything for Ocelli and the Greek and we sit behind and we devise an
agenda and this, that and the other, you know, at all. This would just show up and just say it like
it is as much as possible. Why? Why? Because later on, no one can say, hey, man, you knew and
you didn't say anything. You know, right now it just sounds like, you know, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah,
but it'll happen in terms of time. It'll come to a point where the people will be ready to see
just what's just in front of them. Like right now, the snakes are not biting. Have you ever heard
the term, if it were a snake, it would have bit you? You know, you're looking for something that's
right there, right? Well, guess what? The snakes are not biting right now, right? So anyway,
there's many, many, many levels to it. The objectivity of it, let's just say, you know, we're
here having this private conversation in public. Well, let's just look at what's going on. What's
the purpose of the internet? You know, everybody's kind of strung together, you know, where there used
to be telephone lines. Now it's both wired and unwired, this, that and the other. You know, they
have these things called homepages, major providers, you know, the big search engine companies,
this, that and the other. When you do a cursory examination of what's being put forward,
at least in the iconography or the imagery and the sound, it's still very commercial. It's still
appealing to the way things are, what people have inherited, which is lack of objectivity and your
heresy, what you like. For example, if you have a computer and it opens up to, I'm not going to
mention any major homepage, you're plastered with ads for like stupid stuff, for anything from hair
growth to big boobs, big butts, this, that and the other.
Mail enhancement, tax forms.
Yeah. What's the deal? I mean, you know, it's okay. So here's this technology, you know,
and but no one really, I recall saying, like they did for the printing press,
there was some opposition when printing presses in Europe became inexpensive and it was easy to
print things. There was some opposition. The opposition was as such. They said, well, now,
great, all this gossip and all this junk is going to be scattered everywhere. It's going to spread
even more because before that it had to be told or it was posted up somewhere. Now they're going
to print all these papers, you know, all these things and scatter and all this junk that people
have on their minds is going to be memorialized on paper. Great. That's what we need. And this was a
comment done around the 1500s. Right. So if you look at a lot of the objective commentary that's
been done, whether it was 3000 years ago, 2000 years ago, 1000 years ago, or even 100 years ago,
Samuel Clemens, Mark Twain is one of my favorites, by the way, for 19th century commentators.
Me too. Yeah. Right. It hasn't changed. The commentary on society and the people at large
on this planet is pretty much the same. So why is there a lack of objectivity? Well, the cosmic
censorship and of course the heresy and the hypocrisy. But let's, you know, this is a long
winded maybe attitude I'm taking on because we're still on the Internet and I'm talking about the
Internet. Now here's the purpose of the Internet. It can't be anything significant if you turn on
a homepage and it's still the same junk. So what is really going on? Let's put the financial stuff
aside because, you know, if the Internet goes down, they say the financial community goes down. Right.
Or the ability to do transactions right now and other things. You know, I think they just
have the voting thing and all that stuff, you know, but again, it's not being objectified.
So what is the real purpose of the Internet so far from a cosmic point of view? It's a beta test.
It is no different. What you've been witnessing on the Internet for the past decade, maybe two
decades, is no different than a sound engineer on stage on a rock concert saying, check 123,
check 123. That is not the show, folks. The band is yet to come. Right. He's doing microphone check.
You have right now to this date on the Internet, microphone check when it comes to information.
That's all you folks have been getting. It's going to start in the next few years. It's going to be
very exciting when it happens, but it can't happen and shock the hell out of you. It's going to be
very gradual and you're going to fall for the influx of a new way of thinking where, hey,
where did that come from? Like you see that right now. There's more talk about vaccines,
corn syrup and foods, this treatment, that treatment, this political thing, you know,
a leak here or whatever, you know, or, you know, political stuff, you know, things are coming out
that have never even, let's say, imagined to be on the scale that they are because of the Internet.
So what's going to happen is a level of objectivity that you're going to see starting
most likely what you call the next decade in the early 2020s that will be unprecedented. But the
real purpose of the Internet is much later than that, not much, much later than that, but in the
mid 2020s and a little bit beyond that, let's say the end of the 2020s, it's going to be in place
so everyone on the planet can see certain events with both audio and video happening.
Which I find to be quite valid. It's one of those prevailing, reoccurring images
that has been memorialized in several places. At one point there will be, well, not just the,
you know, biblical text, but over and over again it's been reported that there will be a time of
unanimity where observation will be worldwide. And I got to tell you, as a child I used to
wonder how that could be accomplished based on what I understood. And well, the answer was,
in my estimation, the Internet. So it makes sense.
Well, it pieces, yeah, you could piece it together. Yeah, there is ancient text beyond
the biblical text that say that all mankind will see this. Well, how the hell are they going to
see such a local event happening? Let's say something like down the street somewhere.
Well, there you go. I mean, have you heard of someone, what do they do, a YouTube video,
you know, something and they can get it uploaded and going viral in a day, right?
So this is basically, it's going to get even more elaborate as time goes on. So just relax and
still pay attention to what's going on with the Internet, but it ain't much.
Look, I'll be impressed if someone can email me like a tuna fish sandwich or something,
or peanut butter and jelly. If you can, if someone can just drop a text, you know,
some fried chicken in the chat box right now that I can eat, that'll impress the hell out of me
right now. I'd love to see that, you know, otherwise it's just a dummy load.
No, look, I would be quite impressed with that as well. If somebody could literally just,
and who knows? Look, I think that those possibilities are probably going to emerge
as well. What do you think? Yeah, well, right now I've, you know,
the 3D printing thing is real interesting because now someone just doesn't have to send you
a drawing that you have to look at, but you could have the computer in a certain mode that,
you know, it could actually get the printer moving and you come on three hours later and
there's an object there, you know, that they drew up, you know, technically.
Actually, and on a larger scale, I mean, these things could be utilized to build housing even
from a blueprint, which has been sent to it, you know, from the other side of the planet.
And as long as you tell the machine to execute it with the proper hardware, it can be done.
Well, that's the term again, objective. The object is actually physical, it's tactile,
and thoughts are that way also. Can you think of something where you can actually, in your mind,
taste it, feel it, touch it, like a real good example would be to objectify a thought is,
remember the old number two yellow pencils? You know, when you just sharpen it, you have that
cedar smell, and it's got that real sharp carbon tip, and you touch the metal ferrule on the end
by the eraser, and it's kind of cold, and that little pink rubber eraser had that real rubbery
gum smell, you know? As you're describing it, I'm recalling it. So, yeah. Yeah, so you can
actually objectify a thought. I mean, it might be, you know, laying down on a beach drinking a
pina colada or something while you're having a conversation on the internet or something.
You can objectify thoughts. You know, if someone says, what do you feel like eating?
And they bring up the point, I mean, you just, it's like, in your mind, it's, you're ready,
right? Because you know what it tastes like, and you know what it will taste like when you get it.
So, thoughts can be objectified as well. So, again, when you look and hear about things,
what are they based on? If it's the first, here's the unfortunate part about being objective,
because it's based on knowledge, experience, and then trust. If someone starts, let's say,
communicating or giving testimony or report on something you've never heard of,
means you have no knowledge of it, right? And then there's the trust element. Is this person
trustworthy? Are they telling you the truth about it, right? Or are they giving you a good report?
Is it a reliable source, in other words, from whence the information came, you know?
Right. So, this is how things, but the thing is that people really don't care,
essentially. I mean, you could see this in history as a witness to all the events and even the
current events about objectifying anything. And when I say anything, I mean most things.
And if anything is objectified, it's not really popular. You won't make friends being objective,
by the way. But when you look at what is to be objective, unfortunately, the unfortunate part
is you're going to have to do some homework. And what that does is it prevents haste. You know,
it prevents getting whipped up into a lather about something, right? And what happens,
it's okay to hear something that's emotional or striking, you know, tragic or whatever,
and get the emotional response. But you have to get calm and cool and seek out the facts and the
nature of the thing, right? And that doesn't happen. The initial emotional impulse is carried
through for years and years and years. And if anyone wants to understand how that works,
there's a book I think around 1895 called The Crowd by Gustave Le Bon. And he talks of objectifies
how crowds come together, and it's right on. So how does one objectify? Well, the disadvantage is
you have to be pretty aware and well-informed and have people around you that if you're not
informed or aware of something, and you want to inquire, you have someone around you who is
knowledgeable in that and trustworthy. They've just saved you a lot of time, right? And henceforth,
why you have a lot of people coming out and discussing stuff, writing books, having websites,
almost sort of internet celebrities and others, you know, before the internet as well. And if you
actually examine a lot of their work, they're really appealing to the emotional convention
that was initially laid out for the event. And they tiptoe or omit things that really would lead
to true objectivity. And they pick one thing obsessively and carry it forward. And that's
how their claim to fame. And that is not allowed in objectivity, because you need to look at all
sides of the thing. And by the way, you know, we've made some pretty tall statements here before.
And let's just make another one. I'm tired of hearing of all these people that are into,
oh, I know I have a cult knowledge or this and that. Or, oh, yeah, I know this. I've got wisdom
and all that. I listen to them. I'm like, you got to be joking. You know, because why? Because I'm
trying to objectify it. I don't fall into the crap. And no one should. But here's the thing.
You could rely on people not caring. That's one of the rules, by the way,
for calling in. And people are very reliable when it comes to things like that. They just
like the emotional slop and the heresy. You know, what do you like? I like this person.
I've gotten many emails about approving information. I'm like, why do you need my
approval? Did you read it? Is it a good report? I never even read approval-type links that people
send. Like, what do you think? I'm like, well, what's the point? Is it a good report or not?
Period. I'm not going to look at it. You tell me what you got out of it. I'm not going to waste my
time on it. Because it is a waste of time, usually, what's on the internet these days.
Or anywhere, even in print mostly, I found from doing research years ago.
So the thing here is, how does one objectify and have friends? Well, I think we've said before,
you won't make friends being objective unless you find others that are also objective. But if
they're objective, they're busier than a one-legged man in an ass-kicking contest,
and you probably won't be friends because you won't have time to do stuff that friends do
together. So there you go again. Anyway, it takes a lot of work.
But just like going to a gym, you can't go to the gym for the first day and lift all the weights
and do all the stuff. You'll be sore as heck if you can even do it. It's repetitive. It's
like a muscle. You acquire what needs to be done, the methodology, and the more you do it,
the stronger it gets. And eventually, things that you couldn't even comprehend,
if you focus on being objective, what is it based on? Where did it come from? Am I getting
truthful reporting? Is it accurate reporting? In the beginning, it seems like an overload.
But when you get used to doing it, it's no big deal. You can lift that weight. It seems like
a lot of weight in the beginning. But just like going to a gym, the muscles required to lift it
or handle it are used to it and get stronger and stronger and stronger.
But there's a little bit of a flaw here, and I want you to address it. The fact is that I've
seen very good reports given on very narrow subjects, and I've seen two different people
that I would generally believe to be fairly intelligent based on most standards take
completely different viewpoints on what seems to be an entirely objective report. So it's not all
about the quality of the report always. That's simple, but that's simple also,
Chuck, because if two people have opposing – if both people are coming to you saying
they're discussing the same thing and the truth of the matter and their story
differs, then the only possibility is they're both wrong or only one of them is right because
if they differ that much, they both cannot be correct.
Well, I'll give you an example that will probably seem very circular, but there are people that
have listened to the shows that we've done, and they take entirely different
qualities from those shows that, yes, indeed did occur or sound like they occurred based on my
memory, and they take wholly different points of view of what was actually discussed,
what knowledge was imparted, what knowledge wasn't imparted, etc., etc., and it's always been a
fascinating thing to me that the individual is subject to interpretation no matter what you give
them, no matter what thing is in existence. Even a block of wood represents something different to
different people that handle it, and it's just – it's an odd thing.
Well, it's planet Earth. Remember, if you're visiting – the purpose of this reload is to put
together a sonic manual, if you could accept it as such, for anyone that could pipe in that is
coming to visit Earth to get an idea of what it's like when you start dealing to the
anthropoids on this planet. This is what you're going to expect.
Anthropoids, okay.
Yeah, so they're surface-dwelling Earth-inhabitants. But let's go back to the
occult, and this is very simple. There's the deepest – when you go down to the bottom of
the ocean where it's really super deep, it gets really simple, doesn't it? You just see a couple
of stones and a lot of sand, maybe a really odd-looking fish or some creature, maybe it
looked like a stone and you touched it and it swam away, but it's very simple at the bottom.
You might see a shipwreck, but it's simple. The deeper you go, the simpler it gets.
And I'm not talking about the rabbit hole analogy here, because even that is true.
Eventually you're going to reach the terminus, right?
But let's just share – part of the thing I used to do with the previous one is
let's just maybe demolish a cliché, biblical clichés and other things that are just so
misunderstood. And it's not because I have my interpretation. By the way, there are many
versions but only one interpretation. People are not even using the term correctly. Like if you're
a diplomat and you go to the UN, you have an interpreter. He cannot give a version. He has
to be as accurate as possible based on the etymology of the words used and the point that's
being conveyed. Now, versions are different. Versions is when you pick up the newspaper.
The New York Times said this and this and blah, blah, blah.
So this is…
Well, I understand that. But again, it falls apart because the quality of the interpreter
does sometimes change the message.
Yes.
And look…
Well, we spoke about quality. Quality is important.
Quality is always important. Right. Go ahead.
Yeah. But let's just go – this is a little thing here about being objective and it's
one of the older ways of thinking, especially in Asia. The question was asked to the – the
instructor would ask the students when they got to a certain level, what do all things in the
universe have in common? All things in the universe, no matter what they are, what it is,
that you can imagine or see or interact with, especially being in an anthropomorphic form,
right? You know, head, body and all that. And even outside, when you're using your thoughts outside
of that body, let's say, being constrained, there are basically eight things or four pairs that all
things in the universe have in common. And this is one of the most basic when you get to a certain
level of discussion on objectification, let's say in schools of martial arts or schools of alchemy
and other things like that. These things are brought up. And why aren't they kind of like put
together very simply and discussed? You know, you got all these old farts and young farts coming
around, you know, I'm into cult stuff. And I listen to some of them like, where's the objectivity?
Who cares what you think? You know, what did you discover that could help, right? So here's
the question. I mean, why not drop a little pearl in each show, right? A little bit, you know,
but you're not supposed to cast pearls to swine, right? But who's the swine? I don't know.
But if you look, you know, people are called sheeple. You know, there's – in the ancient
texts, they have the goats, the sheep, and the dogs, and the pigs. Now, what makes them all
different is their qualities. But the pigs are – you know, you've heard don't cast your pearls to
swine, right? But that's incomplete. The rest of it is because they will trample the pearls and then
tear you to pieces because pigs are very violent when they eat. If you throw, let's say, some hog
swaller in a trough and here come all the hungry pigs. If you put your finger in there, they're going
to take it off. I mean a horse could take it off too. But I mean a pig has got incredible clamping
pressure the way their teeth are. So they're violent eaters. Where the sheep are very particular
eaters, the people are not sheeple. In other words, because they eat all these chunks. If you have
sheep and you feed them a wrong type of food, they can get sick and die. Now, that means that
if you give them metaphorically the wrong information, they're like, oh, they'll make me sick,
you know? And then you have the goat. The goat will eat anything, pretty much, right? And they're
kind of like more in this – like how many – a goat would be explaining what cannibals' birthdays
and dolls have in common. They say, oh, that's horrible. And then next week they call you up,
invite you to a birthday party. That's a goat. Where if you're a sheep and you found out what
cannibals' birthdays and dolls have in common, if someone calls you to invite you to a birthday
party, you get sick. Just the concept of it. And then the dog will eat his own vomit,
meaning like the things that are not good for him, he keeps going back to, right? The things that he
said he would not use or do or that he ate before it came up because it wasn't digestible,
he ate it again. Now, the pig is very interesting. That would be the category of people that are
violent, become violent when they're subjected to certain thought forms or language or reports,
right? Now, I have personally seen, especially the higher up you go in the entitled classes,
whether it's legal society, the medical society, political society,
scientifically society, if you show them very simple contradictions that they employ
and all their methodologies that they've inherited, they get really, really upset.
And if you start looking at their body language, they're almost to the point where they're ready
to call security or screwity if you're from the ghetto, and they almost have a sight in their
face like they want to put violence on you, right? So they're not goats. They're not.
And even Black Sabbath being one of my favorite bands, the esoteric messages which are contained
in some of the lyrics, thank you, Mr. Butler, the song War Pigs was very apt, very adequately
titled. It wasn't something chosen at random. It's just not being in the mud. It's about a
level of violence. And most people don't understand. When you say pig, you think,
oh, stinky, sweaty, muddy. But here's the thing. You can't take a pig to a debutante ball,
I always say, because, hey, you want to go debutante ball? Yeah, sure. Okay, well,
you take him out of the mud, you wash him up, put him in a freshly tailored tuxedo.
And on the way to the ball, the first mud pit he sees, he jumps in. Now you've got to take him back,
send the tuxedo back to the cleaners, wash him up again, try it again. Is that how you want to live?
That's one thing. And the other thing, the pig class, they're the ones that want to put violence
on you when you give information. And it could be in the form of a troll also. You've heard of
internet trolls. Some people are trying to put out information and they get almost stalked publicly
by other figures within the same field or people in the audience. I think it's become quite
prevalent these days. It sure has. Yeah. And that's the pig class. They want to put violence
on you. And they really don't care. The only time they react is if someone's coming to take
bacon off their back. And that's the only time they're going to listen to you. If someone's
going to take bacon off their back, that's it. Then they stop it. Otherwise, they have free reign.
I think it was an animal farm, too, that pigs kind of took over, wasn't it? The book and the
thing where the... Anyway. Yeah, no, that's definitely part of it. And it is true that
they react exactly like pigs when it comes down to people trying to troll you and stuff. I mean,
I've literally had death threats over stuff that I've said on my shows. And that is...
Granted, it's keyboard commando and he's probably never going to do it and whatever.
I respond to these guys by giving them my address usually. Yeah. Hello. Ding dong. Yeah.
And I'm still breathing. I'm still breathing. But either way, it's a surreptitious way
of attempting to imply violence based on the fact that there's disagreement,
which is a very pig-like characteristic, right? Right. So the reason I brought that up is because
we asked the question, what do all eight... What do... By the way, of anyone in the audience,
what do all things in the universe have in common? And there's roughly eight things or four pairs.
If anyone, all you people out there is, oh, yeah, I'm pretty studied. Go call in and let's
discuss it. All things in the universe have these things in common. We might as well just give it
out. We will before the time is over. But here's the thing. You see, when you look at someone and
we just mentioned, like the troll, let's say, would be, let's say, the pig metaphor. They're
not really pigs. It's just a metaphor of a characteristic. Why did I bring this up? Because
how many times have you heard people called sheeple? They're not. Because if they were
sheeple, they wouldn't fall for the official stories. They wouldn't fall for the crappy
education. They wouldn't fall for this and that and the dollar is going to collapse and this and
that. And you see, they wouldn't fall for it. It would make them sick. My default response
always is you're being unfair to the sheep. That's right. Their sheep are very few. The
goats are many. There are quite a few dogs. And the pigs are the ones that are controlling with
violence and or inflict violence. So so this isn't this is a form, another form of objectivity by
metaphor. But it has to be accurate. You have to give the point. You can't just say this is what I
think and then have it catch on. That's why I think certain subjects people are not read there
that will be discussed in the future. People are just not ready right now. Because you can just
say we can we can do a project where we say the next three shows we'll discuss this subject in
great depth. But now is not the right time. And why do all that work? Why not just show up here
every week and maybe shoot the shit for a little while and see what happens, you know, right now,
because we do these are sonic events are limited to an extent. But if you're if you're going to be
objective, you're not going to make friends, be confident in yourself, you're going to have to
you don't have to be like a little child when you tell them to do something and say why and then
because this is why and then why and they just keep going, why, why, why, why? Just look for the
object. What is it? You know, I mean, how many times has anyone gone to the bank and ask the
teller if they have federal reserve notes do that. And they don't know what you're talking about.
They say let me go get the manager and the manager comes back like with her hand or his hand over
their forehead and choose the teller away says go take a break and say can I help you know because
the teller has been counting these for 20 years and they don't even know what it is. These are
snakes that haven't bitten them yet, right? So I mean, this is you know, amazing. To the level of
lack of discernment and you were like you were mentioning commentary, you've probably gotten
commentary regarding what we discussed and it's very different. Can you say that they are
objective? Can you say they are giving a report? I'm going to presume they're not right or maybe
they are. I don't know. You didn't mention that part of it. I think they're giving they're giving
a report. But what is the basis for that report is the question because here we go like like I said,
when you have people that take different things from the very same look at the presentation once
it's memorialized, if we call it chapter, whatever. It doesn't really matter if more than
one person listens to it. They listen to the same thing, right? Why do you get 10 opinions on it?
Right? Yeah. Well, because it's planet Earth and because they don't like it. You know, I don't like
it. It's enough. I don't like it. I don't like it. So anyway, that's why I've had discussions
actually broken discussions with these are people, you know, with medical degrees and, you know,
they're pretty people. A lot of people look up to them and do what they say their word is, you know,
whatever. And I have to break the conversation. I'm like, what's your favorite color? Do you like
ice cream? You know, like really like eight year stuff you would ask an eight year old and they
fall for it. And they're like, oh, well, what does that have to do what we're talking about? I said,
everything, because everything you're telling me is not is based on what you're what you personally
like, not what applies to anyone else or should. You know, there was an old story about how a
particular socialist or communist revolution was started underground, they would have these
meetings. And they were promising that if they all band together and help this other group to
overthrow the current monarchy or whatever, everyone will be eating steak for dinner every
night and having strawberries for dessert. You know, I have a lot of freedom and liberty. I mean,
at times you heard liberty, right? So that sounded really great. Well, let's do the revolution. One
guy in the back raises his hand is but I you know, I don't like strawberries. He says, shut up,
you're going to do what we tell you. Wow, you know, so right away, they show exactly what's going you
see. Right? So this is this is basically the situation. So anyway, no one no one reacting
and chat, I guess I haven't looked but what eight things or four pairs does everything in the
universe have in common? How do you start your objectivity? And, you know, actually, it was some
of these things that I haven't gotten any response lately, but years ago in person when I would make
up bring up certain things, let's say when old Freemason like an old Scottish right guy, or, you
know, I was back east or whatever, run into some other people, they're like, you shouldn't be
talking about that in public. That's like some secret stuff. I'm like, great. That means that's
all I'm going to be doing, right? But, but these very basic little things. So what do what do?
What does everything in the universe have in common? Anybody want to give it a shot? Let's
let's just maybe we've got about maybe let's just let's get it now. Let's get it out. Because we've
asked long enough. And what do all things have in common that you will encounter? This is your start
of objectivity. Everything has a front and a back. Everything has a top and a bottom. Everything has
a left and a right. And everything has an inside and everything has an outside. Now, that is
considered, by the way, secret stuff for certain communities. Now, how simple was that? Think about
it. Everything has a front and a back, right? Look at a star, look at a planet, look at anything in
the room, look at another person, even a thought. When you think of something that whatever you're
thinking of has a front and a back. How many times have you heard of left wing, right wing or front
front or back or top or bottom or inside information outside of it? Right? Doesn't it isn't it
interesting? So the rules for objectifying and these are not rules. These are like tips or a toolbox.
Everything has a front and a back, right? A left and a right, a top and a bottom, and an inside and
an outside. And that pretty much will apply to anything you will ever encounter. And that is the
start of objectivity. Seems pretty obvious though. I know it's obvious now that we've now that we've
said it because this is the rules of objectivity. When you're having a discussion from trying to
build versus destroy on objectivity, you make sure all those bases are covered. It's a checklist.
What's the front of it? What's the back of it? How many times have you said, well, what's the benefit?
What's the drawback? Right? How many times have you heard that? You know, what if I, what are the side?
This sounds good, but what, you know, what, what can go wrong? You know, what is the left and the right?
You know, left and right is important. It's direction, right? Even political parties use it
all along. It's navigation. It's all, it's all sorts of things. Even the body, right? If you
look at the, anything that doesn't have perfect symmetry has a clear difference between the left
and the right. And when we say perfect symmetry, how close do you want to look? What tolerance?
You'll see it changes again. And everything has a top and a bottom and an inside and an outside.
However, where is the left and the right on a sphere? Exactly. It's from the anthropomorphic
perspective in a thought perspective. If you can imagine a sphere in your mind right now,
do you see that it has a left and a right? Whether it's static spinning under, I didn't say that it
doesn't change when you rotate it. The things that appear that they do not change, change when you
apply those things. Right? So let's say you bring up a concept. What's the front? What's the back?
What's the left? What's the right? What's the top? What's the bottom? What's the inside? What's the
outside? Every concept, every object has that. I get that, but here's what's amazing to me is that
it's quite a bit dependent upon perspective, because here we go. I view a sphere, we place
the sphere in a room and you're in one part of the room, I'm in another. Well, now the left and the
right may not be exactly the same point. If I told you to put a mark on the left, it may actually be
on the right for me. But that's true, but that doesn't matter because when you learn to be
objective, you won't have anybody around you. You won't have friends to do that with. Anyway,
that's a joke. So that's a moot point. I'm just saying that there is a constant. That was good.
But there are constants that I think are relevant regardless of your perspective.
Okay. But if you objectify it, it's no longer your perspective, it's what you can report on
from your perspective. It's not the be-all end-all, it's just what you can report on.
Just like on a ship, on an airplane in the military, I'll bring those guys up again,
you've got various observers on different parts of the ship, right?
Well, right. Very much like looking at the outside of a house, it may appear one way.
The inside is not necessarily representative of it, but you make certain assumptions or conclusions
based on the outside of that house. I've seen some very rundown places. You go inside and,
gee, the place is really gorgeous inside, really nice, comfortable,
everything well-organized, but the outside of it's a complete disaster.
That's the way to do it because most people that have beautifully manicured outside tend
to be broken in more. If you've got a lot of stuff going on inside that's beautiful,
make sure you've got a messy front yard so that you walk right by it.
But here, you just answered the question. You have to go. To objectify, you look at the front,
you look at the back, you look at the left, the right, the up and the down,
and you look in the inside and look on the outside. You have to actually do it.
Knowing that everything has a front and a back, a left, a right, top, bottom,
inside and outside is not enough. You have to actually do it.
Just like some of the negative commentary that I got about eating seasonally across latitude was
it doesn't work, and I asked what part doesn't work, and they said they didn't do any of it.
They didn't like the way it sounded. Well, great, but everyone who's actually practiced
it found that it worked. What does that do? That goes back to the typical thought process.
You just reminded me of an interesting thing that somebody slid to me on chat,
well, actually, in Skype earlier in the week regarding this eating seasonally.
What about cheese, which is then aged? Now, if it originates in a particular season,
then it's changed for six months. It changes. Now, is that eating out of season? Now,
if you're eating something that's been aged or otherwise preserved, or is it in season because
it exists in that area geographically or not? Yes. Cheese and a lot of things like that that
are subject to what is the basic alchemic. I think we mentioned the metaphor when you go
and you order a hamburger with pickle or no pickle, you don't say cucumber or no cucumber.
That's what it is. It's basically a preserved cucumber that's been brined,
but you don't think of it as such because if you have a fresh, solid cucumber and one that
you would put on a sandwich called a pickle, they're so different, might as well be talking
about completely different objects. If you're talking about a milk product or milk and cheese
or yogurt or whatever, they're so different from milk. It's a basic alchemy. It's changed so much.
Like cake batter after it's been baked becomes a cake, right? Changed so much,
delicious in both conditions. There, you would look at when these things that change radically
are not main staples. How many times does someone say, I'm going to sit down to a big plate of
cheese? Never. It's always a side in moderation. How many times does someone say, hey, I'm going
to sit down to a big plate of pickles? It doesn't really happen. A lot of the things that are
pickled and preserved and changed like that are usually on the side and you're not going to do
much quantity. One thing we could do is how things work. I've been having some really wonderful
discussions recently regarding practitioners and things in alternative or Asian medicine.
We're talking about the aspects of the human body and there are really two aspects. You have the
nutritive and the protective side. The nutritive is how you get nutrition and you have the
protective side that protects that nutrition when you get it. If it protects it too much,
you get constipation. If it doesn't protect it enough, you have diarrhea, would be a simple
analogy. It's called the yin and the yang aspect in the Asian, but you can describe it in other
ways and how to basically start getting on the path of mastership of your own body.
Guess what? It's the only one you got for now. Let's go a little deeper really quickly into
the cheese. A dairy product typically is liquid and when you cheese it, it also has salt. Salt
would not be as sweet. Salt is more prevalently harvested in colder climates, isn't it,
than hot climates. The best salts in the world are taken off the rocks in Ireland and Scotland
and places like that. Pepper too, just to give its component.
That would be spicy. Basically, I've seen people, oh, it's cold outside. I'm going to make it hot
and spicy, so it warms me up. No, that will cool you down. You get that initial hot pepper feeling,
but it opens your pores, your sweat and all that, and it thins out your blood chemistry and you're
going to get worse. You're going to get colder now. Spicy foods you'll find on the menus of
places like Thailand and Southern China and the U.S., like spicy wings, spicy barbecues and
usually where it's temperate and warm or warm spicy foods. As you go to the northern latitudes,
you notice the food is more salt brined and blander. They don't have those exotic spices.
They've incorporated them quite a bit like places in the Austrian-Hungarian Empire,
the Magyar, they use the paprika. Everything's paprika, which is the red pepper powder.
That is a little bit off of their season, but they've mastered it because now they're not
eating red pepper nightshades, which is more of a summer food, but it's paprika. It's roasted and
dried and it's changed. It's a powder now. They also have various varieties. That seems to balance
out with the fat. There's a form of alchemy when it comes to preserving food. Wine is another form
of alchemy. You've got grapes, grape juice, and then there's wine, and then the next level would
be distillation. They're not the same. Look at a grape and look at a bottle of whiskey or look at
cognac or look at a bottle of wine or even grape juice. They really don't resemble each other.
There's extreme changes going on. The way these things have been technically mastered, let's say,
or they're trying to get to the state of the art, is because someone had to be objective,
get a methodology and things to be identified objectively so other people can technically
access it. Chuck, if you wanted to open a winery right now, you don't have to do anything. You could
probably technically access almost every detail of it before you even do it by researching it.
Right. You will learn a lot more when you do it, but you can pretty much get started without
ever doing it. You will learn a lot, obviously, but you're better off doing an apprenticeship
and having hands-on, but you can get enough information without doing it to know if it's
something you want to dedicate your life or time to, right? Although I would certainly advise going
and participating in some way at an existing facility that does the same thing so that you
get a feel for it, so to speak. What happens is the current state of affairs, let's say affairs
plural, with humanity right now. Take, for example, 9-11, which I do not like to discuss,
but it's a good metaphor. When those buildings came down and they were shown as they came down
on TV, I would say billions saw that or are familiar with the image. Billions, not just
millions, right? I was in the woods when I found out a few days later and I saw it on the gasoline
station. Everyone was mad because I thought it was happening live. They were yelling at me,
it happened two days ago. I was out in the woods camping. I didn't know. Anyway, I noticed that
right there, the country was in trouble because it was all emotional, right? People getting mad
at you for not knowing what's going on two days, that means there's no rationale anymore. The
people are not familiar with how certain apparatus work, you hear a lot about, oh, it's thermite,
all these bombs they strung in there, oh, space weapons. It's a very simple apparatus. It's just
one, not many, that did that initial reaction. Because people are not familiar with the
properties of certain things, you can show everyone and they won't get it and they're
going to fall for the emotional stuff. But when you start looking into what can do that,
you cannot cross-reference that. If you put in building turned to dust falling at free-fall
speed, you will not be able to find it that way. It's going to get a little more complicated,
but if you start understanding that it has a front, a back, a left, a right, top, a bottom,
and an inside and an out, you will see that what is being put out there about how those
buildings came down is not true. Now, a little bit of what really happened is being put out.
There is actually a fellow that has done a very good treatise on it, but he's not popular.
Enough people know about him. His testimony is very good. He's a Russian fellow. He didn't come
out of the woodwork with this for 9-11. He gave testimony from 30 years ago that it was known,
or 20-some-odd years ago, very well. But this doesn't matter. The truth of any matter does not
matter. If you had a black-and-white, a glossy picture of someone with a rifle in the right
spot shooting at Kennedy and it was unequivocally true, a few people would, some would. At this
point, the whole thing about the vaccine issue, all these things, humanity is in really, really
bad shape. Why? Because you're in the credits. Whenever I speak publicly, the amount of time
that you have left, folks, things are not going to get worse. They're going to get better. Why?
Why are they going to get better? Because the entire human society is going to have to be
propped up to a high point. Why? Should I say? Well, I know what you're going to say. Go right
ahead. Okay. This is a little twist on it. Well, when man does battle with man, he usually hits
the other guy when he's down, because it's easy to hit him when he's down, right? Man doesn't go
like a weak country doesn't go to war with a strong country typically. There's a parity there.
They want to make the scales unbalanced. It's really easy to beat someone up for sure. You know
you're going to get the job done when they're already down. That's when man does war and battle
or takeover. But when the gods do it, they have to build you up before they take you out.
The gods don't come in when you're complicated, stupid, confused, political, religious or
whatever your society you see on the planet right now across the board. They don't come in. They
have to build you up to the highest point and then they come in and take everything that you hold
sacred and mop it up and put it in the rinse bucket and show you how it's crap. This is what
you're building up because the reason why the gods come in after you've been built up to the max is
because if they didn't do that, some little human later is going to say, but we never had the
chance. You came in and stopped us. You never had the chance. But when you get to the high point
and they take you down, then now you can't come back and say we never had the opportunity to get
it together, right? So this is what you're going to see coming and it's all going to be centered
out of the Middle East folks, not one country in the Middle East. So wait. Let me just throw this
because this is part of the narrative that I give and what you're going to see in the next
year or so is a warming up and a neutralizing of hostilities between what they call Persia or Iran
and Israel and the US and that's started already and it's going to flip. They're going to be allies
not adversaries. So watch that. Why? Because Persia and Iran is going to bring a tremendous
amount of financial resources to the things that are going to be done. So, and I have gone on
record saying this years before, even a few years ago on roundtables. There was an election. Do
you remember when Ahmadinejad was president of Iran? And there was an election. Yeah. And I said,
well, the next president is Iran's going to go into unity. People don't know that Iran has two
governments. They have a secular government, which is a president and a parliament or something like
that. Then they have the religious government with a supreme leader, the Ayatollah. And he
takes precedence over the morality of the country. And they're basically divided. Just like if you
read in ancient history, there were the Medes and the Persians. They're considered one,
but they had different aspects. So if you heard of Zoro-ism, Zoroastrianism,
that came out of there. Have you ever heard of like Batman and Robin, Superman, Mighty Mouse,
all these superhero concept? That's Zoroaster. That's a religion that came out of Iran. You know,
that mankind will be saved by a superhuman type individual that will come out of his society,
you know, whatever. So but years ago, I said when during the election,
Ahmadinejad said, Iran's going to be more unified. So you're not going to see a secular looking
president. He's going to be wearing more of a religious garb. You're not going to have,
you know, because Ahmadinejad looked very secular. He wore like a Brooks Brothers suit and a tie,
right? You know, always in a nice suit. Yeah, he had a bad haircut. But anyway,
true. Yeah. So but so now after that, a few months later, someone started messaging me,
remember what you said about this? Not really. Give me the specifics about being more,
more unified. And here's the new president elect. And guess what he's wearing? He dons the
traditional cultural Islamic headdress and beard. You know, that's their sect, for example. Is it?
How did you know? I'm like, well, you know, that's a I always say how I know, you know,
you got to get information that maybe if you look, if you want a new idea, read an old book,
how's that? It's the simplest way to say it. So but you got to do it correctly. And you got to
do it objectively. But anyway, I just threw that little thing in there, because there's a lot of
activity going on with that that is not being shown to this part of the world. I guess you
said there was some kind of a conference or a congressional thing about some Russian hack or
something. I mean, that do you know that the real wherever there's noise is a distraction,
the real stuff is happening where it's quiet. Always. So always, you know, yeah, yeah, they
always make a distraction. They get everybody looking there. I mean, look at it might be real
noisy on a construction site, you know, when they're cutting all the wood and the timber,
right. But you know, where the real action happens in the forest where the tree grows,
and you go is not noisy in the forest, it's quiet. And that's where all the strength and that's where
the wood is formed from the seed to the sapling to the small tree to the big tree. And that's where
all your power is, because it won't be all that noise on a construction site. If there ain't no
forests growing, you know, so and by the way, folks, if you want to know where you are on the
human timeline, you're building houses out of compressed sawdust. Give me a break. Anyways,
you're driving down a road, you ever see the new houses going up with compressed sawdust.
So there you go, folks, again. So thanks again, Chuck and everybody. See you again soon.
Absolutely. We are done with this one. And it is something to consider the quality of things
has certainly gone down. And they are not built to last any longer.
And let's not forget the show is about being objective. So
and let's try to remain objective as we observe from our perspective. Anyway,
Ocelli in the Greek is done. And we will see you the next time your calendar says it's Thor's Day.