So according to the Pope's work schedule, it is the second day of the second month.
But hey, according to observational,
observational, oh, I don't know, input, let's call it that. Greek, what day is it?
Well, it's seven days since the last time.
Of course it is.
So I would, whatever it was last time we came on and did it, but just for the sake of,
so I don't have to join Assholes Anonymous and stand up and tell everyone what an
asshole I am every time I go to the meeting.
But anyway, let's just say it's around the 23rd of the 12th month.
And I've been getting some emails, believe it or not,
people that are really trying to do it observationally.
And the comments are really interesting.
Especially these are people that are just getting into it.
And you have to run it for about a year.
And just, you know who you are out there.
They gave me a really good email about how they're really looking at the moon
being close to the ecliptic.
And yes, it is.
It's really close.
But you might have heard throughout history, there were days that the earth stood still.
They've even done science fiction titles for movies called The Day the Earth Stood Still,
meaning something very unusual, right?
But what happens when you get into lunacy, right?
Which is the moon.
By the way, people were called lunatics when they wanted to stick with a
system of observation that governed time, right?
So anyway, just like patriots are considered good, but now patriots are considered bad.
But either way.
That in addition to the fact that, well, you know, I want to let you know that in my Skype,
I've got a couple of people that are telling me it looks like it's the 23rd day of the 12th month.
Yes, that's right.
Is that what we said?
23rd day of the 12th month.
What did we say?
Well, you were saying you didn't want to really discuss it.
And then you kind of veered away from it.
No, no, we got back on it.
It's around the 23rd of the 12th.
Yeah.
OK, no, I just wanted to make sure.
Until noon.
That's the other thing.
We never really discussed that much because, you know, whenever you have a count, right?
You know, one through whatever number.
When does one number end and the next number begin?
You know, if you're counting eggs in a basket, well, you see the the ovoid shape and you move
it to the side and go to the next one, right?
So, you know, everything that is counted has a determinable value or starting and ending point.
And we never really discussed how the day starts and ends at noon.
And this is also, you know, the day starts and ends at noon is also
what is called astronomical solar noon, which is the way the days are kept by astronomers,
scientists and other fields for posterity.
Now, what's interesting there to me is that there is an appreciable way to to look at it.
You talk about the eggs.
We'll look if an egg is there, an egg is there.
If an egg is not there, it's not there.
But there are increments to getting to the fullness of the next number.
If you put half an egg into that crate you were just talking about, you don't have two eggs.
You don't have one egg.
You're on your way, though, to a second egg, although it would be difficult to reassemble it.
Right.
You know, so there is that space in between there, which I guess represents the passage of time.
And right.
And that's and let me just throw that in there.
Just let me just throw a little secret out for those that are ready for it.
When the Earth stood still, it was that in-between time that that lasted so long
and it took on another time reference.
All right.
We'll discuss that and actually in about a year or two, if anyone wants to remind me,
we'll get into that kind of stuff.
The reason why is because I'll just make a comment here and we just people should call in,
by the way.
But I just want to say the reason why I don't discuss these things, because the level of
stupidity with humankind right now is so high that, you know, even makes me wonder,
why bother?
Why get together and do the show?
You know, it's just one side.
It's like, oh, it's a complete just waste of two hours.
Right.
But on the other hand, why not?
You never know.
Let's see.
And that's what makes me cringe a bit, because I got to be honest with you.
It sort of feels a bit demoralizing when it's hey, why?
Why do it?
Why not do it?
It doesn't really it just sounds to me like nothing actually matters.
Now it doesn't.
Right.
You know, but but I don't know.
I just I can't wrap my mind around.
Nothing matters.
Well, that's true.
It's like, let's say there let's say you show up with a bucket of water.
Let's just try the analogy, but just use the analogy.
In other words, this is not the analogy, but you show up with a bucket of water and you're
standing in front of a house and you're like, what are you doing?
Well, this house is going to go on fire tomorrow and I'm getting ready.
It sounds kind of kind of crappy, you know, so at the same time.
No, because you should have something around to suppress fire.
If you think there's the possibility of fire tomorrow, don't you think?
Right, right.
But, you know, just imagine that someone's standing in front of a house with a bucket
of water, everyone else is doing whatever they're doing, right?
Yeah.
Well, you would think that they were nuts.
Yeah, exactly.
Thank you.
I was waiting for you to say that.
Yeah, because I wasn't going to say this just sounds like insane to say the things that
we do, because if you've been listening to what's on alternative, all alternative, including
this station and all, because when I say all, I mean all.
It is just patently absurd.
But if this station or any station, mainstream or alternative, didn't say things that were
patently baseless and absurd, no one would listen because you have to accommodate the
audience.
Well, that is one way to look at it.
And if you want to actually join into the discussion without saying things that are
patently absurd, we do have a couple of ways for you to do that.
We did have someone who just tried to call on Skype, by the way, which was at Ocelli and
the Greek at Skype.
And you spell it just like it sounds O-C-H-E-L-L-I and the Greek.
And we do spell Ocelli for you because sometimes, you know, a C in the beginning of a word
makes a CH sound, but it's in Italian, right?
I don't know.
Palate Italiano, right?
Yeah, right.
Little different.
Yeah, so anyway, but it's not the C is not in the beginning of the word.
So it's a CH.
So we did have someone just calling right now with the code name of UU8 and I told them
that I will drag you in.
But for other landline type conventions, which are not, well, just standard mob bell, throw
over, monopoly busting, whatever, what would you call the current telephone system?
It's just a convention still uses an area code and a seven digit number, right?
You can try it that way.
Domestically, right.
You got 218-339-8525.
That is 218-339-8525.
Now, one other thing that needs to be mentioned because the recording no longer tells you,
you have to enter 2012 as a code to get into the conversation.
So 2012 is the code.
And again, the number is 218-339-8525.
And there are two guidelines.
And yes, I know it's repetitious, but worthy of mentioning if we want them followed each
time, I think.
Go ahead.
How about we maybe not mention them this time and see what happens?
Okay.
You know what?
I am all for experimentation.
You know, why not try it a different way?
In fact, I might take things into a different direction tonight.
A lot of times I sit back and just listen to what it is you have to say.
But I might decide to participate a little more if these people don't and see where that
goes.
How about that?
Oh, sure, sure.
But you know, Chuck, there's a lot of stuff to talk about in terms of current events.
Now, I try, I cringe when I look at the news because it's not news.
It's just really dumb stuff.
It's like being around very young children and they always want toys or candy or stuff
that you think children want.
But that stuff isn't really good for them, right?
And some of their actions can be cringeworthy.
I mean, when you watch a toddler, as I did earlier today, by the way, watch a toddler
run full speed into a wall for some reason.
Whatever that reason is, you kind of cringe for a moment thinking they might have injured
themselves if you care about them.
Yeah, you cringe for a moment and then usually they get up and dust off and keep moving.
So I want to bring it.
This is the thing I want to bring in because there's a lot going on and it's sort of
political, but it's not because it's what's in the news.
It's a very simple thing.
There's something about immigration that's in the news right now and immigration at large,
you know, illegal, you know, which I thought illegal just meant a sick bird, right?
An eagle being sick.
Yeah, so because legal is not lawful.
You know, it would be here all week, folks.
You can tip your waitress.
Go ahead.
Right.
And what you've got, right?
Okay.
And what you've got in terms of Islam or being Muslim is not what people think.
It's just as unlawful and baseless as Christianity, Hinduism and Buddhism.
All of the mainstream religions, as we said, we don't have to beat this over the head.
Just if anyone wants to do a very short-lived experiment, just go out into the street.
Yes, I know if you want to stomach that and meet someone who professes to be of any of
the major religions and it's within 30 seconds.
You can prove without a shadow of a doubt.
They know absolutely nothing in any of the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
It doesn't matter if they are just doing it because they've inherited the religion, right?
You know, it's inherent, meaning the family that they grew up in was that or they are
a scholar in that particular religion.
They know absolutely nothing.
Now, they might say, Greek, you know, that sounds, you know, I went and talked to this
guy.
He knew a lot about it.
So let's see what he talked about.
I said, none of that's in the text that they subscribe to.
It just sounded like it was.
Wow.
Okay, more, they used it out of context.
Now, we just talked about how the monopoly was broken up and with the phone companies,
right?
You want to break up the religious monopoly because it is.
It's the religion of stupidity across the world and they already have their divisions
and then within those, you know, do you know how many sects of Christianity there are?
Around the turn of the century, there was about 8 or 9,000.
Now, there's over 21,000, some say 34,000 thousand.
I don't know how they manage that.
I don't even know how that's possible.
I mean, I'm not making this up.
This is a scary number where I'm asking, where can you get this stat from that actually
lists it?
Because to me, it seems, I don't know, unlikely.
It seems like five people get together, open a church, and it's a little different than
all the rest and it's a new denomination.
Yeah, you can just do the research because we could go, like, I think last week, someone
asked, you know, what about the Eastern religions?
I say they're just as bad.
But on the surface, they don't seem that way because they're an escape mechanism.
Just like, by the way, in the East, you have a lot of people like Korea is very big into
Christianity, parts of it, you know, Baptist and all that denomination.
So you also have Asians that are tired of the Asian convention, and they go over to
Western, right?
There's a lot of, quote unquote, Christian and Muslims in China and Korea.
So it goes both ways.
When you get tired of a convention, you switch to another one.
You think it's better, and it's not.
But there's many ways.
You can start your own religion very simply by getting a chocolate chip recipe.
And if one of the cookies happen to come out that looks like the iconography of a religious
figure, you tell everyone, you put pictures of it on the internet, and about a month or
so, you'll have a thousand people knocking on your door, giving you whatever you want,
just so you could tell them how that cookie crumbled, right?
Anyway, so this is the ridiculousness.
And I've had several people experiment with this, by the way.
They've gone to, well, from everyday pedestrian type people to the scholars with multiple degrees
and ones that actually held congregations or were part of clergy.
And on the surface, they always seem like they know what they're talking about, because
they're trying to string together.
And they always have the similar type of litany.
They all say the same things when you challenge them on the validity of what they're saying.
And I think we've mentioned that before, what it is.
And it's all just really, really bizarre.
But why did I spin off on that?
Because you have to throw in the footnote, right?
Now, there's something, going back to the news, there's something about Islam and Muslims
and immigration.
And the immigration thing has been going on, by the way, since the 90s.
It's not a new thing.
There have been many codes, hundreds, if not thousands of codes enacted since what's called
the Clinton administration to start enforcing limitations on immigration.
And also, what people don't know about immigration is that around the era of the turn of the
century, up until World War I, even what's called World War II, what was in the United
States was called quota systems, right?
There were people that were in refugee status from Europe and other parts of the world
that were, ships were turned back en masse because the quotas were met, right?
So this is not a new thing.
But if you have the attention span of a cat, which is about three minutes, you will think
that what you're being fed by the mainstream and alternative media regarding the subject
matter is valid, and it's not.
Why?
The final death knell to the quota system came during the Reagan administration when
he kind of lifted some of the limitations of the quota, some of the final semblance
of it that remained at that time.
But nobody pays attention to that either.
Well, you can't.
You can't because you have to understand the credit system.
Now, let me just explain this, and I don't want to get into talking about the money
system, because even prophetically it states that people will never understand how the
system works.
They would just stop using it at a certain time, right?
When it states that people will stop using the system, it doesn't say they'll stop
using it because they know what it's about.
It just, they just withdraw, right?
So because people don't understand the credit system, they fall for this immigration crap.
Now, before I tell you what's going on, which you could validate in Title 12 of the
U.S. Code or Title 8 of the U.S. Code or Title 50 of the U.S. Code is very simple, but I'm
going to just say it because no one else is.
It's absurd how no one else is, and this is what's going on.
When you have a credit-based economy as it is here, the people have everything.
You have all the financial power, and I mean it comes from your signature or the signature.
In other words, anyone with a birth certificate or a social security number could sign any
piece of paper, write a number to it, go into a financial institution and have that
monetized.
In other words, they can deposit that into an account which they can draw off of just
like a regular check.
Think about that.
It sounds like Alice in Wonderland, but that's really what's going on.
Now, what's really going on is all the entitled classes, government officials, judges, religious
officials, medical society, your professors, all these, they know that you have all the
money, and they have nothing.
All these institutions have nothing.
They have to get it from you without letting you know that you have it.
Think about it.
Chuck, you're walking around with a pallet of gold bars.
You're crying that you're poor, so that means that you obviously don't know that you have
a pallet of gold bars, but I need to get them from you without you realizing that you have
them.
That's what's going on.
Okay, so every time someone comes into the country, even from Mars, they eventually interact
with some form of government agency.
Could be the police.
Could be they go to an office, immigration office.
It could be the courts or whatever, and they see that you are, quote unquote, non-documented.
You have foreign papers.
Oh, now you have to register.
Here.
What's the first thing they give you?
A green card and a social security number or a driver's license.
All those things are the same, right?
Now, once a social security application is created, that's called an exemption, and a
credit line is issued to you.
It's unlimited.
It used to be $650,000.
That's why when you have, if you know anyone that does real estate, there's something
called capital gains tax.
You can make up to $650,000 before you have to, let's say, quote unquote, pay a capital
gains tax.
That's the exemption.
So they set the capital gains tax at that limit.
So what's going on?
Someone, let's say, jumps the fence or comes into the U.S. and they're an illegal immigrant.
The minute they get a social security card, that creates over $650,000 to $2.5 million
right there sitting on the paper.
In other words, you just take the paper to the Federal Reserve.
You can draw off of it.
Now, the person, no one knows this can be done.
That's why no one imposes this.
And the people that have discovered this, they're like bulls in a china shop.
They don't know how to deal with it, right?
So they get thrown in jail.
Everyone says you're ridiculous, you know?
All right.
Now, everything I'm telling you can be proven very simply if you do what's called a forensic
audit, right?
Okay.
I hope we're using language that is coming across to the people.
Now, so what's going on right now?
All the politicians, you notice that the immigration is a group of people in the legal
society and political society.
They're saying, oh no, we can't do the immigration ban, right?
We have to let them in, right?
It's un-American or whatever, right?
You notice the legal society is adamant because the lawyers are the ones that drafted all
these things that I just mentioned, how the credit system runs.
So what's going on is that the people in the government agencies are licking their
chops because they get a percentage, by the way, when this exemption is created.
What is an exemption?
It's when someone applies for a social security number.
They get a percentage.
You know, like birth certificates, the hospital gets up to $50,000 for each birth certificate.
You know, if you know anyone that works in the administrative part of the hospital, see
if they have an account with what are those armored car companies, Brinks and Fargo or
something?
Brinks and Wells Fargo, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
You'll notice anyone that's ever worked in the administrative hospital, they always
come and say, yeah, how did you know that?
I said, oh, yeah, because I'm a secret agent spy.
That's how I know, right?
No, I know how to read, dummy.
But anyway, once a day or once a week, you have these armored cars coming to hospitals
picking up the long-form birth certificates, the ones with the footprints on them.
That's how much they're – why?
Why do you need – let me ask you.
Why do you need armored cars to move this paperwork around with a baby's footprint
on?
Can you explain that to me?
I think we just did.
All right.
So –
They're worth 50 grand a piece.
I mean –
No, no, no, no, no.
No, they're not.
So you're not – listen.
They're over 650 to 2 million each.
The hospital can get up to 50 grand, typically 10 to 20, up to 50.
Well, yeah, but something is only worth what you can get for it.
So the idea is that if you can get 50 grand for it, it's worth 50 grand.
If you can get 10 grand for it, it's worth 10 grand, right?
Right.
It's what's negotiated, right?
Also, they do what's called a eugenics and like, for example, the white male is rated
the highest and a black female is rated the lowest and everybody in between has a rating,
just like you would for the blue book for cars, okay?
And this is a market.
Now, here's the whole thing.
How do these agencies get access to that credit line?
Not a line of credit, credit line without you knowing that you have it.
They are chomping at the bit.
Every time an undocumented person comes into this country, they are jumping up and down
like little nine-year-old girls ready to get some cherry licorice.
They're like, oh, yeah, more exemptions.
Let's get 5,000 today.
You know, there's billions coming in, but they can't tell you that's why they want them coming
because then you're going to say, well, wait a second, don't I have an exemption too?
Now, let me just say this.
This is in the sheer disgust of things.
When I try to explain the credit system to people, no matter who it is, only three individuals
in 10 years have not done this, but everyone else has done it.
As I'm explaining it, the person on the other side and the receiving end, before I even
finish explaining it, they're like, well, how can I get some of that too?
And I say that's why it is the way it is and that's why you'll never get any because it's
about me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
And the people putting this crappy news out about immigration policies and Muslims and
the like and the economy and the like, you've got – there's an idiot that I keep getting
links to.
Please don't send me links to this idiot anymore.
I'm not going to mention his name.
He's a financial commentator.
He's got subscribers.
He does very frequent YouTubes.
He's interviewed all over.
It's like this guy is a total moron.
All of these commentators are, just like I've said before, if there was anyone even remotely
close saying anything remotely true that was based on something, we wouldn't be doing
the show at all.
I'd say, Chuck, man, let's just do the website and I'll just throw links up there
every day on who you should go listen to.
There is no financial commentator giving anything viable.
They are telling you what you want to hear.
Stupid crap.
The dollar is going to collapse.
With this idiot, he's been saying for the past five years every month the dollar is
going to collapse and he has 2,000 subscribers, paid idiots.
Why?
Because if he told them the truth, he wouldn't have any subscribers.
The reason the circus comes into town is because they can separate you from the money you
have.
If the circus couldn't separate you from your money, they wouldn't be coming to town.
That's why it's a circus.
So what is going on with immigration and all this stuff?
It's completely asinine and it's all a distraction.
That's why, how many times have you heard the Greeks say, wherever it's noisy, nothing
is going on.
The real stuff is happening where it's quiet.
Right, which is my contention about this entire political puppet show that we're watching
right now.
That what really, truly worries me is not all of this nonsense and showboating and, gee,
the creator of Survivor speaks at the prayer breakfast for President Trump.
No, not really.
The thing is, what is actually happening quietly behind the scenes?
Simple.
Go ahead.
You can judge the quality of a man or a person in, like I said, many ways.
One way, the Indians say you can't judge anyone until you walk a mile in his moccasins
or whatever, but this is another way because no one's going to really fork over their
moccasins that easily, especially if the shoe doesn't fit.
But you can, number one, judge a book by its cover.
Forget about that cliche that you can't, because if someone drops something that's
three inches thick with yellow on the outside and lots of fine print on your feet, you know
it's a telephone book, idiot, right?
You can judge a book by its cover.
The second thing is that good drink and good food promote good character, right?
And the third thing is you look at the level of political interest that someone has.
And the more level of political interest this person has, the lower the quality of
the character.
The less political interest that person has, the higher the quality of the character.
Now, wait a minute.
What do you mean by political interest?
Oh, political interest is just that.
You're interested in what's going on in politics.
In other words, there was an old saying before, whether you are on the fence about voting,
if you want to determine whether voting should be done, just go have a five-minute
conversation with your average voter.
And that's sarcastic, meaning if you talk to someone who wants to vote for five minutes,
you'll be so disgusted you won't want to vote, right?
You see what I mean?
Now, what I mean about political, but the people want political interest.
So if you're in the public eye like what you do or newspapers or this station or other
stations, you have to talk about it.
Because if you're not, no one will listen.
That's what the people want.
Why did I say if you have political interest, the character is very low?
In other words, the conversation cannot be what we just mentioned.
The reason they want immigrants in is because up to two and a half million exemptions created
on the spot, but they don't want you knowing about that.
And they don't even want the immigrants knowing about that, right?
But they want it, right?
In other words, the government has nothing.
What they do is when they get the paperwork, they bring it to the Federal Reserve.
The Federal Reserve brokers it for them.
And it becomes excess credit, which makes the debt go up.
There's no debt, okay?
In other words, Chuck, we're kind of all over the place.
I'm going to go back to the political thing.
I'm just going to soften the idea.
Chuck, if someone lent you a Ferrari and just on loan, are you going to be looking real
happy and comfortable or are you going to be sweating bullets in case someone wants
to key that thing and now you're responsible for it, right?
Well, I don't want a loan of a Ferrari, no.
All right.
Can you imagine?
Right, because anything that happens to that car when it's in your possession.
See, let's say, let's use typical stupid terms.
If you owned it, it doesn't matter.
You could go out and set it on fire yourself.
Yeah, but what do I care if it's mine?
Yeah, if something happens to it, I'm responsible for it.
I deal with the fault, you know, and I'm not.
What did I lose?
I lost the thing.
Big deal.
You lose all things eventually.
Screw it.
But no, if it's on loan.
So let's say I hand you the keys.
I got a 355 Ferrari Rosetti package engine for Chuck.
Can you hold on to this for a week?
And everybody's looking at you saying, Chuck, why are you sweating bullets?
You know, I got the Greek Ferrari out here, man.
What if something happens?
You know, I got, you know, I'm responsible, right?
Somebody keys in a tree, falls on it.
Yeah, right.
Now, what am I going to tell him if he comes back to get it?
You know, I got, you know, who's going to hold me accountable for it?
And that's exactly what the, what they call the national debt is.
Did you ever see a politician sweating the national debt?
Never.
It's all you idiots that listen to alternative media and mainstream media that are sweating
it and all these financial idiots that are talking to you about this.
That debt represents excess credit from all these signatures that people are doing.
How many people in America sign papers every day?
Think about it.
Don't even, don't even think about the number.
It's huge.
And each signature could be anywhere from a thousand to a million.
So all of this excess credit that is processed through the Federal Reserve is sitting there
at the Treasury and it's not theirs.
That's why it's considered their debt.
The way you make the debt go down is you cut everybody who has a social security number
a check for a quarter of a million dollars.
And then next month you cut them a check for 400,000.
And then the month after you cut them a check for half a million.
Everybody who has a social security number in the country gets a check for a quarter
of a million this month, Chuck, 400,000 the next month.
That's how you bring it down.
Now, what do you think is going to happen if that happens?
So don't even answer that because it'll be 10,000 bucks for a gallon of milk in about
a week, right?
Well, yeah.
Hold on.
Don't laugh.
When did you hear about there was a time period in Europe of a certain country that you needed
a wheelbarrow of money to get a bottle of wine?
The Weimar Republic, yeah.
Thank you.
This is when the credit system gets turned around.
That's why you have to keep the scam going.
Okay, now let's go back to the level of character.
How many times you heard the Greeks say under certain covenants never talk about the leader
of a people living, dead or good or bad because the leader of the people are put there by
gods based on the people, the quality of the people.
The gods don't act in futility.
So speaking about the leader as being the problem is stupid.
It's dumb because it's irrelevant.
It shows poor lack of character of the individual, which is, by the way, this is not contemporary.
This has been going on for thousands of years.
By the way, the Romans used to deify the emperor publicly and officially.
For example, you could look up paperwork, especially Claudius Tiberius Caesar was quite
the historian, and he tries to give the Julian dates from when Augustus became a god.
It was a national day for Augustus.
Now it became a god on Earth.
Okay, so because they knew there was a connection there between the world of the gods and humanity.
Now also in Asia, the Romans, I mean, the Romans, the Asians typically would deify their
emperors and kings.
Okay, they were beyond royalty.
So I'm just showing this as an example on how the society of the gods interacts with
the society of mankind.
It's been acknowledged through history, but it's mistaking though.
The gods will always put a leader over you as they see fit.
So criticize that leader is like indirectly, whether you know it or not, whether you've
inquired about the gods or not is irrelevant.
Now you're commenting that the gods have made a bad decision for you.
Okay, that's why I'm stating this poor character.
Now, you know, people typically that are uneducated, I'm not talking about the education
system, are usually judged as being as poor character.
I mean, I remember growing up in the 60s and 70s and said, oh, I don't want to go to
college.
You know, I was like seven or eight or nine.
And the old man says, if you don't go to college, you're going to be a bum.
You got to go to college.
How many times have you heard that?
Right.
Growing up, let's say in a Western, you know, American society, you got to go to college.
Otherwise, you're going to be a bum.
Well, it doesn't say you're going to be ignorant.
Just as like a bum is a status almost, you know, poor character or whatever, you know.
So but there is in real education, the more education someone has or the more knowledge,
the better their character can be.
Not always.
So what happens is when people lose knowledge of how the gods function, when they interact
with men, what happens to their character?
They criticize politicians.
They criticize this.
They criticize all of these societies around them.
Now, now I'm not making excuses for them, because ultimately you say, well, they don't
know they're ignorant.
They've been pranked by their parents.
The institutions have lied to them, right?
How many times do you hear that?
We're not making.
Yes, all of that is true.
But I'm just stating a fact.
Typically, observe the people that get engrossed in political discussions and economic discussions.
And if you ever met them in real life and had a personal meeting with them, you would
judge them of being of mediocre, fair or poor character.
People of high character.
This sounds dogmatic, but initially, because no one is saying this, the people that don't
get involved in these things and see them as being something that they need to set apart
them, set themselves apart.
Just good times, bad times like this on good times, bad times, right?
OK, when you don't like the lead, when people don't like the leadership and bad things
happen, those are considered bad times for your society.
And it goes up and down, just like the economic charts, right?
You've got booms and busts right now.
You can have a leadership or political condition that the people don't like, but have a booming
period.
You know, there's peace, there's economic growth, right?
Things like that.
Or you can have a political situation where the people are in favor of the leadership,
but they're in a bust and there's war and there's violence, you know, civil unrest,
right?
See?
So one doesn't a good political leader that is like meaning is like doesn't mean you're
going to have peace and prosperity, you see?
So this is where this stuff is not discussed, I assure you, anywhere.
And it just I just look at the ABC.
What do they call them?
The letter blocks that they give to five year olds or three year olds or four year olds.
You know, they have letters on the wooden blocks and another probably plastic to learn
the alphabet.
The highest level commentary that I see on the Internet is still like four or five year
old.
You know, they still got the diaper rash, little red fryer trucks and little baby blocks
types.
And these and the people that are putting this stuff forward on on in commentary, in
blogs, in YouTubes, in alternative media, in mainstream media, the best of the best
of their stuff is still this level.
And it's not because I say so.
It's because that's what's going on.
Show me anyone who is telling you why there is a division in the political world and
throughout government agencies regarding immigration.
It would be insane to say in a realistic base, a world that is based on things to say that
we have an immigration problem and we're going to limit it.
It would be insane for there to be a division within the government regarding that or division
within society.
If it were real.
It would be insane to have division, but there's division because it's not real.
They want them to come in because each one is a few million on the front end.
Minimum, you know, minimum half a million.
But they can't tell you that.
Because then the first thing you're going to say is I want mine, too.
Well, precisely the opposite argument is made constantly that actually what happens
is money is given to them, which comes out of the coffers, which could be distributed
to the us.
Right.
I mean, this is generally a lie argument.
Well, I know it is, but I'm just saying this.
I said I'm not going to get into the validation because it's pedantic.
But one of the things that I said that anyone can validate it is if they look up what's
called forensic accounting or forensic audit.
Like things like the Patriot Act and Title 12 of the U.S.
Code state that if you're going to do a financial exchange with someone, you have the right
to ask where they got the money up to two places.
Because let's say, for example, you have a business in contraband and you lend someone
100 grand and they open a shop and then you get busted.
And on the books, they show that you were doing that, that you want this guy 100 grand.
This guy, you know, they come and take his store and they're like, well, why are you
taking confiscate?
Well, because the money you got the guy from, you know, was doing contraband.
So we have to take your stuff and you didn't even know.
Right.
So you have to know where the money came from.
So go ask a bank where credit card, anything.
Where did you get the money on?
They cannot show you anything because there's nothing there to give you.
Comes right out of the signature.
It's an outlet.
That's why I said I'm not going to give reference.
Just look up what forensic auditing and forensic accounting is.
Forensics just means evidence.
You know, like when you learn about it on TV, when the cops show up and they can't find
anything, the forensic team comes and say, go get the doughnuts.
We'll find what happened here.
They look a little deeper.
But the thing is, people aren't even looking at all.
That's why I said the level of stupidity is just outrageous.
I mean, it's just the but you look.
Why am I saying ultimately it's fine?
Because how many times has the Greek said that the not the Internet and all of your
media is nothing more than a microphone check?
When was the last time you've heard of a rock concert being put together?
All the stage effects and everything.
And the guy gets on stage and he says, testing one, two, three.
And everybody gets mad because they didn't like what he said.
So why are what you're why are why is it that what you are saying is anything beyond
that microphone check then?
Well, because if you have discernment, you would hear it.
And those there's an old statement that says this is for those who have eyes and ears.
In other words, this is this is stuff that is based on something versus baselessness.
And this next time you hear a moron saying the dollar is going to collapse like what
dollar prove prove to me that there is a dollar to collapse.
There isn't.
A dollar is a denomination that is being kept only for the forex.
If you know what that is.
Anyway, it does not exist.
What is what does exist is that there are certain American brokerage houses, financial
institutions that get first dibs on major transactions that happen to be based where?
In America, out of New York.
You can JP Morgan, Goldman Sachs, on and on and on.
They get first dibs on the big petroleum transactions and all that.
And the whole thing about what you hear, what they tell you about the dollar collapsing
because they're no longer going to be trading in the dollar.
Congressman McFadden made a big speech in 1934 about it's on the congressional record.
Go look it up.
Anyway, the whole thing is insane, Chuck.
That's what I'm saying.
Why bother?
You know, this is the ninth time we're coming around.
I don't know.
It's just like, holy crap.
But look, it's nothing to get upset about.
It's nothing to make excuses for.
It is what it is.
Like before we came on, I was speaking with the management at AFR and like how anything
new.
I said, well, I'm very excited.
I mean, nothing new.
There's nothing new going on, but I'm excited because I know there shouldn't be anything
happening and there is nothing happening.
So I'm excited because I know that.
Right kind of thing.
There's nothing happening.
It's the same old stupidity.
And all of the institutions, whether it's religious, legal, medical or whatever, is
relying on the people's ignorance.
And you know what?
People are very reliable.
Everywhere.
And you folks that you think you're awake and alternative and all that stuff, you ain't
got nothing being.
Look, if you turn over in bed at three in the morning and go take a whiz and go back
to bed, that's not awake.
You just got up in the middle of the night.
You're not awake, period.
Get away from that thought.
You're quite asleep.
Now, if you might be awake, but you're aware of nothing, like I say all the time, I mean,
that's you know, that to me, I guess, is a zombie, you know, and if that's what you're
satisfied with, OK, but if you go to bed stupid, if you go to bed stupid, you're going to
wake up stupid.
Generally, yeah, it's the same thing.
You know, things don't happen like that.
So and also be aware there's a lot of people that sound smart.
They know how to string words together and they always like to surround themselves with
people that don't.
And that's how they develop their groups.
So you ask them what it's based on.
Now, whenever you run into these people that have degrees or sound smart or say they know
about this or that, pick something that has a base on it.
Like if you start saying a dollar is going to collapse, everyone's fine.
But what is the basis of the dollar?
Well, the only way you could find it is by looking at who runs the dollar reference standards.
That would be Treasury, Bureau of Standards, Controller of Currency.
They have various codes and things that you could look up to substantiate that there is
no dollar.
So now you know what they're saying is baseless.
So when you interact with these people, just like a cheap sweater, how do you take a cheap
sweater apart?
You know, a sweater can cover an entire body.
It looks like it could have an elaborate pattern.
But if you know it's a cheap sweater, you just got to find one thread and just keep pulling
on that one thread.
What happens to it?
It's a whole sweater apart, doesn't it?
Eventually it unravels, yeah.
So when you run into these people that are making commentary and they sound so dynamic
and so intelligent, you find what they're saying, find what they're saying should be
based on and approach them and just keep pulling on that one point like a child.
Just keep on the whole shit unravels every time, every time.
But the thing is, they usually they call you a troll if you do that right now.
I think they do that and or they'll ignore you or whatever.
But this was easily done when people did public speaking engagements back in the day, right?
These idiots that are on the internet making comments and have subscriptions and all this
other stuff or shows or whatever, they do it all digitally now.
You can't throw a tomato at them.
You can't pull on the sweater, right?
They just call you a troll.
I'm being trolled on the emails.
I'm being trolled in the chat, right?
That's what they...
So they're cowards, they're weaklings and they're full of crap, all of them.
Now, why do I say all of them?
Because I haven't found any that are not.
Stick with... and the same with your religious people.
Anyone bringing up anything religious or Muslims or Buddhists or whatever, stick to find one
thing that it should be based on and just keep pulling on it and watch how they fall apart.
But unfortunately, you can't do it on the internet.
Troll, right?
So, but why would you do that?
Why... when the circus comes to town...
Be careful with your connection because you're cutting in and out a bit electronically.
It sounds like you're moving around a little.
Yes, I am.
Back East, we have what was called the feast, right?
Of St. Andrew, of this, whatever, you know, the pagan feast.
It's in a little Italy and places like that.
San Gennaro.
San Gennaro is a big one, right?
And why would you go mess up their parade?
Why?
These people having a great time eating all that pork and all that stuff.
Why would you mess up?
It's why would you go to the circus and talk about how the tent isn't worthy?
Well, their happiness.
People are happy.
I've watched some people in chats, they get all fired up about these stupid commentaries
about whatever, the dollar, about vaccines, about chemtrails, about you name it.
You know, this president, that president, immigration.
It's none of it is based on anything.
None of it's based on anything.
And now this is the president of the United States of America.
To have a president, you have to have a country, right?
Legally and lawfully, the country was dismantled.
It's in receivership.
But no one's noticed.
Think about that.
That is really intense stuff.
So I'm going to yield.
And we also, we kind of forgot about the Skype person who's probably standing by.
Chuck, go ahead and throw your stuff in.
I'm going to take a five second or 10 second break and make a cup of coffee because I
don't know how much more of this stuff that I could take.
I mean, and I'm not even looking at the news or listening to anybody.
And what I mean is, like, turn on the home page.
I got a couple of things bookmarked.
I spent all of 7.3 seconds on them.
Not seven seconds, not eight seconds, but 7.5 seconds.
And I click off because I have a browser that tells me how long I was on there.
I can't look at it.
Anyway, well, you know, it is interesting to me that that this is the time where I find
communication to be so challenged.
None of it seems to be making sense.
I don't know why it seems so incoherent to me.
Most people are getting along just fine with it, apparently.
I mean, I don't hear anybody else complaining about that, you know.
I don't think I'm complaining.
I'm just saying that the level of stupidity, I mean, it's kind of like, hey, you know,
the pot's going to overflow, you know, you know, makes a mess, right?
No, no, I know it's supposed to be this way.
But imagine the use of resources if it wasn't used this way.
But anyway.
Yeah, no, I understand.
But it's just that it's just a strange state of affairs.
I mean, I just I don't I'm at a point of not knowing how to articulate the disconnect I
see in what I understood to be the language versus the language being used.
I don't understand the disconnect in the hypocritical way with which people are behaving.
I don't understand all of this.
I have gotten to a point of not understanding, not wishing to comply, not wishing to be a
part of this anymore.
OK, well, you shouldn't be anyway.
You should set yourself apart and be in it, but not of it.
It's kind of like, Chuck, if you were getting paid ten thousand a day to clean out the worst
part of the sewer, you'd probably do it for ten grand a day.
You don't have to do it for very long to retire.
Right.
But do you go do you go in there naked, skinny dipping, drink the water or do you make sure
you got the best gear to protect you and breathing tanks?
Right.
No, I understand.
Yeah, of course.
I not only do I understand, I get it.
How about that?
I get that.
But I'm just saying that it's it's it's very odd because this is not a job that I can elect
to do or not to do.
I'm stuck here.
On this planet, I'm not going to be able to extract myself from it.
OK, yeah, it depends on how you're thinking.
If you think in terms of the way things are, the apparatus, I think we gave an analogy
about, you know, commuters that ride these trains and bridges for 15, 20 minutes a day,
they have no idea what the what it takes to build such an infrastructure.
Right.
They just use it.
It's the it's the same thing with our lifespan.
It's right now.
Would you say, well, I don't know, between 70 and 90 conservatively, there's people that
die in their 40s.
There's people that die, there are centurions over 100.
But you live basically 75, 90 years, let's just say 75, 80.
OK, that is so short of a period of time in relative to either the the manifested man
made structure that's put in place, you know, meaning all the societies that have came and
come and gone and ones that what's left of them.
Right.
And borrowed from right all the way to the big scheme of how the universe works.
The 70 or 80 year lifespan is a blink of an eye or not a blink of an eye, but four minutes
relative, right, to what a lifespan is.
So how can you take it all in and manage it and use it within that short lifespan?
So when you say you're stuck here, yeah, you're stuck.
I mean, you know what it's like?
It's like you take an elevator ride and you're in limbo.
You know, you got things to do, but you got to get out of the building.
You take in this elevator, whether it's up or down.
Right.
You can't do anything on the elevator, let's say, really.
It's what it is.
It's like you're in this interim state right now.
Mankind's life relative to the scheme of the infrastructure in place and comprehension
of the infrastructure and its use is tiny.
Your lifespan is too short to do anything about it.
So are you stuck here?
Yeah, but it's so short.
It's like being stuck at a red light for 10 minutes.
Look, one can step back and say, you know, in retrospect, fine, it's a short time span.
But we've also talked about how, you know, look, the future is is not yet here.
The past is already gone.
You only have the moment.
So what am I to do with the only thing I have?
Right.
I can't, you know, trying to wrap your mind around.
All right.
I'm in my mid 40s.
Perhaps it'll be another 20 years.
Perhaps it'll be another 20 minutes.
Doesn't matter.
Perhaps it'll be another 50 years.
I'll be around.
All of that is irrelevant because I have no say over that at the moment.
What I have say over is the moment.
So as of this moment, I am here.
Yeah, I mean, but, you know, there's that could be split again because you can't really
be in the moment.
You're you want to try to capture the moment.
You're ready.
Three, two, one.
Did you get it?
Or you see, before we were talking about the future.
Now we're talking about the past.
The moment can be broken up into so many small pieces that it's never not even there either.
So the whole thing is, are you setting yourself apart?
Are you grabbing the dynamics of it?
This is a dynamic universe based on information.
When you look at through the telescope or a microscope or everything that's going on
around you within the room, that is all information based.
It's not the molecular scientists will tell you this material is this material molecule
and atom in this thermodynamic thing.
No, no.
All that information is holding it all together.
It's it's mind boggling when you start to comprehend that.
Like I got a message, why don't you talk about how if the clouds don't have any water,
how does all those millions of tons of water get produced instantly and dumped on the ground?
Because, you know, clouds don't carry water.
It's not a sponge that's being wrung out, right?
And I said, this is this is all information based.
And it's information that does that.
And this is not not now.
We can actually demonstrate that.
And with certain we can create certain conditions that can lightly demonstrate how water can
be created out of nothing out of certain, let's say, tension type when you stress the
environment a certain way.
Right.
And let's not go down that path right now.
But but you can't do anything with it.
You know, at this point, you know, if you start making extraordinary machines, you will
get stopped, especially if people start if you start talking about it and other people
find out about it.
It doesn't mean that these things don't exist, but they're not known openly and not discussed
openly.
Like one of the most important things that is not discussed is, you know, submarine
propellers.
If you can make a submarine propeller that doesn't make any sound or cavitate the water,
that is one of the biggest secrets, right?
There's a lot of secrets like that.
That's why whenever you see a submarine at a military show, if you look at the ass end
of it, where is it?
They either don't have the propeller on or it's covered with 15 tarps with locks on it.
Not one tarp because it might tear.
Right.
So so there's many things that are going on.
But here's the thing.
What do you do is you set yourself apart.
Like I said, it's information.
Everything around us is information based, yet it's very dynamic.
It's not a static universe.
Your mind is not static.
Nothing is static.
Everything is in a state of change.
We discussed the four pairs, the eight aspects of everything, you know, the front, back,
left, right, top, bottom, inside and out.
You'll find that of interest when you examine things.
And when you go to these so-called scientists and doctors and people and even legal community,
they never use those rules.
What's the front of it?
What's the back?
What's the left?
What's right?
What's the top?
What's the bottom, inside and out?
You know, you do hear that.
I mean, I think one administration had a amputee, a one armed economic advisor, and they told
the president, this guy's only got one arm.
And he says, that's fine because he could never say on the other hand.
But anyway.
Again, you're here all week, but you can tip the waitress.
All right, go ahead.
Yeah, so why bother?
Because you notice how I'm sure you get caught up on it because you have to produce a show
every day.
You look at what's going on, and I'm sure that, you know, there's comments either by
you or around you, not putting you on the spot about what's going, the news du jour,
which is actually de facto, because you have no choice.
To discuss it, right?
Like if you didn't discuss what was in the news, people would say, why aren't you discussing
this?
Right.
That's exactly what happened when I was doing the show three days a week, because I would
go into historical discussions, not touching on current events at all.
I would go into educational discussions, you know, describing certain mechanisms by which
one could, oh, I don't know, take a look at legal forensic autopsies, things like this,
you know, how certain things are determined, criminal investigations, stuff like that.
And yeah, that's exactly the company.
You're not talking about what's happening, right?
You're not talking about the news.
Yeah, yeah.
But then if you talk about the news, they don't like what you're saying.
So what do you do?
What do you do?
I mean, this is, you know, but this is society in the early.
That's why I tell young children, you know, if you're going to give young children
instruction, it's if you're not completely disgusted with humanity, you're not paying
attention.
If you start paying attention with humanity, you know, here's the thing.
I'll even say this to you, Chuck.
For the past 10 years, when I meet people in conversation, we get on this topic, you
know what I tell them?
And I.
Well, you're kind of breaking up again.
So I didn't hear the whole question.
I shouldn't be.
For the past 10 years, I've been telling people when we get on this kind of discussion in
private or whatever, even in public, you know, speaking when I first meet them and
they're like, wow, you've got some interesting points of view.
And I'm like, well, you got to it just might seem that what I'm saying is intelligent
or interesting.
And they're like, why?
And I said, because everyone, you know, in the past, everything you know currently and
everyone you're going to meet is a moron.
And it's people never rebut it.
No one ever says, well, no, that's not true.
They sit there like nod their head.
Yeah.
And I think we gave the joke, you know, people, humans are considered morons.
And what do you call someone in the military?
A weaponized moron.
Anyway, nothing against the unless you have military coming from Venus or Mars, they're
human.
Now they got weapons.
That makes it even worse.
So this is this is the you know, this is the level of humanity.
Now, this might sound like a rant or a complaining or whatever.
But, you know, I think the people there, there's some people out there that can hear this and
actually use the information.
Why?
Because the whole purpose of information is to have efficiency.
Right.
You know, I mean, by efficiency, you know, you don't waste.
Well, that's the thing.
That's the definition of efficient.
And of course, we'll get into a lot more of this in the next hour of it looks like episode
nine of Ocelli and the Greeks.
Stay tuned to American Freedom Radio.
We'll be right back.
So the final hour of this particular moment that you can't quite capture is right here
on Ocelli and the Greek broadcast live on American Freedom Radio and American Freedom
Radio dot com.
Of course, I am one of the elements in the sonic entity, Chuck Ocelli.
That is my name.
I don't often say that during this show, but you can figure it out if you're paying attention.
So the Greek, you know, you said a lot of stuff during that first hour.
And man, oh, man, is anybody paying attention to it?
Does anybody actually understand it?
Is there a point to all this?
Yes.
You know, go ahead.
Yeah, there is.
Well, look, we okay.
You said about history in the moment or in the moment.
But this is something you could consider.
When man writes history, he records the past.
When the gods write history, they record the future.
So the future can be known, right?
The problem is that no one inquires and no one wants to inquire.
And it's not popular to inquire.
I think let's just bring up your personal case.
You've been touted as studying the JFK assassination for many, many years.
Have you ever been in a conversation with not only pedestrian people,
but people who also studied it?
When you brought up a certain topic regarding a piece of evidence or procedure,
all of a sudden, they didn't want to hear it, even though you had all the evidence to back it up.
Right.
You ever run into resistance?
Constantly.
Constantly, yeah.
Okay.
So what do you do?
Do you keep pushing it or do you start watching how reactionary they are?
And maybe it's best to throttle back a little and walk away.
Right.
Possibly.
Well, I change venues.
Okay, fine.
You know what?
I'm not going to try and force that.
Right.
Let's go for something that you might be able to wrap your mind around or accept.
How about this?
And then I start actually probing for what it is they actually have processed.
That's usually what happens because it's like, unless they've already processed it,
I can't make headway, let's say.
Right.
So let's say you're trying to be a world-class guitarist.
Instead of jamming with other world-class guitarists freely,
you're always forced to go back and do guitar lessons to nine-year-olds.
You know what?
For the most part, I've encountered a couple of people in my time that,
you know, like I do that show with Carmine, and he is really knowledgeable about a particular area,
especially in the case.
So sticking to documentation, which is readily available,
we have a very easy time because we both process it and scrutinize it in a similar fashion.
So we can have a conversation.
Well, that's fortunate.
But Chuck, look, what's in that documentation?
People don't know about it, you know.
So people don't know about what's in there.
So it really doesn't matter.
You know, everybody else thinks that, you know.
So that's what you should do, you know.
That's the mindset, right?
So for the most part, yeah.
Yeah, but see people don't...
It was around what they call Ashtar Easter.
I was on radio, not this one.
I'm not an expert in many things.
And I brought up the whole thing, how there is no crucifixion.
And I showed the evidence.
Hold on, because you just totally shattered into robotics there for a second.
So...
Oh, really, shouldn't.
Yeah, shouldn't.
everything is actually, I'm pretty good. Okay, I was having a public conversation
with someone around what they call Easter show. I pretty much proved, they gave me
five minutes, how there is no crucifixion as shown, right? And I showed
all the evidence. In other words, I wasn't there. The only thing we have is evidence of what's memorialized.
Then we can go from there, you know, once we build the time machine and all that. But this
person was also going from memorialized, and I should be, you're not reading it
correctly, you're not reading it, you know, in context. And the answer to this
person, from this person was, excuse me, when I showed that there is no
crucifixion, I said, but there were a lot of people crucified back then. That was
the answer. So, in other words, people phase out, they just phase out. Wait a second, because that's a
weird argument, because honestly, historically, there was a time when
people were crucified, you know, based on the evidence. That's true, but it
doesn't necessarily stand to reason that we're talking about the same time period.
Or the same individual, the account about this particular individual, right?
Right. So the whole thing is when people don't like what they're hearing, they
have to lump, what they do is they fall back on the crowd, what the crowd
believes, because ultimately, if you start professing what the crowd believes,
you have safety by numbers, right? So there's a safety by numbers. Now, what
happens, the mainstream media has a lot of numbers, which could be, I guess,
re-examined, because I hear, for example, some of the main, some of the main
acronym news agencies, their viewership has dropped very, very low,
like, you know, hundreds of thousands instead of millions. You know, the
mainstream is losing attendance, let's say, but still have the full force and
command of what is put out there. And then they flood a certain story for several
days or a week or two. And then everyone else on the fringe, let's say, or
alternative picks up on it and runs along with it, right? So there's this
momentum, the alternative media or people that are supposed to be, let's say,
more truthful, in air quotes, are still hinging on that crowd mentality wave.
You know, for example, the first hour, it dumped a lot of stuff. I didn't want to
give a lot of direct references, which anyone could look up very easily if you
look up the topic about how there's no money. It's a credit-based economy and
these exemptions are created. The money is created from the signature. So people
come to the country, don't have papers, they, how do you get papers? You fill out
a long form, right? Either electronically or manually. And that's where those long
forms are collected, brought to the Federal Reserve and brokered, right? Just
like you broker anything. And funds are created from that. There is no shoebox or
account with a certain amount of funds allotted for this purpose, meaning, you
know, immigration or benefits or housing or food or anything. It's created in situ,
in situ, Latin on the top. So we would say that all of these arguments, you know,
even when you go to the level of medical, you know, how many medical things have
hit the eye of the media, let's say, both alternative and mainstream with the, all
the screaming of all these or the pandemics that were supposed to come out
was like various bird flu, swine flu since the past four or five years. And
the vaccine allotments and all that thing to come with all of that, by the way, is
bogus, completely bogus. Not that there aren't people getting sick, like I
recently had a discussion with someone in the import export business dealing
with many sending eggs to Asia, because they just had a big chicken kill off
there because of a chicken disease, right? And that is for some reason, right?
Think about it. And when they were crying about a big bird flu, there was no
chicken die off. So and they're blaming it on viruses, which don't exist. No one
has ever seen one. Right? They anytime you see a virus, you know, it's a
computer generated thing, right? What it really is, it's broken up mitochondria
from the cells, it's waste product that the liver emits into the bloodstream
when it cannot be sent to be eliminated. So it's a form of toxicology, like
sepsis, right? Infection. It's not a something that could be contagion. And
they when you there's a lot of discussion about vaccines, you can't show me any
studies that were done scientific or otherwise that showed that there was a
control study of how vaccines were administered, and there was a benefit
from them or how they did anything.
Right. The efficacy of the efficacy of vaccines, there is no study that exists
that has shown long term, what happens? Well, they kind of they've done short
term studies. Let's be fair. They have 60 day studies on it.
But have you read the placebo clause in it, where they gave the ones with
placebo, and it was the same?
Yeah, of course. But I'm just saying, I'm not saying the study was good, or
that it showed up.
Yeah, but yeah, there is it just this is all bad science, bad information. By
the way, the science just means knowledge. To be nascent would be the
opposite of science. Science is etymologically, I guess means knowledge
or gathering of knowledge. This is bad knowledge. All of it. So yeah, so
because I know that's a hot topic for you as well. And it shouldn't be a
topic because it's based on pranking. If you know, if you get pranked, by
going to this institution, then one of the side effects like, you know, when
you order a burger through drive thru, they ask you, do you want to shake or
fries with it? Right? Always. Right. So when you go to certain institutions,
they have to prank you with the vaccine. Well, if you're here in this
institution, you have to get a vaccine. So people don't address the initial
prank, meaning schools or certain locations of whatever, that you have to
partake in that that's really the prank that they're addressing only the side
effect, which is the vaccine. But there is no viable discussion on any of this
or health. There's still something called blood pressure medication, right?
I mean, there's where's the pressure in the body? You know, I mean, this goes
on and on and on. You could look at anything that's being discussed, not
whether or not people are interested in it, or the topic is important. I'm not
saying that these are not important topics. They are pandemics, immigration,
credit system, dollar, on and on and on. These are very important topics. But
just like I keep speaking about people that are participant in the mainstream
religions, the same thing. They don't know or do anything that's in the text
that they allegedly subscribe to or anything memorialized or anything real
what it's based on. All these topics are important. But if you start looking at
what viruses are, what vaccines are, what the dollar is, what immigration is, what
the credit system is, you will notice that the discussions have no bearing on
what these things really are based on at all. There's no basis for it. So it's
all could you say a false flag, the media is a false flag. Just about everything in
the media is a false flag at this point.
Well, look, not only the media, but here's here's my argument with with part
of what you're saying here. And it's gonna sound odd, but at some point, it's
people placing their faith in something. Yes. But but everything is I mean, even
look, even what you talk about everything you say, in fact, what you're
basing it on, at some level, there is faith that is in injected into the
situation, you have to trust that, that this is, in fact, the memorialized text,
you have to trust that somebody did preserve it. I mean, you were not born
because you say all things are subject to external input, right? So we're always
I mean, it was put a slightly different way, I think, but either way, you weren't
born with the knowledge, right, according to to what what we've understood here
during these talks. So you're trusting something that has been left there, based
on a set of standards one way or another. Now, I'm not talking about the quality
of those standards. I'm simply saying that in general, at some point, there is a
level of faith, which is injected into the conversation, because you have to
believe that a this was actually written, that this is not a prank in and of
itself. Because everything could be a prank that's here. Yes or no, right. But
if faith in general doesn't make any sense, but the faith in something does
just like belief in something does people say, I believe in what? Well, I
don't know. I just believe that's stupid. To have faith. Oh, I just have faith.
That's stupid. The concept of let's say Alpida, which is Greek or faith or
something like that, or which means to hope also similar term means that you
have it is based on something. Like I think the text you were alluding to was
the scriptures. And by the way, I was having a discussion regarding the
scriptures recently. And you know that a few hundred years ago, that what you
call the Bible now was never an issue. The King James Bible, you know, people
refer to it, oh, it's the only true word of God and all this other stuff. A few
centuries ago, when anyone brought up that discussion, they didn't say the
Bible, or King James, or they said the Hebrew scriptures, go look it up. If you
look at writings, from back, you know, let's say 1700s. And prior to that,
right, only recently that there was a point in time when it wasn't even
mass produced. So nobody had one. All they had is the word of the preacher, or
not even the preacher, the guy who was explaining what the preacher just told
you, from ancient times, from my understanding, which is false. Yeah. You
know, which which? Well, wait, which is false? Is my understanding false? Or was
what the preacher was saying? What the preacher is, because it's a mainstream
religion based out of the circus, meaning the church. Well, right. But but my
under my my idea about the way that this used to be related, before there was a
written text that could be placed in somebody's hand, a version of it,
whatever is true. This is, yeah, but it's not it's not that hard to validate.
Like, for example, let's look at another text. If you go to a bank, okay, and ask
them, what are you guys dealing with here, you know, Federal Reserve notes,
checks and credit slips, and things are also Federal Reserve notes, because
they're Federal Reserve note, credit Association, Federal Reserve Association,
right. So there's a text, it's called us code title 12, and deals with banking,
credit and finance. And title 12, 411. It's ironic how it's 411, because 411
usually means the info, right? Clearly states anyone can read it, that Federal
Reserve notes are to be used by Federal Reserve agents, and no other use is
authorized. So you go to a bank, and you start bringing that point up, they show
you the door. Because they shouldn't be even they, you see, so, so what's so how
difficult is it for anyone that's interested in economics to look that up?
Right now, you anyone can punch in USC 12, section 411 and read it, it's written
underneath grade level, you're not supposed to be using that money. But you
are and no one is addressing it, or go to a bank and ask them, do you know,
there's a title 12. Since you mentioned the text and faith, you know, in title
12, there's a code in there that states that banks are not allowed to lend money
that's on deposit, or any credit. Okay, so the banks, according to the law that
they wrote, what was written for them, they're not allowed to lend any money
they have on deposit, or they're not allowed to lend credit. Okay, Chuck, so
what are they lending? That doesn't doesn't money on deposit in the banks
accounts and credit pretty much cover everything. So what is indirectly, isn't
that saying that they're not allowed to make loans? Indirectly? Yeah. Yeah. So, so
where's the faith? So I have, see, that's what I mean by faith, it has to be backed
up by something. So now, when you have that faith, and you know what's going on,
you could basically say that the system is a scam, is a prank or a scam. Right?
You could say that, I mean, it might sound like a personal commentary, because
most people say, I don't care, Greek, I go to the store, I get what I want. Right? So
it's any text, but not any text as such. It has to be a source document. Let's go
back to the JFK stuff. If you start looking at, I suggest this to anyone that
does any research, especially contemporary, and I think you might agree
or not, but let's just look at it this way, whether you agree or not. It's when
an event happens that is highly public and of significance, let's say like the
assassination of JFK, or many other things, you really have to do forensic
research and look as closely as you can on what was documented, said, and can be
evidenced in the first couple of hours of the event. That is the best place to
start. True, but see, now we're introducing standards into the
discussion. You see what I mean? Look, I was born in 1972. Without giving anything
away here, you're not too much older or younger than me. Okay, but either way,
that's really not, you know, a huge difference between us. But let's just use
the mark 1960. How about that, which would put it 12 years earlier than me
based on the calendar, and I know, you know, let's not have that argument, but
just for the sake of argument, okay, ready? All right, 1960. We have no way of
verifying for ourselves that everything that exists now did not come into
existence in 1960, really, because why? We have to place some sort of faith in the
memorialization process. We have to understand the standards of the
memorialization process, right? I mean, do you see what I'm getting at here? I'm
just going to the very simple modern history point, but go ahead. Well, machinists
call it tolerance. When they machine a part, what tolerance? They're making a
machine to a thousandth of an inch, ten thousand, hundred thousand, millionth of
an inch, you know what? And the more tolerance you get, the more expensive the
job is, right? So it is an expensive job to do this job, meaning a
project or something you have to physically or actually work on mentally
or dedicate time to. Now the thing is, you can start to see how
indirectly, and I'm going to say this half in jest and all in earnest, is that
thousands of years ago, the people knew that certain information had to be kept
for posterity for a long time. That's why they put it in what? In stone. Even today
they use that sentence stone, right? It means it's difficult to change and it was
probably very well thought out before it was done. So that is just, let's say, an
analogy of how a contemporary might see something so significant that they know
that this doubt in the future that maybe none of this existed can be overcome by
maybe setting it in stone, you see? So there are certain weight to information,
there are certain things that can be validated, there's chain of custody,
there's chain, but then again, if you're living in a complete illusion like a
Truman Show type thing, there was a movie done about that, right? A complete
facsimile, then none of this matters. But then again, most people on this planet do
live a baseless life of abandonment and it doesn't matter. I think we even had
someone once call who said they were a minister and I said, well, it doesn't
matter if it was Mickey Mouse then and they agreed. So there you go. So it
doesn't matter to most people. I think getting here, getting together and doing
this is for the very few that maybe a certain way of thinking does matter, you
know? In other words, if it's there all along and no one is looking at it,
isn't it the same as if it doesn't exist, right? But if it's there all
along and you're and a few people are looking at it, now you have something
that no one else sees even though anyone can access it, right? Just like the US
codes I just brought up or if you want to go to the scriptural text, which is
not time yet to discuss that at this point, just look around you. It's not time
to ever discuss the money system, by the way, how it really works. That's been
prophesied. There's many things that are not time to discuss yet. And by the way, I
just want to throw in something. There's a researcher, more than a researcher, I
call him a witness, a Russian guy, his first name is Dmitry. And he had done a
project. He did a lot of stuff on 9-11 because he had known about what was in
place for that event to take place decades before, right? He had
firsthand knowledge of it. And what's interesting is firsthand knowledge
meaning because he was working for the Soviet government to do inventory on
certain things. And it came across his desk, right? In the 80s, let's say, right?
So he had done some research and he had discovered, now this sounds a little
conspiratorial, that after 9-11 there was a underground project to pull
dictionaries out of libraries and out of personal possessions, ones even that were
on CD. And people were paying, certain agents were put together on eBay and
offering hundreds of dollars for a dictionary you would normally get at a
garage sale for a dollar, let's say, right? Or a used bookstore, right? They wanted all
of the dictionaries post-2001. And then when they put them back out at the
libraries, let's say it had a 1992 publication date, they put them back on
the shelf brand new with a 1992 or 1965 or 1995. They still retained the printing
date as if it were, you see? So he had an interesting story about it. He actually
had some pretty good evidence that this was being done. It was very important
that certain terms in the dictionaries were changed. So is it possible to go
back now, for example, with Google is trying to digitize all of these books,
right? Now eventually you will have these books in digital form. How difficult is
it to change a book in digital form? I've talked about this a lot. I call it the
digital, you know, well not only me but others have called it the digital book
burning because it's not memorialized any longer in a form which is, you know,
difficult to change. You buy a book, you know, you buy a book and it doesn't
matter what the subject is, let's just say a cookbook. Okay, fine, I give you a
cookbook, you take it home. Now the only way that thing's going to change is if
you change it. Yeah, it'll look like it's been damaged or you would call it, yeah,
it's been... You'll see an alteration. Now you do this in the electronic realm and
the information just disappears. It's been replaced. There's no way to
forensically, I mean, I guess there is some ways to, but for the most part it's
not, it's not easily self-evident that the thing has been altered and this has
already happened with some of these books. People have taken note because
they have something to compare it to, but eventually paper will be gone.
Eventually, you know, your discs aren't going to work. Eventually you might be
left with nothing but this, you know, vaporous sort of electronic
representation of what once was. Right, and now it becomes a battle of wit,
not a battle of a comparison or what, you know, any
information that everyone can equally access. Now one person might say it
was there five years ago, now it's gone, and the other person says, no, it was
always like that. Now it's a battle of wit versus what's been memorialized. Now
you have no references anymore and it's all about what the person,
the person with the overwhelming character or persona will prevail. So now
it's might makes right versus right being right. You know, this is like,
you hear about how foreclosure proceedings go on and they always
bring in a copy of a note or a debt and the attorneys that are supposedly
representing the creditor have a copy of the signature, right, and then the judge
says that's okay and all that, right, and they never have the original, you know.
Which according to the older standards of evidence, that was not
sufficient. You know, you couldn't bring a photograph of the thing into the
courtroom alone to represent it. That's why there were physical items that used
to be piled on top of tables to say, look, this is the rope that was used.
This is the dress that was worn. You know, not just a prop, but you actually
had to demonstrate it. You actually had to reproduce it as in, well, not
reproduce it, you had to produce it as opposed to reproducing it, excuse me.
Authentic, yeah. To be authentic, correct. But that's no longer the standard when
it comes to, well, financial stuff and all this, yeah. Because it doesn't matter.
And one thing I tell people, you know, I'm arguing with the attorney and the
judge about the copy, I said, deny all the copies. And if they ask you why,
you say, because I don't have the original to compare it to. That's one way
to have them change the subject, because you just deny it all. And you say, it
can't be not even close. Well, bring me the original so I can do a comparison.
And they say, so that kills that, you know, so that they have to come up with
some other way to prank you out of whatever they're there to prank you on.
But, you know, how are you going to do that when everything's been altered?
But altered or it doesn't matter. I think we've also mentioned we're in the
credits part, right? And people, you could hear it in conversation. Growing up in
the 60s and 70s, I remember people saying, hey, I can do what I want. This is
a free country. Do you remember? Were you old enough to hear people say that
kind of stuff back in the day, all the time? Actually, the form it took on for
me is it's a free country, isn't it? Right, right. You know, which was a
response to why the hell are you doing something or other? Yeah. When did that
stop? When did you think that stopped in the 90s? Roughly late 90s? You stopped
hearing? I would say that stopped. Realistically, in the late 80s, it went
away around the time. I can mark these things by presidential installments
around the time that H.W. Bush became president. I think I stopped hearing
that. I don't know why. But what did he put in the people's minds that their
secrets are OK? Like, for example, you notice how the ballots people vote in
secret. That's a terrible thing. Traditionally, it wasn't done like that
in ancient societies. They would separate the people and say, everybody
for this person, yay. And everyone for this person, yay. And the yays that
were louder were the vote, right? It was public. Everyone knew who wanted
what, right? And now what they've done, or it's been a while, that because
they've instilled in the people that you have a right to a secret ballot, that
means that now the government has a right to its secrets. And a real
government doesn't have secrets.
You know, and speaking of secrets, we did forget to mention that you have
the ability to join in on the call here and the discussion. We do have a
caller on the phone line, and I'd like to bring them on in. Let's see now.
It's an anonymous caller. So let's just see what happens here. We didn't
give any sort of guidelines this time. So let's see what happens. So
anonymous caller, you're on the air.
Hello, can you hear me?
Sure can.
Okay, awesome. Just to touch back a little bit on what the Greek was saying
at the beginning of the show about the credit based economy. I did have an
observation I wanted to share with you guys. It seems like what the
government punishes you on if you get arrested, or you know, you get taken
into jail, or you get a fine, or what have you, it's either money or time.
And if you're looking or if you if you work for a good company, what do they
reward you with a reward you with good wages, which is money, or vacation
time. So I guess my point here is, no matter which way that you go on the
spectrum, you're getting money taken away from you, in the form of a fine
for like a parking ticket or speeding ticket or jail time. Or if you work for
a good company or a corporation, then you get rewarded with vacation time and
good wages. So they're using the same system to either reward you or punish
you. But in reality, it's what they want to give you. But it's it's the same
thing you give or take one or the other way, you know?
Right, but let's let's go. That's, that's a good point. Let me just throw
something in what's fresh in the head. Let's look at what these things are
based on. And this is not whether you like it or not. This is the reality. Can
all any money, any amount of money buy you a minute of your time that you've
passed already? Never. No. Right? Yeah. So it's a matter of being compensated
what you you know, for time going. So, you know, all the money in the world
couldn't buy you back five years or a year or anything like that. I'm not
talking about facelifts and things like that. So it's an interesting thing on
the crossover there. But here's the other thing regarding money and time. If
you read about people that were of high net worth years ago, there were there
were men of leisure. Okay, you can study this. But now people of high net worth,
they have no time at all. They're constantly stressed and whatever. And
I've and I've had discussions with people of high net worth. I'm like, you
need to study your history a little bit like what I said, you know, look at
these guys, they were very wealthy, like you back in the day, and they were
people of leisure. You know, and you you have four cell phones and five
associates walking around with you all the time, you don't have a minute to
breathe. What's going on here? So it seems like this evil system, meaning
evil, the opposite of good, and it's not subjective, it's subjective. Because
no one is inquiring on what's going on. And the pranks, because our one way to
ask it is this, are pranks evil? Or are they good? Depends, right? Who the for
the prankster, it's good, because they enjoy doing it. But the pranky, it's
not. But the system has gotten so evil now. And so and it's considered good.
Well, how do you know, ask anyone, you know, I don't care about the system, I
go to the store and get what I want. That the people that were once rewarded
with lawful money had time. And now the people that are rewarded with lots of
this credit, have no time. So anyway, I just wanted to throw that other way of
thinking about it. But yes. Now, when you mentioned one thing about when you go
to jail, they say you're serving time, right? Now, that is a mishmash. These law
merchants, the legal society, by the way, lawyers, attorneys, wherever loosely
they're called, that's the legal society there. In their own terminology, up until
the late 19th century, they were considered the law merchants. In Greek,
they're called viki godos, viki meaning law, or judging and gora, like a gora
meaning market. So they're literally putting the law on the market. That's
what their name means, law merchants. Okay, they are, have mishmashed so many
ancient religions, because they right now are under what's called the goddess
religion, the justice religion. One of the mishmashes that they did when you're
serving time, there was a Titan in ancient Greece. It was Kronos, right? You
had Kronos and Gaia and Uranus or Uranus, right? And those were the Titans in
ancient Greek mythology, right? And Prometheus, right? So you're serving this
particular Titan or God loosely put. The other thing that they melded in with
their law merchant society, because remember, they've got everyone by the
shorthair, so they can make up stuff and the people will believe it. The faith
thing again, right? In the Hindu religion, back in the day, you know, the Hindus
have like a million gods or whatever. Don't hold me to this. It could be 10
million, it could be a thousand, but it's innumerable almost, right? When someone
did something bad, like let's say, rape a little boy and they caught him, right?
They said, well, it's okay. You were appeasing the God of raping little boys
that day. So now you have to do penance. We're going to, you have a debt to society
and we're going to put you in this cell until you finish appeasing this God by
being still now. You see, so they've, so all this stuff about taking your time
away, they've also, it comes from various lores and various other religions
stitched together, because in a lawful society, you might have a fine and there
might be a deed you have to commit, but in lawful societies, there are no prisons.
Did you know that? You could look this up and there have been very few societies
that operated lawfully, because in a lawful society, there is no prison. In
other words, if you steal, you give back two or five times. If you deliberately
murder, you're put to death to appease the earth. But if you murdered by accident,
you have to change your, you have to have a city of refuge. There are all these
lawful societies don't have prisons, but they do have jails, which are temporary,
right? So one thing to understand, you know, if you look wherever you see what's
being done is unlawful. That's why everything is legal. You know, it's not
lawful. Lawful meaning it's within the correct, within the confines of the
environment. And right now, mankind is acting legally and it's borrowing from
these pagan religions. When I mean pagan, meaning that you must be ignorant to
follow it, because no one in their right mind, right, that is rational, and wants
to discern between good and evil, or what's helpful and what's hurtful, would
fall for these types of religions, you see, unless you were to benefit from it.
You know, and to me, see, I just speak for myself. And in a couple of seconds, I
would put it to you this way, time is money, money is time. And they're both
just lube for mental masturbation, as far as I'm concerned. So that's really what
it's about.
You know, when it comes to the real thing of spitting good enough, it ain't love.
But anyway, so
there it is.
Again, you can tip your waitress. He's here all week, folks. Um, so caller, was
there something else you wanted to add into the discussion?
No, that's all.
Yeah, be lawful, set yourself apart and try to have a good time. In the
beginning, it'll it'll really, you'll go mad, seeing that it's everywhere. And
everyone around you that is just irrational and just falls for what I
call heresy. heresy means what you personally like, you know, they used to
burn people at the stake for heresy, you know, they would blame it, they say,
you know, it was based for religious reasons, they said, Well, why are you
reading the mass in Latin, I don't understand what you're saying, you know,
and also, how do we know that it's the Hebrew scriptures, and they say, Oh, this
guy is a heretic, he wants us to do it his way, even though he was asking the
true and correct thing.
So if you go in this world and ask what's true and correct, you will be
considered a heretic. Oh, that's what you like. It's like, Oh, Greek, man, you
always want to look at what things are based on and evidence and being rational
and lawful. That's what you like, you know, man, no, we don't want that. You
know, it's like, what, what, what just happened here? So yeah, so be lawful and
be set apart and report back.
Yeah, well, when I was the main point I was trying to get across was that
they're either rewarding you or punishing you with stuff that's legal. That's not
lawful. It's legal. It's time. It's paying money or you're getting money from
being a good obedient, you know, slave to a corporation somewhere.
Yeah, but not really. Yeah, it is. No, it's slave. It's being a pranky. It's
there's nothing wrong. That's another thing that's been sidetracked. A
corporation, there's many levels to it. A corporation is just a corporate body.
It's basically an insurance thing. You know, years ago, shipping companies that
were owned by families that family had invested in one ship. And if that ship
sank, the whole family lost, you know, they had, you know, they're impoverished.
So they said, let's get, you know, five of these families together with five
ships and will form a corporation. So if one ship sinks, we each take a one fifth
loss. So at least we don't lose the house and our children aren't sold into
slavery. Right. So that was the original purpose of the corporation. And then it
stemmed off into just making the innocent pay for the guilty. How many times have
you heard these corporations put together? There's all these deeds. And then it's
time to get, you know, to create the liability or or damage. And then it's
time to get sued. What do they do? They collapse the corporation and they
don't. You see. So another reason what's been going on is people have been
observing how corporations are set up to make the innocent pay for the guilty
and they've gotten a bad rap. But essentially, the purpose of the
corporation was to create a legal fiction where you would spread divide
liability. So instead of one person taking 100 percent of the hit, you got
five people together where each took 20 percent, you see, of the hit or the
profits work both ways. So there's nothing wrong with having a corporation
that been going on for for thousands of years. The problems are now that it's
just the people are so ignorant of how it works that it's been used against
them, you know. So and also, when you look into the slavery aspect, it's
interesting. You know what the word application I have to look it up again.
But years ago, you know, when you get a job application, you have to you know,
you go to work for a corporation, you have to fill out an application. You
know that word application. One of the meanings of it is to beg for. So now
you're on the status of a vagabond, right? Anyway, think about that. OK, so
anything else? No, that's all I had to give today. Well, thanks for chiming in.
Do appreciate it. Thank you. I'm going to put you on hold and we'll see if
anybody else wants to join into the discussion. Of course, the numbers two,
one, eight, three, three, nine, eight, five, two, five, two, one, eight, three,
three, nine, eight, five, two, five. The code to dial in is two zero one two
twenty twelve is the code so that you guys know. And there's also the Skype.
I thought we had somebody waiting to come on on the Skype. Great. Yeah, I
think we did. I could I could try to bring them in if they're still
standing by. I pretty much closed that screen. Let's see. I'm going to
inquire with them and hopefully they don't feel too neglected. Well, you
know, but it's still that's what they still want in. But let's just give
people a reminder and some Greek speak. You might have heard this, Chuck,
uniquely spoken with you and I together or other places that you've heard
the Greek speak is that many things are seasonal, right? You know, a
lightning bolt has a season, even though it lasts for half a second. It has
a spring, summer, winter and fall season in it, you know, where it starts
off, it grows and then it goes to its peak growth and then it's harvested.
And then it goes to a period where nothing happens. Winter. We're going
into a springtime right now, right on this part of the world. Let's, you
know, we're already in going probably into fall soon, past summer now. But
up here it would be springtime and things are planted. So in springtime,
you know what happens when you go buy a farm or something like that?
Not sure if I'm being heard at this point. The Greek is not. Something
seems to have interrupted what I can hear. So, you know, here I am
continuing. Oh, there he is. I did. I made the mistake of not paying
attention, hitting the button. So the green button, which put this call and
hold. So so what happens in the springtime is you drive by the farm and
it doesn't look like anything is going on. It's the fields still look
fallow. But, you know, all the seeds are planted, right? Everything just
needs to be watered now. It doesn't doesn't look like anything's going on,
but all the seeds are in. Right. Think about it. And so this is the time
period we're coming right now. What's being planted right now that is going
to be growing in the summer? Think about it. And then followed by the
harvest and then winter again. And what's interesting about planting
seeds and farm, certain seeds have characteristics. If you plant them too
deep, they won't grow. If you plant them too shallow, they won't grow as
opposed and also might be eaten by birds and things. So right now, like
we said earlier, don't pay attention to where it's noisy. That's not the
real stuff. The real stuff is going on where it's quiet. And we're coming
into a time period where all the real stuff in the springtime is
underground or in the ground ready to grow. So even though springtime
comes around, you don't see what's been planted. You see, this
agricultural analogy works very well. An example would be like we've
given before. All financial collapses happen in the fall, right? All the
Black Tuesdays and whatever, right? Look in history, the depression and
all these stock market crashes. When do they happen? What they call
September, October, right? So when you hear about people saying there's
going to be a financial collapse in what they call July, just walk away
because they don't happen, right? And in the wintertime is a time for
travel, distant thinking. Think about an agriculture-based society.
Spring, you're working your ass off. Summer, you're working your ass off
because you also do harvesting of certain crops in the summer. And fall,
you're really working your ass off because you're harvesting everything.
And so all that time between spring, summer, and fall, you don't have time
to put a new roof on the house, do you? You don't have time to go travel
cross-country, do you? Right? Now, we're talking about now before the
current conventions of aviation and electronics, right? So the wintertime
was a time when you did what? You raised a barn. You built a barn, right?
You put a new roof on the house. You traveled long distance. All this
stuff. So what does that mean? Well, you'll see there's always a boom
of international affairs in wintertime. But anyway, I've discussed this
on certain private calls for hours on the deep specifics. I think if we did
a specific on the seasonal analogies of politics and human society, I think
it would bore people to death. And just one thing I want people to consider,
could boredom be a form of anger? Anyway, so we're going to try to bring
in this fellow again on Skype. Just from my two cents here, boredom and
anger all seem to be a form of fear. So I don't know. Maybe it's just me.
Well, fear we've described as perhaps a weak state of mind and lack of skill.
I think we've given an analogy on that. And we have someone on Skype.
Yeah, perhaps. Go ahead. Speak up, sir. G'day, g'day.
All right. G'day. How you doing?
Very good. So you wanted to add something
into the conversation. Shoot. You're on.
I turned off my radio to be polite, so I didn't really catch what you guys
were talking about. But I got my neighbors to tune in, so I picked up a little bit.
You guys are talking about money for ages and then the 80s.
OK. Great.
I got heaps of things to talk about. Well, you know, you could always Skype
Ocelli and the Greek and we could talk about them.
But if you got anything for anything for us right now, next few minutes,
anything you want to tell the world about it or the world of five people listening.
I'm sure it's more than five. I brought two in.
OK, great. So seven. Well, either that or we'll just we'll just say
thanks for thanks for the interest and we'll catch up on Skype. How's that?
Sure. No, I got one. Oh, yeah. The Greek. I love your joke about cutting off the wire
and electricity running out of the cable. Oh, yeah. What you mean, waiting in hand
with a dustpan, waiting to sweep the all the electrons are supposed to be flowing.
Yeah. I don't know what they say. They're electrons going up and down the cable. Yeah.
I've done it many times. Physics, then say.
But academics. Yeah. Yeah. I feel I feel bad for people who have anything more than an eighth grade
education for every year that you have more than an eighth grade education. You need about two or
three years to flush it out. And the ultimate prank is what they call university.
Oh, yeah. But OK, my extension to that is what about fields and waves? They're real.
Well, they are. But, you know, when you're when you're looking at them as described,
you're looking at a slice at a cross section. They're really three dimensional.
And in a freeze frame, they both exist. Fields exist and waves exist.
Oh, it's all fields. That's how information is transferred instantly, transversely.
I mean, longitudinally, not transverse. So, well, brilliant. Sounds like you've got things on the
mind there. And does anything else? Well, maybe we got a few more minutes here. We'll just I'll
hit the red button and we'll catch up on Skype personally. How's that? Or maybe bring into a
group or something. Sounds great. OK, I've got one. I've got one more classic question for you,
the Greek. You guys mentioned, you know, you shouldn't drink or smoke before coming and
talking. What about sleep deprivation? Yeah, it might be possible if it has an influence.
There you go. All right. Thanks. And we'll we'll catch up with you soon.
Nice. Well, there you go. A little a little entry from down under sounded like to me.
Yeah, perhaps. Let's just say the rules were don't talk about yourself. Nobody really cares,
even though they act like they do. They're just waiting for you to shut up so they can tell you
what they want to say. And the other thing is, if you're under the influence like this chap brought
up, perhaps we all know you might be. So don't bother calling in. So those were the rules in the
end there. Right. And they do do appreciate you. Was that you you eight, I think, was the I.D.
they're utilized. So do appreciate you adding in. Anyway, we're coming close to the end here.
Is there anything we always. Yeah, well, it seems as though that is the constant state of affairs.
And based on my observations, it does appear as though we are coming toward,
well, that time when the credits might run, there might be an after credits entry, you know,
like they do in the Marvel movies where you get a snippet from what's coming next before everything
actually fades to black. But who knows? I'm not the director or the creator. So good.
No, no. But is it the question then would be, is it an intelligent creator or benevolent creator
or are they not intelligent? They're not benevolent. Typically, when you have an
intelligent or benevolent creator, let's say you buy a dishwasher or a blow dryer or a toaster,
even something rudimentary like that, when you open the contents, what pops out of there usually
an instruction manual, even something as rudimentary as that. I even got a cable
recently, you know, like one of these USB type things. And it had a little instruction thing.
Thanks for buying from what we have. Here's the warranty. And this is how you plug it in. Wow.
Right. So. But the thing, Chuck, is not it's not whether it is or it isn't or whatever.
It's it's that that can be when you have just a few people screaming about it is one thing.
They're crazy or whatever. Or, you know, I do what I want still, let's say. But the thing is the
thing that I always gripe about is it's what's incredible is the lack of inquiry. How many
people are talking about financial stuff and how many actually inquiring with the authorities,
really inquiring what the authorities have memorialized within their codes that are
allegedly these things run by? How many of them actually inquire? None. None is the answer. None.
You know why? Because if they did, they wouldn't be saying what they did. How many doctors inquire
on how the body really works? How many religious people actually inquire in the text in context?
None. Because if they did, they wouldn't be part of that religion. Who's inquiring? I mean,
again, let's just go back to the JFK research. When you started researching it, you were probably
aware of other people that were public figures doing it. And you probably came across a lot of
stuff that they didn't. And it was just kind of like staring like, why hasn't anyone looked at it
like this? Because it's unpopular. And the way it was perhaps initially trailblazed or presented to
the public, this might have been contrary to it. Now, you don't want to say anything contrary to
what the public has accepted, do you? Well, that was the problem with, you know, everybody always
asks why I didn't publish a book. Because nobody would want to hear what I had to say.
Maybe it's like the show, then that's okay. We still do the show publish the book anyway. But
here's the thing. Well, nor do I don't because a lot of people in public say Greek, you need to
write a book. I'm like, well, if I were to say I need to write a book or want to write a book,
I am presuming that people know how to read, right?
That's the problem.
You have to pursue you're presuming because you see what I mean by that is that not everyone who
gets your book is reading it with comprehension. In other words, they might read it and take it out
of context or read into it what you think you're saying that's not even there. So
you know, an odd, an odd question, I would like to enter that I do see and I don't want to enter
too many chat room or text questions into the equation any longer. But I like this one. So I'm
going to throw it in just because we have a few moments here. Have you heard about a new organ
being discovered in the body? No, I have not. And where do we go to find out more about who's
discovering it and what they're discovering? Yeah, I would I would love to hear about this,
too. Because quite honestly, I have heard nothing about it either. So okay, cool. No,
I just thought maybe you might have some insights on that because often I think to myself, you don't
and you have something to say about whatever it is I can throw in. So usually, you know,
doesn't fall flat. No, no, there's a new word. But the thing is just saying that,
okay, that's great. It gives us a little. Oh, well, you know, okay, that's interesting.
Do we start telling people, you know, there's a new organ in the body and we know nothing about
it. So where do we go to find out more about it? And are you know, is it something we can access?
Right. So we can inquire for those who want to inquire. Yeah, I'd like to see it because,
you know, to the best of my knowledge, for hundreds of years, people have been taking
apart the human body, you know, and if they haven't discovered it before, then maybe it
is truly a new thing that is just showing up now, which would be odd. There's a whole thing
of pleomorphism and emergence. And when something dies, it changes. And the body creates these new
emergence, you know, things that come out of nowhere, seemingly that form in dead bodies that
are normally not in living bodies. And then they base medicine around that. Think about it for a
moment. If a dead decomposing cadaver or corpse is very different from one that is alive in
temperature and it's kept when death comes on, chemical decomposition starts almost immediately
in most cases, not all cases based on temperature and other things. Right. So that chemical
decomposition changes things. And this is what medicine is based on, where if you go to some
Eastern medicines, they actually study the body while it's still alive. Like there's over 30
different pulses in the body. When you go to the Western medicine, they only look at the pulse for
the heart, maybe the breathing rate, but they don't look for a kidney or a liver or pancreas pulse or
anything like that. It might sound strange if you've heard this for the first time, but all of
the organs have a pulse. Right. Right. So where, you know, these determinations are not really
being done. And so if there is a new organ, well, is it because it's been in denial? Just like,
for example, when the heart is studied, you know, one side of the heart is an inch thick muscle.
The other side is as thin as tissue paper. And they take that and cut it off and throw it on
the floor. And they only talk about the side that's really thick. Right. But it turns out that
the side that's really thin, that is the one that's really doing all the work and regulating
the movement. So is it because is it a new organ because of bias? You know what I mean? It's been
ignored, not acknowledged, or is it really new because it's a new emergent? You know, I don't
know. Well, at one time, at one time, there were people that did not consider the skin to be an
organ. You know, that's one of the things that's developed over time. So that would be a new
introduction into the glossary, but not necessarily anything new. Right. Right. So the thing is, again,
with anything, is it possible? And it also is the is the field of inquiry level? Or do you have to
pay a lot in quotations here or be a part of a certain group to learn about it? Like you've
heard of that before, right? Oh, you know, medical society, the legal society. Yeah, that's yeah.
So be aware of that when you when when information can only be inquired by a certain
limited group to access it. That is a this. That is the clear sign of a prank, by the way.
Even if you look at some ancient religions where they had high priests,
everything they had done was also known by the people.
There you go. And everything that we knew for two hours was thrown into the conversation, I think.
Well, at least the best you could do in two hours here on the Greek that completes episode
nine or chapter nine of this particular incarnation, let's call it of this sonic event.
What do you think? Yes, sure. And we'll look for the new organ next week. Thanks.
All right. So stay tuned. And well, you know, it might all be useless,
but you got to do something while you're in the waiting room. Take care.