So it is the 26th day of the first month according to the Pope's work schedule.
This is Ocelli and the Greek broadcast live on American Freedom Radio at Americanfreedomradio.com.
Greek, help me out though because, well, the Pope's work schedule is not a way to keep time,
is it? Well, no, it's exactly that. And why did he even start one? I guess it's a question like
why did the chicken cross the road? Who is anybody to question the intentions of a chicken, right?
So I wasn't exactly in the chicken's mind, so I'm not quite sure what his intent was.
It almost sounds like a lawyer's trick there. Yeah, but it's pretty obvious. You see,
they got it. No one's thinking that it's not that it's the Pope's work schedule and it's
not valid as a timepiece, which is true. And anyone can vet that. You can vet it many,
many different ways. The thing is, though, he was correct that people don't think people don't
pay attention. They can't discern. And here's the thing. What is knowledge with no discernment,
right? If you can't discern knowledge, you can be told a lie and you think it's knowledge
and you go along with it as such. And that's a perfect example. I mean, you do internet radio.
You talk to people. I mean, where's the discernment? You've got people talking about
the end of the world and they give dates or slave speak or the dollar is going to collapse or
Fukushima or, you know, then they go from every age range. And where's the discernment from them
or the audience? And I'll tell you, there's none. So here's the thing. If you want to discern
something, you have to kind of figure out what it's based on. Hmm. You know, like we're using
a certain language, right? And it's interesting that there might be countries tuning in and they
don't use this language that we are speaking right now, allegedly. And they can't discern
what we're saying, but they know something's being said. So anyway, with that, OK, if you're
confused, that's fine. You're normal. I'd say it's it appears to be around the 16th day of the 12th
month till noon. And doing a little bit observation, we might have a 13th moon this year. There's
something called intercalation. And it appears that every decade or nine years, because remember,
when the ninth year is over, you're into the 10th year. OK, so it looks like the sun is not rising
due east. That's the beauty of it. On the first and seventh month, seventh months, the sun rises in
cardinal east on the on the even on the corresponding opposite side of the globe. Yes, I said globe.
So there you go. We don't know if we have to. This is observational. We are not scheduling or
scheduling nature in its ways. We just know enough about nature. We always say, well, the Greek says,
you know, we really don't know what a bear is. We really don't. But we know enough about a bear that
we could casually say that we do know what bears are, but you really don't until you sit down and
talk to him for about eight hours. And anyway, so here we are trying to talk at least two hours a
week. And and folks, if you're yeah, if you want to join the conversation, what do you exactly?
That was my next point that I was going to get to. But of course, I wanted to point out that
it is difficult to know whether the chicken crossed the road or not if you did not witness it yourself.
So you may be having a discussion about why without actually knowing what happened.
Keep that in mind. Yeah. But, you know, if you weren't there, would a good report give you most
of the details? And you could say that you had a report that a chicken did cross the road and it's
good enough, but a bad report wouldn't really do much good to anyone other than dummy load them.
Well, it would be a good report. It would be. I would. Yeah, I would rather. Well, it's kind of
like, you know, the fine print is you don't read the fine print that's
called it, you know, educate experience. And if you do read the fine print, you get education.
Right. So so either way, reporting is the reason they're good. Reporting is important. It's
efficient. Right. You don't want to experience, you know, people say firsthand knowledge is very
important. I read a warning label on a blender that it could cause physical harm. I'm not going
stick the hand in the blender while it's on to get firsthand knowledge of that. Right. I don't
need that. So anyway, you know, little children kind of go through that, you know, don't touch
that. It's hot. And they're like, yeah, I know you've been saying that, you know, but daddy,
you're right. It's hot. OK. Touched it. Right. That's a lack of maturity. Yeah. So call in
people. Let's give the Skype part first. If you're using that convention, it would be Ocelli and the
Greek. And on the regular convention would be 218 area code. Finish it up, Chuck. Sure. It is
218-339-8525, 218-339-8525. And one other thing, you need to enter the code 2012 in order to appear
on my board. So 218-339-8525 and 2012-2012 is the code to push in afterwards. And I can add you
right into the discussion as it occurs. How about that? Sure. And the two guidelines I would suggest
is we call in. Don't talk about yourself. That's something to testify about, witness about,
report about, inform us about, or just plain old talk about. Don't talk about yourself because you
know why? People are told to be polite and they act polite because when you're talking about
yourself, everybody's nodding and they're acting as if they're interested. But inside their little
pea brains, they're thinking, when is this ass going to shut up so I can tell them what I think?
So don't talk about yourself. Second rule is if you're under the influence of anything, meaning
like you think you might sound or we might know that you sound like you're under the influence,
don't call in because you might sound like you think you're okay, but you really don't.
So those are the two simple guidelines. And there's actually more eventually,
but the thing is, how do you, if you assess the level of quality of the society on the planet at
large, I mean, then we can dig into a little bit more do's and don'ts. But at this point,
I think that's qualitatively and quantitatively enough. So there we go.
Now, due to the unplanned nature of this show, believe it or not, we don't actually have a
well-hammered out agenda. We just kind of come together and there are things, I mean, true or
false, we don't really interact in between the times we broadcast at this point. We used to
during the first incarnation of the show, let's call it. We used to talk a lot in between,
but we don't do that now. We just sort of let the conversation roll and it somehow,
well, you know, coalesces into something coherent. Where should we start today, you think?
Well, have you heard me say that this is just a private conversation that just happens to
be broadcast on a minor internet radio network, right? So let's continue with that. You got me a
message this week about something about Trump and favoring or unfavoring and backlash of doing
either, right? Because it seems like political sides, especially this one, you're going to get
in trouble with someone, whether you favor something political or don't favor it, right?
Okay. So regarding that, you know, it was just the leftover. And let me just ask you,
is it all right if we just go on that for a moment?
Yeah, look, not a problem. Not a problem. I mean, it's kind of the continuation of
the conversation I keep having to have on my own show, because people have attached
themselves to certain ideas and then decided that they can create lists of those that are their
friends or foes based on that. It's rather interesting. It almost looks to me like
the old religious debates I used to listen to. And it's kind of funny.
Well, it's a dummy load, right?
Isn't it?
Yeah. Well, it is. It's costing me a bit because I'm trying to have conversations that I think
are productive. And for the purposes of exposition, right, to bring it to other people,
I don't take it as this is a private conversation that you're just happening to get to hear.
Some parts of the conversation are like that because people get comfortable. But in general,
it's an attempt to educate people about something, each one of the shows I do.
And yet, because of these particular concepts, I have people revolting against me and not being
able to work with me and so on and so forth. And it's a very strange place to be in at this point.
Yes.
Well, things are strange. I can go after the way you described the show and revolts and things
like that, but I won't. I would say that what we say and how we say it and the quality of those
things matters. And I can give you an example. There's a covenant in an old book. And by the
way, if you want a really new idea, go read an old book, right? And there's a description that
says that even on that day, so you're without excuse, never curse. This is the King James
version. Never curse a leader, not even in your mind, a leader of a people, right?
So what that does is it kind of suggests that you remain removed about any talk or thought
about the leader of a people. Now, let's just say it like this. What is a leader of a people?
Well, I just defined it. It's like what color is George Washington's white horse, right?
What is a leader of a people? He is a leader of a people. And this is one case where you
can use the word to define itself, right? Or the phrase to define itself.
Okay. Now, typically a leader of a people, unless those people are under complete subjugation,
is one of them, right? For example, if you had the people on the earth and a bunch of Martians
came here and they decided to subjugate everyone and be their leaders, where in this case,
the Martians wouldn't be of the people, right? The people would happen to have that kind of
leader under subjugation or conquest. Now, perceivably, that doesn't seem to be the case.
So, the convention, the mindset, even down to what the leader wears is reflected or a social,
let's say, abstract or sample of what the people accept as being theirs, right? Okay.
So, let's not look at the leader of a people because it's just an extrapolation or an abstract.
In other words, if you've got a mountain made of granite, whether you're at the very top at
the peak of the pyramid, let's say, or at the very base, what is it all made of? Granite, right?
Whether, yeah, you could take mashed potatoes and shape it like a pyramid. What's at the top of
the pyramid? Mashed potatoes, what's at the bottom? And I'm using these metaphors because that's,
you know, the top of the pyramid metaphor and bottom, right? Supposedly, as you get,
it gets narrower up at the top, right? And the leader is at the top.
So, yeah, it makes sense for a lot of reasons. The aesthetics are in line with the concept of
less and more and the select individuals that end up at the top, so on and so forth.
So, it makes sense. I got mashed potatoes at the bottom. You're going to get mashed potatoes at the
top because that's how you form it, right? So, let's just look at the bottom because that's
the foundation. Foundation, and this is because the purpose of the leadership is not only one
narrow thing because it actually crosses over into the tangible, the physical, you know, literally,
you know, there are people under the employment or subjugation of the leadership to make other
people do things. So, it's not just a state of mind. They actually physically do things, right?
So, if you look at, that means that it covers everything, the leadership of the people,
the state of mind. So, let's just look at what they call United States of America
in a nutshell, very, very simply and objectively, which is almost not possible at this point.
But let's just do it anyway for the sake of anyone that feels like they're being talked at
to, you know, and here's the talking at you, folks. There's something called money. And the
reason you have money is because there's an old writ that also says that most problems that anyone
can have can pretty much be solved with money. You don't have any money. You have a credit-based
economy until money is brought back and needs to be sorted out. That's why when you look at
everything, it's a note. Now, Chuck, if I give you a note or a promise to mow the lawn or buy
you lunch, now, as long as you have that note and that's all I've done, are you going to get the lawn
mowed or get lunch? No. Eventually, you're going to have to call the note on me. Say,
Greek man, it's been like two years or a week or two days. You said you were going to mow the
lawn or buy me lunch, right? No pun intended, buy me lunch. I said, well, you got the note.
Yeah, I do, but let's bring this thing to reality and it never happens. You think you're going to
be hungry and is the grass going to be almost waist high? Absolutely, in this case, that's exactly
unless you manifest it. So you got notes for money. Now, a lot of people are so wooden-headed.
By the way, wooden-headed is a term that Oliver Heaviside put out a while back. When you run into
wooden-headed people, it's almost not worth rationalizing with them. All you have to do is
smile, just smile at them. You ever see when people say things in public or whatever,
whether the people like it or not, they just smile and walk away, right? So when you're dealing with
wooden-headed people, you just have to smile because they will get very annoyed and even
the most passive type can show in their face if they want to bring physical violence to your harm.
You have no money and what that means, the wooden-headed people don't get it,
so I'm smiling for those. What that means is what happens when nothing comes into fruition,
nothing can be judged, like for example, on its quality. Now, Chuck, if you just have a note for
let's say the Greek getting you lunch or cutting the lawn, and you never get the lunch and you
never get the lawn cut, could you ever judge whether the job was done right or it wasn't
done right or I damaged something while I was doing it? No, you can't. Well, I couldn't judge
the quality of something that didn't happen or that I don't have. So how am I to judge the
quality of nothing? Exactly. So this is what's happening with money because you have a fiat
credit-based. Now, the credit-based economy is not fiat. It's quite real, but your perception
of it is fiat. You say it's fiat. That's good enough. Any semi-rational being in a society
that acknowledges that it's fiat currency for more than three days should set themselves on fire and
run down the street, in protest at least, and this is not happening. I'll show you how apathetic
people are. But here's the thing. So we just said you can't judge something that hasn't happened.
So when you're under this credit-based economy that is considered fiat, guess what happened?
You lost your law. You lose your law. That's what happens when you lose money. Think about it for a
minute. Let me say it one more time. Okay, so what? We're just trading pieces of paper. Yeah, that's fine.
It could be lawful, but it's not because why? You lose your law. It got substituted with what?
The legal society, which doesn't go by law. Anyway, they're pranksters. Now, the way that
it functions in value is not anything that you will perceive other than the exchanges that you
make, but on the other end, those that control the credit system do know how it works. And here, I'll
just throw this in just as a little dig because this is so simple an eight-year-old or four-year-old
can comprehend it. Chuck, I'm going to show you how the money system works, and I'll show you how
apathetic the people are empathetic at this point because they don't research it at all. Let's use
slave talk, like mine, yours, hers, his, because there's no ownership. It's very difficult. All
right. Now, Chuck, I write you a check for $100. There's no dollars. Let's just use this talk.
I write you a check for $100, and I send it to you in the mail. You go and open it, and you say,
look, the Greek sent me $100. I'm going to my bank, right? And you hand the check to the teller,
and she hands it right back to you. She goes, I can't use it until you do what? Sign the back,
right? Oh, yeah. Right? Right? Okay. Have you ever had that happen? You got to sign the back
for it to use it, right? Oh, sure. I've even forgotten to sign a check that I brought to
the bank. Yeah. Well, the front would be, you need two signatures, the issuing signature and
then the endorsing signature, just like on the notes. You got a signature on the left of the
alleged president and a signature on the right. That's how the credit system works.
So now you sign the back, right? And the moment you give it back to the teller, what the bank has
in inventory are transaction numbers. That's their inventory. So the next one, they pull up a
transaction number, and let's say it's $100. They credit to you $100 that was created out of those
two signatures right there on the spot. Right? Sounds good. So now you get a transaction. You
look at the account and you say, oh, thanks to the Greek, I just got $100 more in the account
or whatever balance works out. If it was zero, it's 100 now, right? Okay. Now, what people are
shown now, I go to the bank that I use and I see $100 was taken out, right? And I'm like, oh,
that's because Chuck, it got transferred over to Chuck. Right? No, that's not what's happening
because they created the money with the two signatures. So what are they doing to me? Well,
I'll tell you what they're doing to me. They know the convention that this is how people
are taught to think. So the bank that I have, what it does is it takes the money out of the
account that I can see, right? So it makes sense to me that it got transferred. But what they're
really doing is putting it in another account under my name in the comptroller's part of the
bank. And they let it sit there because they have to take it out, right? Because it makes sense to
the way you've been taught through the schools, the churches, the radio, the TV. Now, it's still
sitting there in my name. After a certain time, about 30 or 90 days, they file paperwork that
those funds have been abandoned. And no one knows. I mean, they know. And then after a certain amount
of time, then they file other paperwork for them to claim it, right? And now it's gone.
So how many times have you heard of someone, well, I lost my job. In two weeks, I'm going to lose the
apartment and the children can't eat because the bank account went down. It's not because any money
got transferred anywhere. Your own bank is taking it from you. And they're claiming it as being a
bad. It's not their problem that you don't know this system works this way. So anyway, but this
is all right. Whoever's paying attention will get it. This is an archive. You could play it over and
over. So basically, all you need is like when you're born, get $1,000. You go put it in the bank,
deposit it, and spend it. And then when you get your next statement, you go and claim it all back
from your bank and redeposit it. And just the same $1,000, you could spend the rest of your life just
doing those forms over and over. Anyway. All right. I know we lost about 99% of the people
now. But I assure you, if you follow this through with what's called a forensic audit,
you know what forensics means, evidence for you, but looking very close, you'll find it.
And this is something that I would have never said in public a year ago. But you know, what the hay,
right? I mean, anyway. So you got no money, folks, and you're being ripped off every which way. It's
not the Federal Reserve that's ripping you off. That's why they're never going to audit the Fed,
because there's nothing to audit. They're a middleman. They don't care. They're actually
one of the most set apart institutions you can imagine. I'm going to say that right now.
They are one of the most set apart. Set apart from what? The system. They're a middleman.
I'll give you an example. Years ago, do you remember when the Hummers were really, the GM
had the Hummer brand vehicle car, right? And there was an environmental group that torched a lot in
a dealer's lot in California, based on environmental, you know, because the cars
were destroying the environment, right? So they torched the lot. They burned most of the cars in
there. So they're interviewing the quote unquote owner of the dealership. And he's like, well,
how do you feel about it? He's like, no big deal. I don't care. I'm just a dealer, man.
It's not mine. I just get a cut every time one goes through my hands. You see, there's nothing
to audit here. I don't keep that stuff. The only thing I have to audit is what goes through.
Anyway, so you got no money, folks, and nobody's paying attention. No one cares. All right,
let's go to the next thing. You got no courts. How do I know? Well, I'm not going to give
references, but you could look up something called the U.S. Constitution. I think it's
around Article 10. It says, I'm paraphrasing here, let it not be misconstrued that there are no
judicial courts of law or equity in the United States. I don't think I even need to repeat that.
Anybody could look it up. If I said to you, Chuck, let it not be misconstrued means I should
have be paying attention that there are no courts in the United States. What does that mean? Just
like it sounds. And by the way, folks, if you don't really think there's any money, I'm just
going to tie this in because remember, we said there's no law, so you have no courts. It makes
sense, right? Go look up the United States Code, Title 12, Section 411. It's about 40 words. It's
unusual for legalese. It basically tells you that Federal Reserve notes are only authorized
to be used by Federal Reserve banks and Federal Reserve agents and no other use is authorized.
Now, I don't know about you, Chuck, but do you need someone to translate what no other
use is authorized means? Well, the only problem there is what is use, right? What is use?
Well, the intended use of the note is to be in the financial system,
whether you're buying lemonade or doing an international transaction. By the way,
I just gave the example of how checks work in people's accounts. That's the same thing that
it works in international trade. And you ever hear of somebody saying, I'm waiting for money
to be transferred, and they do this dog and pony show like it has to clear to this act,
you know, like a prank, you know? There's no money. I assure you, no money has ever been
transferred in about 70 years. It's created on the spot. You ever know what bills of laden are?
Anyway, oh, boy, where do you start? You got no money, you got no law. Now,
what you perceive as a judicial court is not. It's a justice court. It's the revived goddess
religion. It's not my opinion, folks. I mean, it's right in front of you. Actually, if you walk
around, they usually prop these statues up on the top of buildings are pretty high, so you can
actually walk into one and not even knowing, right, if it wasn't out of the way, right? If
had these statues down on the ground, somebody would probably already hit it with a car. But
they, you know, they've got them high up. And anyway, so what's going on right now is when
people get in trouble by these guys with black robes and other guys with briefcases, it's no
different than you had a nine year old with a lemonade stand that had an army of paramilitary
people with badges and guns and buildings with bars. And then what's the difference?
Same thing. Everything in this country is done administratively.
So you're always in the wrong court anyway, and there is no court. So this is I've had
discussions with this with a guy named John Fitzgerald Malloy. He was a Supreme Court
justice. He authored. Have you ever heard the Miranda rights? You have the right to
mean silent, right? He's the author. Look him up. And when I had these types of discussions
with him, you know what he would just say? Who are you going to go tell this to? He never
said you're not correct. Or what about this? He always says, who are you going to go tell
this to? What does that mean? We got everybody by the balls. Doesn't matter.
Yeah, well, no, that's but that's why it's not really a threat to tell people this stuff
because they won't believe you anyway. You know, I can't hear it. Yeah. Yeah. So so this
is your country so far. Now, this is what you're being. This is what your leaders are
either not telling you or anything. These are these are OK. There's something called
the Federal Register. OK, you could look it up. And what they do is they put notices
up on what the federal government has in mind of publishing in it. And you've been
under a state of emergency. Do I need to define what a state of emergency is? No. Do you know?
Right. No, not at all. I'm aware that that's been the case now for since the 1930s, if
I'm not mistaken. And on top of that, we have something called Trading with the Enemies
Act, where there's a clear delineation between what's called the capital territory and the
rest of the country. And you've been declared the enemy. So. All right. So let's keep going.
So this is what the current leader, the who, what's it, whoever it is, male, female,
young or old, is leading. OK, does it matter? I think I think the the things that we just
mentioned, Trump, no pun intended, the character position and intent of the current leader
or what he's signing or not signing or the way he wears his hair or his suit.
I think these things trump that. No pun intended. You get it.
That's funny. That's funny, because, you know, I just boil it down to it's all
a bunch of actors. And what they've done is convinced you that the show is real.
Well, what it is, we're talking about what's really going on. Well, but it's the show. Well,
here's the thing. The show is real, Chuck. But when the show is over and the screen comes up
and you see a brick wall, that kind of wakes people up a little bit more, doesn't it?
Usually. Yeah, that's what we're describing. They come out of that that induced, you know,
a lot of different descriptions for it. But it's like a form of hypnosis, right?
Yeah. Where you suspend disbelief and all of that. You do the same thing in a movie theater.
So, yeah. So you have no medicine either. We don't need to get into that. That's pretty obvious.
You have no education. Think about it. The trustees of most universities are run by a
board of trustees. And when you look at a degree, that's what it says. The trustees
of this university recommend that you get this degree. That's what all the diplomas typically
say, paraphrasing. The trustees, whenever they've been interviewed or anything like that,
they say, no, we're not here to educate anybody. We're here to basically train them
and make sure that they do what they're told, basically. I'm paraphrasing because there's many,
many, right? You have no education, period. If you want to know what education is or
an institutional education, look up what's called a Victorian grammar school, or there are some
grammar schools at large right now. Basically, you go to school between seven and 13. And if you want
more education, you go to university. That's why when you look up the bio of a lot of the
intellectual giants of the 19th century, you say that this guy, that this year got his degree from
Cambridge or Oxford. And you look at it, and you do the math, what year he got his degree and when
he was born, simple math, and you see he's 17 or 18. You're like, wait a second. How did he get a
degree from, huh, huh, huh? Because that's the way it was done. You only need three or four years of
education to learn everything. I can personally teach anyone what they teach from kindergarten
to senior year in high school in less than six months, casually. And actually, you will beat
the regents, and you'll probably be listed in a very, it's not because it's difficult.
Anyway, all right, then you go on. This is what's cost. You have no money. You have no judicial
system. You have no law. You have no medicine. I'm not even going to get into that. You have no
education. Should we keep going? Do you see the point here?
Why not? What do you have?
Yeah. Well, what do you have is a very interesting continent. In other words, the east coast,
left coast, right coast, you got oceans, right? And also you have the majority of the continent,
this section of the continent, because the continent stretches, I mean, where do you start?
Panama Canal may be cut off all the way up to Alaska, let's say. But what they call the United
States of America with the northern and southern borders, respectively, you've got a wonderful
seaboard on left and right coasts, right? And predominantly very fertile land. So not only
can you, the US, what's called America, can pretty much produce foodstuffs for the entire world.
And yet they have the worst food on the planet at this point, right? All right, so we go on and on
and on. Just like, for example, you have no courts, but you have more people in prison than any other
place on the planet. This doesn't make sense either. You have no money, but you're considered
the wealthiest planet on the world. Might as well be the wealthiest country on the planet.
Wealthiest country on the planet, yeah.
And you have no money, okay? And you have no education, yet people from your Ivy Leagues,
you know. Anyway, so where do you, okay, so okay, I feel sorry for the leader of such a people,
and I feel sorry for the people. So let's just put it together. I feel sorry for people with
such a leader, or a leader over such people. No matter how you slice it, it's not good, folks.
It doesn't matter who it is. So this is, I don't know if we can get it any more objective other
than referring to everything in more presumptive terms, like there is a country with a latitude,
longitude with this. And I don't think we, we can say United States of America. I said we'll use a
little bit of slave talk. And by the way, people that always talk about slave talk, they're actually
just as they're interested, they can't see through it either. Because you always hear them using
terms that are slave talk. But anyway, how can we objectify? Very simple. Stop reading into things.
Right? The one thing I had a discussion with someone today is that this is pretty accurate if
you examine it. On its face, it may not seem, it might seem presumptuous. But most people stop
mentally or spiritually developing around 9 or 12 years old. And I'm giving them the leeway at 12,
because a 12 is the definition of a moron, by the way, when someone ceases to develop behind
that. That's why I would like to find another word to address the population at large other than
morons. It's not a pejorative. It's not a put down. It's a fairly, I like to be accurate.
So most people stop developing at that point, even though they look older or have degrees like we
just suggested and whatever, right? So what happens is they're constantly reading into it.
In other words, whether they're 12 or 65 or 75, when they look at a piece of information,
they're trying to correlate it. They're comparing it to everything they've downloaded up until about
9 years old and compare it. And there's a comparative there where if it's about 50%
or even 40% close enough, they judge it as they just put it in that file.
And they can't see what's going on. Give you an example. There's a technical aspect of not
being able to see or hear things or perceive. There is a video on YouTube where there are five
people standing around. And the video suggests that these people will be standing around and
passing a ball. And you have to count how many times they pass the ball. And after they run the
video for another minute, did you count? Well, it says, well, while you're counting,
did you notice the gorilla walk through the people? And you're like, no, let's play it back
slowly. So while you're focusing on the ball, they have a guy in a gorilla suit walk through
the people. And you didn't even see that because you were told to count the balls.
That would be how many times the ball was passed. That's an extreme example.
This is a recreation of an example that's utilized to explain eyewitness testimony
and how it can be skewed and lacking certain details and be focused on particular details.
They actually teach this to lawyers exactly the same way you just described it.
OK. Yeah. The thing is, well, let's just dig on that for a second. These professionals,
whether they're religious or not, people think, oh, they're so special. They're experts. We got
an expert. Right. Now, where do these people come from? Well, they're regular morons like everyone
else that are pulled out and supposedly get some kind of training so they can justify that position
or that title. Right. That sounds reasonable. And most people buy that as being something good.
Now, what separates these morons from the rest of the morons is that they have certain training.
Right. So if you want to justify and objectify them, whether they're religious, legal, political,
scientific, where do you start? We have to look at the quality of their training, don't we?
So I dare anyone to go look at any Ivy League law school or high level science school or high level
school of divinity or whatever and look at their curriculum because the curriculum pretty much
shows what they're being trained of or as, right? Right. So if you look at the legal schools or the
scientific schools or the schools of divinity, you'll find that what they're being trained of
is baseless. For example, if you go to any Ivy League law degree curriculum, you can download
it. It's very ordinary. Just go to any site, pick a famous Ivy League school law curriculum,
bachelor's degree, master's. They'll show you. Well, basically it says, well, how to start a
clinic. I'm going out of here. Certain opinions about this document. Right. I don't need to mention
it. We mentioned it before. There's certain historical cases, which is all hearsay, by the way,
and how to open a clinic. OK, no mention about the revived goddess religion or there's
there is no law. The Constitution states that there are no courts in the U.S. or businesses.
Right. OK, so then you go to the medical, you know, they got anatomy, you know, it's all molecular,
you know, cadavers, dead stuff. So you're an expert at that stuff. You go to school of divinity.
It's like, oh, yeah, history of the circus, you know, the church. And then as you get later on,
you get into cultures and traditions. So I would direct anyone to cannibals, birthdays and dolls.
And then they actually said in one of the schools of divinity actually raises we're going to read
the whole of this class is about reading the whole book of John. Wow, man, look at the whole
book. Did you hear that? Well, this is ridiculous, people. Ridiculous. And then you go to the
science stuff and it's all sponsored by Walt Disney. I shit you not. You know, the planetary
model of the atom was going to be debunked around the 1940s or 50s. Walt Disney says, no, no,
I like it. He invested millions of his own to do propaganda videos that there's an electron
proton and all that stuff. Anyway, so. OK, so where are we now? Well, this is where we are. So
the are you going to make it better? No, you're not. You know why you're not going to make it
better? Because the very things that I explained are irrefutable and no one not only whether you
understand it or not is irrelevant. Is is anyone going to go in direction in this direction and
research these things to have a good foundation, whether they're just going to think about it
or put any of it into action? The answer is absolutely not. And I mean, absolutely not.
It is not going to happen. So you're you're stuck. Go ahead and enjoy the dummy load. I tell people
look, you have an interim life of light. I call it the interim life. The lifespan is very short.
And when you come to this planet, however you come, whatever you do here and then you leave,
right, you're done, you're finished, you go to sleep. What you do in between at this point
doesn't matter very much because things are really set. And just to prove it is give you an
example. You know how we talk about the credits and things ending and how the gods really work
in big numbers and they have no qualms, you know, wiping out billions or creating destruction or
whatever, because this is how they operate. If if this if this society or this reality
was truly based on evolution where things evolved like, you know,
as the conventional thought is still the death of just one or two people is tragic because it's
such a subtle balance. But when you read ancient writs about what the gods are going to do,
they don't mind taking out 90 percent of the population at all because they can create more.
Right. Well, you know, but here's an interesting point. If that's the case,
then what is the point of being lawful or separating yourself or being fit and proper?
What's the point if all of it is set and it doesn't really matter?
No, I didn't say it doesn't really matter, but it is but it is set.
It did sound like you were suggesting that nothing that you do in the interim of your
short lifespan actually matters. That's what it sounded like to me. Maybe I misunderstood it.
Yeah. The misunderstanding might be from this. The majority of the people don't do what it takes
to make anything matter, just like I explained as a leader of what we just explained.
There's no money. There's no courts. You have no medicine. You have no schools. You have no.
And is anyone before you go and address who the leader is? Have you addressed all these other
things that you need to have in place before you put a leader in place? If I said you have a
country with no money, no courts, no education, no medicine and so on and so forth, is that a
country? Don't you have to get those things in place and a post office, let's say, before you
put a leader over that? Well, I certainly, if that's the actual condition, wouldn't bother to
invest anything into having someone lead something that is so empty.
So let's let's go. Let's traverse. Let's traverse back around and backwards towards what you said.
It doesn't matter. What does matter is setting yourself apart from it so you could see what
really does matter. OK, in other words, if people do well or they do poorly, it shouldn't matter to
you because you're set apart either way because you don't want to get involved with the stupidity.
Or do you? I'm just saying this is just colloquial terms. So so what that does is it keeps your life
very base and keeps your life very even keeled, doesn't it? You know, because it's so it's so
we're getting a little beeping from the from the mothership.
So, yeah, apparently, I don't know, maybe it's somebody trying to call into the listener line.
I'm not sure, but they're not appearing on the board. The number is 218-339-8525, 218-339-8525.
And if you dial 2012-2012 after you're connected, you get on the board. But I don't know,
it sounds like a call waiting noise to me. OK, well, OK, we'll see how it goes then if we if
it gets into the dropped into our lap, so to speak, so we can actually do something with it,
because right now it's just a sonic interruption. But yes, but let's how about writing a book
called The Art of the Prank? Anyway, I think someone wrote a book called The Art of Something
Else. So anyway, yes. So so you see, this is this is not so we took you see how a little short
message or interaction that you and I had between now and the last show can be turned into somewhat
of a viable subject matter, even though it's not viable because no one really can do anything with
it, because if they try to do anything with it and actually research and find out everything we just
said is true, we don't know if they have the intestinal fortitude to handle it or can deal
with it. They might set themselves on fire and run down the street. I mean, this is how far gone it
is. Right. And yes. So so you notice that no one is paying any attention. So it's fine. But back to
many other aspects of things that can be discussed here. You know, there's an essence of completion.
You know, we kind of we're not numerology or chemotry or anything like that. But the last
episode being seven, we talked about the divine and seven being a number towards man from the
divine. This is number eight, which in many Asian cultures is viewed as good fortune. Yes. I don't
like to use the word good luck. There's another thing about luck. It's like justice. But anyway.
Right. There's good fortune, infinity symbol, which is kind of like more of an urban thing
and completion. We don't know a lot about that time period, you know, the year eight thousand
or so. And by the way, folks were it appears we're around the year six thousand eighteen or so
since that new kid on the block we call Adam. But anyway, there's many there's many things
to be looked at. So things do get really interesting when you start seeing that
there's an old saying, for example, give me the wisdom to change to know what can't be changed.
And, you know, maybe that what I can change, you know. Right. So what you can change is your
position. Like, for example, if you're working with something dangerous, you should know that
it's dangerous and either keep back, respect it and insulate yourself. Right. We've given the
analogy if you're working in the sewer or working with 100 kilovolt power lines, you don't do it and
flip flops in a tank top. Right. You take measures to protect yourself. And that gets very interesting,
you know. So instead of saying every time, you know, that hundred thousand volt line is going
to fry you, how about saying, Chuck, man, look, I got some fleece lined insulated gear, man. This
stuff is really cool. You know, isn't that a little better? You know, so so either way,
you know, here's the thing. And there's a little personal note. I don't even know why we get
together and do this show every week. I mean, if we call this the last episode, it wouldn't matter
because it seems like we rehash the same mindset every week and every time. And the mindset is no
one is paying attention. When I say no one, I mean statistically. And what makes it worse is no one
really cares enough to pay attention. And then the third part is they don't really care at all. But
because you have a material body, you have what's called emotions. In other words, if you were just
pure spirit with no physical body, what you call emotions would be very different. Right. And think
about it for a second. Like, you know, are you ticklish? Do sharp objects hurt? Do things burn?
And do you get an emotional reaction from those things that I mentioned or even an orgasm? Right.
That is all purely because your spirit is animated through the physical body. When the spirit is not
animated through the physical body, you still might have things that make you comfortable in
mind and uncomfortable, but they're nothing like that, like being tied into a body. So at this
point, the bodies that we see, I think we referred people to space heaters because what they all have
in common is they do take up space. You can have a graduated tank, dunk someone in there in the
water. The amount the water goes up is the volume they take up. Most living people give off heat,
even though some have cold hands and cold feet. So you can generally say that most people,
surface-dwelling earth inhabitants at large right now, take up space and give off heat,
rendering them space heaters. And some do talk, just like these devices they call smartphones.
And by the way, I wanted to get into that for a moment. And this is, I know this ends up sometimes
being the Greek rant, but not really. But you know, you've heard of these smart devices, you know,
smartphones? I tried one recently. Let me give you a report on that.
By the way, I'm waiting for people to be smart and phones to be dumb. But I had it for a little
while and I got rid of it. I went back to a standard flip phone because I found it to be
too subjective. In other words, if you don't use it and learn what it wants you to do exactly or
allow you to be inundated by what it presents to you, it does not work. Or it doesn't allow you to
work it as intended. And it's too subjective. It's, if you want to know the ultimate expression
of a nine-year-old girl, go look at the operating systems in these smartphones. Okay. And also,
the guys that design these things are nerds. I don't know how else to say it. And they have
taken, it's a tyranny of the nerds. Let me just... I think that was pretty clear. I really do.
Yeah. And if you don't have their mindset, and these mindsets are coming at... See,
in architecture, they had something in America called the ADA, the American with Disabilities
Act. And you had to have a ramp or an elevator if you had a commercial building that takes more
than 21 people. And typically, if you're, let's say you're a general contractor, you're not going
to have too many need for someone with a wheelchair coming in the building, in the office, right?
Or things like that. So you basically, I call that the tyranny of the invalids. Nothing against
people who are handicapped. But now we have a small group of people, all the rights bestowed
or privileges, yes. But to force a small company to spend 80,000 bucks to put a ramp for this,
where it will never be used, is a form of tyranny. And then we have, that started in the late 70s,
80s. And then we had other forms of tyranny, certain groups. And recently, it's the tyranny
of the same-sex people. They're not gay, they're sodomites. Sorry, people. That's the conventional
term. Now there's a tyranny of that. And overlapping that, the tyranny of the nerds.
Well, let me slow you down just a little bit. First of all, H.W. Bush is the one who passed
the Americans with Disabilities Act, so makes it late 80s. Secondly, I want you to preserve the
rest of what you're about to say, because we do have a caller on the line. And I'd like to have
them in as quickly as possible and give them a chance to partake in the discussion. So we have
the 574 area code. And if you could do me a favor and turn your radio, what you're listening to,
down. Okay. Hello? All right. We'll give them three, two, one. Maybe click them off and we'll
bring them back. Okay. Okay. So caller with the 574 area code, you have your radio kicking back
at us, your device, whatever it may be, kicking back at us. And you need to turn it down and I'll
add you into the discussion. I'll give another minute or so for you to get that message.
And let's continue. All right. So the form of tyranny, people are screaming about that, right?
And it's sort of a backburner. They can't define it. It doesn't have to be a despot or a
dictatorship. And by the way, dictatorships can be malevolent or benevolent, right? To dictate,
you know, in the corporate culture, you have dictation, don't you? Right? What is that? You
know, to dictate, basically to speak and have it recorded or done. There's nothing wrong with
a dictator. It's just, there's nothing wrong with a monarchy. There's nothing wrong. You see,
it's just, is it malevolent or benevolent? Like, give me an example. In this part of the world,
they talk about capitalism being a good thing. Let me give you a loose definition of capitalism
based on objectifying what it does, not what they show you on paper. A loose definition of
capitalism is that when you're finished using something, you destroy it so no one else can use
it. Think about that for a moment. Right? Does that sound good? Okay.
No, that sounds good. That sounds good. And that makes sense.
I'll give you an example. I'll give you an example. I was traveling and I was at a donut shop.
Starts with the letter D. I think it ends with the letter D. And they have a reputation for being
around for a long time and getting up, making the donuts and all that stuff. So I'm standing in line
and I'm eyeing these glazed donuts, right? And I'm waiting and waiting, waiting. All of a sudden,
this guy comes out from the back with a garbage can and he grabs all the donuts and dumps them
in the garbage. And I'm like, hey, wait a second. And he brings out a whole new batch. And I'm like,
well, those are fine. He says, yeah, but they pass the time limit. And I say, well, you know,
I'm going in the dumpster to get them. And he says, no, you can't because the dumpster's locked.
Now, when you're dumping those donuts away, it doesn't represent a 50 cent or 80 cent donut.
It represents the soil, all the wheat that was grown, all the water that was used to irrigate
the wheat, the wheat being harvested, the wheat being ground, the wheat being transported,
all the other ingredients from their point of origin and all the labor involved
to that point being thrown away. It's not a freaking donut. You have to look at what the
donut is made from and what all those things that it's made from come from and what it took to get
it to that point. There is an incredible infrastructure to making a donut. You have to,
right? Let's say it's made of wheat flour. Think about it. Even if wheat grew on trees,
it wouldn't matter. You still have to take, you see? No, there's a lot of things to the process
that come to fruition in the form of that little donut, not to mention the fact that somebody had
to deliver the components, the water had to be collected, the labor involved, all of that.
The energy to cook it. Now, here's the thing. The rational thing is, look, I wanted that donut. Now,
that donut went into a plastic pail around the back. Hey, why do I need to stand in line and
buy it? I can go in the garbage and get it out, right? What does he say? You can't because I'm
done with it and no one else can get to it. We've locked the dumpster. This is capitalism.
Now, with that, I would like to try and re-add the caller again, so hopefully they've gotten
their device turned down and they're ready to participate in the discussion with the last
couple of minutes here in the first hour. If they make an interesting point or they are part
of the discussion, truly, we'll hold them over. 574, I'm bringing you back on the air. Can you
hear me, caller? Yes. Can you hear me? Yes, I can. Okay. Before we had your device kicking back at
us, and I don't think you could hear us or we could hear you, so you're on the air with Ocelli
the Greek, man. All right. Awesome. Thanks for taking my call. I hope you guys don't mind
switching gears for a minute, but I wanted to share an observation that I had while listening
to the last Sonic episode that you guys put on last week. Okay. Shoot. Okay. What I wanted to
do was offer an objective report, or hopefully, what's an objective report that occurred to me
while listening to last week's episode, which is that every major religion or belief system,
aka Christianity, Judaism, or Islam, seem to all agree on the premise that the state of human
society is not as it should be, which is true. This is evident because they have all attempted
to change or mold the world forcibly to conform to their specific paradigm. The Christians have
the Crusade and the Inquisition, the Jews in Exodus, and Islam is still attempting to do so
today, allegedly, with ISIS, Al-Qaeda, etc. While they're all wrong in their own version or vision
of how the world should be, not to mention also wrong in how they conduct themselves because they
don't follow what is written in their own books, possibly except for the Eastern traditions,
they all say that human society is currently something that should not be. So I guess the
irony here is that they all have a correct premise in that something is wrong, yet none of
the solutions they offer, or their conclusions, are correct. And this is all due to the effect
of cosmic censorship. So would you say that objectively is an accurate assessment?
Yeah, yeah. It's a good slice of something that you can continue with, and when you make statements
like that, they sound rational, because they are rational in this case. But when you present
something like this to your common surface-toiling earth inhabitant, they can't fathom it because
they have no background on it, right? But intuitively, people do comprehend this. Now,
you have to also understand that there's a slightly, you could use a broader brush,
and that the earth is under malevolent control. And anything that's malevolent,
in order for it to succeed, it has to present itself as benevolent, right? And
it's written in some ancient texts that this chief adversary, this chief malevolent adversary,
is in control of all the institutions. So even though they're trying to do what they're trying
to do, which is I call the dummy load, they are under control of a malevolent entity.
And that's why sometimes I say, if you're part of any world religion, you're basically,
could become an expert in demonology, because that's all it's based on.
And the other thing I wanted to just add is, thank you for paying attention. You've used some
of the terms that we like to use here, because I think that you found them to be applicable in your
conversation. So appreciate that as well. And it's, it's a fair report, as described earlier,
not necessarily containing every single detail, but can be a representative
report. No other word for it. It's actually happening. So yeah, absolutely. Perfectly
placed here on the show. We may run out of time on you caller. And if you if you don't mind,
we'll hold you over till the next hour, because I'm sure you have something else to add, right?
I have a few other thoughts. Yes. All right. You could entertain it and entertain us if you want.
Yeah. With him. Yeah. I mean, if you want to try and squeeze something in now, let's do that. But
but I do want to, you know, make sure we can hold you over because I like where you're going. So
let's let's just do that. And even if we didn't like where he was going, if it was true, we had
to accept it. So there you go. Well, that's it. So I have put you back on hold. And we have to put
the show on hold because it's time to take a break here on Ocelli and the Greek, which is being
broadcast from American Freedom Radio. Stick around. There may be more reports to come.
Second hour begins of this particular sonic event called Ocelli and the Greek. And you know,
it is incumbent upon us, I believe, to let you know how it is you can reach out and touch this
particular event. First of all, you could, if you wish, when you're listening to the show and archive
or whatever, reach out to the Greek directly via email by going to where Greek Uncommon Radio.
It is a courtesy website. So put in www.uncommonradio.com. Just you spell it just like
it sounds. And you will see it's basically a courtesy website, a list of links you can click
on for archives that have been posted by others and a contact box and an email so we can or the
Greek can see what you have to say or write. And that's pretty much it on that. And you have one
as well, ocelli.com, I believe, right? Yes, at ocelli.com. Comments are always welcome.
There is a contact form there as well. It does get to me one way or another. However,
in case you are hearing this live, or you think about it next time you want to come on live,
there's other ways to get in touch with us as well. Directly during the show,
there is the Skype convention. If you utilize that, go ahead and tell them that one Greek.
Ocelli and the Greek, how you spell it just like it sounds O-C-H-E-L-L-I for Ocelli
and the Greek. And request a contact, I will grab you as a contact and bring you in on air. And
Chuck, you have the landline supposedly? Yes, at the moment it sure does appear that I do,
and I still have the caller on the line from the last hour who I'm going to add right in.
And you could also come on into the discussion as well by using that thing they call a telephone
and dialing 218-339-8525. 218-339-8525. And what you have to do is enter 2012 or 2012
after you are connected in order to join in and I will add you in. So with that, I want to go back
to the caller. And we may revisit this information later in the discussion, but I want to go back to
the caller right away who was holding at the 574 area code. So can you hear me all right?
Yes, I can. Okay, all right, we'll continue. Please.
Well, from apart from what I just said, I just have a few topics that I've written down during
the break that I would like to pick your brains on. Most of it is related to what I just said.
Are you guys okay with that? Oh, yeah, go for it. Absolutely.
Awesome. Well, I mentioned how the major Western religions have attempted to forcibly
get everybody else to see things in their way via violence, the Crusades, Inquisition,
etc., etc. With the Jews in the Exodus, they were told to kill everybody in the land that
they were invading. Every man, woman, and child is actually very ungodly.
Sorry if I interject while you're speaking, just so we kind of keep things on a certain track.
There were no Jews back then. You will find no Jews, Christian or Hindu or anything like that
in these ancient texts. All the ancient texts refer to people by their family line or aka blood
line. I have discussed why that was done. Let me just interject a secret. Have you ever heard how
there's a lot of these moronic commentators that are academic and they say it was a different God
of the Old Testament, different God of the New Testament? Well, it was the same God and it was
actually the Christ himself that did that. Do you remember I had given several times with you,
Chuck, and others why they were told to do that? Because the people were unrehabilitatable. I
have given an example on how we would take a windy walk through a Canaanite or Phoenician village
and what the goings-on were with the bestiality, the human sacrifice, and all the other things.
These people said we would rather die than this change and they were just simply accommodated.
So, go on. That's much the way that our world is right now. I guess the main point I was trying
to get at is how does that tie in with the Nephilim and the supposed giants that were around?
Okay. The Nephilim were simply a hybrid because, again, in the King James you have an erroneous
translation. It doesn't say, for example, in the King James it would say that the sons of the gods
took the daughters of man and they were the Nephilim. So, right there is a hybrid. It doesn't
say, well, sons of Elohim, the gods, meaning Ben or the protege of the gods, yes, took the
daughters of men. It wasn't men. It was the daughters of Adam. So, it's delineating a very
specific line of Adam, right? I've also explained loosely that these gods, they're the builder
gods. They're the ones that are basically the subcontractors on a construction project, right?
Like you have the plumbers, the carpenters, or whatever. These gods were in control of forming
things that we see as the various aspects of nature, including the elementals. When they
have offspring, their offspring are not born of a woman. They come into fruition as males,
full grown, and they have a thousand year plus lifespan. You can look at some ancient texts.
If you see sometimes people are addressed, you, born of a woman. Have you ever heard of that in
literature? Or you, man, born of a woman. Why would you address someone as such? Isn't it
obvious that everyone's born from a woman? Not really. If you've also heard of certain lore,
literary, and other where these people lived a really long time. The problem with living a long
time like that is if you're living in a neighborhood for 50 or 70 years and it doesn't
look like you've aged a day, people start asking questions. So, you have to pack up and move every
decade or two, don't you? This is stuff that will come more factual in the future. There are
plenty of these characters around. Now, the Nephilim were a hybrid because these sons of
gods are 100% genetically compatible with human women, let's just say, or the ones that are
descended from Adam. One of the two characteristics of the Nephilim are that they're typically
polydectile, meaning six fingers and six toes, or they're very large in size.
All right? So, that's the hybrid gene line or hereditary line that you see there.
So, thank you for letting me fill in just so, as you're going along, we're just filling in. So,
continue, unless I derailed you. Oh, no, you're fine. I guess getting off of that topic and jumping
to the next one that I have written down here, would you say that the Eastern traditions are
more along the line of how human society should be structured? No, not at all. That is a typical,
you see, this is a Western convention. You know, like in academia, this is known as the Christian
era, meaning the whole globe, right? The whole planet. So, there's basically a Western convention
that has been overlaid over the entire society on the planet. And what happens is, if you're
Western or not, and you're paying attention to the current convention, you'll be in utter disgust
with all the mainstream religions. So, you think, well, let me go Eastern. But what happens when a
lot of Westerners, it's very popular starting in the 60s for a lot of Westerners to abandon
the Western traditions and go for Eastern traditions, but they approach them reading
into them what they wanted, as opposed to seeing what they were based on also. They're just as bad.
And I don't go into detail because with what the Easterners are doing, because
typically, I'm presuming that we're addressing a predominantly Western audience. Would you say so,
Chuck? Predominantly? Yeah, predominantly, sure. Yeah. So, if you look at a lot of,
sometimes they're even more worse. If you look at people that have, quote unquote,
discovered Buddhism or Hinduism and all that, they're even more in the dark than those that
are wrestling with the Western convention, because they just want to get away. It's just
like in the 50s, they started putting out all the space age stuff to people to kind of have them
wander on, oh, there might be something out there, so you can't focus on what's going on here.
So, anyway, we could probably do a very factual reference-based show maybe on what the Eastern
traditions should be based on and what they're actually doing, if they profess that they're
something. But I haven't met anyone in the West Eastern traditions that knows anything in the
texts or what's been memorialized about their religion, period. Not even Easterners. So,
go ahead. So, basically, they're just as erroneous as all the Westerners. Yes. Yes,
I gave you the explanation why there's a viewpoint on that. For example, they say cars pollute,
right? So, let's get a hybrid, right? Because that's a hybrid, the engine doesn't run as long,
got electrical running, which doesn't pollute. But what people fail to notice that when a
combustion engine warms up, the emissions go down. And when it's cold, the emissions are very high.
That's why when you first start a lawnmower or a car, you smell the emissions, right? And when
it warms up, you don't as much. These little hybrids that are going around town with the
engines cold, even though they're small engines, they're spewing out more unburned fuel than the
big cars that are warmed up. So, then again, there you go, you see. And also, they want 5,000
bucks for replacing the batteries every five years. So, either way, yeah. Do you get the point
there? Yeah, I do. Yeah, they go to the Eastern traditions from the Western, it's just as toxic,
but they can tell everyone that they've gone over to the Eastern, they get a pat on the back,
right? So, it looks a little different. I mean, it's much like the political adherence,
it's the same thing. Oh, this looks different, even though it's really just all part of the same
charade. Escape. Yeah, it's escape to psychological to protect the mind. Otherwise,
you just feel like you're locked in a box with this garbage around you. So, anyway. Yeah, so
continue. Anything else? Yeah, one more thing. Back in the last Sonic episode that I listened
to, which was actually today that you guys put on, you had mentioned the metaphor of the racetrack,
where the starting line is also the finishing line, and everything comes back in a circle,
right? And you had mentioned the manifestation of the old gods. And then you briefly mentioned
something about a new temple that was built to Odin somewhere in the Nordic land. Iceland?
Yeah, well, they've officially acknowledged that they don't mind reviving that religion.
And there are many people in agreement to it, and they're actually going to base it on something
versus the Christian thing, which is based on nothing. But what I mean, based on nothing,
if you speak to a Christian, they'll tell you what it's based on. But if you try to look up
what they're saying, where they tell you it should be, you won't find it. So, anyway, yeah,
this is sad. But yeah, so go ahead about the Icelanders. Yeah. Well, yeah, I guess my point
was, instead of looking to the Bible, or what we call the Bible, for a prophecy of how the world
will pass into a new age via, you talked about two asteroids and the sun exploding or something
like that. What if we're looking at the wrong area of the world? If the Nords are already
showing a manifestation of the old gods in the old ways, what's to say that it won't come to
fruition, it will come full circle over in that part of the world, as opposed to the Middle East
and the Middle Eastern Union that is supposedly supposed to come about?
Okay, okay, let me just clarify, because you kind of answered yourself in a way indirectly.
Civilization started in the Middle East, what's called the Middle East, not near Iceland.
And that's acknowledged by both, any side you look at, even the crap conventional education
system tells you the civilization started between the Tigris and Euphrates, Mesopotamia.
And so, and it goes on from there. That's where man was deposited after he was made, let's say,
right? Although there are a lot of people, and this was, I'm not looking to the chat room very
much, but there are a lot of people who would contend that on the African continent is where
man seems to have sprung from, you know, all across the planet, ever after. How does that work?
Because if civilization began in the Middle East, the Middle East is not Africa, right?
Well, while the African continent also is that entire landmass is attached,
if you disregard some canals, right, that all those landmasses were connected, you could walk
from the top right, you know, Russia, all the way down to the bottom tip of Africa.
It's all land connected until the canal was built there, right? There's a, the thing is,
there's a lot of people that could say a lot of things. There's a, on the continent of Australia,
they, the indigenous people there have some story about that, but you can't find it.
So, there's a lot of reports. The thing is, are you, what level of reporting are you looking for?
Like in the military intelligence, when they take in all the information, they grade it. This
is grade A level reporting. This is B, this is C, right? It goes down. So, I would consider solely
the claim that it's on what's called the African continent to be a low level report,
even though all reports should be considered, right? And I'm not here, when you report,
you can't make stuff up unless you're doing fake news. But anyway.
Well, that's true. So, back to you, Caller, any other things you wanted to cover or?
Yeah, just one. And I'm glad the conversation went this way because I want to
ask if you guys have ever heard of the, what's called the Bach Saga, that's B-O-C-K Saga.
No. Enlighten us on it. If it's worth it.
It is, apparently it is a, I don't know, for better, for lack of a better term,
it's an alternative history that has been passed down orally for millions, if not billions of years.
And apparently this person that came out with the information in 1984, by the name of Eor Bach,
it's I-O-G Bach, B-O-C-K, has had this history in his family for at least a thousand years.
And it's an oral tradition. It's not a written tradition. So, you won't find it memorialized in
the texts of the ancients, the Greeks, the Egyptians, what have you. And what they say is
basically before the earth was tilted on 23 degree angle towards the sun, it was upright. And I'm not
going to go into it now, but there's a whole other lineage of history.
Now, the interesting thing to consider, alternative can be defined as something meaning better.
And if I look at everything considered alternative, I don't necessarily see it being better, but it's
sideways. So, that's fine. It would need to be investigated and somehow
see what kind of weight it has. But I assure you at this point, it would be considered something
that would be more of entertainment value. I don't mean to be dogmatic on that, because one of the
ways to validate a good information is that it requires belief that things that are stated will
happen as stated. It's like, for example, if I... Now, belief shouldn't be based on... A lot of
people in the conventional religions say, I believe. Well, so what? We'll believe in what?
They can't tell you. They'll bring up some figure. That's why, for example, when people
send emails that say Jesus, I'm like, you lost me with the Jesus thing, because there's like 14 of
them and none of them are scriptural. So, you have to be more specific of which one of the 14 Jesus
is, or are you talking about the scriptural Christ? And by the way, if you know who the biblical
Christ is, you probably... I mean, that's a secret. I mean, you probably also know the nuclear launch
codes. So, you see, so it's really difficult subject matter, but if he's got what's called
prophecy in there that comes true, yeah, it's going to be something to be reckoned with.
And what I mean by that is, let's say I tell you, you know, here's a string of numbers, and if you
go to this building in the back, and you'll see a safe, and you put these numbers in, you'll open
the safe and get the treasure in there. So, on the way, before you do that, you believe that
you have everything you need for this to happen. So, if they don't give... one of the ways to
signify good information is prophetic. And that's actually stated in most of the definitions of
what makes something worth memorializing. Okay. I have a question for the caller,
actually, though. Are you talking about the alternative history that describes this character
named Thoth and the Atlanteans versus the people that came from Mars? Is that the history you're
talking about? Nothing to do with people that come from Mars, but Thoth, definitely, and Atlantis, yes.
There's all explanations for all of that in the Bach Saga, which is why I wanted to, you know,
nobody else knows about this that I've talked to, so I thought I'd pick you guys' brains.
Yeah, there's a... okay, I wouldn't really knock it, but let me just put some heresy in here.
Personally, I wouldn't go down that path. For me, it might be for someone else. You know, like
skydiving and roller coasters make me miserable, but those things are still very popular, right? So,
who am I to tell someone what they should do or not? But I would suggest that, if it makes you
happy, go for it, but I don't see... when you start talking about millions and billions and all that,
yeah, and there's nothing really in there that's telling you what's going to happen. I'm not
saying that you should solely be based on prophecy, because here's the ultimate way to look at
the way society is structured, that your rules, meaning your law, comes from your God, and if it's
not chock-full of laws, you know, do this, do that, and with discernment, that's very low-level
information. It doesn't mean it's wrong, you know, it's just low-level information.
I'm not, like, an advocate for the Bach saga at all, but I'm always...
That's fine to bring it up, yeah.
I consider myself a student of all viewpoints.
Oh, yeah.
I don't, I don't...
The thing is, you should discern it, like, for example, you know, when a movie comes out,
they say, oh, it made a hundred million this month, I mean, this week, that means it's good?
No, I don't think so. Is it a good movie or not, right? Is the information, whether it's
alternative or mainstream, is it good? Is it based on something? Can it be validated? How is it
qualitatively? And I like to stress the qualitative point, because you've got billions of people,
or a billion plus, in most of these mainstream religions. It doesn't matter how many people
believe in something or do something, what's the quality of it? And I just, I think I want to stress
the quality, because that's where discernment comes in.
Right. Now, look, I've seen the story that I think that the caller's referring to, though,
linked to Mars, like I said, linked to the Emerald Tablets, linked to various things about Egypt.
I've seen this told in a lot of interesting ways, and it's a little confusing to try and
track down what the actual source is here. Now, I would say that an orally preserved tradition
is not something to be discounted, though. No, no, but what's the quality of it? See,
what would give something value or a lens to be discounted is the quality of the information. So,
yes, if the quality of the information is high, and can be validated with your own eyes and with
your own interaction with it, you know, if it says, do this and this will happen, or do this
and this, that will happen, and if you can prove it out, then, yeah, it's good. It has to be
qualitative. There's a lot of, I shouldn't say it like this, but the Internet is, you know,
you're at the point still in the history of the Internet that it's just basically a microphone
check. You're going to have to sift through a lot of stuff. And also, I'm sure this would have
probably been around before what's called the inane net, but always look for the quality of
something, you know, quality of the reporting, which doesn't really seem to matter to most
people anymore. So, but yeah, let's not, I would not necessarily discount it, but it's not,
for the Greek, I don't see it as being something I would want to pursue. But you know what,
if you want to pursue and extrapolate based on the few basic things that might sound dogmatic,
but the essence of it is, is that mankind's operating system comes from his God, right?
And also, does it give you history of the past and history of the future? See, when man records
history, he writes about the past. When the gods record history, they write about the future.
And are there gods there? Are they using proper terminology referring to the other society that
we call the ones or the gods or the Elohim or, you see, so there's many levels of discerning
something, you know, it's a QC, quality check or quality control. QA. Yeah, QC or whatever,
QA, yeah, just quality check it. Yeah. Yeah, which is very hard to do with a purely oral
tradition that's passed down. It's hard to, to qualify that or to quantify that.
Yeah, but if you want to get lascivious, purely oral is good sometimes too. But anyway,
okay. Okay. Yeah, I okay. That's lasciviousness. What am I gonna say? I'm certainly not going to
disagree with you. You know, is there is there any other point you wanted to bring out or something
you wanted to add here, caller? Oh, yeah, he's doing fine. Or is he still there? Okay.
Oh, I was I was hoping but okay, well, perhaps something has gone wrong with his particular
phone because it seems to still be there. But not hearing him. Yeah. And also just to
Yeah, if we don't have maybe just want to kiss his noise or anything, take care of that. But
there's a lot of this escapism that's important to consider. Instead of a, you know, I mentioned
in the 50s and 60s, they said, Look, there's space aliens and all this other stuff to get people
focusing out there instead of what's going on right here. And then they have the people,
the Westerners leaving the Western Convention for an Eastern Convention. And nowhere are they
paying attention. You know, when you have a pressure vessel, if you want to maintain its
structure or keep the liability of it exploding low, you put in a pressure relief valve.
So there's, there's plenty of things to, but both to get entertained or dummy load yourself with.
But, and I'm not saying that this particular thing is a dummy load, but it just has all the
earmarks of it, by the way was described. But you when the dummy load becomes the predominant,
like, for example, it you know, how in the beginning hour, we discussed, you know,
what's going on in the United States of America in terms of money, politics, science, education,
and all this other stuff. When you start bringing up information that anyone can access as being
what something is should be founded on, they'll give you a million reasons why it's not that,
but they'll never address what you're saying. You see, they can't go there.
Well, you know, on this show, I've definitely addressed a lot of what you're saying and not
attacked the foundation of it. But I do have a question at this point in time. And it might sound
a bit, you know, adversarial, but I think it's a fair question. You talk about the, the claims
that are made in the text, right? And are they reasonable? And we've gone over how, you know,
a legal claim, someone nails a notice to your door, you have to pay attention to it, because it has
you've been given notice, right? Right. Or you don't have to pay attention to it and see what
happens. Right. Well, okay, fair enough. Right. But what is to say that that legal notice is
legitimate? In other words, could it not be that something that's been memorialized is also
just a fiction? In general? Sure, that's that's simple. Let's say you get a legal notice,
it'll have points of authority, you know, though, even journalists use the who, what,
where, where and why, right kind of thing. And you could actually look up the points of authority
that are listed there. And you'll find them in other places as well. But historically,
immemorialized as such. But that doesn't stop. But that doesn't stop someone from doing what
would we call it? Let's see. What do they call it when they duplicate money? Let's just say,
they call that, you know, when you make counterfeiting, so what's to say that this
is not a counterfeit or legitimate claim? How would one prove that you use discernment,
just like with the counterfeit, they got the little white thing you put under it,
and you look at it real close. Right? If you look at it with an eye loop, or you get about 10
magnification on, you'll see it. But the thing is, maybe let me just take your the question
a little further, what would you compare it to? Because with a counterfeit note,
you might have one that's, let's say, not counterfeit. And they usually just define
one as being counterfeit through comparative analysis. Because at a glance, it looks pretty
good, right? Right. So the same with these legal claims at a glance, they look pretty good,
but we have nothing else to look at it with Dewey, what the actual text provides it,
and it gives you the points of and people I think know what text we're talking about here.
So it's the only text on the planet that has those kinds of claims, by the way. So
it actually provides that Do you remember, I think, in the last few times we've met, I said
that people you have no right to extract a notion, a term or something out of a given body of work,
where it's being defined, and then change its definition or define or ignore that definition,
right? That's understood. But there are other given bodies of work that you would say are
illegitimate. Even though they have a claim in them, they've been memorialized, right?
There is no other claim like them. That one, but the question,
hold on, Chuck, the question, they don't go as high, though.
They don't go as high. So then you see what I mean? And high in terms of the
level of extreme, the extreme level of claim that's being made.
You see, so that's, that's an interest. That's a good question. But if you start looking at it,
you will see that there's a hierarchy again, that's most extreme, right? In this particular
one versus the others, which are more mild mannered, and less discernible. And the thing
is, the definitions that are held within their keep itself contained. And also there's a numeric
system. If anyone wants to look up Ivan Panin, P-A-N-I-N, he had done some studies on the text
and the numerical codes behind the words. Still, even today with all the supercomputers,
couldn't compile it. And it shows that there's a fingerprint of some form of intelligence that
is beyond what man is capable of. And it doesn't mean that, let's go back to the question you
asked, that that couldn't even be counterfeited or created fictionally by someone with not just
two pencils in their pocket, but 100 pencils in their pocket. Back in the days, that's how they
used to define engineers. You know, if you had more than two or three pencils, you're a pretty
good engineer, you know, in your pocket. Remember the slide? Anyway, okay, so, so yeah, that's,
so, but ultimately, here's the thing. These are a lot of questions that someone may not want to
spend a lot of time on because life's too short. Have you heard that? Life's too short, man.
But if you had a much longer lifespan, you would see how these things pan out.
True enough. Yeah.
Yeah. Doubt is, doubt is a good thing, but it has to be doubt based on discernment,
doubt based on something. When you doubt something, or have skepticism about something,
you still have to have something to base that skepticism about. Show up with a guide rule.
You know, if someone, if you go to a construction site and someone says, I've got this board here,
it's eight feet long, and you kind of look at it and you're skeptic, that's a little short for
eight feet. Hold on. Do you tell them that's not eight feet and you start arguing back and forth,
or does someone have to pull out a tape measure and use it to measure it?
Right. Eventually.
And, but all I see going on is carpenters cutting wood and they're really upset. And I say, why are
you so upset? This is why I cut this board three times. It's still too short. I think you need to,
you're going in the wrong direction.
Right. So the caller on the line, I think has lost connection for being able to speak to us.
So I'm going to drop them off the line. If you want to call back in, you can do that.
I just got a message that said I was unmuted. So I guess I must have been muted for a while.
Please continue.
There you are. There you are. Okay. Go ahead. Excellent. Go ahead and continue if you want
to continue. Yeah.
Yeah. Just one more off the wall topic here for both of you guys. There seems to be two
differing views when it comes to quote unquote aliens. Some people think that there is a wide
universe and we're not stuck in a dome, which the biblical text says that we are. And
Not anymore.
There are races out there.
Go ahead.
And then the opposing view would be that all of the aliens are actually demons
flying around in saucers and whatnot. What are your thoughts on that?
I think I've discussed this. Electrogravitics started with a guy named J.J. Thompson in 1895,
where he showed mass and weight is, weight and momentum is not part of mass. It's electrical
lines of force that attach things that give the illusion that a brick hitting you on the head
is heavier than a feather. And they were able to, by the 30s and certain parts of what they
call 1930s, have almost mastered that. And they're not sharing it. The word demon just
means something spiritual, typically with a negative connotation, the way it's being used.
There's a lot of stuff about aliens. You got to realize the majority of alien talk has come
out of a certain level of propaganda. And whenever aliens are trying to be validated
or alien suppression is trying to be validated, there's always some kind of quote-unquote
pseudo-military government involvement. And if you understand how the military documents things,
if you are not part of the national government or national citizenry, you're dubbed an alien.
So a lot of the paperwork that came out of the 40s and 50s and such, when they talked about
retrieving alien craft and all that, it just means it wasn't American because it's all military
paperwork. And that's how they speak. They don't speak. It's like legalese. When you say certain
words, they don't mean what you think. And just like in the military. So this is a big subject.
But essentially, we can answer it many ways. And if you want to give the Greeks personal opinion
on that, no, there are no aliens as such as people have been propagandized to believe.
But there are beings that are not seen and not tangible in this reality. Just like, for example,
you have the visible spectrum. There's a physical spectrum, the sound spectrum,
ultrasonic, subsonic. And you have infrared on one end of the visible spectrum and ultraviolet
on the other. There's also something with thought. And it's super-sensible or sub-sensible.
And humans are very mid-range thinkers. They don't comprehend complex. They don't
comprehend simple. And then even beyond the complex, you have the super-sensible.
And below that is sub-sensible. So if you look, instead of looking at what else can interact with
us, look at how humans are interacting. What are their limitations? Well, the other thing to consider
here, too, though, is that you can't say that there's not some life that does not simply reside
here. Right. So in a very technical sense, there are aliens in truth. Now, the nature of those
things is another thing. That is not correct. Yes. But there is other life, of course. Right.
Yeah. To say that the humans or the animal species and all the even though the massive
variety that's on this planet is the only life around is absurd, really. But what we're being
told, and I think during the first hour I explained, you know, the leadership of any
country, because what I said about the United States of America applies to most countries,
you have no money, you have no courts, you have no medical system, you have no education,
on and on and on. So why would you have any information about aliens? I mean, that doesn't
mean I should plausibly carry it over. But if we that's another discussion. And also, there's
something called the alternative thinking alternative movement, which is not alternative
at all, because I believe the term alternative means a better choice. I think it's just a step
a move sideways to just dummy load the people. So but here's the thing, the beauty of it is now,
many of these discussions, especially with the color that we've had, these are topics that have
been, let's say, kicked around for years and decades, right? And when you consider the amount
of time that's left, and what is going to be known after that it is so close, that it's almost best
to be patient. And again, set yourself apart, make sure you got good food, good drink, good
conversation, and, and be pleasant, be good to your body. So your mind can be in a good state.
And, and then go on from there, you know, and have you must have discernment.
You know, you know, in another, in other words, you're not going to, if you start taking in
everything without discerning it, or QC and quality control or whatever, you're just taking
stuff in. I mean, how much can you handle? Right. And a couple of other solid things
that were related to what we were just discussing came in. So I want to interject them.
First of all, where in the text does it mention the dome? First of all, does it specifically
mention that? And secondly, you said really quickly there, well, not anymore, as if we were
once in a dome, so to speak, when I'm using the we, so we understand each other. Sure.
But we were once in a dome, but now we're not in a dome. So those two things I would
like you to address to the musical notations are based on planetary positions. And up until
many changes, and I guess even a few hundred years ago, musical notations were carried by
something called thorough base. And then they went back and adopted something else that we have now.
And there's the resonance of the spheres and things like that. If you look at a lot of the
what's out there, the way it's been memorialized doesn't really correlate to the way we we look
at things now. They had telescopes and microscopes back then, they called them looking glasses.
So things were very different. Around what's called the flood account, one of the things that
brought the flood was that the windows of heaven were broken or opened. And the term that's being
used there is not metaphor. It means there was something there that came down. The other thing,
you want me to stretch it a little bit? I'll stretch it. I don't really like to go on this
topic too much, because I haven't spent enough to really tie it all together. But let's just tie
half the shoelaces here. There's something called the green glass in Sahara. If you go in the Sahara
desert, you can look anywhere and you'll find this green glass. It looks like melted coke bottles.
Now, typically, that type of fusion either happens with what's called thermonuclear,
or it happens by typical glasses found when there's typically an asteroid hit on the Earth.
And the thing is, though, this type of glass doesn't have the trace elements,
like the platinum group metals, the platinum, rhodium, osmium, ruthenium,
and iron that you find in most green glass that is based on an asteroid hit. But it has all the
characteristics of something impacting the Earth. So typically, when a rock made of iron or nickel,
all these other things, create these platinum group metals on impact that you find in the
glass all over these craters. But this seems to have been an impact of something that was not
made of anything other than maybe a big block of ice hitting the ground. Imagine.
Would a big block of ice hitting something so hard create a thermonuclear reaction,
almost intense heat, plasma, that would fuse glass? And if it did so, would it leave trace
elements? No. Maybe some hydrogen and oxygen. So this is a loose thing of some evidence of
things happening. And also, when we discuss the flood, it didn't really happen on the planet all
at one time. It would be as if you were looking at the weather reports in Europe right now, if you're
in the States, and they're in a complete deluge. And then like a week later, the U.S. is in a
deluge. And then the East, as you see, it goes around the planet, right?
So wouldn't a large block of ice, theoretically, because here I am with theoretical, but
theoretically, a large block of ice striking anything of a different substance with enough
violence, couldn't that cause a wholly different type of reaction that could be similar to the
friction that was required to create some of these other, you know, explosive reactions?
Isn't that a possibility? Sure. Well, glass being fused is an intense fit. If you study ballistics,
what really happens when you have something with an armament piercing a target at the point of
contact initially, that material goes to gas, you know, the one that is not as dense, right?
It vaporizes and then continues until the momentum is lost, right? So yeah, this is like, so this is
something, this is for people who want to carry a little forward with it. But there's these things
will be known, by the way, during when you're not sure about where a scene was shot, or who wrote
what in a script of a movie, guess what, you just wait for the credits, and most likely they're gonna
what, show it to you, right? So we've discussed how we're in the credits. But yeah, there's much
to talk about. I'd like to just focus, it's kind of good to throw little tidbits out like that.
And it's because it's all about state of mind. But what kind of a state of mind do you have if
you can't discern things? So there you go. Well, there you go. And anyway, you know, one last time
to the very same caller has been quite the trooper here, for lack of a better term.
Is there anything else you want to add in here? No, not you run me fresh out of ideas to talk
about. So thank you for letting me join in. And I hope to speak to you guys soon again.
Yeah, well, likewise. Yeah. Thank you for calling. Absolutely.
I'll hang up now and you guys can finish the last 20 or so minutes of the show now.
Thanks. And please come back again. So yeah, that was that was pretty good. It was insightful.
That's very much like a lot of the message, the private messaging that I get. It's on point. It's
not just like, I think during the break, we were discussing, you know, ask someone, how does that
taste? And like, it's good. Like, it doesn't tell you anything, you know, right? Maybe, you know,
so well, I like it, you know, I like for this to be a little salty. It's the right temperature.
It seems like it was prepared well, and it tastes fresh, you know, so yeah, so we this is, you know,
this is, it's good to have, because it incites more of the mindset of discernment, you know,
to, and the thing is, asking questions is good. It's also good to ask the answer.
You know, you want to also when you do research, try to find those that are of like mind, not
necessarily like the same things you do. But if you're looking to study a subject, find others
that are similar, have expertise or done a lot of work in a similar subject, like, for example,
Chuck with JFK, you don't necessarily need to seek out and other many other people that studied the
JFK assassination, but you might want to seek out a ballistics expert, right? That just absolutely
knows nothing about the JFK, but is good, right? Because that allows you his work to give you more
understanding about your work. Oh, yeah, perfect. A perfect example of that is when I was studying
the x rays. I did not seek out someone who was an expert on the case, I sought out someone who
works in the x ray field, I saw technicians to speak to, I sought out people that read these
things, so that they could give me their benefit of their experience, essentially. So that's what I
did. Yeah. And just for the audience, I've been in medical establishments, so many times that
sometimes I'd walk in regarding someone to inquire, and I see three or four doctors standing around
with x rays on the wall. So what do you guys don't know? We have to wait for someone to come and read
these. And I was like, What do you mean? Don't you? I mean, I just it's an x ray. Well, you know,
these, you need someone who understands the subtleties of reading an x ray. You know, even the
most experienced doctors stand and wait around for someone I see. So just just for the audience in
case they did not know. Yeah, I mean, and the thing is that I would turn around and take the
assertions of one x ray technician, and then actually compare them to another without ever
revealing to them what it is they were looking at just telling them, look, this is an x ray.
What do you see? You know, interpret for me what it is that you see. And in that way, I'm getting
sort of a blind. What do they call that a blind result, right? Right. Kind of kind of ironic, but
a blind result from someone interpreting just the evidence in hand, as opposed to interjecting any
other viewpoint into it. Let's bring up something real quick. How do you know that's not a counterfeit
x ray? Well, you know, I did the best I could to make sure that the source was legitimate.
And how do you how do you know it's legitimate? Because when you look at something as legitimate,
it's another whole, a whole other set of rules, again, regardless, regardless of the topic,
right? All right. And custody and all that. Yeah, exactly. Authenticity. And generally speaking,
what it comes down to at the end of the day is that you're unless you were there yourself,
you're accepting the word and the record based on what is presented to you. So this person says they
the x ray. This person says they developed it. This person says they read it, you know, so on and
so forth. It appears to be the subject in the x ray is correct. You also have to know beyond that
also, like for just to throw this in, there was a certain person in the media, also a leader
and his birth certificate, birth certificate issued to him was in question. And when I first
saw the subject, it took me about 10 seconds to see that it was what the people complaining
about it was, it was not true. And but the reason that I gave was not what they were saying. And the
reason I gave is because when the time this man was born, there was no such thing as Kenya,
it was called something else. So that's your first clue, you don't need to investigate anymore.
You see my point. So when you start looking at things too closely, this myopic thing, sometimes
you don't have to, right? But you but the more you look, the better it gets. Usually, if you see
the one, if you miss the 800 pound gorilla, you still might find a little speck of dust
under the rug. But you can't discount that there's an 800 pound gorilla in the room.
Yeah, we often find that people state that they made, you know, post posthumously to the event
state that they went to a town. And if you go ahead and check, you might find that that town
didn't exist at the time they claim they made that particular trip, or it was named something else.
Which is another interesting thing, it doesn't fit. And therefore their claim starts to fall
apart. Because I got to tell you, I wouldn't remember something in reverse like that.
You know, if they had used some previous name for the place, that's a possibility.
So you have to take in all the information. And people say, Well, I don't have the time for that.
No, all you have is time, you have to make the time just and also, the more you learn to take
in more, the more the easier it is to do that. Just like when you go to the gym for the first day,
you mean I'm going to sit and lift all these weights on all these machines, eventually,
the first day, you'll just spend 15 minutes on one or two machines, you'll be sore as heck.
But in about a year, you'll be able to operate on all of them as much as you like, right. So
it's like building a muscle, this investigative stuff, you do have to look at everything. It
sounds overwhelming in the beginning. But if you're atrophied, you're going to have to bring
yourself to walk and then become an athlete. Right now, most people will. Correctly, you know,
if you took anyone sitting on a couch with a six pack and say, Hey, go jump, go jump into the
Olympics for the 150 yard run. They'll say no, but there are actually some people that think they can
write and that's why things don't get done. But so you do have to take in everything.
Well, as best you can, because at some point, quite honestly, there's always some level of
you're not going to like this, you can't always be fully objective. Because there is some subjective
things built into this. Why do I say that? Well, look, you weren't there in a lot of cases, right?
I wasn't there in a lot of cases, I have to rely on certain claims that are made.
Okay, and check that as best I can. But truthfully, at the end of the day, I have to believe that the
National Archives is legitimate source for sources, right? I have to believe that these
things that have been presented to me and all of the past conventions for authenticity makes sense.
If I don't believe any of that, well, it's all out the window and none of them.
Well, there's the word again, believe if you if you believe in something, eventually, you're going
to have to take some time aside and see why you believe that and confirm it. Otherwise, that belief
is unfounded. So then you're going to have to go and look at the quality that's and the truthfulness
of the, let's use that word of the National Archives. So here's the truthfulness of the
National Archives, by the way, one of the legal definitions legal because this is a legal society
of archive means that it has no more force in effect. So have you heard there's a certain
document that this country was founded on that where is it the national what right?
Yes, it is. So that means it has no more force in effect. That's one of the definitions of archiving
something. So be wary of that. But anyway, that's the way they see it. They let you talk as if it is
and you meaning whoever you are, which is actually the legitimate reason why there is a 75 year
hold on allowing the public to view anything in the National Archives in most cases, because
it's no longer in force or effect by the time 75 years has gone by because it doesn't relate
to a living person, generally speaking. Right. But if you had a lifespan of 500,
it would because that would be roughly 10 years, let's say, or 15. Yeah.
You know, that's another thing folks to discuss. I think we have briefly is lifespan. It does have
a bearing on the way we perceive things. So and if you could start objectifying that even,
you will see that the importance of good reporting and finding things that are good,
good information and objectivity or things that have been memorialized,
you'll find even more value in them when you appreciate how short life is.
So and before we go Greek, because we are going to run out of time pretty quickly. I think we've
gone quite a bit around a great many different topics that do interlock tonight, that's for sure.
But and dropped dropped a few interesting hints that, like you said, you wouldn't normally have
discussed a year ago. OK, go back and review in case you missed them. Right. Money system and
all these other things, perhaps. Yeah. Things that aren't really complete in to be presented.
That's all right. But the thing is that I do want to hit a little bit of current business,
which is that American Freedom Radio has a donate button on American Freedom Radio dot com.
And it does help if people feel compelled to do something with that, contribute to it. That's for
sure. And it's it's easy to find if you can navigate the Internet, which you obviously can
because you're hearing this show. So well, here's the thing. If so many people that do like the
station and what you're doing are not contributing, how about we just tell the people who don't like
it maybe should contribute as well? Maybe maybe the people who like it shouldn't contribute
because it doesn't seem like they're being very active. How about the ones you guys that don't
like it? I know you're listening. Go ahead and contribute. I think that's let's not be
let's be more inclusive. So anyway. Oh, yeah. Yeah. So let's be as inclusive and let's be
objective about it. It does the same thing, whether you appreciate it or you don't appreciate
it. If you send funds to keep us going, then you'll have a good excuse for not liking something.
You know, so, you know, you know, the the like I say, quote, unquote, the money is never in the
solution. It's always in the problem. Right. You know, your cures for cancer, cure this for that
war on this war and that, you know, there's you know, if these things that's why in school they
only teach theory, no conclusion because there's nothing, you know, it seems like there are things
being open ended to our quote, unquote, more profitable than things coming to a conclusion
or being sewed up anyway. Yeah. Yeah, that's the truth. And of course, you can also contribute to
get me a cup of coffee because I'm have to stay awake for the rest of the night doing some work
at Ocelli Dotcom, Ocelli Dotcom. There may be some other places you can go in the future
to contribute in one way or another. Another way to contribute is at Uncommon Radio. Now,
what you do there is contribute your thoughts, your experiences, so on and so forth through that
contact form. We discussed that earlier as well. And is there anything else we should add before
we kind of depart from this particular sonic event, Greek? Yeah, but here's, you know, what
mentioned earlier, you notice there's an underlying theme that whenever you and I come together,
whenever you hear the Greek speaking, the Greek speak, there's an underlying theme. And the theme
is have discernment. No one's paying attention. Don't don't look to what the next guy is doing.
But at the same time, if half the people in the world helped one person, the whole world is taken
care of. Set yourself apart. There's there's constantly the underlying theme. Setting
yourself apart is as simple as insulating yourself from things that are ambiguous,
that may do harm. It's the same stuff over and over and over. Why? Because it's important and
it works. Why discuss things that don't work? And yeah, you're not going to make friends with this
kind of talk, by the way. If you feel inspired to pursue on your own time, whoever you are,
the things that are being discussed here, you will really find out who your friends and loved ones
are. So I mean that sarcastically. Yeah. And if you're around wooden headed people, just smile.
And you could look up what wooden headed means. And basically, the theme is over and over. We've
had a lot of interesting titles to some of these sonic events, the container, the dummy load
and other things like that. We have little catchphrases that are efficient ways of
communicating ideas. And these things are seem to be an underlying theme. And then I just wanted
to recap that. No, absolutely. And of course, this is just about the end of what we're calling
chapter eight to this particular reloaded version of Ocelli in the Greek. But we do appreciate the
fact that you have taken the time to use some discernment over the information given. So,
Greek, what do you think? Good enough for today? That's good enough. But, you know, good enough
could be the enemy of perfection. So let's see how perfect we can get it the next time.
Thanks, everyone. Absolutely. See you next time when, well, the pope's work schedule tells you
it's Thor's day. Take care. There you go.