So, just after 10 p.m., according to the wind-up toy that they call a clock, on the 19th day
of the first month, according to the Pope's work schedule, this is Ocelli in the Greek.
However, that's not what day it is.
What would it be, according to your observations, Greek?
Well, what anyone could observe were apparently in the 12th moon around the 9th day till noon.
Now, well, anyone can see that, but no one's really looking.
Yeah, and it's really seven days since the last time we met, but I'd say it appears to be around the 12th month.
So, yeah, go figure.
Go figure. Well, you know, a couple of subjects that I want to get to right off the bat here tonight,
but I think we should take time to give people the option to participate in the show,
because this is one of the things about reloading the show.
We've definitely tried to focus on and encourage participation from the audience, yes or no?
Oh, yeah. Well, yeah. Let's get any kind of sonic attempt from the other side of, you know, being the audience
versus those sitting on the platform, let's say the host.
So, basically, the two basic guidelines would be if you decide to call in, give us a good report, share some testimony,
maybe a subject matter or anything like that, but don't talk about yourself.
Everyone around you kind of like acts like they do want to hear about your personal stuff,
but no one really cares when you're talking about yourself in any situation on this planet.
Everyone is just waiting for you to shut up so they could tell you what they think.
So, anyway, I think we're probably the only ones, Chuck, that actually come out and are that, let's say,
quote, unquote, honest about reality regarding that subject, right?
Oh, yeah, definitely, definitely. Blunt guidelines, plain and simple, really.
Yeah, and the second one would be if you're under the influence, everybody knows you are except for you, so don't call in.
You do sound like you're under the influence if you're under the influence of your substance of choice
or maybe it's non-material, but either way, yeah.
Yeah, look, it's not a fit and proper use of one's time to engage in a discussion with someone who is under the influence
unless you, too, are under the influence and you and I are currently, as we speak, not under the influence,
so you are disqualified if you are under the influence. Fair enough?
Right, but we're all under external input, and that's another thing that we try to bring up to people.
And the other thing we're trying to do, well, be careful because sometimes that word try has failure built into it,
but is the highest and best use of this minor Internet radio show and minor Internet radio station,
let's say, on the World Wide Web, kind of a web that is, but on the inane net, we're trying to perhaps,
well, I could speak for the Greek, let's say, third party there, the highest and best use of anything
and perhaps have good conversation and impart some information and, I don't know,
maybe shake people up a little bit because nothing else seems to be working.
So there you go. So call in, folks. Let's give the Skype first.
If you're using the Skype convention, you just go to your contacts in the search box and put in Ocelli and the Greek.
It's spelled just like it sounds with the O-C-H-E-L-L-I and the Greek.
And I am at the helm of that convention, and I will pull you in after a request.
And Chuck will give out the call-in number using basically an error code in seven digits, which is?
218-339-8525. That is 218-339-8525, in exactly that order, and the same guidelines do apply over there,
except that I will pull you in when I see a call on the board and I am in control of the board.
And you will be identified by your area code or whatever it does say on the board.
That's it. Other than that, again, not looking for you to talk about yourself.
So it doesn't really matter who you are specifically, although we might ask just as a matter of, well, I don't know,
engaging one in a direct sense so that we're not speaking to who knows who, right?
Oh, yeah. So, Chuck, right before we came on air, you mentioned there's a couple of matters
or points of discussion, perhaps, that maybe you want to mull through before we get rolling.
Well, yes. I wanted to provide you with a couple of things here and ask you, in a way, sort of, I don't know,
drop these topics for discussion real quick, although we've covered them extensively before with the exception of one.
So if you don't mind, I have three things in mind. Is that okay?
Go for it.
Okay. First of all, let's start with cosmic censorship.
I have observed recently that communication is degrading among the surface-dwelling inhabitants here.
I have noticed that, whether it be through the media, in face-to-face conversations, et cetera, et cetera,
no one is listening, no one is speaking to the topic at hand,
no one is having anything resembling a coherent conversation seemingly in almost every corner I look.
And it's not you, Chuck. It's them.
Here's the odd thing, and I appreciate you saying that, but here's the odd thing to me.
It seems to be getting worse.
Well, have you ever heard of the formula F equals P over V, force equals pressure over volume?
What happens when pressure over volume is the number that resembles pressure divided by the number resembling volume?
So as the volume gets smaller, the number gets smaller.
So when you divide something by a smaller number, it's a larger number, right?
So that's why when you let out a balloon in the air that's fully in the room, let's say, that's fully inflated,
you notice it kind of flies around as it's ejecting the compressed air from the backside.
But as it gets smaller and smaller, it moves faster and faster and faster, right?
Because the F equals P over V formula kind of works out there.
So what's happening is we're going into another stage starting around next year.
The year starts in the spring, folks.
So if you think it's New Year, you're a little early or a little late.
It doesn't matter because it's arbitrary what you're doing.
But generally the years run from spring to fall.
So you have another spring to fall interval.
And when that next fall comes, that winter is an interim.
And then the next spring, not this one coming, but the one after that in the northern part of the world,
is around the time where you're going to start transitioning into another period.
And that period is going to lead to the lifting of this mindset.
Let's just call it a mindset that has been prevailing for the past seven years, very sticky.
It's always been around.
This cosmic censorship I believe we've discussed started roughly with what is academic historians
or one of them considers to be the main axial period of mankind, which was around 2,500 years ago.
And we've discussed that quite a bit, I think, right?
And that's when the cosmic censorship started.
That's where all of your modern conventions were put in place
and all of your major religions that are in place were put in against what you might believe or think.
And this period that's coming up is going to be the precursor to another period.
So here's another thing.
It's getting worse, you said, right?
We're nearly ending this past seven-year cycle, which is a time of distraction and confusion.
I've been saying for years and years that this seven-year period is the time period of distraction and confusion and tension.
So when you look at the media, all you're getting for the past seven or eight years,
let's say seven, six years I should say really, is this tension of financial threat of financial collapse,
missing airplanes and political corruption.
If you actually look at the mainstay of all of your media communications
and what's on people's minds regarding the geopolitical scene
and whatever they think to be concerned of is financial collapse, missing airplanes and corrupt political conditions.
This has been the main – as a matter of fact, since I started speaking about this,
some people would email me or send me a private message.
Look, another airplane is missing or crashed.
Or look, another politician is being thrown under the bus.
Or look at this idiot over here talking about eminent financial collapse of the dollar
when this idiot doesn't even know that there hasn't been a dollar since 1934.
But what's weird here is that it's not only in these larger scopes, let's just say, geopolitical, social.
Airplanes are fairly large objects.
I'm talking about face-to-face conversations between people.
If I sit and objectively view them and if I were to write them down into a report
and say this is the conversation that took place, you would think that I was missing things
like minutes of time that are gone because the conversations don't make sense.
They literally don't. This is my observation.
Well, the level of – they're punch drunk from it.
They're becoming apathetic. They don't know why because it's all external input.
See, the streams that come into the mind have been messed with because it's a very high tension.
We've also – one thing that – you mentioned three loose topics there, but they're all tied together.
But the other thing that we could throw in as a fourth to maybe be an accoutrement to the rest
is we're in the credits time period.
All these things that you brought up also are part of the credits. It's the end.
People are discussing the end, these Christian people.
Every year, they give a calendar date on the pope's calendar.
This is when the apocalypse is going to happen and it goes away.
Nothing ever happens.
If you subscribe to any major religion, by the way, this is pretty much –
it might sound dogmatic, but it's true.
I assure you, you will never understand prophecy.
When I say never, I mean never is going to end soon because you're stuck in this –
yeah, it's such a low level of thinking, first of all, to be a member of any of these mainstream –
or when I say mainstream, there are 34,000 sects of Christianity or Islam and Judaism and Hinduism, Buddhism.
They have many sects.
If you subscribe to any of these, you will – I assure you, you will not understand anything in any –
or in the point where it's functional in any of the holy rites that you're supposedly supposed to adhere or subscribe to.
But the cosmic censorship is part of – it started 2,500 years ago, but like you said recently, it's getting worse
because it's this type of censorship is ending.
It's not only this type of censorship that started seven years ago,
but it's also the type of censorship that started 2,500 years ago is ending.
What does that mean?
Do you remember the main transportation convention up until the late 19th century was the train?
You took a train cross-country on long distances.
People talk about the petrochemical companies being influential,
but it was the train barons in the 19th century that pretty much ran everything, right, the military and such.
At one point, the train barons had a conspiracy to take over countries
so they could have a train line that goes across the planet, basically up through Russia, across Alaska,
and all the way down to whatever, connecting the Americas and all that.
Once you get across to Russia, you could go down into Europe, right?
So they were very powerful.
But when you think of traveling long distances now, who thinks of taking a train?
You really think of a plane or a ship, don't you?
Right.
Now, what happened right before the trains sort of were replaced by other modalities, buses, automobiles, let's say, planes,
they became very, very opulent, didn't they, right before they finished?
Well, that's true, yeah.
When the cruise ship modality was the way to get across the ocean before aviation, they became extremely opulent.
So again, the F equals P over V, as something starts to fizzle out, it gets more intense, seemingly, doesn't it?
Well, it gets more intense, it becomes more sophisticated, seemingly, in one way or another.
Now, by sophisticated, I don't mean to say that the communication is sophisticated at this point.
What I'm saying is the…
Having a discussion with a bag of hammers is not very sophisticated, but anyway.
No, but it's also very difficult to do.
If you can pull that off, you're pretty impressive.
But the thing is the profundity of the lack of ability to communicate is increasing.
It's getting more sophisticated.
It's getting stranger to sort it out.
How about that?
Yeah, that's quantitative, Chuck.
How about the quality of the communications also?
That's going down.
Yeah, because technically you're saying – let me just grab it from one end.
Let's grab the tail end, I think.
You're having technical difficulties.
In other words, there are people as if you didn't say anything or they didn't hear you or whatever.
But I'm also – right?
When they're communicating, but also I'm thinking about qualitatively the subject matter.
How many times have you ever heard people talking about the dollar collapsing or the economy and this and that?
It's like where have these idiots been for the past 80 years?
Don't they know it's a credit-based economy?
Or when they talk about health and all this, what are they talking about?
Molecular biology or life?
I haven't found any subject matter that is being addressed, mainstream or alternative, in an objective way.
It's always what's been fed to the public, what memes have been created, what convention of thought,
which is usually bullshit, and they keep discussing that.
So the quality I've found of the conversations, whether they're paying attention or not, has always been low.
Once you start objectifying it –
Yeah, well, and that's the interesting thing because this does lead to the idea that, hey, look,
the dramatic conclusion has to be amped up a bit and ramped up so that you have this grand conclusion
before the credits really start to roll or while the credits are rolling, right, in any movie.
Yeah, it is going to – well, the credits started rolling roughly 18 years ago.
You're about halfway through it.
And we've – so anyway, are you satisfied because this could lead –
this thing segues into another thing, into another thing, into another thing.
Are you satisfied with the cosmic censorship so far
or do you want to see if we could tie the next aspect of it together?
What was the next thing you thought of?
I think you already did by bringing in the aspect of the closing credits
because here's something that I know has been discussed elsewhere.
We've touched upon it before.
You've discussed it recently with Roderigo.
I think that's how you say his name on that thing on YouTube.
But the kill shot or kill shots which are forthcoming,
now why would I bring that up when we're talking about the closing credits of the movie?
That's much later.
That's where – the reason I wanted to see what we're going to talk about next perhaps is to tie it all together
because this is – these are not a la carte venues, right?
They have to – they're all part of a meal.
They're all part of a big thing, yeah.
This all goes in order.
I'm just giving people the foreshadowing of where it's going.
It's not pulling corn out of someone's poo either.
This is really – that's the interesting part about it.
This kind of information is beyond what people are used to hearing.
But anyway, the kill shots are not going to be viewed as kill shots.
Do you remember that part of the discussion?
Because the people will be so amped up about the current – about the coming state that they're going to be in
and the promises that were made to them will be totally engrossing their mind,
and they will not view these as kill shots because they will be buying into desirously
and enthusiastically into the – not propagandized, but it is propagandized thought that the society
that they had prior to the kill shots was going to last 1,000 years, which is peace and prosperity.
Why do the gods do that?
Because they will not take out a civilization when they're in a low state.
See, when man goes after, let's say, in a warlike fashion against another man's society,
they bring you down before they take you out, right?
They weaken you.
When the gods go after a society, they prop you up to your highest position.
Then they go after you just to show you how – so there's no excuse.
Right.
Well, you soften up the target if you're a man-driven army.
It's very simple.
You soften it up before you attack.
Right, and the gods harden you up.
Right.
They give you all the armor, and they say, look, even that means nothing.
So here's the thing.
We are looking at the bridge between the credits and the kill shot really is a massive epiphany,
which if one considers that the cosmic censorship suddenly goes away,
all of this confusion goes away, and guess what?
There is a mass or a total epiphany which will be granted to seemingly everyone
unless I'm following this the wrong way.
Well, okay, the cosmic censorship regarding what?
The gods.
Whenever you read any of the holy writs and they give you a simple –
let's say there's a book that says during the end times,
people will travel to and fro and knowledge will increase.
And people read these prophecies and say, oh, see, look, now we have airplane transportation
and we've got the Internet, so knowledge is increasing.
No, that's not the context that these things are written on.
They're not going to write – they're not going to give a prophetic statement that is general
unless they tell you it is.
When they give you a prophetic statement that says people will travel widely really
and knowledge will increase, it's people will travel regarding the gods
and knowledge of the gods will increase.
It's regarding them, knowledge will increase.
That's why people don't understand these ancient writs.
It's because they want to apply it to themselves and what they think these things are
versus the contextual way that these things were compiled and communicated.
So why did I bring that up out of left field?
Because the censorship regarding the gods is going to be lifted.
The people will still – do you remember, I think it was recently we discussed that prophetically,
people will never understand the money system.
Near a time around the kill shots, they will just stop using it.
It doesn't say they will comprehend it and say it's immoral and fraudulent
and that's why they're abandoning it.
No, it just says they stop using it just like they decide they don't want to use it anymore.
It doesn't say at any point that the fraudulent nature or the untrue or lying nature
of the money system will be known.
So that you could safely read into it because these ancient texts are very specific
about why occurrences happen with very few words.
So let's say, Chuck, let's say we make a statement.
These are like little roundabouts.
These are like spokes out of a hub going to a wheel.
The hub would be the kill shots and I'm giving the spokes
and we're going to attach it to the rim so we could roll down the road with it.
So the other spoke is this.
Let me just ask rhetorically and you, Chuck, if indirectly or directly, prophetically,
people will never understand certain things like the money system.
Could it be because they're censored from it?
Yeah, because how easy is it to read the codes regarding the banking system?
Very easy, but no one does it.
And even if they read it, they just walk away
and you're discussing how the credit system works with anyone
before you even finish discussing it.
They're like, well, how can I get some of it, right?
So that means that there's still going to be censorship.
When I say the censorship is going to be lifted, it is regarding the gods.
I don't think we brought up the specifics of that right now.
Now, why is it that being censored about the gods also leads to a lot of other censorship?
Because have you ever heard of the – there's a social argument about evolution
and intelligent design, right, evolution versus the gods creating, right?
Well, that will kind of like go to the side because when the knowledge of the gods increases,
the arguments like that will be able to be rationalized a little more, right?
So there's still going to be censorship,
but there's going to be more knowledge about regarding why people do things.
And why is it important also?
How many times have we said or the Greek has said,
and I've even gotten e-mails recently that say I want to know about being lawful
or what about people being immoral and immoral and unlawful and inappropriate?
How do you remedy that?
And I'm like, you don't.
Those things like law and morality come from your god, your god, not God,
because there's no such thing as plurality of them, right?
So you can't answer that question.
How does one become lawful?
Well, which god are you talking about?
There's so many, but there's only one that gives predominantly law form.
So all right, let's tie this all back together because it seems rather loose.
Let's put some tension on the spokes so the rim could support itself.
Sounds good.
Going back to the kill shots, loosely examining ancient texts,
do you know that these kill shots would have came 2,000 years ago?
I'm just going to throw that out there.
There's no yes or no, I knew it or I didn't.
I never heard that before.
That's something entirely new.
Of course, I've been quite exposed to the historical reality that seemingly around,
you know, September according to the Pope's work schedule,
it seems as though there are always, nearly on an allegedly yearly basis,
there is new theories regarding, you know, the doomsday of the comets,
the doomsday from outer space, the extraterrestrial involvement,
you know, the Nabooru, the hidden planets, the brown giants.
Let me throw this in, Chuck.
This is something that I would only discuss in private a year ago,
and I think coming together and giving a little more raw material is okay,
and I usually don't like to give out raw material because it's in a raw state.
It hasn't been.
When I bring up the concept of roughly 2,000 years ago, there's three things to consider.
One thing, that was the time period, let's say, of the first century A.D.
Let's use this loosely so people can understand, you know,
what we're talking about in the Pope's work schedule, let's say.
That was the time of the Christ and basically destruction.
All things were shut down.
The other thing that you'll notice is that the current calendrical system keeps time from there,
doesn't it, A.D., B.C., right, you know, regardless of what you believe in,
and it's almost as if that's a form of another form of credits that's being measured out.
And the other thing is this is the raw form.
The dark ages that were enlisted calendrically around the time of 500 or 600 A.D. to about 1,000 A.D.,
I'd say that's pretty conservative, maybe 850,
because we don't really start hearing about an emergence of much culture out of Europe
until like 1100 or 1200 again, right, until the Renaissance, 1400, right?
So between 500 and 1,000 A.D., conservatively or loosely on the tail end,
there was a tremendous amount of natural disaster, cosmic natural disaster, global, unleashed on this planet.
And that would have been a residue or, you know, when someone kind of cocks the gun to pull the trigger,
and they maybe let it go a little bit, maybe one goes out the barrel, not all six kind of thing.
That happened around the dark ages.
People are not familiar with their history.
How many people do you hear screaming about environmental destruction, right, right now,
and all this echo and global warming stuff?
These people are total morons.
Why aren't they discussing in contrast around that time period, let's say between 500 and 1,000 A.D.,
do you know that 75% of the planet, people on the planet had died within that time period,
90% of Europe due to natural disasters, meaning what would that be?
Asteroid strikes, comet strikes, volcanoes going off, years without summer,
where there would be snow and ice on the ground for the entire interim of what they call a year, right?
So there's no farming.
The animals died, right?
Okay.
So we're talking about 90% European population reduction and 70% on the planet.
And this is fairly what, 1,000 years ago, let's say,
and yet it's not being brought up to the fore discussion or comparative analysis to what they consider economic,
I mean ecological maladies or destruction.
These are not being discussed, these things, at all.
So when you compare what I just mentioned about the dark ages,
perhaps one bullet came out of the barrel, right, around then.
When you look at that in contrast to what is discussed as the environment today,
we're in a veritable Garden of Eden right now, aren't we, compared to 1,000 years ago?
Yeah.
You see the hypocrisy?
So this is why I mention these things.
And the gods use nature just like man uses nature to do war, right?
If you're going to wage war using mechanized warfare,
all of your machines and armaments are produced out of natural materials that are refined and cast into whatever you're doing.
So nature is what you watch that is going to be used.
And the kill shots, I hope we're kind of going around.
These are topics that are very big, and they're not a la carte, right?
They're all tied in together.
When the censorship begins to be lifted in the next year,
the following seven years is going to create the mindset on this planet.
What mindset is that?
That it is acceptable that the current conventions that have been in place,
which is the Greek convention, by the way, right?
And people may not think that.
Some people say it's Roman, but it's really Greek.
Well, it's adapted to Greek stuff, so, yeah.
Sure.
They get a little confused, yeah.
If you look at all your scientific and law conventions,
they're using Greek words even still, right?
In Greek philosophy, Greek democracy, whatever.
Even in what they call the medical establishment, everything is in Greek.
Yes.
And your government situation, even though it's been adjusted for Roman influence during that time.
Right.
You're going to abandon that, and you're going to go further back
into looking at a convention that was prior to that,
and it's also going to open the mindset that the current convention has not served man well.
I've been in many conversations through the years saying, oh, the Greek philosophers, this.
Oh, the science.
I said, okay, all right, stop right there.
If the Greek philosophers were so great, and their work and their form of thinking
and their mindset is so good, how well has that served you for the past 2,000 years?
How well has it served you?
Not well at all, right?
Nope.
So what you're seeing is you're going to also see the mindset being softened
to accept a loose-fitted Middle East union.
I use air quotes for that because it's not going to jump together
and be a confederacy like the European Union,
which is nonetheless nothing more than Europe united under Germany,
which is what the National Socialist Party wanted to do anyway, right?
No one in the EU really makes any major moves or any conventions are put in place
or discarded unless it's agreed by the German councils there, right,
which is also a puppet setup.
But anyway, you're going to see more discussion on who the gods are in general.
I mean that's just a big topic.
And just to show you right now, before we got on the show, it's the seventh episode,
I just did a query on a browser, and I read who are the gods,
and there were 10 pages straight on, site after site after site,
just talking about the Greek Olympic gods.
So the mindset is still there, that it's Greek.
On the Internet there is no discussion or on a search, if you just search who are the gods,
all you get is Greek gods, Greek gods, pages and pages and pages.
Well, and that's the first thing that people jump to when you say,
oh, there's more than one god.
Almost the very first example that will be presented to you is, oh, like the Greeks and the Romans.
The Greek pantheon, yeah.
Yeah, the pantheon itself, right?
But everybody does forget that in the pantheon there was the unknown god as well.
But anyway.
Yeah, those are actually, we want to touch on that for a quick moment.
A lot of these gods that people consider, especially in the mainstream religions,
are actually minor imps and demons in their society, in their society, the god society.
It would be, okay, let's just put it this way.
Let's say you're in some urban environment at 2 in the morning and you see a bum fight, okay,
in the middle of the street, two homeless guys having a fight,
and you grab one and you take him, you put him on your spaceship,
and you take him to another planet and say, where am I going?
He says, well, you're going to be a god on this planet.
Think about that for a moment.
I had to think about that, yeah.
That's the level of, so in other words, when you discuss the gods or god or whatever
with your common surface-dwelling earth inhabitants, they have no idea.
They're dealing with the lowest of the low, right?
They can't, I mean, just look at it.
I mean, look at, we just have a major religion that actually props up young children
on a fiery red visage of a being sitting, seated position, making a wish of prosperity.
It has a white beard, right, and jingle bells.
I don't need to say, that is like such a minor demon.
Now, the unknown god is this.
You showed how what most people consider to be the gods are very minor.
Back in ancient days, there were things called exorcisms as well.
People, a lot of the maladies, insanity, you know, what they call psychological
or spiritual problems were not considered chemical as they are today.
They were considered a form of possession, and when the exorcist or the priest
or the shaman or whatever would encounter the person who was to be exorcised,
the first thing they would try to do is identify the being that was in possession
of the man, woman, or child, right?
And they usually would evoke some kind of identification by name or character.
Now, the most difficult ones or the ones that were left alone were the ones that didn't speak.
They were known as the dumb spirit of possession, and those were almost impossible to exercise
because when you approached the person, there would be no speak.
You couldn't identify who it was.
You couldn't deal with them directly, and usually those people were cast as being wasted.
You know, this demon is going to eat them because, I mean, not eat them physically,
but, you know, they're going to spend the rest of their lives like that
because the demon was a dumb demon, would not speak, so he was an unknown demon.
Okay, now let's go back five minutes when you said there is the unknown god.
When we hear about the unknown god, those were the basic demons that did possession
that did not speak, and they were known as the unknown ones.
Well, literally because they had not been identified by name.
You can't deal with them if they don't.
Right.
They could not be exercised, and that's what was so impressive in the biblical Christ
when he exercised one of those that the rabbis and the Pharisees and the Sadducees
during that time in that writ could not do.
And when he exercised one of those, he said, wow, this has never been done before
because part of the thing about exorcism is to communicate with the actual spirit
that is in possession.
Well, right, and no matter what discipline you're talking about,
even in the darker practices, etc., etc., the name is important,
so this would be something really extraordinary based on any convention.
So the most tenacious and the most evil of these spirits
are the ones that don't speak or don't communicate.
Well, they're the most problematic.
Yeah, and this is what impressed some of the angels to call the unknown gods
because if you actually look at what the term in English gods was not being used
by these older cultures, they used terms like the Elohim or the emanators, right,
or the spirits.
So anyway, I just wanted to – that was like a long bit of trivia,
but I think it should clear things up, at least from a semi-academic point of view,
and academic meaning like, you know, you've got a good reference now.
This is not just, oh, the Greek thinks this, blah, blah, blah.
You can go and spin off on your own way and become an expert on this.
So let's go back to the kill shots, I guess.
You're going to understand more about this other world that is influencing this world,
the unseen.
You know how you still have people on a moronic level talking about multiple dimensions?
How many times have you heard that?
Or quantum or ascension and all this other stuff, you know,
which is ridiculous.
There's only one dimension, and that encompasses everything.
And within that dimension you have the tangible and the intangible,
the seen and the unseen, the perceivable and the imperceivable, period.
Now once you comprehend that, well, now what has been memorialized for thousands
of years, it starts to make sense, doesn't it?
Because it doesn't say the gods came from another dimension.
It just says they are what?
Unseen.
Right.
So, you know, it's just, but, you know, I mean, this is planet Earth.
I mean, if you expect anything other than more, I don't know, idiocy,
you're delusional.
And this is the way it's been for a long time, folks.
Well, simply, you know, and simply put, too, simply because something is unseen
does not mean that it is not ever present or a factor.
I point to the fact that we breathe air.
We don't really see air.
Yeah.
Or the effects, or wind.
You don't see the wind, but you sure see its effect.
Yes.
Or you don't see light.
And you don't see light.
You see its effect.
That's the truth, too.
Yeah.
And there's different kinds of light, but you never see any of it.
So the kill shots, again, that's interesting.
You know, there's seven main episodes that are going to be coming.
Three of them, I'd say three and a half of them are from out there.
You know, what I mean by out there, go outside and point up.
That's out there, right?
It seems like these days it's bad if you say outer space or this or that.
There's some people that have some funky ideas about that,
so I don't want to go there.
But if you just go outside and there's nothing over you and you point up,
that's where it's coming from, okay, no matter where you are on the planet,
even if you're upside down, right, in Australia or whatever.
Okay.
And the other three and a half, when I say three and a half,
it's because there's an overlap, are going to be from you guys,
you guys meaning surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
Is it possible for, let's say, hmm, you ever heard of the term,
these are good people, innocent people?
You've heard that a lot, right?
Okay.
Is it possible that good people, innocent people, non-criminal types,
well-intended family people or Christians or whatever or faithful or whatever
can get involved in activity that creates damage and harm?
Have you ever seen, this is popular maybe because maybe I've noticed that it's
popular in the mindset that I have about it.
Certain basketball teams lose the championship or win the championship
and outside there's a mob that just sets cars on fire for no reason or stabs
someone, you know, rap concerts, basketball final championships.
I don't hear a lot about that with the stupid bowl or the World Series type
stuff, right, but rap concerts, soccer games, the hooligans, right?
So that's the mindset that's going to take over people,
that one-third of humanity will be, let's say,
ungraciously dealt with by the other two-thirds.
And it's not going to be like you hear these morons on the Internet and
whatever talking about the government crackdown.
They have some special police force that's going to come and do it.
It's going to be brother against brother, father against son,
son against father, and daughter against mother-in-law.
Anyway.
It's not going to be the war on Christianity either.
No, there won't be any Christianity as such.
There won't be any Judaism, none of that stuff.
I mean, here, yeah, that stuff is for people who don't research
or care to research or care to learn.
And, by the way, you don't go to the gods through faith.
You go to them through knowledge, not because I say it,
because they have written that.
And the only time you'll find the word faith shown in any of the written texts
is because it's called the faith, not just faith.
And it's the faith that what they're telling you is going to happen before it.
They always tell you what's going to happen before to mind these things.
That's what you have the faith in,
not just some ridiculous convention that you see.
So, anyway.
So these kill shots are going to be coming in when mankind is at its peak,
which he has never had.
In other words, you look forward in the next, say, 10 years or so,
you will be amidst the greatest society man has ever had.
Now, what makes a great society?
Let's not say what makes it.
Let's say what makes it when it's not present, like war,
when you don't have war going on, right,
when you don't have affliction, when you don't have suppression.
These things will be diminished almost to a minimum.
There will still be squirmishes because when this confederacy,
loose confederacy of nations comes together,
they will do it by force after a certain time when everyone agrees to it.
Now, doesn't this also mean, though,
that most of the concerns that do plague the surface-dwelling inhabitants
will also be removed?
I mean, doesn't it seem as though, oh, I don't know,
the needless massive starvation will probably stop?
Yes.
The seeming strategy of scarcity will not really be the primary moving factor
on the planet, this kind of thing as well?
That's right.
Let's say a given prosperity that has never seen.
I don't mean a prosperity like everyone's walking around like they're wealthy.
But there will be a given prosperity that has never been seen, you know,
like things you've heard promised in the old, not Bolshevik perhaps,
but, yeah, Bolshevik societies, you know, in early 20th century, you know.
It was, you know, they'd have a little meeting
and promise everyone steak dinner every night and strawberry for dessert.
And if you raised your hand in the back and said,
I'm allergic to strawberries, they said, well,
you're going to do what we tell you anyway, you know.
So when everything sounds really good, there's still this human element in there.
That's why it's very difficult to listen to alternative information
because you have talks, and I'm sure you do as well, on the Ocelli effect.
People come on and they talk about a very specific thing.
Well, this is a problem.
And they'll go into it to a certain degree, and they get all hyped up about it.
And I'm like, well, it is a problem, but it's really a symptom, you know.
I've been getting some messaging regarding vaccines just to throw this in,
and I'm still yet to answer some of these messages.
But regarding vaccines, I said, how did you come across, you know,
they want to vaccinate the child.
They're like, well, you know, they want to go to school and the doctor.
Okay, hold on.
The vaccine is irrelevant.
The school is what's relevant.
Why are you sending them there?
To be pranked.
Oh, I see, because, oh, you're pranking them too.
Oh, I see.
All right, so you're a pranking little prick,
and you're raising another little prick to be a prankster.
So what?
Pump them up with mercury.
You see, the problem here is not the vaccine.
You see, it's the prank.
What are you doing?
No, I get it.
I mean, just for the record, I mean, like, not only, you know,
going right along with not vaccinating,
I'm not going to send them to those institutions.
I'm not going to send Frankie there specifically.
Well, it's not an issue if you don't.
No, it's not.
But that's what I'm saying.
That's exactly why it's all commensurate with, you know, reducing.
It's not an issue.
The amount of toxins, you know,
not only the ones that are obvious in the vaccination,
but the ones to his mindset.
I want to try and reduce that as much as possible.
In other words, just sort of set him apart, if you will.
Oh, yeah.
And it's not hard to do, but you're going to have to study.
You see, what rules man is law form,
and what rules the animals is law form, except what's the difference?
What's the difference, Chuck,
between getting a computer that has a pre-downloaded operating system,
programs, and files?
You plug it in, it's ready to go.
What's the difference between that and one that's brand new in the box
that nothing is downloaded?
What's the difference?
One has to be worked with and has to be given the programs,
has to be given the software.
All the animals, the fish, the birds, the tigers,
even certain elemental things like forests and rivers,
they have pre-downloaded software in their hardware.
Humanity doesn't.
So you have a lot of people that are saying,
well, you know, there's natural law, universal law.
Yeah, there is, but you're not going to stare at anything.
Look, all these people, by the way, that are talking about nature this
or there's a form of Druidism and all that,
these people are so easy to destroy.
All you got to ask them is what day is it?
And they resort back to the Pope's work schedule.
It's all fluff.
The reason why I don't partake in anything on the Internet,
other than using it as looking at the weather and whatever and doing this,
is because when you're looking to eat wheat, there's no wheat.
There's puffed wheat.
If you want corn, they're not giving any corn.
They're giving puffed corn.
If you want something sweet, it's artificial sweetener.
What happens if you eat that processed crap?
You get sick.
It sounds good in the beginning, but I'm not being dogmatic about keeping time,
but I'll tell you what,
it's one hell of a place to separate those who know and those who don't know.
It's really, really fast.
It cuts to the chase, doesn't it?
There's many other things.
But the thing is, the reason why we come together here is to,
I didn't say to really educate anyone or maybe give some information,
was to shake people a little bit.
Why?
Because we've discussed anyone who goes out and says to make the world a better place is a freaking idiot.
They're not paying attention.
You're not supposed to make the world better because if you try to make it better,
you have all the malevolent, non-seen beings against you.
Why?
Because they're malevolent.
They don't want to see it get better.
But isn't even the desire to shake people kind of along the lines of wanting to make the world a little better?
No, because if you shake them, they don't get bed sores.
This is true.
Look, if you shake a hysterical person who is focused on the wrong thing,
often that is what calms them down.
But again.
If a woman says like some people have fear of spiders or fear of snakes or anything,
fear, you've heard of that, especially young women or whatever.
They've been taught that.
Just when they're in a hysterical thing, get a half a glass of water and throw it in their face
and watch how all of a sudden they're not afraid of spiders and snakes anymore.
They're really upset because of the water, right?
This is true.
I will not advise you try this at home, though.
Yeah, it's an act.
But go ahead.
Yeah, I'm actually working with animals.
Some people have problematic animals and I'd go look at it and I'd say,
well, it's an act.
That animal is acting that way.
It's frustrated.
It knows that whenever it acts this way, it elicits a standard response from you and it enjoys that.
So watch.
I can prove to you that the animal is acting.
Let's go do the situation that you're complaining about and I'll distract the animal
and you'll see how it's not going to be doing that anymore.
And nine out of ten times it's true.
So you've heard of like dog whispers and horse whispers and stuff like that.
That stuff is not magic mystical.
There are people that are very talented at it, but that is something that can be taught.
Yes, nature does act as well, and it acts accordingly and disaccordingly occasionally.
But just to go back to what we were saying about the operating system, we don't have one,
so you're going to have to get it from your gods or your authority.
And we've mentioned that sometimes gods are not necessarily unseen.
The position of the highest authority would be what we're saying as a god,
and that could be apparent to someone who is in their formative years, right,
between when they were born until about, what would you say, two, three, four,
and then they start to get bigger concepts.
And how are they going to do when they're being pranked by their parents?
It's not the government.
It's not the education system or the Illuminati or whatever.
It's the parents that I see are pranking the children into this stuff.
How many times have you heard the parents say,
Well, we know the education system is garbage, but you're going to do it because I did it.
So, whoa, wait a second.
You want to take all the children away, and you can't do that like the Pied Piper.
You know, it's like going to an animal shelter to look for dogs.
You want to take them all home.
You can't, right?
It's not a realistic thing to do.
I mean, for most people.
I guess there are individuals that might have the type of resources to support that,
but it only goes just so far.
You can empty one shelter.
Maybe you can empty two because you've got a large piece of property.
But after a little while, it becomes unmanageable, let's just say.
How about that?
Oh, yeah, unmanageable.
Well, here's the thing.
We've also brought up the subculture regarding children.
I'm going to skip into what the subculture is called.
It's called kids' world, kids' meals, kids' music, kids' clothes, kids' toys, kids' this, kids' that.
There's a subculture.
And you know when they instill this ridiculousness, which, by the way, is not only juvenile,
but it's lascivious.
How many times have you heard Disney putting in pornographic
and explicit sexual scenes in their work towards these children, right?
And there's no transition out of that.
Like how old does the child, you know, is it past the formative years?
And then it goes into adolescence.
What do they have for adolescence?
Do they have James Dean posters?
What do they do?
Nine-inch nails?
I mean, I don't know.
And then it goes into this other insanity.
So, yeah, so the thing is these little children are small people,
and they are immature and inexperienced and uneducated.
And that's where you go education maybe is reading the fine print
and experience is when you don't read the fine print.
So, well, there you go.
And what does this lead us to?
Well, the purpose of Episode 7, in my estimation,
which is the examination of divinity.
Now, I liked covering each of these topics in short tonight
because I felt they needed to be addressed.
Addressed.
Why?
Because they all fit into this concept because, after all,
how are you supposed to do anything any differently
if you don't understand that concept?
Number seven is the number of what, by the way?
Just numerology.
From a numerological standpoint, excuse me.
Well, from a general point, it's a number of divinity,
but it's divinity aiming at man, where eight would be divinity and man, right?
They call it the infinity and all that.
So, you know, six would be the number of man, seven is the number of divinity,
but it's not necessarily just for them.
It's when they're relating back.
And, by the way, we're in the seventh millennium since Adam,
about 18 years into it, right?
Now, there's many things to cover.
I think we have covered the external input,
and your operating system comes from your god and all that.
And how important is it to understand that?
Well, even if you don't think you have a god, you're still operating by default.
Like I used to say, you know, well, you know, Greek, I'm atheist.
What you're saying doesn't apply.
I don't have a god.
And I say, well, then, do you believe in the laws of the state?
And they're like, yes, I do.
Well, then the state is your god and April 1st is your holiday.
I mean, that's how, you know, and they even have a god for you, justice.
It's a goddess.
She's very cruel and dishonest.
And, yeah, and bringing up the kill shots directly, explicitly what they are.
I've done that.
You and I have done that back and forth.
I believe it's proprietary information, but at any point it doesn't really matter.
There was an old saying that says if you want to hide something from the American public,
put it in the public library.
So what a better way to hide what you've discovered than doing it on a minor Internet radio show.
And as we come near the close of the first hour, though,
I think to focus on divinity itself and the understanding of it,
not from just a numerological standpoint, like I said earlier,
but to really examine it in the next hour I think would be, well, a fair use of that hour.
What do you say?
Sure, and we could get into, before this hour wraps up,
let's just say the number seven is an interesting number to comprehend.
If you have seven objects, the center object is the fourth,
and you have three on the left and three on the right, don't you?
That's for sure, yeah.
And in importance, the first and the last, number one and number seven, are fairly equal,
but your starting point with number seven is always the fourth and center position.
And I just gave a very simple format that if you apply it to looking at any ancient writ,
you will always look for the middle.
Open up some ancient writ, and if it's 100 pages long,
go to the 50th page, the 49th, 50th, and 51st pages,
and the entire meaning of the thing will be defined there.
Now, how's that for a little secret?
Ah, there you go.
And look, for other things that you may want to interject,
the number to call on your phones is 218-339-8525,
218-339-8525, if you want to participate in this discussion.
And we will add you in.
Another way is via Skype, Greek.
Yes, and that would be Ocelli and the Greek, Skype contact request.
Ocelli and the Greek, just like it sounds.
You spell it just like it sounds, O-C-H-E-L-L-I and the Greek.
So type away and do it.
So we could hear from you, maybe not, but we've got plenty to talk about,
and it's going to be a mouthful.
So whether you make a sonic appearance or not, the conversation will continue,
as most things do, but the opportunity has been given one way or another.
Yeah, so the number seven, folks, examine that, you know, the lucky seven.
You've heard about, you know, luck is a goddess also.
I would use the word fortunate over the word luck.
So we'll see you on the other side.
Absolutely.
Stay tuned to Ocelli and the Greek.
We'll be right back after this.
So this is the second hour of episode seven of the reloaded version of Ocelli and the Greek,
because we did do this before.
But was anyone paying attention?
And could they, given the cosmic censorship?
They could try.
But try has failure built into it occasionally.
That is one of those things.
What did they say in the Star Wars movies?
Do not try.
Do.
All right.
Yeah, in their case, it would be do-do, but yeah, whoever they are, yeah.
That's true.
So, yeah, some comments.
By the way, Chuck, do you want to give some minor promotional notes for donations and things like that?
Or are we good?
Well, look, why don't you start?
Because a lot of the e-mails you receive are extremely helpful,
and you get them over at a website where you actually read the e-mails.
So why don't you give that out first?
Yeah, well, that's uncommonradio.com.
Go ahead and do the www.uncommonradio.com because it doesn't get that many hits on a search engine query.
And there is a contact form there, and just basically it's a courtesy site.
So kind of look semi-prepared for the, you know, internet, inane net convention.
And I will read them and respond.
And when I say read them and respond, if they deem that,
and unfortunately or fortunately that's subjective on my part.
But also I want to thank everyone.
All of them have been very positive and thoughtful, meaning to the point.
And I did discuss some of the very positive e-mails regarding health matters.
People had tried some things, restoring vacuum to the body.
Yes, the body operates under a slight vacuum, and some people have had very good success with it,
basically just by affecting the volume of the body, you know.
And we could probably, I think that was discussed on the container a few years ago,
a number two that you and I, our first go-around.
So without getting into too many specifics on that, also the other thing I wanted to mention,
the information that Chuck and I discussed here, some people might want more detail.
And I think that the details that we're giving are perhaps enough,
unless there's a very specific question.
And what I said to Chuck during the break is like, you know,
how do you go in public and give away 10 or 15 years of full-time research for nothing?
You know, don't send chickens and corn and stuff in the mail or whatever.
But there's some kind of exchange, which I'm not looking from the general audience,
because if you go to theuncommonradio.com, you'll see there is no donation.
I'm not asking for anything, at least at this time.
But that's where I stand right now.
I think these discussions are really a primer or to create the mindset that will be necessary for the detail.
But with that, go ahead, Chuck.
Well, at my website, I do have a donate button.
It is ocelli.com, spelled O-C-H-E-L-L-I.com.
You will recognize it because it does come up at the very top, indeed telling you that you're there.
And that sort of thing is, well, you know, look, it's up to the listener if they feel as though I've done a good job with this show
or with any other presenting something.
And I am part of the presentation here, although I did not do the research that you've done.
I'm part of the presentation, and you feel as though there's some value to it,
perfectly acceptable to make a donation over there or become a member,
which is helpful and also, you know, look, yeah.
Even when you had a donate button on ocelliandthegreek.com, actually that button went to me,
which I do appreciate everybody who has donated and will in the future.
So leave it at that.
But there's also American Freedom Radio, Greg, which provides us with the platform to do this, correct?
Mm-hmm.
Two hours in the movies will wreck your wallet for, what, $12 these days in the city,
an urban environment up to $20.
So you're getting two hours here with us.
What's it worth to go ahead and do the right thing?
There you go, and there is indeed a donate button at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
So now you've been given all the options for participation, one last one, which I'll mention again,
although it seems to take a bit of courage to participate in this one.
First, Greg, give the Skype convention, if you will, because there are international listeners who said,
well, gee, it's kind of expensive to call internationally.
So tell you what, no matter where you are in the world, Skype works if you have Internet,
and you must if you're hearing us.
So if you have Internet and access to Skype, go ahead, Greg.
Ocelli and the Greek on the Skype request, contact request.
It would be spelled just like it sounds, O-C-H-E-L-L-I and the Greek, and there you go.
And the call-in number would be the 218 area code, and I don't have the number in front of me.
Go ahead.
No problem, 218-339-8525.
That's 218-339-8525.
And, yeah, if you dial in, you'll be added in.
If you Skype in, you'll be added in.
And we already went over the rules, so we're not doing that again.
So let's continue on with the conversation.
Greg, what do you say?
Yeah, we left off with seven sort of being the divine number,
but it's really when the divine is aiming towards man, right?
And sevens come in good and bad, by the way.
There are roughly going to be seven kill shots, and three of them, let's say,
administered from up there, and the other three pretty much down here, or three and a half.
These things are broken up where they overlap, right?
Let's just say, cutting to the chase, you know, we never – did we ever discuss –
we have discussed, by the way, in specific the kill shots, the cosmic ones,
the meaning planetary ones, and let's just do a brief – you know,
there was a comment that you mentioned maybe cutting to the chase and giving a little detail.
Let's just do this real quick.
Two of them will be stones, rocks, asteroids, whatever.
How else would we dub a large substrate-type substance made of rock, iron, or whatever?
They're called asteroids, right?
Well, look, stone, rock, asteroid.
Asteroid definitely implies that it's not a rock that is earthbound at this moment,
but will become.
Two of those.
Perfect sense.
And why two?
Because what is the form of capital punishment in the biblical sense?
No, it's not death by crucifixion or guillotine or electric chair.
No, it's stoning, as far as I know.
That's right.
That's the convention, and the actual stoning convention for capital punishment
is both a metaphor for the earth being hit by stones and vice versa.
Now, the third one is going to be a solar event, not a solar flare.
An event where the sun, we know it's going to happen at the beginning of the month.
Why?
Because it states that when this solar maximus, super maximus happens,
that the full moon will be as bright as the noonday sun.
Now, you have to remember that when the moon is full, that is secondary light.
That's the light bouncing off of the moon back to the earth.
Now, imagine how intensely bright the sun will be
for the moon to actually appear as the sun would normally.
That's pretty bright.
And we know when it's going to happen around,
it's going to be near the beginning of the month,
because that's when the full moon comes around.
And we also know that it's going to be very, very intense.
And we also know, prophetically, that no vegetation will survive, right?
It doesn't mean that there will never be vegetation again.
It's just that if you were to destroy all the vegetation on the planet,
you usually wait anywhere between two weeks and six months for it to restart regrowing,
a la forest fires, let's say, right?
So, yeah, so that's that aspect.
Now, want to give a little more detail,
or you think we should probably save it for another format?
Well, no, I'd like to hear just a little more detail,
because I'm sure it is something interesting in the mind of the listener
that there are three-and-a-half events, and one of them seems to overlap.
What do you mean by that in general?
Because, remember, there are seven events that are going to happen,
and three of them are essentially man-made,
and the other three are these cosmic kill shots, which we typically discuss.
But in the middle, in the midpoint,
there's a transition from where man's attention is being taken away
from what he's doing to each other to the skies, right?
And his attention will be drawn away not by a kill shot, by another event,
which I believe I'm not going to be explaining at this point or even bringing up.
But that event is something that has to do with a certain location in the sky.
It will be visual.
And when the things are put more in place, maybe the information to back it up,
basically one of the constellations, a major constellation in the sky,
which has a set of stars, one of those stars is going to change radically,
and that will be that midpoint,
and that will also be the change where the events or those leading the planet,
you are going to have world-type leaders are also going to change.
So that is going to be in the middle.
But, yeah, maybe this is a teaser.
In other words, when we bring up – do you ever notice when we do discussions,
it's not like watching a sitcom where you've got a pat answer.
There has to be explanation behind it.
Of course.
Yeah.
So there's going to be celestial events, signs in the sky.
How many times have you heard that, right?
Way too often, in fact.
But, yeah.
Right.
And you know what?
The signs in the sky, an interpretation,
one of the interpretations of that is not necessarily seeing flying things or whatever,
but it's things that were considered immovable changing, right?
Like a sign in the sky was all of a sudden another sun appears,
and you have two suns now.
They're very, very major events.
It's not just like seeing a UFO or a blood-red moon and all this other stuff, right?
That is also it, but you can't take it out of context.
I think last week we mentioned that if you approach a literary
or non-literary body of work, what I mean by a body of work,
it has a beginning and an end.
It can be communicated.
It has information, story, fact, or fiction.
It doesn't matter.
Any body of work that can be communicated,
if concepts are brought up in this body of work and they are defined within that body of work,
you are not allowed, neither do you have the right, the liberty,
or the freedom to redefine them if the definitions are given.
Right.
You see?
And we bring that up all the time.
There's people in the Christian convention and other religious conventions
that use terms like Antichrist or 666 or God or Satan or Lucifer and all that,
and they are using definitions that are made up that are not in the actual body of work
from where they were extracted from.
It has nothing to do with interpretation or belief or version.
You have no liberty, freedom, or right to change what things mean
when the meanings are given within the constraints of a body of work.
Yes.
At a very earlier age in my life, I did tell someone once that there was no definition
given for the devil, the Satan that they were talking about,
and they said, sure there is.
There's this, this, this, this, this.
And they named a bunch of things, and long story short here,
they named for me a bunch of descriptive information,
which was not the definition, was it?
Or maybe it was even taken out.
Those descriptions, were they from the original body of work,
or just were they conventions and fictions and stories and things that were superstitious?
They were mostly drawn from the allegedly original body of work,
which as we all know is not original either.
But even so, based on their understanding,
they had completely perverted the definitions by giving examples of observation
allegedly portrayed in the work.
So it gets all confusing when you deviate from that particular norm, right?
Yeah, and observation, is the observation subjective or objective?
It's because of something they heard four times over and it's changed,
or they actually saw it with their own eye.
Again, that's the thing.
Was you there or was you not?
There is such a thing as first-hand knowledge of information.
There's first-hand knowledge of the event,
but then like if you were reading a diary of someone who had died 200 years ago
or 300 years ago, you don't have first-hand knowledge of who wrote the diary.
But if you read the diary,
and you can report on it on a first-hand basis regarding that diary.
So you can have first-hand knowledge of information,
but not first-hand knowledge of the event.
You can observe a primary source, but that doesn't make you a primary source.
That's right, and you could speak with it authoritatively.
Like I've had discussions regarding the U.S. Constitution with people,
and ultimately I hear people say, well, we weren't there, we don't know.
But what kind of an excuse is that?
Because the document can be experienced first-hand.
Do you understand it?
Do you comprehend it?
The whole point is they don't.
Which we discussed on the episode which I called Holy Constitution Greek Man.
But that was discussed in great detail there.
So go ahead.
By the way, just to throw in one more little detail,
and I have mentioned this together here and in other places as well.
I think one of them was a member's area.
I have gotten some e-mails.
I had done some stuff.
I'll mention Freeman, and some people e-mailed me,
and they said they joined to hear the second hour.
And I was like, well, you know,
they could have joined Uncommon Radio or Chuck or done something else.
But, you know, good for them, good for Freeman or whatever,
if it was attractive enough for them to do that.
But the little bits about more of the detail of one of the cosmic kill shots,
you know, you will be shown the first asteroid,
but you won't be shown the second one.
Why?
You know what I mean by shown.
You know, how many times have you, you know, looked at, you know,
we have a near miss or this, you know, here is an observatory, you know,
or satellite photos of the asteroid or a computer-generated image of it, right?
You see that often.
Even in the literary sense, when this has been presented as a scenario,
there is the warning, hey, look, we see the incoming object, this and that.
And usually, you know, it looks like a stone, a potato-shaped thing.
It's never really, it's not very smooth or round or, yeah, it's almost like a random,
but basically they look like potatoes flying through space, right?
The second one you will not be shown.
Why?
Because it has a very, very, very, very high degree of manufacture.
What does that mean?
It's pretty flat.
It's very, very smooth with very, very clearly defined edges.
So, and it looks like a very specific object that most people are not familiar with anymore
because it's an ancient object.
So that's all I'm going to say about that.
So.
There you go.
For now.
That's interesting.
Of course, I didn't hear that hour, but.
I think we mentioned it as well.
We've mentioned it somewhere.
I'm not necessarily going to point you to it, but go ahead.
Yeah, because it's plausible just to show asteroids that look, you know,
like what people are accustomed to.
But you can't show people something that has obviously been made.
You know, it's not, doesn't occur in nature.
You don't have very, very smooth, shiny surfaces with very sharp angles
and other features unless it's made, right?
That's what I mean by hydro.
And you will not be shown that because that just brings up too many questions.
It's pretty clear when you see something that has a high degree of manufacture
versus a natural stone.
And it's just who made it is the first thing, right?
Well, right.
Look, if a rock falls on your head when you're walking through a canyon
and the rock appears to be without continuity in its shape,
you're going to assume that this is a naturally occurring accident
or could very well be at the very least.
You know, a cannonball lands on your head in the same place.
You're going to think more along the lines of who made it,
who brought it here, where it come from.
There's a chain of custody, right?
There's a chain of custody on it.
And the next thing you're going to ask is what's the serial number,
where was it made, right?
So, you know, if something is made, it's like, well, who made it?
You know, not only who sent it or dropped it,
but where'd they get it and where'd they get it and where'd they get it from?
Too many questions and you're not going to be shown that.
And that's going to cause a lot of damage, both of them are.
But the people will be in such a fervor about, you know,
that we're in a perfect society,
we'll just clean up the billion that died last night and we'll be fine.
Well, right now, if you had a billion dead or a billion and a half dead overnight,
it would be – I don't think it would not only make the news,
it would probably stop everyone for a very long time.
Yes, in the mindset tonight that we have today, tonight, yesterday,
tomorrow even.
So basically, to go back to the divinity and the gods,
have we mentioned once before that, you know,
I don't like using the word pagan anymore because actually a lot of the practices,
would you say natural practices, you know,
about looking at nature is actually correct,
that are practiced in a lot of these pagan cultures.
The only problem that is is that it's too corrupt and too ignorant to carry over
into anything being effective unless they're working more with the lower level demons
through incantations and things.
So the word pagan, I kind of like to leave alone.
But the word atheist, which means without a god,
is more of a clear way to kind of explain the current population on the planet at large.
The majority of the people on the planet today are atheists.
And what I mean by that is if you're familiar with Mickey Mouse,
that doesn't make you a zoologist, even though Mickey Mouse is a mouse.
Do you see my point?
That is a fictional.
He's not really a mouse.
No, no.
It's usually if you see Mickey Mouse, it's usually a drawing of some sort
or it's someone in a Mickey Mouse suit.
So what people consider the conventional religions or faiths of the world today
are so fictional and superstitious and removed even from anything practical
that it's safe to call them atheists, just like it's safe to,
if someone is an expert on Mickey Mouse,
they cannot be considered a zoologist or a biologist
because what is the zoology and biology of Mickey Mouse?
It's not even worth discussing.
It's a fictional character.
So, yeah, this might sound insulting to a lot of people.
There are actually people that actually still go to schools of divinity,
consider themselves religious scholars in many religions,
and there are still many religious institutions throughout the planet
that are absurd.
Why are they absurd?
Because essentially it's about pranking, isn't it?
This is a society of pranksters, and what is a prank?
A ludicrous trick.
And in order to perform a ludicrous trick,
you have to present the prevailing condition as a fiction, right?
Another way to do it is to say perhaps is avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence
because once you know there's a trap there, it's no longer a trap.
It's a tragedy, right?
The traps are set to be hidden.
So let's say back to the pranksters.
It has to be presented and cloaked in fiction in order for the prank to take place.
Like, for example, hey, Chuck, thank you for coming over.
I'm a prankster.
I put a thumbtack on a seat, for example.
I say, Chuck, why don't you come in and have a seat?
Get a load off your legs.
Well, you know, a Greek, I don't feel like sitting right now.
Well, you know, come on, come on.
You look tired.
Just have a seat.
Take a load off.
Sit down.
See, I'm cloaking this whole thing.
I'm not telling you there's a thumbtack there.
And once you sit down, you jump up, and you're like, why did you put a thumbtack on the seat?
Well, you sat on it, you know.
You agreed to sit on it.
I allowed myself to be misled because I didn't look.
It's like, well, why did you put the thumbtack on the seat, Greek?
Well, because it's fun.
Right?
This is the level.
This is your legal society, your religious society, your scientific society, your political society.
Should I go on?
They're all pranksters at large, pretty much.
Now, there are people within there that are innocently held within the field because they're ignorant of it,
and they stay ignorant and continue through it.
Then there are others that are quite evil that know it's about pranking.
So you have the innocent and the evil in most of your entitled classes.
And then there's a small group, a transient group that lasts between six months and two years.
When they find out what's going on within the religious class, the legal class, and the medical field,
and the political field, they say, what the hell did I just get myself into?
I need an exit strategy, but I've devoted all my life to this.
I can't just go out and wash cars and flip burgers.
I need to figure out how I'm going to make a living now I bought into this crap.
So it usually takes them six months or two years to transition.
So those people would be exempt from being evil or ignorant, you see,
because you can't condemn an entire group, and it's not a matter of condemning them,
the legal society, religious society, scientific society, or the political society,
because if you talk to any common oaf on the street in any society,
should you have this legal society, this medical society, this religious society,
this scientific and political society, they all say yes.
At any cost, we should have it.
So they're there to accommodate the people.
So you're in a catch.
You know, in performance, when performance shows are done,
they have amplification speakers, amplifiers.
You know when you get the feedback loop happening with the mic and the speakers?
There's no remedy for that.
You have to unplug it, unplug something, usually the input, the mic.
It has to be unplugged.
Now, if you leave it on, you'll blow up the amps, blow up the speakers,
damage the board, right?
Right now, you're in a feedback loop that isn't being heard.
You're in a catch-22 right now, and there is no remedy for it,
because it's not these groups.
Changing a group or reforming a group is not going to help either.
It might give you a little relief, but the redo is the only way to do it,
and no man can do it.
This is going to be done by a very powerful primary force.
That's why I think when we started off,
we talked about what about being set apart amongst these other things.
Remember?
This was kind of like off to the side.
Absolutely.
Well, before we go right to there, there are a couple of text questions regarding,
and I don't want to get too deep into the text,
because I'd rather you guys called in with this stuff, please.
That's fine.
But I want to answer this, because it seems fascinating to me.
What is the source for the seven kill shots information?
Oh, okay.
Let's give a preface.
Well, I can only be subjectively objective about it, and that would be this.
Amongst any research, especially like you understand, Chuck,
from the research you've been done, you've been known as a researcher, let's say,
for example, or a reporter on things,
you always want to look for first-class information, right?
Higher-grade information, more to the source.
If you're drinking water,
do you want to drink off of a puddle on the side of the road or a river
where all the fish are pooping and things are floating down,
or do you want to go to the spring?
And also first-class information tends to have better quality and more of it, right?
First-class information would be if you're getting an airplane ride across the planet.
It's a free ticket to get on the plane.
Do you want to sit first-class business or coach?
Well, the biblical text is first-class on ancient writs.
I'm not talking about anything Christian or Jewish or whatever.
Those religions have nothing to do with that text at all.
And I keep saying that.
And if you either pass off that statement or you don't like it, that's too bad.
It's true.
It's not dogma.
It's just so evident it's ridiculous to consider otherwise.
So that's where I would get it from.
And it would be shown in the law, the writings, and the prophets.
There are three major sections.
And, you know, here's another thing I want to bring up, Chuck,
and we'll get to the text.
Last week I didn't get any comments on this.
It said that what they call the New Testament is not scripture.
And I didn't get any comment on that.
Why?
It actually is scripture.
And you know why I said it isn't?
Because all of what they call the New Testament
and the people in there lived by what's called scripture,
which is what's called the Old Testament, right?
Right.
So it's a report.
It's a reflection back.
And here's the other thing.
Scripture will continue.
Actually, there's a little bit of a secret thing.
Certain books, you can tell there's a format to how things end,
and certain books were left open to continue.
Certain books, if you read them, you get to the last word, and you're like,
oh, oh, oh, this is like mid-sentence.
What happened?
Right?
Those will continue later.
Just like anything, actually, you know, movies, anything,
you can always tell when, you know, look, this is the end of the entire arc here,
and in other cases, here's your cliffhanger.
It's wide open.
Yeah.
So this is where I would get that.
Now, also, let's not be rigid, right?
And people say, well, I don't believe in that.
Well, I never talked about believing in anything.
Are you examining things, right?
I like to use some of the Hopi prophecies.
Some of it is online.
If you actually look at a lot of what they call the Hopi
and Native American or American original people prophecies,
you'll see that it's very synonymous and parallel to what I've been discussing.
You could look at any – the thing is, try to go to source material,
and you will see that all holy writs –
when I say holy, meaning this is conventional set-apart writs
or communications regarding the gods, regarding the gods,
you'll also find that man reaches a peak in his society
and then is taken down to be cleared after a certain time period to go to the next level.
And the next level, of course, is you're not going to be subject to death,
or as it is now, and disease and other things like that.
And also your life.
I think we mentioned last week, Chuck, it's so difficult to communicate things
because the human lifespan is too short.
What is it, 70, 80, 100?
A hundred years, if you're kind of rare, really 80 is probably a normal expectancy.
Yeah, 65 to 80.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
It's too short, and the infrastructure around –
the infrastructure would be all of nature, all of what we call creation, nature.
Seen and unseen is too big,
and it's actually the subtleties that proclaim what these things really are being ignored.
You know, someone can give you a hint about something that's going to happen,
and if you get the hint, you have more harmony
than if someone sends a brick through the window with a note on it, right?
Wouldn't you rather just take the hint than someone sending a brick through the window?
With a letter strapped to it, right?
Absolutely, yeah.
Yeah, and right now people just aren't getting any hints,
but they do see the hints all around them.
We've always been discussing, I mean, to go backwards in architecture.
Backwards is most recently going, traveling down what they call a highway and byway.
I saw houses going up, and you know what they were building them out of?
Compressed sawdust.
Yeah.
Think about it.
I mean, right?
And, you know, these skyscrapers that you see going up right now,
they're underwritten for 20 years.
You know, 1,000 years ago, architecture was developed to last 1,000 years.
Look at the architecture from 1,000 years ago.
A lot of it's still very robust.
100 years ago, if you look at the skyscrapers built around the turn of the 20th century in Manhattan,
very robust.
Chrysler Building, Empire State Building, and on and on.
You know, what they call, you know, pre-war, post-war skyscrapers are still up.
Right?
Here's a parallel for you.
Much like communication, the quality is decreasing in the newer, you know, what shall I call them?
The newer expressions are lower in quality.
Okay.
There's no reason for more quality.
There's no reason for more quality because things are kicking down, aren't they?
That's right.
Well, here's the thing.
You've heard of – I'm not really – I don't even know what a millennial is until recently.
I had to look it up three times because those things don't – I don't want to – they don't stick.
You know, like if you handed me a 19 – yeah, yeah.
So, but I finally got it.
But, you know, there's Generation X and there's Generation Y, and then there's Generation Z.
Interesting.
Well, what comes after that?
Nada.
English alphabet, nothing, yeah.
Nothing, yeah.
For Canadians or whatever, I guess Zed.
But either way, same thing, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
See, so this is all in front of you, folks, and no one is taking a hint.
So instead of getting a brick through the window with a note, you're going to get the kill shots and other things.
So, I mean, is shaking people up making the world better?
No, no.
Just for context, of course, I'm 44, and I was part of Generation X.
So there you go.
So now, is there a Z?
Yeah, is there a Z?
I'm not sure, but – so close enough.
Close enough, yeah.
Yeah, so regarding – back to regarding the gods.
Now, the wonderful thing about it is that you're going to be seeing not only people's interest in it.
By the way, when people start researching and looking into who the gods are, plural, you're going to see that there are more than one,
and there is a hierarchy, which we've discussed, the hierarchy.
The military order is a wonderful metaphor, you know, because when you say the word army, do you think of just a single unit individual,
or is it a multitude?
When you hear the word god, it's always been transcribed or versionated or translated out of the language as a singular,
but the original language, it's always plural.
Well, an army is a singular thing made up of many parts.
That's right.
So is not god exactly the same?
Yes.
I wonder.
There's a hierarchy, but it's the gods, plural, everywhere else, and there's a plurality of it, and there's a hierarchy there.
But see, more accurately, when you look at an army, they would be soldiers or, you know, whatever.
So really, this is dumbing down the language again.
Yes, English.
Yeah.
English is very poor.
It's a mishmash.
You know, I tell people if you speak English, you know at least 50 Greek words, 30 Hebrew words, 100 Latin words,
and maybe 50 German words right away.
At a minimum, yeah.
Yeah.
So, you know, there's a – so, yeah.
But regarding knowledge of the gods, you're also going to see manifestations of that.
You're going to see a decrease of attendance in these conventional religions and more breakup of them.
Just like if you say you're a zoologist and all you know about is Mickey Mouse,
eventually it's going to catch up to you, and you say, well, if I keep saying I'm a zoologist or a biologist,
I'm going to have to figure out what mice really are.
You see?
This Mickey Mouse stuff doesn't work anymore, so they're going to have to really figure out what things are.
And when these things are – this is bad news for your conventional religious people across the board,
east, west, north, south, any religion.
This is not good news, by the way, right?
I like when we use musical, you know, analogies here.
Look at it this way.
If you walk around with a guitar and you tell people you're a musician,
I guess that's really great until somebody says, okay, play it.
Then you just hang out with musicians or a wannabe, right?
The interesting point is this.
Just like the legal people get over on your ignorance.
You see, there's two ways to fight.
One is to bring the other person down and kick them or you raise yourself up.
But what's happening with the religious society, legal society, medical society, political society, on and on,
is they just bring people down so they can have more of an elevated position, you see,
because they don't want the parody, you know.
That's why you hear about the dumbing down and the health problems in the medical
and the legal society is just, you know, they're getting more guns behind them, right,
more police and all that.
And the religious society now is, I don't know, that's in shambles.
They seek only the most ignorant.
So either way, this aspect of gaining more knowledge about the spiritual realm is going to be a plus for most,
but a negative for some as well.
The interesting point now is that you also have a lot of people that are not in entitled classes
that are at large in society that write books, consider themselves gurus, witches, warlocks,
wizards, spiritualists, contemplated, you know, all this stuff.
They're not going to do so well either, you know, when this information,
people get more engrossed into finding out what things are based.
You know, right now, these people that are witches, wizards, contemplators, meditators, gurus or whatever,
they tend to gravitate to the most ignorant as well because they can't, you know, they buy into it.
And as information starts to become more digested and taken in, these people at large in society, you know,
writing books or having little groups and discussions are going to fall to the side also,
even though they're not part of the institutional class, you know.
So watch for that as well.
A lot of people come to me with discussions and say, oh, this person, he's so intelligent, he's so smart.
I say, well, there's a difference between someone sounding intelligent and sounding smart versus actually they really are.
You see, that's why I would give advice to people years ago when they would question me about doing a presentation.
I'm like, well, who's the audience?
And they would mention the audience.
I'm like, oh, man, it's you're not going to be able to get the information correct in time.
So you know what?
All you got to do is sound like you know what you're talking about.
So, yeah, no, that's it.
Look, like I said, with the guy holding the guitar there, you know, he kind of looks like a musician.
He says he's a musician.
But, hey, don't ever ask him to play the thing because you might discover that he's not,
and he has no clue what's actually happening there.
He just wants to look like a musician.
So there you go.
So there's information.
Also, this mentioned you see the manifestations about the credits, you know,
how things don't have durability anymore or longevity is not built in or considered.
You're going to see a manifestation of the gods.
Like, for example, recently, I don't endorse this or whatever, but Iceland, I think it was Iceland, correct, if anyone.
About a year or two ago, the government actually said that they're going to be installing, reviving the ancient religion there.
It was a form of Odinism, Odin or Wodin, the pagan rites and culture.
They're actually building a temple in Iceland, right, because that was their conventional, you know,
for the people that lived there for, you know, many, many centuries, and they're bringing it back.
Now, there are some people who say, well, that's, you know, not Christian or whatever.
I said, well, the Christian stuff is not any better,
and at least these people are honest, you know, about it.
I'm not, you know, condoning it in any way.
I'm just saying, look, you know, there's a revival.
Why now? Why are they going to bring – another thing is –
Realistically, I've even said, look, you know, you're doing about as much good as erecting the first church of Mr. Potato Head.
And people laugh at me, and I go, well, you know what?
I'll bet you that if it doesn't exist, now that I said it, somebody will do it, and that will be that.
It's actually not really any different.
Well, actually, it slightly is, because they're going back and studying what this god was about
and this system and this convention was about.
So it's based on something.
They're not – if you ask anyone about that pagan temple that they're building in Iceland or that revival of that religion,
they won't just say, oh, my son, you just have to believe.
They won't say that.
They'll start giving you a history.
No, no, no.
I'm talking about the standard conventions that people think of.
Oh, yes, yes.
But, you know, those – also China right now is demolishing a lot of crucifixes, right?
I've been looking at this.
They don't want them, which is – you know, it's part of – it's symbolic of the Christian faith.
But if the Christian faith is supposed to be biblical, that's – it's erroneous, right, by far.
As we've shown in an earlier episode that the image and the shape of the crucifix is not Christian in origin whatsoever.
But it is, because Christianity started – it's just an adaptation of the cult of Serapis and Aeschylus.
But, see, that's not Christianity according to the Christians.
Well, according to the Christians, you just have to believe it doesn't matter.
And I can't stand it when they start throwing Bible verses at you real fast.
And you know what?
You ever hear that?
They say, well, Corinthians, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, or Timothy, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
You know what it sounds like to me when they do that?
Two old beef patties, special sauce, onions, pickles, sesame, whatever, lettuce and a sesame seed bun.
That's what it sounds like to me, McDonald's-style stuff.
So, you know.
Well, you know, it does appear to be food.
Yeah.
So there's going to be a lot.
All of the – you know, Islam is in a shakedown, right?
Obviously, in contrast to the Western world, right?
The Western world does not understand Islam.
Muslims don't understand Islam because it's not based on the Koran.
It's based on Sharia, which is some kind of Freemasonic thing that was put together recently.
So because the Koran explicitly tells you if you want to understand the law, you have to go back and study Moses.
Right?
It actually does.
Because I've actually read a Koran, unlike most people that comment on it.
And in private, I discuss what the source of the Koran and other documents were in private
because it's just too much information has to be laid down and all this other stuff that surrounds people's emotional attachments to things.
And also, when you're – I think we started off the conversation.
When you – let's say you want to have a conversation with someone, Chuck,
and you have three points you want to bring up, and you communicate those points,
and then you get a response from the person, and you're like, how come they didn't get anything I said?
Or that's not what I said.
You know, it's like they're not present.
They're not ready to hear anything right now.
And this is at large.
Which seems to be the general prevailing condition.
Condition, yes.
That I was telling you I'm observing directly, constantly, and I don't think –
I don't know why I'm even observing it to be honest with you because I know I'm not immune to it.
Here I am talking to my – talking about myself unfortunately,
but it's only because I have to contrast myself in the report I'm given here
because if I was completely oblivious, I wouldn't notice this.
But for some reason, I am, and it doesn't appear as though others are.
Why is that happening?
Well, it's pretty blunt.
It's pretty obvious, right?
I mean, it's – well, you can't ignore it maybe.
This is – I think we've mentioned the Internet at large is just a microphone test still, you know,
because the purpose of this global, let's say, you know, the devices, right?
Everyone has handheld devices that do what computers did a while back.
In other words, they can get a data feed, and they can get audio and video streamed to them in a handheld device.
This is going to be increasing and increasing through the entire planet.
I was – I recently just put on a documentary, and it was basically continent of Africa.
You know, we're talking about, you know, huts and things,
and here's a young child walking through the village with a smartphone, right?
You know, I'm like, wow, look at that.
You know, so that means that they can pick up anything anywhere in the world,
even though they're adhering to more of an old world culture, right?
You know, in other words, they're still using straw huts and things like that.
They're not making the houses out of compressed sawdust.
But anyway, yeah, so this is the carry-on.
It's very important to see that when you hear a threat of the Internet being shut down,
it's not going to happen because there's forces behind it beyond what mankind is acknowledging, right?
And what the gods demand is that there's no excuses.
You see, everyone has to know these things for a reason.
The last thing you want is later on they say, well, we didn't know, right, and yet we were subject to it.
It's very important.
And the gods, you don't have to follow what they want to communicate to mankind through ancient writ.
And if you don't want to follow it, that's okay, but you should inquire.
There should be some inquiry.
You know, how many times have you ever heard someone, you ask someone a question about their preference,
and they say, well, I don't like that, and you say, why?
And you ask them why, and they don't have a reason, you know,
like they've never even inquired or tasted it, you know, or anything like that, right?
Let's say ice cream.
You know, they'll say, well, I don't like strawberry.
Why?
Well, you know, I just don't like it.
Well, have you ever tasted it?
No, I have not even inquired, you know.
So that's something that people will not be able to get away with on this planet.
No, I get it, and that's the interesting thing because really, honestly, that's what children often do.
They simply decide they don't like something, although they have no idea why.
They've never experienced it.
No inquiry.
Yeah, no inquiry at all.
And there will be more inquiry or exposure to this.
So, again, the main thing basically to comprehend is that there's going to be a loosening or opening of this topic
and being able to communicate it in about a year or so.
Right now, you're still throwing marshmallows at a brick wall regarding it,
unless there are those who have decided or the stream has allowed to start getting a head start.
And, by the way, it's a little late in the game, but not really.
Those that do tend to practice objectivity in their research or their findings or reports
are going to be far ahead of the game than those that contemplate the fads and the things that are in place right now.
Right?
If you look at a lot of the researchers, I mean,
look at all the political events that happened in the past couple of years,
buildup of threats of government crackdown, EMPs, economic and environmental disasters.
How many of them have ever really come to fruition?
None.
And I find myself at odds with nearly everyone examining everything because I keep saying,
what are you looking at?
And they speak to me about sentimentality.
They speak to me about some preconceived notion that has nothing to do with the particular subject at hand.
It's really, really bizarre to me.
To me.
Well, I've been noticing this for almost two decades, and I don't wish it upon anyone.
But if you are noticing it now, it should be the impetus to actually buckle down and get real.
In other words, stay with the objectivity and seek it out and give good reports.
Some advice I'd give to people, if they want to have more fruitful communion with people,
is avoid people that practice heresy.
In other words, something is good or something is right because they like it.
Right?
Or true because they like it.
What if something is true and you don't like it?
Can you then say, I don't like it, so it's not true?
You see?
This is what people are engaging in now still, this thing about intent.
How can you have intent without inquiry?
Right?
A broken car on the side of the road, most of the time you can intend for it to go as much as you want.
It ain't going anywhere until someone with technical expertise or mechanic or technical expertise on your own is able to remedy the situation.
And this is the aspect of law.
There is no morality or law at large.
There is only morality and law that comes from the gods or a god, period.
And then you have to go up the ladder in hierarchy, just like the military.
If you're a private, the sergeant tells you, and then above him would be the major and colonel, then the general and the emperor.
And as you go higher up, you notice there are more rules and laws.
And these laws are liberating, by the way.
And I've been in conversations with people regarding this.
And they're like, well, who makes the laws, Greek?
Who decides on what laws we do?
I was like, you do.
You do.
You see?
Because it's very simple.
There's this overwhelming thing to be buried by numbers, right?
Oh, there's so much to do.
It disables.
You can't do anything.
You eat it one bite at a time.
And a very simple way to fix the world, which is not going to happen, but is very simple.
Half the people, just half, it sounds like a big number, but just half, helped one person.
Doesn't that take care of the whole world, the whole other half?
How simple is it just to help one person or one thing at a time?
If half the people decided to do one thing at a time, that would take care of the other half immediately.
So all these things that people are questioning and targeting as their woes and ailments and all that are just asinine.
But knowledge of the gods is going to be important because the focus is also going to be geographical.
Chuck, you know when you look at a racetrack or an event track, something that goes round or circular,
imagine the starting line.
And once the event goes, it's in a circular fashion.
Now, I want you to imagine the finish line.
Where is the finish line?
The same place the starting line is.
That's right.
Where does all information lead to where mankind started?
That part of the world, doesn't it?
You know what I mean by that part of the world?
Certainly.
What they call that part, Tigris, Euphrates.
Some people might say African continent.
No one's ever going to say it all started near the North Pole or in China or in South America.
You notice how everyone is sort of in agreement that it all started there?
It's definitely not Australia.
And this whole conversation really boils down to one thing in my mind,
which is an old African proverb, which loosely I will translate to say,
how does one eat an elephant?
Well, one bite at a time.
And I know that sounded, oh, now he's gone cryptic too.
But that's my commentary here regarding this.
Yeah, no cloven hoof doesn't chew the cud.
So yeah, but yeah, there you go.
It's not fit for eating, but the metaphor is very fit.
Right.
So everything will be going back.
How do you know the event is going to be over?
When you're approaching the finishing line and everything has been focusing there.
And when the fires are put out in the Middle East and these things start to happen,
it's going to seem very normal and natural.
So you're basically being set up.
All of humankind is being set up.
Now here's the thing.
Once you consider, this is loosely,
we brought this up about being set apart in the first few minutes of what we started,
the sonic project tonight.
When you really focus on being set apart and you look at how superficial
and shallow people are in general at large,
that when you're set apart, it doesn't matter if they are doing well or not.
In other words, if society goes better, you still stay set apart.
If society goes downhill, you still stay set apart.
Whether society at large is doing well or doing poorly,
you remain set apart from it just from the very fact that the society of humans on this planet
until the next phase is so unstable, it's not worth buying into their good stuff or their bad stuff.
You know what I mean?
So if you're in the special forces, you're always in the special forces.
Even if you're not on duty and you're at home sleeping,
all of that training and what you know you can apply can be applied at any time,
whether you're in the field or at home.
That's the thing about being set apart.
You're always set apart and you try to be lawful based on your god, and I say your god.
You'll notice that you're not going to find a lot of law based on what is put out there as god or gods.
And as you start seeking law, you'll see that it gets narrower and narrower and narrower.
And there really is only one authority that gives law in that capacity.
But then again, if everyone wanted to be set apart, would there be any set apartness anymore?
No, right?
In other words, if everything was hot, would there be any cold anymore?
No.
There would be no way to discern it.
See, if everything was good, would there be any evil?
No.
If everything was evil, would there be any good?
So you need the contrast.
So this is a time of contrast.
And this contrast of being set apart appears to be going on.
We don't have much information about what comes after the next thousand years,
but it appears that it will still be their positioning of setting oneself apart.
But here's the thing.
It's going to be a little painful in the next decade and a half,
but you're going to be leading into a wonderful, wonderful situation for all life,
not just humans throughout the, should we use the term, universe.
And that's something we've never really discussed, but the universe is not as big as you're being told.
It's more like a facade that's being shown.
So anyway, did I just say that?
Yes, you did.
You know what might be painful for some people is that we're just about at the end of this particular sonic event,
which is Ocelli and the Greek Reloaded.
Once again, you can email thegreek at uncommonradio.com.
I can be reached through ocelli.com.
Americanfreedomradio.com is the place where this show exists.
And nowhere else does this particular interaction exist.
That's that.
And, Greek, what do you think we should cap this one off with?
Oh, go ahead and give us a thought there.
We can go on and on and on about this, but the thing is there's a scarcity,
not a scarcity, there's a scarcity of a base or a foundation to keep building on.
You see what I mean?
And when you're building a foundation or a base, you're destroying and building at the same time.
You know how you have to break the soil, dig things out.
It gets dirty and messy.
If it rains, it gets muddy.
There's no foundation in society right now to build on more of this subject.
Well, we may have to move on to the universe because I think we've thoroughly covered the particular rock we're standing on
and the inhabitants therein.
So I think that the next episode we should focus on the universe and the facade.
What do you think?
Yeah, we could.
And I think that'll be quite an interesting thing to see,
maybe to discuss a little bit of what's behind the curtain or the tent.
There you go.
So this ends Episode 7 of Ocelli and the Greek Reloaded.
And Episode 8 will occur, well, approximately seven days from this one.
Everybody have a good night.
And American Freedom Radio is the place where this came from.
Greek, thanks again.
Thank you, Chuck.
Take care, everybody.