All righty, everyone, we have the Greek on for round two.
Daniel, if you want to take it away, I know you had some questions to prepare.
Yeah, sure.
So we did leave some loose ends last time.
Namely, the Greek gave the recipe for gold.
And if I understood right, that was monatomic gold?
Biological.
It is gold as one would consider gold in appearance and in property, but it's biological.
It would have a much lower melting point because it was just created by some fungus in the mitochondria of fungus.
It has an evolution of its own.
And can you consume this gold like we hear, ormus, or monatomic gold?
Yes, you could, but it needs to go to another level eventually in order to be –
it would be better to consume it by feeding it to other biologicals like plants or animals that you're going to eat,
but hopefully just plants, if that makes sense.
Yeah, so they could finish the process.
It's kind of like eating a green tomato or something that is not –
you can eat food that is not ready to be eaten, let's say organic food, vegetables and fruits,
but they would not be as pleasant as effective, right?
Yeah, and is there an optimum dose?
I bet there is such a thing as too much, right?
Yes, but remember, the optimum dose then again would be to what you would dilute this in water to put in your garden
and then eat the vegetables later.
So the optimum dose would be on how good you are on making tinctures and dilutions, if you understand that concept.
If you take the purely mechanistic chemical sense, the more the better.
But if you understand the energetic side of it, it could be the less the better,
and the less of it should be of highest quality.
I see.
And the other loose thread was you promised a recipe for aqua sargentis.
Yes, very, very, very, very important.
Can I say very about ten times?
Then that's how important it is.
There is something called colloidal silver.
Should I just give the background or do you want to ask any more about it before you –
No, go ahead.
Okay.
Even in old texts they say silver is good for your health,
and it's very well known that silver is a fungicide and bactericide.
And by the way, fungus and bacteria, notice I didn't say the V-I-R-U-S word
because that is something completely different.
Those things, the only time they bring harm to the body, they do not bring harm to any body.
It's what they produce in their own metabolic rate is what harms another body, right?
For example, you could be loaded –
you could take something that's living and load it with a certain type of fungus
or bacteria and they're fine.
But depending on what that fungus or bacteria takes from the system,
consumes, or gives off, defecates, those end results
and primary initial reactions is what damages the host, you see.
It's not the presence of the bacteria or the fungus itself.
So just to hearken back to the gold recipe earlier, you know,
that gold was produced by the intelligence of the Saccharomyces vs. Cervasius fungus,
saying we need to sacrifice a part of our colony to bond itself to the silver
because the silver is dangerous to us.
Metabolize gold in the DNA on the mitochondria and then plate the silver with gold
so now it becomes inert, you see.
Okay, so that's another proof is if the silver was not antifungal or antibacterial,
that process would not be able to take place, right?
So there's this big wave that's been going on for many decades now
about colloidal silver for health.
And if you go online or whatever,
they tout that their method of producing colloidal silver,
which is a very fine metal particle suspended in the water,
is best because it has the highest count of silver.
And I always shook my head on that because that is a chemical mechanical process
that if you have a metal in solution, actually in metal form,
the body can view it as a toxin, okay?
And this goes almost for most metals.
Even though there are things in certain cultures that if you consume gold
in certain ways, you know, that's why the monatomic gold is so important.
It's nonmetallic.
So what we found out is since we know that without a doubt there are benefits
to having silver in the body, how do we do that?
So we found out that the best way to do that is to have a colloidal silver method
where they have the two electrodes, positive and negative.
Actually, sometimes we use a neutral in between.
So three electrodes, the one in the middle is neutral.
But let's just say positive, negative in the water.
And what you – the best thing to do is because this ultimately is going to be
used for consumption by an organic living biological being, right?
We're not making it for an industrial process.
So we notice that in the world whenever we have electricity, it's usually a single cell.
If you take an orange or a potato or a lemon and you put electrodes in it
in a voltmeter, you'll see there's voltage in there, okay?
So we found that a single cell, something like a battery that you would use
for a torch or a flashlight, a AA, AAA, or D battery,
they're all considered single cells.
And whenever you make a chemical reaction to make electricity,
each cell roughly is one-and-a-half volts, right?
Depending on the chemicals, it could be higher,
or if it's a biological acid and other substrates and minerals, it's much lower.
So what I suggest is you have your two silver electrodes.
They must be fine silver, not sterling silver where you have an alloy of copper
and zinc and lead, just fine silver.
The more fine, the better.
And only apply a voltage, even a used battery that's one volt is even better,
just for a few seconds to five or ten minutes maximum.
And the silver with the electricity will, quote-unquote,
let's just use whichever word you like, program, rearrange, structure the water,
the memory of the water.
This sounds like a lot of pseudoscience to people,
but it's been proven that water has memory.
In accord with the silver.
Now, if you take this solution that only took a few seconds or a minute or two
or even five minutes to make, and you took it to a material lab,
they will not find any silver in it, material at all.
But anyone who takes this or consumes it for antibacterial, antifungal,
or certain things that you can say the silver will help,
they'll have immediate results.
I mean, much, much more powerful than any chemical silver that are touting to
have a high silver content.
Some silver purveyors, colloidal silver purveyors,
show you a colloidal silver solution that is cloudy with silver.
I'm like, that is like something you should maybe make a new battery with.
Don't drink that.
So that is, and the thing is, I don't call it colloidal silver,
because whenever you take this to a material scientist,
because they say there's no trace of silver here,
but it acts like the most powerful silver solution.
So calling it colloidal silver is a misnomer,
because colloidal just means very small particle.
You won't find anything in there.
So I call it aqueous argentum, which argentum is silver,
aqueous meaning water, so basically silver solution,
but no silver present.
The interesting thing with this also, there's no electrode wear.
The only caveat to doing this system is,
because it works on a much higher energetic level,
when you're using, let's say, two clean pieces of silver,
one goes to the positive of the one volt battery,
and the other one goes to the negative of the one volt battery,
you must be very careful and sure that you always connect those pieces
appropriately as such.
If you ever reverse them, the next, let's say,
the first time you do it, silver piece A is to positive
and silver piece B goes to negative on the battery.
If you reverse them and B goes the other terminal,
it will make the dirtiest, it would look very, very dirty.
So it seems to also go both ways.
The silver does not only react with the water,
but the water reacts with the silver,
where you should never reverse polarity.
I tell people if you reverse polarity,
you'll notice it gets very, very dirty,
and it will not work again, which doesn't make sense scientifically,
because a metal is just a piece of metal.
It doesn't matter which polarity, right?
You see how they say?
So you have to start off with new pieces of silver if accidentally you
reverse the polarity.
Or you can hammer the silver and heat it and re-temper it
and reprogram the silver.
So I know this might sound a little kooky to many,
but I just wanted to put it out for those that recognize what I'm saying.
Sure, sure.
And what is the best way to go about imbibing this?
You mean on using it?
Yes.
I would say that, again, the approach would be very, very simple.
The same way you have this solution, you can either,
let's say you just made a glass of it,
you can drink the glass or you can put the glass in a dark,
cold place and add just a few, a little bit of it to another glass.
In other words, you can dilute it quite a ways,
depending on the condition of the person.
Like someone has a strong candida condition or various other things,
or athlete's foot or things like that,
you might want to just use it immediately,
because I would say it has a shelf life of less than three days, 72 hours.
And it should be kept in the fridge and in the dark, away from light.
Because there's like a photophoresis effect that the light actually changes it
and the temperature changes it.
I think we've never gone over that water should always be stored at 39 degrees
Fahrenheit or 4 degrees Celsius, right?
And it should be in the dark if you want to increase the quality of the water.
So we would consider that.
Also, when you're making this material, it should not be a very high mineral water.
Bottled spring water or very good filtered water usually is best.
It doesn't have to be distilled water, but distilled water works just as well.
So it would be for drinking and adding to drinking water.
Not for cooking, by the way, because the heat will destroy it.
I see.
And in addition to drinking cool water,
which I think you said that we should always do that,
or at least put it in the fridge and then drink it,
I think you also stressed the importance of using the ovoid shape.
Can you go over that?
Sure.
The ovoid shape is the best shape that's in nature that's available to us to keep
self-sustained movement in the fluid.
For example, when fluid is moving, there's no pathogen that can develop, right?
So give us a very simple example.
I won't use rectilinear boxes or rectangles, just round things for now.
When you have a sphere and you put a liquid in it,
because the center of the sphere to the inside walls is exactly the same distance,
if there's any heat convection or movement in the liquid,
because the center is the same distance all around,
it will stabilize and become stagnant very quickly.
If we make an ellipse shape where it's the sphere elongated evenly on either side,
well, the elongated portions of that container are not the same distance,
so what will happen is it will take longer to become stagnant,
and eventually the symmetry of the two ends of the ellipse will catch up with each
other, they'll mirror each other, and cancel out any movement in between.
When you have an ovoid shape,
which is basically a sphere with one end of it elongated to a point
and the other end more oblong or round,
the distance, the center of the object, of that ovoid,
is no longer in the geometric center.
The geometric center is much lower.
It offsets almost as if you put a pentagram.
If you put it in a pentagram and find the center of a pentagram,
it would match, by the way.
So the fluid would move in the container,
and when it reaches the pointy part of the egg,
it will move towards the point and then up here,
the opposite end will want to move towards the more oblong,
less curved section.
And when they come back to the middle,
the fluid that was from the narrower part of the egg will meet the fluid that
was at the wider part of the egg and pass each other because they're at a
different wave, let's say.
You see a different motion, rate of motion.
And when they pass each other,
now the side that was against the more oblong, flatter part of the egg,
that water meets the point,
and the water that was on the narrower part meets the wider part.
They will reverse their frequency or movement or wave motion and move towards
the center again, and this will just keep repeating indefinitely.
And now you have a very mild form of convection or movement inside of the
ovoid-shaped vessel without adding external energy,
like an impeller or something to move it.
So are you saying that we should always drink our liquids from a wine glass?
Well, let's just say before we go to drinking,
liquids, especially high-quality liquids,
should always be stored in something that is like that, high-quality liquids.
Like if you look at the ancient amphoras that the ancient used,
their wines were stored, their oils and water in amphoras where they were very
narrow at one end and very wide on the other, right?
This also goes for seeds, seed storage and things like that.
When you're drinking it, let's say,
the primary concern is the storage of good, high-quality liquids in ovoid.
When you say should we drink it out of a wine glass or something like that,
think about the process.
When you remove it, let's say, from the amphora
or the ovoid-shaped container to drink it, there's not a lot of time there.
You've just removed it, and when you pour something to drink,
how long does it stay stagnant before you drink it?
Whether it's immediate or a few minutes, maybe an hour,
it's not going to have a big effect on it.
It's more how the liquids are stored.
Yeah, I see.
Makes sense.
Since we're on the subject of hidden truth related to health,
can you speak about how much role does light play in our bodies?
Massive.
We have light approaching us from the outer, and we have light on the inner.
I think we did, on the last time we met, on the last sonic event,
a lot of comparisons for people to look up a car tire, the intestines,
the skin, the lung, and so forth, right?
I would encourage anyone now if you – actually, we could all do it right now.
It's better if we do it in real time.
If you look up a cross-section of a large fiber-optic cable,
and if you just type that in, fiber-optic cable,
if someone's listening to this and they're driving or whatever,
fiber-optic cable cross-section,
which means you're just cutting 90 degrees through the length,
and if you view that, you'll get a sense of what's going on geometrically.
You don't have to know anything about fiber-optic cable.
It's just what do you see.
There's a certain image.
And then if you do a search, image search, on nerve cross-section, right,
as in nerves that animals and plants and humans have.
Let's just say animals and humans.
They're the same, geometrically.
Proportion, geometric, right?
You see that?
The filaments, even the filament structure, where if you say fiber-optic cable,
usually when you see the way it's promoted, they won't show you the housing.
They'll just pull out a little cable.
It looks almost like a fishing line with light going through the end of it, right, typically.
That would be called a filament.
So if you look at the cross-section of the nerves, you'll see similar filaments.
And you made a passing reference about growing skin back with light,
and was that on a need-to-know, or could you go into that?
Both, yeah.
So I would recommend people go and study a guy, Chromotherapy,
C-H-R, just like Chroma, Chromotherapy, I believe it's called.
There are several books on it.
Are you ready for this?
The author's name is Dinshaw Ghadialdi.
And Dinshaw Ghadialdi believed
and demonstrated in the early 20th century the effects of light.
Is he Punjabi or something?
Yeah, he's from India, yeah, Persia, that whole area, Persia.
I think he was Persian.
His interesting story was back in the – he had a lab in the 1930s,
you might like this, or late 20s,
and he was encroaching already on the medical industry because he was healing people
with very intense colored light.
And they sent the Army, and they dropped a 50-pound bomb on his house,
and all the neighbors saw it because back then it was the Army Air Corps.
And if you look at the history of that, it says his lab was in his house
and it was destroyed by a fire.
Yeah, after the Army drops a 50-pound bomb on your roof, yes, it will be.
By the way, that's still being done today.
It's less common than it was, let's say, during the Obama years.
But if they didn't like you, they dropped an F-16, dropped the bomb on your house.
It happened on the West Coast several times.
And then they would call the gas company to come and dump some old gas lines
and say it was a gas line explosion.
Now they use drones, by the way, small ones.
He's a man, huh?
What's that?
Big Mike was born a man, right?
Yeah.
Well, we'll get into the cloning aspect one day, maybe further down the road.
And I would just say from a cloning aspect, that's his mom.
But that's another story.
Who became a man and then became a woman.
Yeah.
A Greek has lost his mind, right?
Okay.
So let's go back to the light healing.
He found out early on there was a few people that were very ill,
probably even the late 1800s, and they couldn't do anything for him.
So they brought him in.
He was always looking for holistic techniques.
This is Dinsha Gadialdi, chromotherapy.
He put some milk and water in blue glass, just standard blue glass bottles,
in the sun.
And when the person drank this after a few days, they were recovered.
He found out various the main one was blue, the color blue.
So basically putting water in blue glass, putting it out in the sun for a few
minutes or in light and drink that water, it will imbue the water with that
energy, the blue.
By the way, I just want to say from a personal experiment,
if anyone has ever gotten too much sun, like you can experiment with this,
especially people who live near the coast in the summer.
If you're ever getting too much sun, you get a sunburn, a mild sunburn,
or even a pretty sunburn where it hurts to the touch, right?
Most people have had that.
It might last a few days, actually by the end of the day or so,
or the next day still.
But if you ever notice you're in a condition like that,
what you could do is get a very intense blue light.
LEDs don't work as well as incandescent, but you can do it with LEDs.
Go in a room, put up blankets so there's no light from the outside coming in,
and put yourself under some very intense blue light for about an hour.
You walk out later, and guess what happened to your sunburn?
Gone.
And if we get more intense with this, what if you had a burn with a blister?
You do maybe two hours, more intense blue light,
guess what happens to that burn?
Gone.
On and on.
He was able to recover people in burn victims in hospitals that they were just
giving them morphine because they had half of the skin burned off of their
body, second and third degree burns.
And he just didn't use a blue light.
But he also used yellow lights and green lights to regrow the skin,
and it was a therapy that took over two or three days.
And the lights that he used were basically very strong theatrical lights,
you would call them today,
or thousand-watt lights with colored glass in front of them.
In other words,
the lights were so intense that you should wear eye protection, right?
So the technicians would wear a blindfold,
the patient would wear a blindfold.
There's still some photos online about this.
There are people that have a lot of success,
but most of them do not have a lot of success,
just like with the colloidal silver and things like that,
is because they're not doing what is being prescribed initially.
Just like Tesla, you know,
a lot of times when industry puts up patents in the patent office,
you could look it up.
They leave out some key components, so you cannot reproduce it.
Or they might put something in that if you do put that thing in,
it will not work.
But if you go look at Tesla's patents, I assure you,
if you follow the patent strictly, it will work.
And I don't mean when he has wire and certain things,
you don't go to a modern electronic supply,
because when Tesla built these things,
there was no electrical supply, electronic supply.
He got pieces of wood, brass, copper, cloth, leather, rubber,
and he made it himself.
So the reason why, let's see, so, again, back to the chromotherapy,
most people that try this now are not being successful because they're not
using the intensity, the light intensity that's necessary.
And I could add that there is another scientist who deals,
focuses on this bioluminescence,
and he dropped out of Silicon Valley and invested all his money into
studying this and actually delivered, after many years,
a product that is called Analema Wand.
And all it contains is very, very structured water inside of quartz.
And all you do is put it in a cup of water and the structure is, yeah.
Yeah, I've heard of this, yeah.
And the results are spectacular in terms of the plants live much longer
and overall in humans as well.
He's all about statistics.
And the point is it never diminishes its effectiveness.
It only ever goes up, actually.
And what you do to recharge it is expose it to the sun every few months,
and that's all it needs to maintain its coherence.
Yes, the sun is, let's just divert real quick because we brought up light
and we brought up the silver and the light and the water.
I hope, well, this might take some people aback.
Some people know this.
They say the sun is hot, but as you start going up higher and higher,
the closer you go to the sun, it gets colder and colder, right?
And they say that if you go out of the atmosphere, it's even colder.
What you see as the sun is you cannot see it in space.
If you went into outer space, if you believe in such a thing,
and you looked in the direction of the sun, you will not see it.
But if you look at your body, the spacesuit or your spaceship will have light on it, right?
And the purpose of this is, for example, it's easy to prove,
because you see when the sun is rising and it's kind of like a yellowish orange,
but when it sets, it's more red.
How can it change colors?
It has nothing to do with the sun.
It's because the sun only appears the way it does because of our atmosphere.
That's why, for example, planets like Mercury that are really closest to the sun,
they have polar ice caps on Mercury, right?
You can look this up.
Are you familiar with this then?
No.
Is it hot?
We just need to go over this again.
I know it's the atmosphere.
Well, it only gets as hot as the atmosphere will allow it to, right?
Okay.
Mars, it supposedly gets purple at night, and it's a 28-hour day.
Sure, because of the Mars atmosphere, not the dust in the air.
Like, for example, you could look this up.
Do you know that the Earth is closest to the sun during winter
in the northern hemisphere?
What?
What did you say?
I thought the closer we got to the sun, the hotter it got.
Mercury, that's so close to the sun, man.
There's molten.
They tell you there's molten lead on the surface, right?
But it has polar ice caps.
I'm not saying it.
It's in their own mainstream stuff.
Now it is.
Okay.
All right.
By the way, everybody cover your ears.
I'm going to say something.
A lot of people have gotten in trouble, these observatories.
You know when there's maximum solar events, that means a lot of sunspots,
you know, the black spots?
Make sure everybody's covering their ears for this.
When they looked inside of those sunspots very closely,
they saw structures and machinery.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
You could take your cover.
Let's go back to the conversation.
That's really out there, right, for some.
Okay.
So the sun is basically what you would call, it's like a portal.
It's a center.
It's an area that's giving power to the solar system through,
and we call it light in our visible spectrum.
But 99% of the energy from the sun is not light.
In other words, if you really know what you're doing
and you really understand what Tesla was saying, which is difficult,
because Tesla did not use engineering terms or scientific terms,
you will get more energy from the sun at night
or without getting it from the light itself, you see.
All right, if that makes any sense.
I think it's the difference between transversal and longitudinal light,
the fact that you don't see the sun normally.
Right, the transverse.
Like, for example, if you went up into the atmosphere right now
and removed the atmosphere in a certain area
and it would look black where the sun, you wouldn't see blue,
you wouldn't see the sun at all.
You would see the sun on other parts, right.
You need the filter of the transformation of the transverse light.
Just like, for example, during the day,
if you go into a very deep mineshaft and you look up,
the mineshaft should be more than 200 or 300 feet down.
If you look up at the blue sky, you will see the stars in the blue sky,
just like at night.
But as you come up the mineshaft,
the transverse light that starts bouncing around everywhere
and agitating and perturbating the atmosphere
and itself through the atmosphere,
like micromirrors and other things like that with the gases,
it blurs out all of the stars.
Yeah, light is a – so also, you know, you don't see with your eye,
you see with your brain, right, if that makes any sense.
The eye is just a sensor.
It just processes what comes in.
It's upside down.
The brain then makes use of it.
So you don't – in order – when it comes to optics, by the way,
you don't have to fool the eye like they say.
That's a misnomer.
You have to fool the brain.
So if you can convince someone that they're not seeing what they see,
that's good enough, even though it came through the eye, right?
You see how simple this is?
You said outer space if you believe in that.
What were you alluding to?
There's many ways to say that.
Like, for example, when you say outer space,
most people will say what they're being shown by mainstream, right,
NASA and all that, right?
And we know that very easy 90%, if not more, is fake.
So how can we use something fake that's being shown to us that is CGI
or false information as a notion, right?
And I think you also hinted last episode to the fact that flat Earth
also got it partially correct.
Can you go into a little detail there?
Sure.
Yeah, I made a big deal about the flat Earth and the round Earth
and the concave Earth back in the late 80s.
But that was not the time to make a big deal about it, right?
So there was actually a flat Earth club and all that.
I wasn't a part of it, but I attended just to see what the arguments were,
of course, right?
So you know how I said that you don't see with your eye,
you see with your mind, right?
Okay, that's why, for example, in some of the SSP stuff,
your eyes can be replaced with a cyborg eye, right?
It works just as well as long as you can interface with the brain.
And you see it in sci-fi also.
And actually it exists.
But when you talk about flat Earth and round Earth,
it depends on what part of the cruise ship you're on
and also what you're trying to master.
To the common people, it's irrelevant.
But to the commoner or someone who wants to be a master at what they do,
and this is a term that's no longer being used except for in college,
which is irrelevant, by the way, if you want to be a master farmer,
the best farmer, aggie, agriculturalist,
you know that the Earth is stationary.
Not you believe.
You know the Earth is stationary and the sun moves around the Earth
because you see it.
It rises in the eastern part.
It goes overhead and it sets in the west,
and it takes a different path in the winter than it does in the summer.
And in the fall and the spring, it takes the same path for a few days
or a week.
The reason why this is very important to you,
that the Earth is flat and the sun moves around the Earth,
is to orientate your crops.
Certain crops need to be in certain forms of light, right?
Also, you know if you're a farmer, the Earth is flat,
because if you're digging a ditch to bring water for a long distance,
water keeps its level.
So it has to start at a higher point.
And the destination, as the water moves along the Earth to its destination,
that point must be lowering and lowering in order to deliver it to your crops.
You see?
So in order to be agriculture, it must be flat.
If you're going to do architecture, it must be flat.
They have things called levels and plumbobs, which is vertical or A-frame.
When you're building, putting up a building,
the outer wall on the north side, you're not going to say,
it's okay if it bends this way out towards the south,
and the wall that's towards the north bends out towards the north,
because the Earth is round.
We should compensate, right?
No, no, no.
Any building that you go to,
the walls are purely vertical based on devices as if the Earth is flat,
you see, for architecture also.
Here's the other thing.
If you are a surveyor, though, you're surveying,
you're measuring the Earth to make maps and things like that,
you better know, not believe, you know the Earth is round, right?
Now it became round, right?
Why?
Because I've done this.
I did an internship with surveying 40 years ago,
and we went out with theodolites and rods to measure heights and things,
and some people started five miles away, and we met in the middle,
but we didn't meet in the middle.
We were about 100 meters off, right?
And we did it again over and over.
That's why when you look at maps, you'll see that certain lines,
they have to jag it off, especially in the U.S.
when they try to do a grid method.
But some meet like the four corners area,
but you can't do a four corners with all the states like that.
So if you're doing surveying, and also some navigation,
if not most navigation, you know the Earth is round.
There's some people that try to use that the Earth is flat,
and the navigators and airplane pilots say they fly in a straight line.
I believe that's disinformation.
So the navigators and the surveyors, I know firsthand,
you know the Earth is round and curved,
but if you're doing agriculture or architecture, you know –
notice I didn't say believe – you know the Earth is flat.
So now what is reality?
It depends on where you are.
If you're just – to cover yours again,
a poor schmuck running around this Earth trying to figure out why you're here,
and you're born and you die and you want a retirement
and you drive a bus or whatever, nothing against bus drivers,
but you know what I mean, and you watch football and drink beer,
it has nothing to do with you.
The only concern is for people who want to be a master at something.
So that's another way of saying that it doesn't even matter what label we put on it,
whether it's flat or not.
It does because if I'm a master agriculturist, it's flat.
If I'm a master surveyor or a master navigator –
Objectively.
Objectively, then even when you're giving information,
you have to see who you're giving the information to
to be in the appropriate vessel.
You have to be a master, but if you're –
let me just throw a lascivious joke.
If you're a master baiter, it doesn't matter either.
So, yeah, again, even – let's say, Daniel,
that's a good point you bring up because I always say in the older sonic events
from years and years ago, be objective as possible, be objective.
Let's objectify, right?
That eliminates the duality and separation.
The reason why I always stress objectivity is for unification.
Subjectivity is division.
Objectivity is unification.
Do you see that simply?
Yeah.
And some people are taught – okay, here's the ultimate for humanity.
You ready?
We pick a leader, either human or nonhuman,
and we all start taking – we merge our emotions with our minds,
and we develop a hive mind, and then we go to the next level.
Do you notice that some of the things in there that I said
were going to irk people the wrong way?
You know, even in a hive, they're all individual, by the way.
You merge your emotion with your reason, so now you have full control.
You see, this kind of stuff pisses people off.
Let me give you an example.
The best way for people to live is through anarchy.
Oh, that's a terrible word, Greek.
Well, anarchy is the Greek word which means – ana means without.
Archos means leader.
What – in order to have – by the way, when you have an anarchy in real life,
not what you've been told, but the propaganda, in anarchy,
there is no chaos and there is no crime.
Anarchy means that each man – anarchy means castle doctrine.
Each man, each family where they live is their castle.
You cannot have anarchy unless everyone is very highly educated
and they're on the same page with each other.
If you lived in an anarchistic society where everybody was highly educated
and you didn't have any armies either, by the way.
Everyone had enough ordinance and knowledge to protect their country
without a separate army.
You see where I'm going with this?
This is called castle doctrine in some American states.
You have the right to protect to the death your own property and your family.
So you've been told that anarchy is a bad word.
It just means no leader.
It's a leaderless society.
Everyone is a leader.
So whether you're talking – so an anarchistic society – oh, the Greeks are anarchists.
That's bad.
Okay, that's what most people will be thinking to this point.
So they purge the bullshit.
I used a medical term there, by the way.
So when you – let's say you were to go to a true anarchistic society.
It doesn't matter if it was 100 people or a billion people.
It doesn't matter who you talk to.
You're going to get the same story from everyone.
Everybody knows the laws.
Everybody knows science.
Everybody knows what your quote-unquote rights are.
I don't think there's – rights mean you've broken the law,
and now you have rights, you see.
So everybody knows what the right – the difference between right and wrong
and is willing to fight and protect it, you see.
Free people do not ask for rights.
That's – right for what?
What did I do wrong that now I'm under rights that I've given up my freedom?
This has nothing to do with sovereignty, by the way, because you're not sovereign either, you see.
Do you see where I'm going with this?
The flat earth and the curved earth is exactly the same.
It's the same category with objectivity.
And the biggest factor is where you are, right?
Like the planet decides the laws.
The – well, the planet is actually like a bird's nest.
I've never said this before.
When you have birds in a nest, it's a place of protection.
And when you say the planet also, when you build a roof – build a house,
do you live on the roof or do you build inside of it?
So if you see a planet like ours, you fly by because these are primitive people here.
We want to communicate with the ones that are smart enough to live inside of it, right?
If you saw a neighbor that built a new house and lived on his roof for 10 years,
don't you feel like after a week you want to go to him and say,
hey, dummy, why don't you come down and go inside, you see?
Okay, so this stuff that I talk about is not for this society.
It's for the next society.
But let me go back to the hive mind.
Even when Zan was – oh, that's a bad thing, the hive mind.
Well, when – hive mind meaning you're a very high form of telepathy.
Can there be any corruption or lying if everybody knows what everybody else is thinking?
No, not at all.
Does it mean you're going to lose your individuality?
No, but I'll take what you say, yes.
But there would be no off-ticking down the timeline of deceit and stuff like that
where politicians stand up on podiums and lie to everyone.
There's no politicians in anarchy.
I know.
I'm just saying there would just be none of that leading the herd off a cliff.
Right.
In other words, you never want to pick – in an anarchistic society,
you could still have leaders as representatives,
but you would never want to pick someone who wanted to be a leader.
You want to go and find someone who is wise, good at decision-making,
very psychic telepathic tendencies also, can read people well,
and if you approach them and say, we want you to be our leader,
he will tell you, no, hell no.
That's the one you want to make your leader,
and you find some way to incentivize him, the one who doesn't want to be your leader.
Let me give you an example.
They still propagandize that George Washington was the first president of the United States, right?
Total hogwash.
There was like six presidents before him under the Articles of Confederation.
The Articles of Confederation, which were done, had presidents,
and they only lasted six months or so.
And then they did the Constitution 17 or 15 years later,
and they never expunged or got rid of the Articles of Confederation.
They just trampled it, just like now you hear a constitutionalist say,
oh, the NDAA and the Patriot Act is trampling the Constitution.
Well, the Constitution trampled the original government, right?
And if you listen to an academic, one that is knowledgeable,
which you're not going to find anymore,
they will tell you that George Washington was the first president under the Constitution.
But there were six presidents.
Like John Hansen is a popular one.
He was a Moor, by the way.
If you know what a Moor is, I'm not going to get into that.
So forget about Obama.
You know what I mean?
Go look this up.
Actually, on the $2 bill,
there's a scene where there's a Moorish man running with a piece of paper on the scene.
If you look at it very closely, it's like saying, hey,
what are you guys abandoning our law form here?
So basically the U.S. went rogue.
Let's say, Zan, you would probably be more familiar with this.
Let's say they shut down the U.S. Constitution
and everything is running in the U.S. now under NDAA and Patriot Act only.
They have quick courts.
Have you read the Patriot Act?
You know what a quick court is?
Quick court?
Yeah, quick court is like you do something bad.
If you've got two police officers there, they could execute you.
As long as the two police officers decide that what you did was bad,
they could shoot you on the spot and sign off on it.
Actually, they have police courts.
They do have police courts now.
But anyway, let's say the Patriot Act completely took over
and all the Bill of Rights and all that was shredded and everybody agreed.
That's what the Constitution did to the Articles of Confederation.
There's only one or two academics that are actually saying what I'm saying.
They did the public scene.
They wrote a few books and said, what about the Articles of Confederation, guys?
And they're kind of saying it below their voice.
They don't want to say it too loud, right?
We're still under that.
You have to repeal.
In other words, they were never repealed, right?
And since you segued into history, would you mind –
Go back to the sun, by the way.
But go ahead.
Segue into history, yes.
Oh, okay.
Sure.
Yeah, if you have anything on the sun.
Also, if you know what the difference between a planet and a star formation is
and how do planets form, if you think that's relevant.
I've never experienced it.
I could – okay.
In science, you have a postulate, hypothesis, theory,
and then experiment and conclusion, right?
That's the method.
So at this point, this has to be done backwards because we're already on a planet
that came before.
That experiment, we can't do because it's already made
or anybody else you're going to try to make a planet.
So we can theorize and hypothesize.
It's very simple.
Do you know the concept of fractals, right?
Yes.
The big and the small.
Like for people that may not know real quick, if you get a head of broccoli,
if you look at one of the flowers, it looks like the whole head of broccoli.
And if you look at the flower very carefully, there's a little bud.
If you take it off with a tweezer and look at it with a magnifying glass,
it looks like the whole head of broccoli again, right?
Unlike the Mandelbrot fractal, you'll find many of them in nature
that are more impressive like that, cauliflower, broccoli, and things like that.
So if we look at something like a planet, you know,
it looks a lot like a cell, doesn't it, right, in a human body?
And by the way, you have an atmosphere also.
The human body has an atmosphere.
If you ever smell anyone when they're walking by,
you're smelling their atmosphere, by the way.
You can change your atmosphere by putting cologne or aftershave on.
Are you with me, how simple this is?
So, for example, you know the concept of galvanic reaction?
If you put a – do you ever chew on aluminum foil and you're like,
oh, what's that?
It's a very strong reaction, right?
And you spit it out or put a penny in your mouth.
Do you know that you can taste that penny or aluminum foil
just by putting it very close to the tongue?
You don't even have to touch it?
That's why you don't eat caviar off of metal.
You use mother of pearl, right?
Say again.
That's why you don't eat caviar like beluga caviar.
You use oyster shell or mother of pearl to eat your fish.
Oh, sure.
That's one thing.
I don't eat that – I'll eat carp rather because the –
I don't eat fish unless they have fins and scales.
And catfish and beluga, they have fins, but they don't have scales.
I can get into what humans should eat according to the Elohim,
which is another thing.
And also no pork on my fork ever, right?
So I have a hard time if I go down to New Orleans
because everything is unclean.
But I have had crocodile gumbo, and I've had snake.
I've had – back before I knew what I should be doing.
And when I asked him how long do you cook the roux,
he says two beers' worth.
But anyway, to go back to the atmosphere, metals have an atmosphere and all that.
Everything has an atmosphere to it.
So you have to pick which fractal you want to look at on a planet.
I would suggest that water is not H2O.
We did not get into this.
And without understanding water,
you will never understand suns or planets or yourself or anything.
So that's another sonic event maybe.
But the planets are fractal.
So you take your pick on anything that might resemble a planet,
and your idea would probably be closer to what is being taught.
The molten iron core is total BS because molten iron, by the way,
is above the Curie point.
It cannot be magnetic.
You can use their own science to disprove their own science.
By the way, science died in the 1920s.
You haven't had any with Einstein when Einstein was brought forward.
Einstein is like Osama bin Laden or Oswald Schott Kennedy.
He's a patsy.
So they killed science in the 1920s.
So if anybody says this is science, well, he's rolling in his grave,
this science guy right now rolling in his grave,
clawing to get out and start beating people up because there's no more science,
by the way.
Why?
It's because we're not allowed, right?
Someone had enough power to shut down any sort of real antidote.
Yes, because it was decided a while back that you're going to be put in a
waiting room.
I even did a lot of sonics called the waiting room,
or you're in a holding pattern for the past 100 years.
They stalled the 20th century with all the wars,
and they killed science in the 1920s, and also they killed politics.
Everybody is under some neo-fascist communistic system.
If you don't know that,
you don't know why did they put Hitler, Stalin,
and FDR in office exactly within two months of each other.
It's a new system.
Also, you're in an even more stalled situation now with this one.
Look at how all the movies and all the arts are going down.
Morality is going down.
They're stalling it.
You're in a holding pattern.
Waiting room is what I used to call it a decade ago.
Who's holding this for how long?
You've got about less than a decade left before the holding pattern is broken.
It'll actually be broken before that, but who it is, it's very elaborate.
It's kind of like the flat earth question, and is it round or flat?
It depends on which god you have allegiance to.
That's where you'll get that information.
I'm not religious, by the way.
I found every religion on the planet and every sect of every religion repugnant.
With the time you have, can we please go over this?
I mean this is encapsulating all three of us,
and Daniel and I don't have all the pieces or more pieces like you do.
I just noticed this is societal decay.
It just keeps getting worse and worse, and I try to be a shining beacon.
I'm trying my best.
I mean can you tell me who's stopping us and why and all this stuff?
No, the who doesn't matter.
In other words, your dog got run over by the car.
Does it matter what make, model, or car it was?
Okay.
The thing that matters – well, here's the thing.
It's happening on a high spiritual level, and even the most repugnant –
like I said, there's no elite.
Yes, there is an elite class, but if you know who they are, they're disgusting, right?
I mean disgusting with a capital S, okay?
So are they – okay, they're extremely spiritual,
meaning they rely on the stuff that people would poo-poo as being airy-fairy.
It's not what you believe.
It's what they believe that you need to know, right?
So I'm going to pause right here because we went – Daniel, we went into –
we just broke off like tree roots, and we went into different directions.
You see how it works?
Did you have anything in store in terms of the questions that we presented?
Yeah, well, if you want to finish, because I also had this prepared that you glossed over quickly,
that if you are to eat animals, you must make sure that they –
so supposing they have four legs that they chew their cud –
Oh, what should we eat humans?
Okay, okay, yeah, yeah, that must –
Meaning they ruminate.
Suggested.
Okay, when you buy a car or dishwasher or whatever, there's a manual in there.
So if you're not familiar, well, that's okay.
We're benevolent.
We're not expecting that everyone that buys a car or dishwasher or toaster or whatever
or a certain animal knows, so we include a manual, something to help, because we're benevolent, right?
We don't want to prank people and see them fail.
We want to see them succeed.
So this particular Elohim said for humans, in order to be in a better state or a proper state,
more proper state, there are rules for food, for example.
So very simple.
If you're going to eat animal – which, by the way, this comes from the biblical text.
I'm not religious, and by the way, I don't recommend anyone read the Bible
because after you read the word the, you'll be completely lost,
so you're not going to understand anything in it.
I'm not saying this to put anyone down.
It just happens to be what I see.
You won't comprehend it, especially the way it's presented.
But it can be distilled very simply.
An animal with four legs should chew the cud and have a clove and hoof.
It states, for example, like a pig has a clove and hoof, but he doesn't chew the cud.
A rabbit chews the cud, but he has a paw.
He doesn't have a hoof, right?
And the Koran, for example, doesn't give that distinction.
It says don't eat swine and don't eat animals that have died on their own.
So there's no discernment.
If you go to this text, it has a lot of discernment, and it gives examples.
So, for example, let's say we're out in the Himalayas.
We're trying to find some place in Tibet, and we're really hungry.
We've run out of supplies, and we're starving,
and we see an animal we've never seen before,
and we might want to eat its flesh for our protein.
And we've never seen it before, but we see that it chews the cud,
and it has a clove and hoof.
Well, even though we've never seen it before, we don't know what to call it,
but we could start by calling it dinner, right?
You see, because it meets those criteria.
Okay, so let's go to the next one.
If it comes out of the water, it should have fins and scales, fins and scales.
So most fish do, but catfish has fins, but it doesn't have scales.
It has skin.
Eel has fins.
It doesn't have scales.
It has bone, just like shark has fins, but it doesn't have scales.
Beluga does not have.
Sturgeon does not have.
Okay, does a clam?
Does a clam have fins and scales?
Heck no.
How about crabs?
Do they have fins and scales?
How about shrimp?
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
All right.
Let me see.
Now, this is not inclusive directly, but indirectly.
If it's a plant, it should be green and bear seed.
Okay, so that's most of them.
Let me ask you, does algae do that?
No.
So I got the super food.
It measures in the laboratory.
Oh, man, great.
This is a super food, super green.
I don't want it.
If I want algae, I could go out to neighboring swimming pools, right?
All right, so those are the simple.
Let me ask you, are mushrooms, do mushrooms have, are they green and bear seed?
No.
They have mitosis, right?
So I got the super mushroom food.
Yeah, you can keep it.
But if you give me that expensive mushroom powder, I might rub it on my chest maybe, but I won't eat it, you see?
So that's how I am.
I'm an Old Testament fool or whatever you want to call it.
Most people think you are, but it works really well once you comprehend it.
Also, biblical timekeeping is lawful.
All the timekeeping, even scientific, is lawful.
They don't use the Pope's work schedule.
So, yeah, go ahead.
Well, regarding if you're not sure that something is safe to eat, I think you had a certain protocol for this, right?
Yes, very simple.
Usually that survivalist or protocol is with plants usually.
And what you would do there is you have a very simple approach.
First you touch it with your fingers, and you wait a few minutes,
and then you rub it on the most exposed areas where your energy and sensitivity readings are,
is like the inside of your wrist, your armpit, inside your elbow, your groin, in between your butt cheeks, in between your toes.
Those are still all external, very highly sensitive areas.
You take the plant and put it, let's say, on the inside of your wrist or on your armpit or in between your toes,
and you wait about an hour or so or two.
If there's no reaction, negative reaction, then you put it in your mouth and just take it out and wait about an hour or so.
Remember, you've got nothing to do.
You're starving.
You've got plenty of time, right?
And if no reaction but just touching it in your lips, let's say, and tongue at the same time for about an hour or so,
you can put it in your mouth and just bite, break into it with your teeth, take it out, wait another hour or two.
If there's no negative reaction, you see where I'm going with this?
Yep.
On and on and on.
You don't do it right away.
Oh, I touched it between my toes.
It's five minutes.
How long have you been doing this?
Five minutes.
No, you have to wait because some things are very slow.
So you can take a bite, chew it, spit it out, wait another hour.
No negative reaction, take a small bite, chew it, swallow it, wait an hour.
If this fool didn't die doing that, let's try another fool, right?
You might want to try another person, right?
Yeah.
The kings used to have testers for this, right?
And would you say that this ability to live off the grid is going to be vital in the near future?
Yes and no because when you switch from this society to the next one,
there's going to be not a very long time for dust to settle, about 40 years.
It depends.
Well, 40 years, Greek, I'm not 40 years old right now.
What do you mean it's not a long time?
You're not going to have this type of centralized community.
You're going to have small communities where you'll have that castle doctrine.
Wait a second.
If we go back in history, didn't they have, like, these walled cities?
And when you went into a walled city, it was like its own country, right?
You're going to go back.
So it's not going to be like each household.
You know, even if you look at very rural communities,
you'll see a lot of land and then a house and then a long distance.
They still have a community.
You're still going to have community.
You're just not going to have centralized power
and centralized military and all that.
Each small enclave will be able to protect itself and all that.
And since we're on the topic of the future,
do you know if sea level rise is foreseen in these prophecies?
Yes, of course, of course.
Well, we are in a sea level rise right now.
Just to explore this briefly, if you go off the coast of the Caribbean, Cuba,
off the coast of Japan, any coastal area,
and you just do some searching on the reefs and go out even 100 miles,
there are cities, there are temples underwater.
So aren't we in a coastal rise situation right now compared to 7,000 years ago?
Heck yeah, right?
And it's going to get worse, yeah.
In other words, if you're living anywhere that's, you know,
well, some people like Holland and Louisiana are below sea level slightly
or at sea level, yeah, there's no future there, yeah.
No.
And climate change, would you say it's a valid concern?
Because I mainly ask because ETs also are often reproachful of –
reprimand humans for their treatment of Earth
and say that much of it is their fault.
Those ETs I wouldn't trust.
If they see climate change as a big deal,
those are, like, the ones that are pranking you.
It is – climate change is a fraud.
You hear very easy to destroy it.
Yeah, to destroy carbon-based beings.
But we're not – yeah, just the carbon-based being great
because carbon has nothing to do with the greenhouse effect.
The greenhouse – what they're talking about, global warming,
is the greenhouse effect.
Don't go for the global warming.
Greenhouse effect is only caused by water vapor,
so we have to get rid of all water vapor, which isn't going to happen.
The carbon is just like Osama bin Laden vaporized the towers
with 19 hijackers and box cutters.
That's how ridiculous – but people – Gustav Le Bon, the crowd.
The dumber it is and the more false it is, the more people will believe it, right?
So let me ask you, just don't answer.
What kind of a future does a society like this have,
and do they deserve to have a future?
And the answer to that is obvious.
In other words, the people that you see here now, the majority, 7 billion,
with a very, very small exception, and so small that you could fit them in a stadium,
do not deserve to – not because I say this.
Cosmically are not deserving to go to the next level.
But this time it's going to be a little bit different.
They're going to let more of the non-deserving ones stay to prove
that they didn't have to be this way.
So anyway, but there is no – here's the bullshit also about the hole in the ozone layer.
Anybody that knows – they say that it's letting the UV in.
That's an oxymoron because even a high school experiment will show that
if you have an ozone generator with UV light, it generates oxygen, ozone.
So the actual ozone layer is created by the UV.
So they're saying the ozone layer is gone and it's letting the dangerous UV in.
No, no, it's the dangerous UV that creates the ozone layer.
How dumb can you be?
Someone read me a post.
This was from a high school teacher.
I don't know if you guys saw it.
It went around and then it was eliminated.
High school teacher says we need to stop animal cruelty.
We need to stop killing animals for food
and just get animals from the store where they make it.
Just like they ask little children where does milk come from, and milk comes from the store.
But we are hurting the soul, spirit or whatever, but if it's anything, it's through our mind, right?
Yes, you're doing it because your mindset is be in darkness versus light.
But you need to know the dark.
People say avoid darkness, which we try to define good, bad, and evil.
Those are three things.
It's not good and evil.
It's good, bad, and when you do bad, you get evil, right?
So the evil is not in the picture.
But you have to know the dark side to know the light.
In other words, how do you become tempered?
How do you become strong?
Years ago, society was a society of light, meaning from a physical sense,
whatever products they used were developed in the light.
So when they built things with their houses, they used trees and materials that grew in the light.
When they used minerals and animal products, animals grew in the light.
When they used minerals and metals, they were surface metals that were in the light.
They didn't do very deep mining unless a cave afforded it to.
They used surface materials and things that were made in the light,
their products and everything that they came in touch with.
Now society is in the dark because we are sitting in three different places right now.
Can you touch anything that is not made or with petroleum as an ingredient?
Almost impossible.
Where does petroleum come from?
You said it's rock oil, and part of it has to do with this black goo, which you said is more layers.
Yeah, the black goo is like the water that has memory.
No, it's not that I said.
You say it also, and anybody who discovers this can say it.
I'm not being an ass here.
I'm just making it very closely.
Oil is a hydrocarbon.
You take hydrogen from water.
Water is not H2O, by the way.
You can get H2O from water.
And carbon dioxide, what happens if you break off enough hydrogen?
Let's just use the mechanistic method.
You can synthesize oil from water and carbon dioxide if you know how to do it.
You need a catalyst like nickel and a few other things, osmium and things like that,
and certain pressures and temperatures.
And those pressures actually have to go into a vacuum condition, ha-ha,
which we spent a lot of time talking about.
So is it so difficult to know that there is carbon dioxide and carbon gas,
carbon liquid compounds?
You know, there is a gel state of carbon dioxide.
It doesn't have to be a gas.
You can have carbon dioxide in a room temperature state underground that form this from rocks,
rocks being a catalyst as well.
It's basically rock oil.
Petrol means rock, and oleum means oil.
So if you say corn oil, where does that come from, right?
If you say olive oil, where does that come from?
If you say rock oil, where does that come from?
Rocks.
The Germans were synthesizing petroleum before World War I, by the way,
Germans meaning the Prussians, right?
They were synthesizing India ink, which cut into, you know, we – someone asked about,
I think you did, why did the Americans ally with the British when they were allied with the Germans?
Well, it's not that they had a choice.
They liked – Americans, Zen will know this too in his heart of being here,
they love ingenuity.
They love being inventive.
They love being productive.
They like helping people.
Not the government.
I'm talking about the people.
That's why they're here.
Like a lot of the people that immigrated here was because they reached a brick wall in whatever village
or country they were in.
They were like, screw this.
I'm going to go where we can expand, right?
Well, they were working with the Germans on synthesizing everything,
but the British already had control of all these things from natural products,
and the British did not really – the Americans did not really ally with the British
and abandon the Germans.
What happened there was it was time to take the Americans out,
down from what had happened for the revolution,
and they went under the wing and the tutelage of the British.
By that alliance being abandoned between Germany and America,
that signified the beginning of the end of America,
which led to the Federal Reserve Act, Woodrow Wilson,
and then all the way to the bankruptcy and dissolution of the American government
became the American administration under the new state under Roosevelt,
which was 100 times worse than anything that's ever happened to this country that people talk about.
And the reason why people don't talk about the bankruptcy of March of 1933
and how Roosevelt destroyed the government is because it's in the Federal Register.
It's in the Congressional Record.
That's why nobody knows about it.
Just like nobody knows anything about anything spiritual
because it's already written in their books, right?
So it was the beginning of the end of America.
I don't think it was the Americans said one day,
hey, let's forget about the Germans and go to the British.
It was the infiltration and the effect that took them away to destroy them.
If they would have stuck with the Germans,
it would have been impossible to have bankrupted them.
We wouldn't have a state.
We would have a government.
I know it sounds kind of crazy, right?
The Greeks is insane, right?
It's just that at the same time,
nations have kind of started fraternizing soon afterwards.
They made deals, and ever since,
you can't really say that any war was really justified.
I mean, it was all planned, and there were no more enemies.
No, the wars are there to prevent revolutions and internal distractions.
For example, let's just take the wars.
World War I, the soldiers were promised to fight.
Most Americans don't know it was less than a year, right?
They created the American army flu,
which they sent to Spain because no one else would take them,
and everyone died.
It killed one quarter of the American population,
like 10 or 15 million people, not 500,000 like they say.
It was engineered here the way that all plagues are engineered,
not in the lab, but that was World War I.
The soldiers did not get paid for going to World War I,
and they protested in Washington, D.C., and people like MacArthur
and so went and gassed and killed the soldier.
You can look this up, the riots.
World War II, when they were going to go into World War II,
there were massive protests here.
People were jailed, and how come you don't hear about that, the propaganda?
Whenever there's a lot of social unrest,
they create an international war,
just like what's going on right now with Russia and Ukraine.
That's a made-for-TV war like the Iraq War was, right?
There are people being killed, yes, but it's nothing like you're being told.
There are more people with cameras
than there are people with guns in Ukraine right now.
Another much-talked-about thing that you mentioned
was that Germany won World War II in an alternate timeline?
James Rake mentioned that too, yeah.
It's not only that they won World War II.
World War II, the ones that did this in an alternate timeline
or in this timeline, really, it's all one big thing.
Like, okay, look at a map of various, let's say a country or city
that has several highways that go through it.
Which one is the alternate highway?
Sometimes they call it an alternate, but they're all there at the same time.
You see what I mean?
They're all present on the geography.
These alternate timelines are all on the same geographic map
known as our reality, which we just don't see.
I don't know enough about them,
but I had gotten from a pretty good source a few years ago,
someone that's out in Texas.
Good source because of other things.
I'm not going to, just to say,
the Nazis approached the Pentagon in 1946
and said that we destroyed your reality.
You're living in a synthetic reality that we are creating
with anti-grav ships and also underground.
We destroyed you, and you're in a synthetic reality.
We're in control.
We won the war.
We won everything.
We control your reality.
There was like 10 guys there, and the Pentagon arrested them right away
because they came to the Pentagon's door.
They were plainclothes.
They said, you guys are crazy.
What are you doing here?
He says, okay, we'll prove it to you.
Let three of us go, and we'll prove it to you.
So they let three of them go, and they kept the seven apprehended.
The three came back with a box and gave it to the Pentagon officials.
The Pentagon officials opened the box,
and what was inside the box were the most highly secret objects
that the Pentagon had in their vaults.
So with the technology they had, they could see through everything
because they were creating this reality.
It sounds pretty crazy, right?
So basically nothing we do matters.
All this is just for fun.
No, it does.
Let's just say, for example, okay, everything that you know turned into a sewer
or you went down to the sewer.
Are you going to say how do we stop this and how do we change it,
or do we say that sewers are necessary to take the shit away?
It just so happens you don't want to fall into it, do you?
I'm just trying to think how I can contribute, man, in this timeline, in this life.
By setting yourself apart, what you do is you set yourself apart from it,
and you show others how you did it.
Just like this.
Let's say you're in a crisis situation, survival situation.
How do you help others?
Well, you show them how to get water, how to make food, how to make clothes
by doing it yourself.
So you don't do it in secret.
You do it in a way that other people can see it,
and those that are willing to do it will do it,
and those that aren't, well, you're not going to make them do it, right?
Like the old adage, when the airplane is going down,
they say put on your oxygen mask first, and then the person next to you, right?
So be an example.
Set yourself apart.
Like this morning I said I'll be here on the meeting
because I've got to water the veg and feed the animals, right?
Do I go around talking about people, about organic gardening
and husbandry and stuff like that?
I was on a Skype call recently, someone I'd spoken to in a while,
and he said, hey, Greek, why don't you tell them about that motorcycle
you sold me back then?
I said, oh, what about it?
Well, why don't you tell them how you got it to run on water?
I'm like, oh, man, people that – you don't hear me talking about that stuff, right?
You know it all, man.
You got it all.
You're not –
Why is it that when you go online and you try to make devices
that run engines on water and none of them work,
but there are engines that are running on water?
Why is it the people that make them work running on water aren't doing YouTubes
and going online making pages?
Why?
Why is that?
Because it's not about – it's about setting yourself apart,
pulling out, but not doing it completely in secret.
From what I heard, if what you're inventing overlaps with the black projects by over 85%,
then they get it and they punish you somehow.
If you do – well, they punish you if you're going to bring it to the great unwashed,
the masses, right?
Because they always give an example to the masses.
They give this artificial – okay, especially people that live in America,
they know that there was the booming era of the 1950s, 60s,
and the energy crisis in the 70s, and the financial boom in the 80s,
and the tech boom in the 90s, and everything's great in America.
All that is synthetic.
All that was fake, completely fake.
All those booms that I mentioned that you guys are familiar with
and most listeners are completely synthesized.
To see what spiritual level, consciousness level are you able to control,
merge your emotions and your rationales so you have control of physical reality,
your level of psychic ability, your spiritual ability would be developed
when you have all this other physical prosperity.
But what did they do when they had all this physical prosperity in the 50s, 60s,
the energy crisis in the 70s, but then prosperity in the 80s, 90s until now?
Did they focus the society – did they focus on spiritual development,
psychic development, mental, emotional development?
You guys can answer that.
I don't have to say.
People were greedy.
They got worse and worse.
So you have about 60 or 70 years where they basically said,
here's prosperity, physical prosperity.
You turn on the tap.
Water comes out.
You don't have to dig a well.
You hit the switch on the wall.
Lights come on any time of day.
Are you developing yourself spiritually, mentally, psychically?
And the answer is no.
They actually went the other way.
They became more greedy, more criminal, more corrupt, you see.
Now it's over.
So now the average human is a quote-unquote scumbag, right, category.
The average human, 7 billion because of the last 70 years or more.
And this has happened before and before and before.
But there has to be an aim.
Yes.
The aim right now is to clean up.
Oh, here's another analogy.
I'm tired of these analogies.
You guys ever have a big party?
What does it look like when everyone goes home at 4 in the morning?
What does it look like at 10 a.m.?
What does the place look like?
It's a wreck.
So what do you do?
You leave it like that?
Five years later people say, why is the place a wreck?
Was that a party here five years ago?
Yeah.
Yes.
Clean it.
You clean it.
But when you're cleaning it up, you've got to take a day off maybe, right?
So if you ever listen to the old sonic events I've done, I call it the mop-up crew is coming.
Not the gods, not the Anunnaki, not the saviors, the mop-up crew.
Well, who is this mop-up crew for this timeline?
Is the earth flat or is it round?
I gave the analogies before.
Pick a god and then come back and we'll discuss it.
Pick a god.