All righty, so Greek you are on the record. But yeah, so like I was saying, Greek, I listened
to 25 episodes that were on that Consolidated Concise Ocelli playlist, which really opened my
eyes. And so what I did was, I'm sorry the notes I sent you are so half-assed. It's just as I was
listening and multitasking or driving or on the stairs, I'm like, ooh, okay, I want to ask about
this. Ooh, okay. So I know I gave you like just quick random bullet points, but you covered so
much of the things that I've always wondered in life. And I know now better how to, I think,
ask points towards you and have a better understanding of your knowledge. So.
Okay. Well, let me just put it this way. No matter who you're speaking to, whether you're
speaking to young people, hopefully the younger the better, the whole world is wide open. Let me
just give a quick maybe thing. Everything, every subject that you heard on there, which is maybe a
dozen or so subjects, you'll notice that the perspective that I gave is, you guys, you guys
need to hear this. I don't want anybody to believe it. Just, you need to hear it and what you do with
it is up to you. But all those subjects that were covered, you know, whatever this is, if you really
meditate on what was said, every subject under the sun and beyond the sun is completely wide open.
What I mean by that is, well, let's just, well, let's not be conspiratorial, but pretty much
everything we're told about any subject is what? Right? It's taboo. Anytime you're taught it's a
lie that actually will lead to something anecdotal, you're going to get, you're going to get shut down
or people just can't wrap their minds around it. Or you would say, you know, it's cosmic censorship.
Right. It's a, it's a big story. Uh, it's, it's, um, here's the thing. You could drop,
uh, certain details on what the big picture things are going on, but people lack the
language and the thought process to, to use it. So it's wasted.
Loathing. I think people do, but you said there's such a loathing for knowledge,
which makes you made it perfectly understandable. I really think there are people out there that
way smarter than me, uh, my father, my brother, who's still in law school right now. But I mean,
I'll never forget when I brought up just the subject of the MRNA being bad at last Christmas,
my brother shrieked like, no, and made a scene and like stomped upstairs. I'm like,
he just can't even get in them. He, they just. Okay. That's different. That's the impulsive.
I think we do spoke a little bit about, um, especially with Daniel yesterday,
we had a private call and, uh, we, we talked about the, the, the, what the spirit, the soul
and the body is in short, you know, the carne as the body, the material, and the soul is the
metabolism, the breath. Okay. And the spirit is the mind. Well, amongst that we have an emotional
body as well. Right. And it's the heart, you know, like they say, uh, how do you, how does your heart
feel? You know, go with your heart, whatever. Right. And then you have the mind, which is the
more logical, reasonable, uh, and the great goes dead. If you have sure. If you, if you, well,
yeah, that's a good way to the Drake. That's right. Um, which ones, uh, they, they have like
12 major races, but, but here's the thing. Um, the, the essence of human evolution is to combine
and make it holistic, not separate or fractional. Like how many times you hear, oh, that's left
brain. That's right. Brain. Uh, that's too emotional. He's too clinical, too logical,
right? Emotional is good. Logical is bad. Right? So we're in a fractional state,
just like when you read ancient texts, the kingdom is here. It's just divided.
You know what I mean? And so if you apply it to yourself, uh, you're, you have everything you
need. It's just divided. You just can't access it. Right. It's kind of like, uh, you know,
your wardrobe, most people know their wardrobe pretty well. When you look at it, you get a
better, uh, sense of what's there, but imagine I took your wardrobe apart. Let's say you have
a hundred items in your wardrobe and I put it in a hundred different places all over the earth,
still your wardrobe, but go get your socks. They're in China, right? Go get your shirt,
you know? So everything. So that's, that's what's going on amongst people. So they need to, uh,
evolve, uh, through the process of unifying themselves, no more fractional thinking,
no more fractional talk, like no left brain, right brain, no female, no male, uh, in a sense,
like, you know, that's a particular attitude or, you know, no matriarchal or patriarchal,
no emotional, no rational, combine it all and start working with it. It's the same thing.
It's just like, think about, okay, a toolbox. You have a comprehensive auto mechanic toolbox
and, uh, 500 pieces and put them in 500 envelopes and send it to 500 cities all over the world.
It's useless. It's still your toolbox though. Until you consolidate it all. Right.
With this fractal thinking, you made a point that I almost ran off the road because it made so much
sense to me. Okay. I was headed to, uh, uh, pay a bill in North Louisiana and you started talking
about how babies instinctively put things on their tongue and how the tongue means, uh,
super or subliminal. Uh, I'm sorry to explain. I can't explain it as well as you can. And then
you started talking about, uh, ferro and diamagnetic or die electrical charges in the
body and how there's an aura and just tons of things that made perfect sense when it comes to
biology. And that just, yeah. Yeah. That's everyone needs to discover that on their own. But when it's,
uh, most information that's shoved down your throat or requires this elitist academic paradigm,
you're not going to get, uh, it's going to be to benefit one, not the other, uh, one group,
not the other, not the, not the whole. See advanced races look at the earth and they say,
answer me this human. Why do your leaders keep you dumb and poison your food and make wars to
decrease your population? Aren't your leaders supposed to enlighten you, spread knowledge,
and make you stronger? Why do you allow that on your planet? And that's why I'm so, you're not,
no, you're not going to do it. It's going to happen. And I'm not going to do it. Neither is
Daniel or anybody else. There are those that will do it, but they're on a different realm,
much higher than this one. And they're going to do it. Like here's a smaller example. I also,
by the way, before I get into that, most people don't know, maybe what we're referencing
the Ocelli and the Greek archives, if they're still up or can be found. I think that everything,
right. That's what we're very much referenced. The Ocelli affects YouTube channels. We're always
getting my information. Right. And that's from, uh, maybe, uh, I don't know, five, six,
seven years ago. It's 2015 through 2021. Okay. There we go. Okay.
Yeah. And actually before that, there's, uh, stuff I started speaking online around 2008,
2010. I think someone, one of the things I was trying to find, but yeah, it's, it's,
someone had 400 hours of Greek speak on a, on a server and it got somehow absconded with,
but, but here's the point. Uh, the first thing is let's go down a laundry list. First of all,
you should shed and eliminate any fear you have of anything. Okay. You're basically told this when
you go to the beach as a young child and everyone's going in the water and you don't want to go in
because it's too cold. Right. That's like a very shallow example of fear. And you could take that
all the way to someone in the trenches in a war. That's just shaking in their britches and can't
pull, you know, can't aim the rifle at the enemy supposedly. So there's different levels of fear,
but if you eliminate all fear in your life, uh, not one fear is supposed to be there as a defensive
mechanism or as a protection mechanism, but just in the background, because one thing I said on
those recordings is that, uh, people are motivated by basically two things. One is fear, um, which is
an anti motivator, a paralyzer. And the other one, uh, they're motivated by the threat of penalties.
So they do things because if they don't do them, they'll be penalized versus doing things because
it's the right thing to do. Ask anyone, well, why do you file taxes? Well, because if I don't,
I'll go to jail. Uh, why do you get a driver's license? Because if I don't, I'll go to jail.
You're right. Uh, why do you vote? Well, you know, they don't know, uh, right. So again,
all topics are wide open. And here's the sad thing. I don't want this to be, uh, an arrogant
statement or anything, but the internet is a wasteland. There's really nothing on the internet,
unless you're really good at sifting stuff. Now it's a needle in a haystack scenario,
which sounds discouraging, but how quick can you find a needle in a haystack with a magnet?
Real fast. So that's what, what I was trying to do, uh, with, with all these talks and maybe
the last talk we did here as well, uh, just get a magnet, make things easier. You know,
is the glass half full or half empty? It's not a question of pessimism or optimism. It's a
question of engineering. If someone's asking you, is the glass half full or half empty? It's an
engineering question. Meaning the glass is obviously too big. You see? And I think it might
go back to when you said that everything is wide open. It might go back to the fact that, uh,
science has, we know it is only something like 150 years old, or you can say it's scientism,
which is a new religion. And, uh, this religion has, is basically, um, uh, has its foundation on
death, uh, which you can see, for example, in medicine, uh, with the electron microscopy.
Right. And also they study cadavers, not live people. If you, when you're taking anatomy and,
and, uh, in medical school, 90% of your time would be what? Dissecting what?
Dead things. Yes. When you take cells and put them under a microscope, are they alive or dead?
Dead. So it's all based on death. Um, it's a death cult. Now, the reason why they worship
the death cult is because everything's subject to death. So if everything's subject to death,
that death is the most powerful attribute or God on this planet. Then the other thing is law. You
shouldn't have law. Well, because you have this one particular God that supposedly his stuff has
been hijacked and applied to the whole world. And, uh, they say that, well, he only gave man
these laws, but he didn't give the elephant, the bird or the cockroach, these laws. So if you
decide to observe his laws, you're less free than the elephant, the bird, or the cockroach.
Not only are you less free, you're actually lower than a cockroach. If you follow these laws,
that's like a high order Freemasonic credo, not the Freemasons, the guys going down the street
and joining a lodge so they could have pork in April and wear a stupid apron and take photographs
with. But I'm talking about the 300 secret societies. They're basically into free will
and, uh, domination and exploration of life itself and everything they can. And people that are
limit themselves to laws or rules are frowned upon. Just like, um, if you look at the subtle
hints in Hollywood, they play a game, you know, Hollywood in the media, they're playing games
with the people. Whenever you have someone who's quote unquote intellectual or smart,
how do they portray him in the media and in Hollywood as a nerd, as a geek, an egghead?
Yeah. Right. That's a big, uh, that's a big contrast also to how, but you have that. And
the contrast is when you go to academia, who do they hold up as their, as their pillars of
or heroes are the Greek philosophers and others. So on one side they have, they hold them up very
high and they show them really noble with marble busts and all this. And on the other side,
they show you that they're not desirable. So which one is it? Right.
And is, is CERN related to this? Um, and what do you think its goal is?
Talked about CERN. Oh yeah. Okay. I can't wait.
Unknown directly until we, here's the thing. You can speculate and also you can closely examine
what's being shown to you. And I believe everything is being shown to us always.
It's just what level of, let's say vision you have, just like people have different
levels of vision to get your eye, like an eye test. So it depends on what kind of an eye test
result you have when you look at CERN and also what people are saying about it. Um, you know,
that's another subject altogether. Basically the subject is, it's not a concern again,
because if you, the more you find out about it, if it'll click on that fear, um, uh, thing,
right? Because you're being left out. But, uh, what happens when you spin, when you spin things
at very high velocities with high energies, right? That's a universal concept. Well,
you have tornadoes, hurricanes, CERN, uh, anti-grav, uh, electromagnetic phenomenon,
dimensional phenomenon. You see where I'm going? Yeah. And, uh, is it true that, uh,
they're kind of wasting their resources and you could replicate it with a cheaper material?
We could replicate it with a benchtop model that fits on the desk next to your laptop. Yeah.
And, uh, is it, uh, also the, as it related this whole scientism to the, uh, goddess religion and
its, uh, agenda? Big time. The goddess religion copies, it's a, it's a corruption. See, like,
like, let's look at the food industry. Throughout years, people are like, well, we're agricultural.
If someone doesn't farm or if we don't farm and grow food or husband animals and get milk and
all that, we're going to starve, right? Because we're not breatharians. So they just keep that
meme going. So the big corporations are like, oh yeah, GMO is good. We'll end food. We'll end
hunger, right? Uh, take your shots, take our medicine because it's good for you. Supplements,
you know, like, uh, take these supplements, your body will absorb them, right? All this ridiculous
stuff. So they transition you from, um, something in Greek called anangi or necessity, right? Because,
uh, it's a necessity and they transition you into this new thing, which is not a necessity,
meaning the toxic, uh, science. And, and then people do, you do that long enough,
uh, especially after you throw a big war at them, you hint, you know, World War II in the 50s,
60s and 70s is when all this really came in big time. It existed in the 19, in the 1800s,
by the way, but it didn't come in until after the war. Now people find, um, all these chemicals and
toxic things in their food and necessity, which is actually sick. Have you heard me on the comment
I made on there shouldn't be any organic food? And that really kicks up some people that are
into, you know, healthy eating. What do you mean Greek shouldn't be organic food? Well,
what kind of a society would go to a market and the food market would be divided organic and
non-organic. And so the, you give the people a choice of toxified, deranged, corrupt, grotesque
food or food that is not, why would you offer a, you know, if you lived in a halfway decent,
halfway moral society, the moment the organic food popped up, it should have woken up people
and said, wait a second, why is the organic food costs more and better for you? You mean
this other food is deliberately toxified? Who's doing it? Where do they live? Let's go get them.
Let's stop them. Right? But people didn't do that, did they?
No, they're not big above the law corporations that have all consolidated.
Well, they're not above the lawless. Like for example, every country in their so-called
constitution has in their code, not in their constitution, but in their code, which is
actually an extension of the constitutions, tells you that they're unlawful, that they don't go by
any laws. The one, if you're in the United States or of America, you look up title 12, that's their
Bible, it goes from title one to title 50, title 12, 411, title 12, 411 and read it and they tell
you they're not lawful right there. So you never go to them asking for, show me the law, because
they're just going to beat you over the head and throw you in, you know, whatever, in a cage.
Every country I've found it has somewhere in their code, it's hidden or it's there,
that they tell you they don't go by law. So I think you've witnessed that,
Zan, right? The title 12, 411, it tells you the money is not lawful.
Yeah, I took a screenshot of that and then you did title 28, 622 or something. You dropped a
couple of things throughout the episodes that I took screenshots of.
The good thing about the US is they, in many places, they tell you they don't go by law.
Well, how come we're going up to those standards and not some corporation?
Well, here's the thing about a corporation. When I hear people harping about corporations,
I say the same thing about a tyrannical dictatorship, people harping about a tyrannical
dictatorship or harping about fascism, harping about communism. I have no problem with any of
that. If you have a tyrannical, let's say a corporation, any corporation, big or small,
international or domestic, or a tyrant, a dictator, a communist or fascist society,
I have no problem with that. If what they do in action, not just in words,
is to spread knowledge for the advancement of the people, provide good food, good water,
provide protection and all that, what's wrong with that? Let's say you had a fascist communist
dictator and he said, okay, all the 5,000 patents that were sequestered for national
security are now released. In six months, you can go to a government or a state depot
and pick up your free energy box, right? All the food, all food chemicals are now banned.
No hindrance, prosperity, so that we can move in a linear fashion.
Yeah, yeah. Everything that was in the Library of Alexandria is going to be published and put
in print and textbooks. Okay, so what's wrong with this fascist, tyrannical dictator? Is
anything wrong with him so far? No. No, not with what you mentioned.
Yeah, but if you, let's say you have more of a network democracy and freedom and that,
and all they do is lie, cheat, steal, poison and steal your children and rape your children,
all that. Well, what's wrong with that? You see? A lot. And they're all the same.
Here's the thing I was saying. When you look at the planets, and this Hollywood shows this,
there are many movies that talk about this. For example, there are no more governments.
Remember that movie with Will Smith, the other guy, it was called Enemy of the what?
Enemy of the State, yes. Right, it wasn't Enemy of the Government,
it was Enemy of the State. Right, so there was another movie where they're driving on a bus,
a public bus right by the UN, and she goes, look at all those flags. Those are not countries,
those are corporations. I could give you 100 examples and Hollywood's trying to tell you
what's going on. So what's going on right now on the Earth is, the Earth is like,
imagine a huge amusement park, Great Adventure, Disney or whatever. And in that amusement park,
you have all these different rides and each ride has a different theme. So when you look at the
186 member countries of the UN, look at the UN as being a big amusement park and each country
is a different theme ride. So when you go to Romania, it's the teacups. When you go to the
US, it's the haunted mansion. When you go to Canada, it's this water slide. You see?
They're all the same. You buy your ticket, your ticket is your birth certificate,
they monetize that, otherwise you're going to be captured, beaten up, and put one on you anyway.
So basically, the Earth is already under globalism. It started 150 years ago.
The IPU. What's that?
The IPU. International Postal Union, yeah.
Here's the thing, this is real interesting. You know how you start a country? When you settle
a territory and are able to defend it? Anybody could settle anywhere. Right now, you could create
a new country around your house, right? You could declare a new country of Zanjonia, if you want,
around your house and have your neighbors agree, make a new country and send a letter to the Hague
and the UN. That's fine. You could do that. But the question is, can you defend it?
Right? You can't. Because the police, first they'll send the police. If you knock the police
out, they'll send the National Guard. If you knock them out, they'll send the military. And then
knock them out, they'll send all the country's other military after you. So this is what's
going on on Earth. You've already been, it's basically Earth is run by the rules of piracy.
You know how they talk about maritime law and admiralty, which is basically abandonment and
all that. So, you know, you could still function within it. But I wouldn't be optimistic of anything.
I wouldn't be altruistic at all. Things are going to go the way they're going to go.
Because it's, that's just the way, that's just the way it was meant. I know it sounds.
Parliamentary union or something?
Well, I was saying the way you start a country.
The first thing, what's the first thing you set up in order to start a country? Okay,
let's say, let's go back to the territory. You start, you start putting some meters out there
and landmarks and you create Zanjania or Daniel Salia somewhere, or the Greek Alia somewhere.
And we can defend it. We have a shield and weaponry that no one can penetrate us, right?
What's the next thing you do to keep your, to start your country other than defending it?
You start a post office. Yeah.
So you can receive and send out messages, official, official. So in other words,
they know if they send it through that post office, it'll get there.
The next thing you do is you do what's called the governing body,
which is either councils or, you know, how you, you know, house it, whatever you want to call it,
right? Governing bodies, branches and all that. And that's how you start a country
is first thing that goes in is the post office. So let me ask you in terms of first in line and
first in time and priority, if you want to know the state of a country, shouldn't you look at
the state of their postal division or post office? If it starts to fall apart, doesn't that mean that
some of the priorities are coming apart? People start looking at what CNN is saying about
Congress did or whatever. Every time Congress goes in session, all of our lives are threatened,
of course, right? The question is, what's going on with the post office? Well,
in the US, we don't have the post office is still there, but it's not functioning.
It's the Postal Service, which is a corporate entity built underneath it. You see.
And the corporate CEO of the Postal Service also can act as the postmaster general.
So here's the thing. There was something in the news recently that was one little area in Santa
Monica, California, the post office, Postal Service went around putting up notices that
they are stopping mail delivery because the neighborhood's too tough for them, you know.
So what does that mean? Country's falling apart. And I believe you said something along the lines
of the Constitution itself. The reason for it was written is to to establish a business plan.
Yeah, that's right. Well, whenever you see a constitution in a country
with three branches of government, that is a corporate setup for shareholders to acquire.
Who has acquired all of the United States? Shareholders. There's a they just like if
you know anything about foundations or trusts, you have the prime head planning,
then you have trustees and shareholders. You can sell off shares. Yeah, it's unknown. It's
not necessary. It's just like people say, well, Greek, if if I don't know who it is,
it doesn't exist. And I say, well, what city do you live in? You live in a major city. Yes,
I do. OK, you know, if you look in the Yellow Pages downtown, there's an FBI office. Can you
name all the agents in the FBI office? No, I can't. Well, don't you think this would be even
a higher secret than that? Because they're not even in the Yellow Pages, but it's not hard to
find out who it is if you just look at who comes and goes, right, how they come and go,
meaning people in public. And I mean, celebrity is also a lot is dished out by the celebrities.
And it's also the typical statement that's been said a million times every day on the Internet
is follow the money, all the money. But we don't have real money. We have no real health
care. Just like we're already on a dollar collapse. Just like, yeah, you said in the 30s,
the government or people in the government spend it all like some crackheads or something.
Oh, no, no. Yeah. What happened was, OK, the government was created as the ruling body.
It's this beautiful Southern belle. OK, you with me? Get the image. And she's courted and courted
and courted. And she after she's courted, she decides to go to a soiree with someone and they
end up injecting her with heroin, beating the crap out of her and gang raping her. And they do this
every day for about three months. And the next time you see her, she doesn't look like a Southern
belle anymore. Now she belongs to them. That's what happened to the government, every government,
the state came in, it's called the sovereign states, which are neither sovereign. Ask any
academic to define a sovereign state. They can't. They don't have the language for it because the
sovereign state is neither sovereign nor is it a state just like the Federal Reserve is neither
federal or have any reserves. Right. Just like Federal Express is not part of the government.
OK, so sovereign state is a constitutional republic or constitutional body, democratic usually.
And for example, if you look at how does the North Korea define themselves,
they are the North Korean Democratic Republic, aren't they? So, OK, they're a corporation and
and they view everything they interact with as property and they only interact with their
property. So if you're interacting with the state, that means you're being held as property.
I'm not saying it's good or bad. I have no problem with it.
Imagine a tyrannical again, the analogy I gave about the tyrannical communist, fascist
dictatorship. It's not what you label them, it's what they do. Right. Again, if we have a tyrannical
dictatorship, fascist, communistic, whatever, put every negative, anarchistic, whatever word that
you've been associated with. But they say, OK, everyone gets a free energy box.
Library of Alexandria is all in the textbooks. We have medical beds, let's say. Opened. Yeah,
public. Healthy food. Yeah, healthy food. Everybody's encouraged. Yes, we have a space
program. We have we have ships that are three kilometers long circling Jupiter.
We'll do it. We can't put all of you all on there. So we'll pull a lottery. How's that?
Right. Well, can you see the significance of this inter-parliamentary council, please,
or union or whatever that you mentioned? And we were never inter-parliamentary.
Oh, inter-parliamentary. Oh, yeah, there's several. I'm going to this is another thing
without because we don't let's keep this limited. Keep it short. OK, sorry. I'm going to be going
off a memory. You know, that's fine. Start researching. Let your fingers do the walking
on international governing bodies like the U.N. that are older than the U.N. There's a few of
them. This one was in the eighteen hundreds and it's still around. There's also a website for the
Vatican Nazi Peter's Basilica where the guy with the funny fish hat is there. You know, I'm talking
to the Pope. The Vatican is a red brick building behind St. Peter's Basilica that all state
departments of all member nations get their policy from and no appeal is allowed. Except
guy, right? Yeah, there's always an exception. There's that one guy, he's the Queen Beatrix
husband. Well, those are just formalities. Whenever you everybody, if you've ever seen
them or heard them from George Washington, Julius Caesar, Napoleon, it doesn't matter,
Trump, whatever, whatever, whatever. They have no their middle their mid-level management actors.
They're not even real mid-level management. Their mid-level management placeholders.
So like before this last election happened, people were all hyped up, you know, and all that in the
U.S. And I said, it doesn't matter whoever is put in next, you're just going to be the placeholder
for the next phase of the downfall of this country and North America. Right. It doesn't
matter who it is because it's the plan is bigger than them. Right. Trust the plan. Remember?
Yeah, you should trust the plan. If you know, if you know the plan, not the one that they're
telling you. Right. Who's they? But here's the thing. Grab a grab a hold of something that
you're good at doing. For example. Yeah, I really cringe when you hear on the news. Oh,
we're creating new jobs. That's what? Why don't you find out what people are naturally
inclined and good at doing and encourage them to do that for the rest of their lives?
Why do they need a job? That would be supposed that we live in a lawful world.
Not lawful, but that's if we had the right kind of tyrannical dictatorship under a fascist
communist, if we had the right one. Yes. You see what I mean? But do you think that this
new wave of currency, cryptocurrency and the like is the next is the next phase that they
envisioned that part of a continuation of this Babylonian system?
It's not a Babylon. It's more of an Egyptian system. The Babylonian system is still secret.
And I can explain very simply the model of and I'll go back to the crypto. The Egyptian system
works this way. When you need something from the state, you give them all your land
and they give you a little bit of what it's worth. Less than 10 percent. And then you obviously you
don't have any more land. So now you need food. So then you have to give them your body. You have
to sign over, which is slavery, your body and actually all your possessions and your animals
and then your physical body to them. And that's the Egyptian system. Right. If we're working with
the whole planet, the Babylonian system is a more mystical one, meaning more occult, occulted and
more metaphysical. It's more metaphysical, I should say. That has to do with when you hear
we have to capture the hearts and minds. Right. That goes more into allegiances with other
beings. I don't like to call them gods. And if you heard on the Achille of the Greek, well,
we call them gods because that's the common parlance we use. But they're just a race. Like
if you read, for example, the Bible, it says God. There is no God in the Bible. If you look in the
text, there is the Elohim. And the Elohim is a race of beings, just like you would say any other
race of beings. Right. Well, they're all around, right? You're saying some are just non-corporeal,
but they're all subject to death except for this Yahweh character. Right. Because he's managing
that aspect of it like like a video game at this point. Imagine you have the cheat codes of a
video game and you start playing with other people. Oh, you dirty boy. How come you're
winning every time? Right. Because I have the cheat. You know what I mean about cheat codes in
a video game. Right. You're not going to be taken out. So so here's the thing. Go back to the
crypto crypto currencies. I could give you this as an opinion, which I rarely say, but it's an
opinion. It's an intelligence agency artifact, meaning a subject. What? Why? Very simple. When
the intelligence agencies get into a business model, their model is a thousand percent to five
thousand percent profit. Crack cocaine, cocaine. Right. It costs about eighty dollars a ton,
but it produces a billion dollars a ton. Right. To make action. Sorry. Eight eight thousand dollars
or something to make that and you get a billion freight that every every ten thousand dollars,
let's say you invest, you get a billion. That's whenever you see stuff like that,
like cryptocurrency go from like two hundred dollars to fifty thousand. That's when you see
that huge percentage profit. That's all intelligence agency stuff. You kidnap a child.
It doesn't cost. What? I don't know what that costs. And you sell the child for thirty, fifty,
hundred, fifty thousand hundred, ten thousand percent. Whenever you see these thousand,
five thousand, ten thousand percent profit models, that's intelligent agencies. It doesn't
matter if it's human trafficking, drugs, cryptocurrency, whatever, piracy doesn't
matter. Are you with me on this? Yes. Religion, by the way, is like that also.
So and that's that's where it comes from, by the way. Intelligence agencies is the secret
religious orders, by the way. There's nothing. Don't mystify. There's nothing governmental.
They're state agencies. I call them panty sniffers. So anyway.
Well, then brought up the gods from the Bible. And I was wondering, who do you think wrote the Bible?
Well, it's very simple. Why don't we just look at it and see who it says wrote it first?
And then let's just see what other information we could get to back that up. That's that goes
with anything. You said there's a bunch of Jesus's, but the biblical Jesus, that's
biblical. Christ is a secret. Yes. Why? The biblical God is still a secret. Everything in
the Bible. Pick any character in the Bible, major or minor, and I will show you how the identity of
that is still a secret. Very simple. The biblical Christ is, sir. Of course. Anybody who reads the
book with comprehension will get it. OK. The problem is that the translations,
because they have sneaky ones where they interject words that are like holy and like giants, right?
Yes. Well, yeah, the Giants was never in that was put in a subdued. But but here's the thing,
even with the real crappy King James Version, by the way, don't if you're stuck on the King
James Version of the Bible, they're all the same. They start getting them to fight. You know how
divide and conquer like the people say, oh, this King James is better than the new international
version or this or that is so stupid. But anyway, if you are stuck on the King James
Version, it's a disease. I call it KJV syndrome. It's very hard to recover from that. But if you
do recover from that and you you do read it, even what's in the bad, that's not a translation.
It's a version. It never says it's a version. A version is hearsay. But even if you read the
really bad version, you will still get what really happened very, you know, very clearly,
actually. But what happens is we have something called image training from young children.
They show you Disney cartoons and Bible movies in your mind. So let's say you're reading the
Exodus when they leave Egypt and you see that piece of crap movie Cecil B. DeMille did with
Charlton Heston and the water opens up. They use Jell-O for special effect and they walk on the
bottom. So when you start reading that in Exodus, your brain says, when I was four years old,
I saw that movie. This is the part I saw in the movie. And you just read over it,
even though it says something completely different happened. Right. 9-11 is a perfect example.
Let's talk about that. Well, let's do it. Go on it for eight hours. I could give you extreme
details, but not necessary. Look, it's all in the language. Look up the definition of ground zero.
That was a technical term. A lot of people say, well, that just means the center of something
bad. No, it was a technical term. And let's just fast forward to the end. All those 10,000,
50,000, 30,000 people that got sick, every single one of them had a radiological disease,
some form of melanoma or carcinoma or leukemia. And here's the other thing I'm going to say,
look up Wikipedia shows the ultra HD photos of the World Trade Center after it collapsed. Right.
You know, the burned out areas, right. Aerial view. If you go to Wikipedia or just put in
high definition World Trade Center aftermath and find the ones that are HD, like the high
res, the ones you could blow up and, you know, really high resolution megapixel thing.
OK. And you look at the bottom, it credits. It says G.O.V. and then question mark. And then you
go. All right. Click on that or next to it. It says a photo taken by the N.N.S.A.
All those high definition photos and ground photos were taken by an agency called the N.N.S.A.
Now, who is the N.N.S.A.? It is the National Nuclear Safety Administration.
Oh, the reason why the National Nuclear Safety Administration spent invested so much time
on surveying and offering cleanup direction at World Trade Center is because obviously
the National Nuclear Safety Administration was set up to handle jet fuel fires.
That's obvious, isn't it? I'm being sarcastic. I know. Yeah, of course. Of course. Yeah. Yeah.
Obviously, you know, if you have a jet fuel fire, who do you call? You call the National
Nuclear Safety Administration, right? Duh. Isn't it said that certain federal
buildings can be built without nukes already in them? That's right. Certain jurisdictions
New York, Chicago, if you go over 56 stories, you have to submit what's called an emergency
demolition scheme. If you put this building up, how are you going to take it down, jerk off?
Well, the problem is that the heaviest armament that's used in the military
infantry is not even a third the thickness of the steel columns that were used in
buildings like the Willis Tower in Chicago or the U.N. Building, Dag Hammarskjld Tower,
the World Trade Center's Building 7. You can't take those buildings down. So you can't
use dynamite or anything to take down a four-inch-thick steel member. Actually,
the blast furnaces in Pittsburgh and places where they make the steel,
the blast furnace structure itself is not four inches thick, where they melt the steel.
So they pulled it off really well, though. I'm not going to get into all the details.
Dmitry Kalazov, he was part of the Directory 12. You could look him up. He has old stuff.
Most of it's been scrubbed. But the main thing that gave it away is, other than knowing,
since the 80s, that that function was there, but I didn't know really how to associate. I was always
told, stay away from those buildings. There are nukes in there. I said, what are these crazy
old engineers telling me that? But later on, it made more sense when I started looking at other
things. But here's the thing. If it walks like a duck and looks like a duck and smells like a duck,
it's a duck, right? Okay. So for weeks and months after the 9-11 thing happened, downwind,
people on the New Jersey side, hundreds, if not thousands of people in New Jersey and lower
Manhattan kept calling the EPA environmental offices saying, I can't stand the smell.
What's wrong with the smell? Well, it smells like burned electrical wires and rubber and gasoline.
Well, they're like, well, that's just because there are a lot of electrical wires in the
buildings. No, that smell, if you go back, there's plenty of letters and a book compiled.
There was one called Seven Hours to Zero, an author wrote, which was the dropping of the
bombs on Japan. After the war, the cessation of hostilities in the field ended. They sent
Marines to go clean up Hiroshima and Nagasaki. And those Marines wrote letters back and took
notes. And those were compiled in various short books. And if you read those books,
you can look them up. The Marines who went to do the cleanup after nuclear events in Japan,
atomic events, they were called. What did they all say? Are you guys familiar with it?
They couldn't stand the smell. It smelled like burnt electrical wires, gasoline, and
it's exactly the same. OK, what that is, it's called strong ionization. Have you ever been
near, have you ever dumped a bottle of bleach? OK, hydrogen, not hydrogen, sorry, sodium
hypochlorite. Or have you ever used an ozone machine, that really strong ozone, that's ionization.
Well, multiply that, if you have an ozone machine, get one that's a thousand watts,
that's strong enough that if you hold a piece of paper six inches away, a paper catches fire,
you'll get leukemia if you hang around that thing. But that strong ionization smell smells like
burnt electrical wires, gasoline, right? So that smell was very much coming out of the ground.
And they were underground, not in the buildings, obviously.
There were like 3,600 nuclear tests and 2,900 or 3,200, sorry, most of them underground because
the effects of what, when you say nuclear, most people say, think of flash, boom, bang,
like that moron, what's her name, Judy Wood, the shill, you know, gets you to folk, can't be
nuclear because you would say, well, nobody's talking about what happens, you put it underground.
It's a completely different phenomenon, surface reactions. There's videos where the Russians
were using them in the Soviet Union to stop gas leaks underground and to make gas chambers and,
you know, to store things because it makes a perfect glass sphere underground.
Anyway, we shouldn't even be getting into details on that.
But you did drop something that really piqued my interest about 9-11 before you move on,
which is the fact that it has been known about since the 80s and which kind of made me think
that the towers themselves must have been sort of prefabricated with this in mind or something.
Yes. Well, no, the blueprints for buildings like those towers and other buildings were
sitting on the books or on the desks of architects for almost a decade.
They would not issue building permits for them because you have to show how you're
going to take it down and nobody knew how. And then Project Plowshare showed in the SALT
Treaty, there's something called the Peaceful Use of Nuclear Devices Addendums.
You can only use three or four hundred and fifty kiloton maximum yield per day.
And the world was shocked. That's why I say the U.S. has no, there are no enemies.
Right. There are no enemies because if there was an enemy, obviously you'd say, look, they
nuked themselves. But here's the thing here. You want to talk about big balls, like big hairy balls
is Iran. In 2016 or 17, they detonated the Plasco Building, which was the tallest building in Tehran,
17 stories or something. They used a small nuke to bring that down also. That was when Obama was
going back and forth with the Iran and stuff. He says, look, we can do the same thing you did.
And nobody noticed, obviously, because, you know, but what they did notice, the building
dustified. And a month later, as they dug down to clear out the building, they would put the
front loader, the bulldozer, you know, the front loader bucket to pull out dirt and it would melt
because the rock underneath the building was at 3000 degrees still. Right.
So the Iranians showed the world that they have the same technology. Everyone does. They've
actually been, you know, using these nukes since the 80s like candy throwing. When you hear about
a car bomb that, you know, a little four door Nissan Sentra had dynamite or explosives and it
leaves a 30 foot by 40 foot deep crater. And anybody that's in the military and ballistics
will do the math and tell you, well, that's about two and a half tons of TNT to do that
because everybody knows you could put two and a half tons in the back of a Nissan Sentra, right?
Sure. But I still I'm dying to know if you think that the airplanes were holograms and.
No, there were no airplanes. Here's the thing. I have not firsthand knowledge because I wasn't
there, but I knew someone who was walking across the Brooklyn Bridge and he says the side of the
building just exploded. And all the videos that they show you, the people don't look up until
the building explodes when they show the plane. Now, I don't know about you, but you go near
airport and a plane even flies twice as high as it did there. You're going to look up because it's
freaking loud, especially when. Right. Nobody looked up in the sky until the building exploded.
So that's obviously put in later. The buildings, the planes went up and they were landed at West
Over Air Force Base in Massachusetts, which is 20 minutes away. There were hundreds of people
that called in on the way between New York and Massachusetts. I think there's going to be a
plane crash because an American Airlines plane just flew a treetop level over my house. Right.
And it's also impossible to make calls from the height that we're supposed
to go. They made the call. Yeah. And the hijackers were obviously the pilots and the crew, obviously.
But whatever happened to those planes? Well, they landed at Westover because they have a
10,000 foot runway. And coincidentally, the day before on nine, nine, ten, everyone on Westover
Base was all the people that report and live on the base. Guess what? They were told to stay in hotels.
That's that should make that should really be a signal, shouldn't it?
But how did that happen? It's very easy. Well, it's very easy. What you do is when you have a
base like that sequestered the next day, you just fly them off to wherever you're going to fly them
off to some scrapyard or something. There was a guy they killed. They killed him, his dog and
his children, who said that they're in Nevada and some great what do you call it? Airplane graveyard
or whatever. The planes are not the issue. Yeah, they're not the issues. The issue is,
for example, you had that event, which was an American event. But anything that happens to
America, remember, they say anything what's good for GM is good for the country. Remember, they
used to say that what's good for General Motors is good for America. Now what's good for America
is good for the world. So they so they did that there to get an international response because
the whole world was watching. Remember all those artists in England or whatever were recording and
they said it happened, they recorded a special song or whatever. Okay. Then if you listen to
Ocelli, what I said was the next thing is going to be like that with no planes and no towers,
but it's going to be something that's going to be repeated and repeated and repeated in the news,
and it's going to be international. It's going to be much bigger than that
because they're testing society. So between the 9-11 and the events we had the past two years,
the next step is the people are so cowardly and so ignorant, they're ready for forced slavery.
They don't need to do any more events like this. They keep softening us up.
They don't need to anymore. Those were just tests. They didn't even have to soften you up.
People were already living with their head up their butt for over 150 years. Actually, sorry,
what happened 150 years ago in America is far more shocking than those other these past two events,
you know, the Civil War. Now just let me just throw this in. We were going to talk about the
Civil War, which we probably didn't. We didn't produce anything on it. But here, if you study
the history, especially periodicals and local papers, five years before the Civil War started,
people in farms and small, really small communities around the Ohio area, western
Pennsylvania, southern New York, were reporting these marauding bands of people with black
uniforms or black, killing their property, kidnapping their children, setting fires,
on and on and on, you know, like imagine like some terrorist group. So what they were softening,
they were basically assaulting the people, right, for four or five years before the Civil War broke
out, you see, to get the people on edge. Because it's much easier, you don't think about reacting
when you're on edge, when you're stressed out, right? You don't think about things before you
do them. Now here's the other thing I want to give you. If you know anyone in Switzerland who's into
like Knights Templar history and likes to go hiking in the woods, they'll find all these
little enclaves, like little castles or manors in the woods in Switzerland, and when you approach
one of them, you know it's Knights Templar stuff because they have this regalia, and they're very
wealthy because you could see the iron gates and the way the buildings are made, and the wine
cellars and all that, right? When you start looking at these manors and these castles that the Knights
Templars have in Switzerland, and they have their regalia that, you know, the typical symbols of the
Knights Templars, what other symbols do you find amongst the Knights Templar symbols on these
buildings on the outside and inside? So if you don't know, I'll tell you. Do you know what the
confederate flag looks like? That's what you'll find in Switzerland. So, oh, those dirty confederates,
they were so original. Not. So basically, the Civil War was the Knights Templars versus the Freemasons.
Did the Civil War have anything to do with two kind of hypotheses I've heard? The Vatican,
and you mentioned like how it was the federal versus the states and all that stuff,
pulled the Yankees in because there's no one there, but did the Vatican have anything to do
with the federal government and owning these northern states? And also, too, did the world
fairs have anything to do with any of this stuff? Were the world's fairs used to reset,
or what was the problem? Did they tie into the Civil War? Were they kind of ways to fuck up
people's heads? Yes and no. Yes and no. The world's fairs are like fantasyland. When you
don't know anything about the world's fairs, if you show the world's fairs to someone who doesn't
know anything about the world's fairs, like a child or someone who's ignorant of them,
what's the first thing they're going to say when they see the imagery? Oh, it looks like what?
Disneyland, right? Doesn't it? Like a fantasyland. So that's all it is. Just like I said, for
example, in the U.S. and the Western world, the 50s, 60s, 70s, 80s, dot com boom and all that
was all fake, completely fake. It was a big move after the World Wars. Because you know,
who's the guy who wrote the three World Wars, the Freemasonic guy? Anyway, it's not just him.
I'm not blaming him. This is just part of it, because reality is fake anyway. But they wrote
there were going to be three World Wars, right, in the 1800s. And the Third World War didn't really
come. It sort of did with the fake Cold War. But in the meantime, they put, they stalled the
century with the World Wars, and then they stalled it with the fake prosperity of the 50s, industry,
60s, 70s, you know, skewing who won World War Two, which was the Japanese. And they're still
fighting the quote unquote Nazis, by the way, which is the National Socialist Party.
That never ended. That's still going on today. That's why they still make movies that Nazis are
the bad guys, right? So they're hiding all that. So the 50s, 60s, and 70s. So any quote unquote
in America, Westworld says, oh, go back to normal. You moron. That prosperity and that normalcy was
not normal in the first place. It was fake, obviously, right? So now you're going to go,
what they did was they stalled the century, they gave you fake prosperity of 70 years,
and now they're going to the next move, which is you pass or you fail. So if you pass,
you move on to the next level. If you fail, well, you got to do it again. But there's nothing,
you can't really do anything again in time. So what they're going to do is just break it down,
right? Imagine, what do you do with a failed restaurant? You sell off all the fixtures,
anything that's worth anything. And that kitchen hood that cost you $80,000 to install because
the fire department has to be approved of it, well, now you sell it for scrap metal for $300,
you see? So that's where you're going to now because the past 70 years were completely fake.
I know this is, I think I'm the only one saying this, by the way, it makes me sound like a nut
job. But if anyone who has at least two brain cells they could rub together, three would be
better, by the way, you'll see this is true, so. Greg, why weren't people in this generation,
like you and Daniel and I, allowed an actual shot at true prosperity and true freedom and trying to,
you know, how come we don't get this? It's just because- Oh, you do. Well, it depends on how you
define it. Okay, I knew a guy years ago, he managed private funds, like for wealthy people,
he had three, a private guy that managed private funds in the $3 billion range, right?
And his personal wealth was in the $50 to $60 million. And remember when the 2008 economic
thing went down? He went from 50, you know, the recession or the bank bailouts, well, he went
from personal wealth of like $50 to $60 million down to eight. And he's on the phone with me and
he says, I don't know how I'm going to survive. And I'm like, survive? If I see a blade of grass
growing in the street in the median, I know I could survive because there's a blade of grass I
can eat. As long as we got a decent place to sleep, decent food and water, we don't have it
too bad. Yeah. I was watching something yesterday. I'll plug this YouTube, but it's a bunch of young
German lads and they're really good at what they do. It's called Broken Window Theory,
YouTube channel. And they go around, they secretly enter castles and things and they're
very much into good photography. So they found this place in Germany where this artist, he spent
$1 million on getting cars, a car collection that he put out in the forest. And so they would
naturally decay. Rolls Royces, Porsches, things like that from the 1950s all the way to now.
And people go and photograph them because it was like a tree growing through a Rolls Royce. Yeah,
probably. Yeah. That's it. Broken Window Theory. Thank you. Yeah.
Watch those guys and support them if you would, because I enjoy them. They do really quality
work. Any other YouTubes you want to plug that I could subscribe to, sir, for supplemental education?
Zanjon. And also Daniel Sala's St. Olga's 69. Yeah. So let's just say this.
What they're showing there, the moral of the last, the million dollar car graveyard is showing that
no matter how wealthy you are, no matter what possessions you have, you die and all those
things return back to nature. Right. I'm picking up what you're laying down for sure, sir.
Yeah. I would say just don't stress, don't fret. Look, if we set out to make the home we live in
or the place we live in the best possible and the food we consume, our intake and drink,
water, wine, whatever we have the best. Great. All I do is maintain my truck,
which I don't have any knowledge to make it burn on water or anything like that,
yet I keep my house pristine and I eat the best food. Hell, you know what? I'll show you. I'll
show you what I got going on. So we got some bone marrow. This was a tomahawk, but they frenched it
some jumbo asparagus with lemon zest. And then what I'm cooking for my guests tonight is a
whole bunch of oysters Rockefeller. I don't know if y'all can see that. Yeah, it's a three dozen
right there. And then I put it on my big green egg out here. And I mentioned you said you like
wine, so I don't know. Yeah, you got a lot of reds there. I got some. I got some au brion. I
got it. But what's really cool is my dad, he sells wine for Sotheby's and stuff. He had this the other
day and didn't call me. A 64 calosegura three liter. He said it still tasted jammy and sweet.
He said the insides were just impeccable. I was like, well, so they'd never hit it with sulfites
or battery acid. Yeah, they probably let it naturally ferment. Sorry to take it off the whole
knowledge aspect. I just couldn't help. No, that's knowledge, too. Thank you for sharing.
I'm so passionate about that stuff, too. If you or Daniel ever can make it here.
Anyway, yes. So back to the thing at hand. Yeah, I understand. So it's about perspective.
OK, well, that's perspective. And it's also you are not what you think you are, what you
experience. What I mean, but you could think whatever thought high level, low level in the
middle of the night, you're walking over to get a glass of water and you bump your big toe on the
kitchen table. That experience will change your thoughts real fast. Right. So you are really what
you experience. So no matter what, you know, so here's the thing is knowledge power in the knower
or is knowledge power in the doer. In the doer, of course, so it's what you're doing that that
does it, but you have to have good knowledge to do good stuff, right? Yes. And that's why I seek you
and one more thing for I'll let Daniel, I'm sorry, I keep on railroading. I just
drink. I can't help. But. I mean, you'll get over it, you'll get it take you about two or three or
six months to calm down about it. That's fine. Well, you owe us nothing, man. I just and you
still give us the time of day and this is knowledge I can't get anywhere else or I don't
know how to get anywhere else. Well, you do know you do know how to do it. I just I think on some
of the early episodes, I always stated how to how to seek how to get it. You know, if there's
reference material on something, that means there was a benevolent force behind it. So if you're a
benevolent force and you create something, you just don't throw it to the next guy doesn't know
what it is. You include a manual, right? Yeah. So you talked about like the viruses at the CDC,
which is they call it the CDC, not the CDM or CDR or something. It's a Center for Disease Control,
not treatment protection. But you were saying how with the whole virus theory, you'll say that
they'll issue something that's like 903 pages. But in the abstract, say we've never been able
to isolate this and it probably doesn't exist in so many words. But and then why read the whole
why read the whole 900 pages? You read the introduction and the conclusion. If the
conclusion is non non conclusive, the rest of it is just look at the pictures and the graphs, right?
So if I if I have a nine, it was the National Institute of Health, NIH. Yeah, they have a 989
PDF on the study of transmittable diseases through viruses. And the introduction states,
this is all the studies we've had for the past 35 years on this. And now you've got 985 pages to go.
But you skip to the conclusion. And it says even after all these studies, it's still inconclusive.
We don't know. You can say you read the damn thing and the thing says you don't know.
Right. Even without reading it. But just look when you this is how you read a technical manual,
you look at the table of context with the subject, the title table of context shows you
each title on the table of context is there because it's it changes the subject and it's
a significant subject change, right? The basic list category of categories to be covered.
And the next thing you do is you page through it and see look if their graphs are pictures,
because if there's a graph or a picture means it's real important to illustrate it right to
break out of text. And then you go back and you go to each chapter and you read the first paragraph
and you read the last paragraph, because in basic writing, you have to write the conclusion
introduction. So now you've invested about, let's say you have a 700 page technical manual,
you've invested less than an hour, you can have a conversation with the author.
Most people you give them a 700 page technical manual comma week later, I'm only up to chapter
three, man. Why didn't you do a quick preview over the whole thing? See if it's even worth going to
chapter two or three? You see? Do you see my the approach on this? Yes, no, it's completely
pragmatic. And that's actually how I do whenever we're assigned all the stupid book reading as a
child to read all these damn books, I would read like the first paragraph and the last.
Well, let's let's go back to the analogy of the 989 NIH document says that viruses have nothing to
do with disease. If I just spent half an hour reading the the way I just said and say that I
read it and they don't conclude that viruses have anything to do with communicable diseases,
if someone did spend the time, even the person who wrote it, would they agree or disagree with me?
They would have to agree. Right. And I only spent a half an hour on it.
I do this all the time. On their level of cosmic censorship.
Yeah, but you can here's the thing, what's the first? OK, avoidance of a trap as knowledge of
its existence. It becomes a trap into a tragedy, like you'd say, right? If I tell you, in other
words, let's explain it for others. If you know there's a trap there and you still step in it,
it's your own damn fault. Can't blame anybody. Right? Yeah, no, you don't. Yeah, I completely
understand. And so. So, OK, the other thing is you have to be very confident, you know,
like the concept of when, you know, landmines, that's a nasty, nasty demonic thing to do when
you have a war. You put landmines, so unsuspected people, children, farmers walk on and get their
legs blown off. Right. It condemns it condemns large swaths of land to being abandoned because
people don't want to have their legs blown off. Right. So there's two ways to go after it. One is
a very light technical ginger way. Hope, you know, well, don't the hope and faith. Hopefully
I won't step on one. And the other one is let's develop something technically to sense the way
they are. But then there's the other one where you're so confident you build this
armored vehicle that is so damn heavy that it just rolls right over him and it doesn't do anything
because, you know, the yield of the mine is not that big. It's not more than five or six
pounds of explosive. So you build something that is as thick as the World Trade Center tower
beams were and you roll the damn thing over the land back and forth. And if one blows off
underneath it, we're inside. We say, hey, do you hear something? Sound like someone
dropped a rock on here. Right. It doesn't matter. So I'm saying when you develop confidence and
you know how to do something, be like that. So when you step on the mine. Right. It's like
someone wanted to debate me once. I'm saying this humbly, debate me on a couple of topics.
One of them was a medical and he was an older guy who's a professor. Right. Because they can't
exist. They can't allow their their false paradigm to shatter. And this is in no way kiss ass. But I
mean, no, no. And this is what I said. I said, well, if the purpose is I said I asked him,
what is the purpose of the debate is to win, of course. Oh, I'm going to grant you the win right
now. And he says, no, you can't do that. You can't do that. You have to do the debate. I said,
OK, give me a half an hour. I said, why? You need to prepare, huh? I said, no, I'm going to coach
this 12 year old girl right here. She's going to debate you and then beat you. She knows nothing
about the subject. And then he left. It becomes actually he said to me, how dare you talk to an
academic like he's an asshole? Yeah, well, fuck you is what I was doing. I feel like I'm in
railroad and just hijacking this interview. Please, please. No, we're just having a talk
here. It happens to be recorded. That's all. Go ahead. Exactly. But but you did gloss over
the fact that 9-11 and Corona were prototypes for something. And because to keep with the theme of
the Greek speaking, being like a trailer of sorts, could you give us some insight about
what the what it was, what they were a prototype for? Oh, what's called is the
disclosure. They keep saying disclosure. They allow that. All right. Of of how we're how the
new order society is going to be built, be built up. Let's go back. You had the stalled century.
In other words, the 20th century was stalled with World War One, World War Two, Cold War,
the renaming of all the countries in Europe and Africa, you know, not all. But, you know,
the fall of the Soviet Union, the dot com, everybody's connected. Like, for example,
do you know you could look this up maybe while I'm saying this, Suzanne Thomas Jefferson,
Thomas Jefferson had a quote that one day the government will be able to put something in the
body of its citizens to track every movement. Let me say that again. Thomas Jefferson,
Thomas Jefferson, you know, that guy lives down the street right now or the guy that maybe they
lived down the street 300 years ago. Which one am I talking about? Right. The one that lived 300
years ago or 200. He said one day the government will be able to put something in the bodies of
their citizens to track their every movement. I'm paraphrasing there. You could find that quote,
by the way. So does that sound like something that's happening now?
Yeah, they had a forethought and understood. Right. So Thomas Jefferson said this. So here's
the thing. So we put it all together. Right, Daniel. And this is more of a disclosure of that.
Right. Basically, you were given 70 years of prosperity, which was all fake,
was contrived by hiding history. When they hide the true history from you and tell you,
you can you can buy things, more things are available. That's all fake. Right.
They're hiding something from you. So you failed that test as a society. In other words,
they did this. He said these people, they should learn on their own. You should never rely on
somebody else to educate you. And if they do tell you something, you should check up on it.
And they don't. So is there was there any spirit? I'm going to we've went over this before the past
70 years, 50, 60, 70s, dot com till now or society as a whole. Did they spiritually evolve
with that open trade and ease of living, easier living or so? Did they spiritually evolve? Did
they get more gluttonous, more greedy? Look at you see. So they failed spiritually because the
people that are running, they're very spiritual. Spiritual can be good or bad, by the way. Right.
Like the devil is spiritual. And so is God. Let's say. Yeah, because I was spiritual. Yeah.
So they failed spiritually. So now what's the next step is those that have the spiritual
attainment, both good and bad, say, OK, what are these people good for? Well, they're good for
labor. They're good for sex slaves, good for general slaves or some of some people like to
eat other people. And then that's it. That's where you're going. I think I talked about the
cannibalism agenda. Do you remember that in the Charlie said the next thing is going to be the
cannibalism agenda versus the transgender and all that stuff. So really. OK, that makes sense.
I remember you telling me about our hearing you talk about all the baby remains found with bleach
white bones that were scraped and had scraping marks on them that are just either covered up
or destroyed or ignored. Yeah. Every every archaeological dig, there's like 2000 archaeological
digs all over the world going on every day. But how come we're not getting anything information
because once they start seeing on how the people are living, they write their report and they say
we find baby bones in pots, even pots with the shape of a baby. You ever see like those
fish baking trays that they make in the shape of a fish? Yes. OK. But can you explain how
birthday cakes and dolls are related to birthday cakes, cannibals and dolls, what they have in
birth? OK, birthday. What do birthdays, cannibals and dolls have in common? That's how you explain
the society. OK. Early on in the Mesopotamian region, they worship the balls, which means
the Lord. Like today, they worship the Lord. A lord is a ball. And the priest class was called
not a pastor, a priest was called a kahan. So the priest of ball was the kahan ball,
right? Priest of the Lord. Just like you have priests of the Lord today. And the way you
worshiped and gave offerings to the Lord is by sacrificing a child. And when you sacrifice the
child, the child, parts of the child were eaten. Some of the blood was taken. Like satanic
ceremonies are today, just a small portion. Everyone partakes in it. That's why eating of
human flesh is still referred to as kahan ballism. Right. Now, when the family returned and made this
offering, the other brothers and sisters asked, where's our brother? Where's our sister? So the
kahan balls, the altar boys, made a little effigy of a child, a doll, and said, give this
one. If any of the children ask, where's the missing child? Give them this to play with in
the meantime. So if you ask anyone where to play, giving specific female dolls or boy dolls to
children came from. They don't know. Right now, after a while, they didn't want to do this anymore
for many reasons. Sometimes they stopped it. Sometimes they didn't. They said, OK,
let's do the ceremony anyway, a parody of the ceremony. So you bake a loaf of sweet bread,
which represents the body of the child, and you put lights in it. And everyone attending,
the child that was representative there would blow out the lights, meaning blow out the life,
and everybody eats a piece of the sweet bread, which represents the body. And to show that this
brings prosperity, the child makes a wish of prosperity, and everyone attending the ceremony
brings a gift for the child. And I was reading this in a little book written in the 1800s,
and I didn't know what the hell they were talking about. I said, one day I woke up, I was like,
loaf of sweet bread, blowing out the lights, a wish of prosperity, bring a gift. That's the
birthday ceremony. God damn it. So that's why when I tell people, people say I'm going to a
birthday party. So you're going to have a real one or the fake one with the cake and the candles?
Because a real one would be, you know. I'm thinking of what you're laying down.
So you have a pretty sick society, pretty sick people doing this. You know what I mean?
How can people want to kill other people innocently? Okay, like let me just say there's
this random child. I'm a Satanist. You know, I'm looking at that child. How can they quantify it?
Let me just go kill someone innocent. How come they never have the thought, or they do,
but they can override the thought? Like, what if I was that child? Would I like that done to me?
Yeah, let me just interject one thing. They've captured the word Satanist also,
because the biblical Satan is not like that also. They've revived actually ancient gods,
but when they say Satanist, it's easier for the Christian mythos, because we live in the
Christian era, to associate with something bad. But because if Satan knocked on your door right
now and came in and you told him this, he would blush. And if you told him, let's go to the
Vatican, he'd say, why the hell do you want to go to that godforsaken place, right? So it's all
misplaced, but I'm not faulting you. That's okay, because whoever's listening to this will get the
I gave a couple of talks on this very simply. It has to do with the structure of the human body
being a fractal representation of life in the universe, life in the planet. So in other words,
it has to do with how the human body works, why children are being offered as sacrifice,
I guess. Would that satisfy your question? Why are children being sacrificed?
They're always seeing their omnipresence, so the only way to get their attention is through blood
offering, like you were saying, but the thing is...
Well, no, that's different. There are other entities that require you do other things with
children, like put them through extreme pain through anal sex. Let's take the one, the Vatican,
the demon that the Vatican in Scientology, it's the same demon.
But why does one have to get hurt? Like, why can't...
Because that's an external... It's like an ET comes to you and says, I need a cup full of
razor blades for breakfast. I mean, that's weird to you, but that's what they require, right?
From you, once you go into business with them, right? It's a strange business contract.
But the reason why children are sacrificed is something else. For example, what is the most
important organ in the human body? The genitals, yes, because they give you life
prosperity, so that things are phallic or... No, no, no, hold on, hold on, because if you
say the heart or whatever, you see, you can eliminate that and people will still be able
to procreate those that still have their heart. But if you eliminate everyone's genitalia,
everyone will be missing, gone in 40 years. Let's say sans cloning and in vitro and all that
stuff. Okay, so what is the fruit of the genitalia? It's the child. So in the ancient
mythos, you bring your God, the best of your fruit. So the best of your fruit would be the
best of fruit of your body, and you offer it, and they usually want an offering, and they like
the smell of burned flesh because when you go to outer space, and if you went into outer space
right now, very high altitude, you're near the moon, and you pulled off your, opened your visor
and took a breath, you would choke because it smells like burning flesh. When I say burning
flesh, I'm not talking about that tomahawk steak on the grill. I'm talking about burning hair,
nails, skin, and everything at the same time. Okay, that's what outer space smells like,
and I've been saying this for a long time, and then recently NASA even put up a video. Yeah,
when you open the door to the space shuttle and close it, it smells like a burning steak.
You know, I'm like, finally, they're starting to tell people, you know.
This is all in the ancient texts, by the way, everything I'm telling you, so.
But you see, you're robbing something that has the potential to have been someone. That could
have been the next. Yes, but hold on a second. You were not considered alive until you were
five years old back then because you were on mother's milk till five years old. Yes, you were
on your mom's teat till you were five, and the moment you got off your mom's teat at five years
old around that time, then you were considered alive. So, if you bring a child, let's say you
have a baby and you raise four years old or five, even at five, it's not considered a human yet
or an entity, a living entity. It is alive, yes, because if it wasn't alive, how would it be on
the mother? But this is the tradition, and this is the way things are done back then, and they're
still carried through now. You just don't know it. It's just not talked about. And I guess what
patron deity you have depends on your location, right? Yep, you were saying. It's cosmic geography.
Yeah, cosmic censorship, cosmic geography, cosmic law, right? All that stuff. Yes, it's all cosmic.
Yeah. I'm sure that there are also well-aligned elites out there that don't take part in human
sacrifice, right? Yes, there are, but they can only go so far. Just like people in Hollywood
and politicians, you're not going to be prominent unless you do those things, right?
Even the best politicians before the election, they're told that they're chosen to be the head
of the corporation, and if they agree, then they have to go into this room where there's
some children and some people with cameras, and if they agree to that, then they're in. All of
them, right, do that. Wow, okay. I thought it was different there. No, no, no. All of them.
Even the ones that have mango-colored hair, Zan. Well, look, how can one usurp that?
What happens if you were armed and you just... Oh, very easy. The answer, for example, is...
Remember how we said the governments or the state and the codes tell you that they're not lawful?
They give you the remedy right there. If you read Title 12.4.11, it says,
you're not authorized to use the money, and it's not lawful, but if you want lawful money,
you have to demand it, right? You have to demand... So this is a real simple way you
can fix the U.S., very simple. Instead of unconditionally endorsing stuff, put conditions
on it, and go to the state officials, because you have to go to the officials because they're put
in front. Just like when you go to the restaurant, you deal with the waiter. You don't go, who's the
owner? You ask the waiter who the owner is, right? Then the waiter doesn't bring you to the
owner. The waiter brings you to the manager, and the manager uses discernment. You might want to
keep the owner private, but even if he keeps the owner private of the restaurant, the message will
get to them, right? So what you do is you go to your state officials, doesn't matter who they
are, and you demand that the government is restored, and you know that it cannot be restored.
First of all, they don't even know what you're talking about because they've been so dumbed
down now also. Many of them now, they don't even know because they could have Freudian slips.
Like if you look, the last time you had people, politicians, that knew what was going on was with
the later Bush administrations, like Rumsfeld and Cheney and all those people around the
Condoleezza Rice, they knew. You know why I'm saying this? Because how many Freudian slips did
they have on camera? Many, right? Anyway, they were talking more than 20 years ago,
a lot of Freudian slips. Now they have them, so they don't know anything at all, so they can't
slip up. So you go to them and you say, we know that this is the worst thing to say to them,
by the way. We know that the state is administrating the bankruptcy of the government.
So for example, all the attorneys, all the banks, the banks are not banks, they're national
associations. National associations like the Sierra Club, Boy Scouts, Girl Scouts, right?
Anyway, so we know that the government is bankrupt. We have all the paperwork, all the states went in
on it, all the locals went in on it. What is it going to take to bring it back and make it lawful?
We want to do this illegally first, and then we want to switch over to a lawful system.
And how do we resolve the bankruptcy? Oh my goodness. But not just one person, because
they're going to brand you crazy, right? You need about 9 million people doing this,
which is 3%. What are the chances of getting 900? Zero. You could do this in any country,
by the way. They're all the same. Like if you're in Disneyland and you're riding the teacups or in
the Haunted House or in the Fun House or the Ferris Wheel, what's the difference? You're in
the same. To you, they're slightly different. And at this point, I think you also said something
like even the well-aligned of the higher echelon are all accepting of the fact that the remaking
or starting new is inevitable and that we are beyond saving at this point.
Yeah, there's nothing this. Yeah. What they're going to do is reorganize. OK. You have a car
and it gets in a crash and it's so bad you can't fix it. You got a guy outside that showed up
that's just started working on my fucking house, some welders that I didn't even pay yet. So I
don't. I don't just deal with it. We got it. OK. All right. Cool. Sorry. Just come back soon,
though. Well, no, no, I don't know what I don't know what the hell is going on.
That's what those loud noises were. These guys. Oh, OK. All right. You want to end this and start
one private without me, you know, saying or it's fine, whatever you guys want to do. But I'm just
going to I'm sorry, all these people, you're not here now because you got to deal with that. So
deal with it. Yeah. Whatever you got to do. I'm going to end this. I got to go. OK. All right.