Great, I really appreciate you reaching out man. How's everything been? What's going on?
You told me you gave me some updates on China and Taiwan. Oh, yeah the date. Well, you want to go political?
You're running for Senate Senate, you know, it's just a here before we go political
You got to realize that you know, what mid-level management is, right?
That's that's the highest you're gonna go
It's kind of like when you go shopping for stuff. You're getting all the mid-level stuff, right?
That's the best you're gonna get
There's a lot of reasons for it. But here when you read about all the ancient kings and all that too, you know
In ancient history, they were mid-level management. Also, I know things like that
Say again, maybe you can answer things like that. Yeah, they were all mid-level management. Actually you brought up Nebuchadnezzar
and you read in Scripture he was
Basically, let his hair grow. Let his nail nails grow kind of like Sam Hughes or whatever
Yeah, you see that and Babylonian things with the curly hair know what the well
I'll know to show that he was mid-level management. If you read in the book of Daniel and other places
He went nuts. He lived he went out in the forest and ate what the animals ate
He let his hair grow. He didn't bathe his nails grew out. He acted like a wild animal for about seven years living under a tree
Wow, are you familiar with that? Yeah, you could read that find this down
Yeah, yeah, it's in it's in the right smack in the middle of what's called the book of Daniel
Danielle and what's interesting about that is after he went through that period of seven years. I would what would you call that?
Right. I mean pretty much insane, right?
He declared that the Elohim were running the planet the Elohim by the way when you look at that
King James Bible they call them God and they're not God and the top the head honcho in
There is Yahweh and they call him Lord
Which is appropriate because the head honcho is the Lord, right?
So, I mean, yeah, yes long ship. They live forever and all the other jobs are jealous
I'm just trying to recall what you teach. Yeah
Also, he had well in the machine the water that does like the clouds and it comes and flows out the Garden of Eden was
Never here. Anyway, I mean interrupting. Oh, yeah, you've seen Independence Day, right the big spaceships. Welcome to
Yeah, right. Exactly. That's what's going on at the Elohim
The word God by the way is to
Teutonic old German old English. It means the Sun or it means those that are up in heaven, you know, like Anunnaki or whatever
Well, since we got on to the politics
there is
Geo, there's geopolitical politics, which I think we just disqualified as any of having any significance and we jumped right to cosmic
Politics now one thing that when you look at all the religions of the world all of them bar none
They are giving you cosmic politics inner not the inner cosmic politics
But what you think you should know after you've been declared an idiot
That that's how they view the people by the way. So if you if you look at
All of it from that perspective, which is the correct and true perspective
They're mostly lies, but in order for a lie to be believable you have to have some truth, right?
So if you find what the some truths are in the religions
They all lead back to the the volumes of texts that they subscribe to, you know
the in the Hindu tradition
they have the Rig Vedas the Puranas the biblical is the Christian and the Judaean the
The biblical is also the Muslim by the way
Because you know in the Koran Syria 26 and Syria 28 basically says that
There's no God's law is not in the Koran. You have to go get it from Moses
Well, where do you get that you have to go to the Old Testament? So the actual Koran directs the reader to go
To the biblical text how many Muslims you think do that?
Big fat zero, right?
Okay, so and also the biblical law by the way is commanded all throughout the Bible. It's never done away with
So all of these religions and the way they're behaving is basically once you've been declared an idiot then you have a choice
That's why when you go to a government building or a hospital, they ask you what religion you are
You know, so so what you know, what idiot what what idiotic membership? Are you part of?
Okay, just to go back to the cosmic politics
The Elohim are the human collective
Meaning they have the the five-pointed star, you know, the two arms two legs and head, right?
Most most beings have that they're the human collective
and what you will see in the ancient texts and it's very sparse and very
Minimal but very significant is you have this concept of the serpent a sky serpent the dragon the Draco
The reptile on and on. Okay when you see that look
Examine the context and now we're going to get into the inner cosmic political world
And when you get into the inner cosmic political world
You will find however old you think the universe is or however big it is that this universe is run by an imperial force
Okay, I'm actually using their terms now
Who who are they and that imperial force is comprised of these dragons?
reptiles Draco types in other words, they are the original species the first
progenitor type
Group to enter into this universe
Okay
Who where and who they came from? I don't know
I don't want to act like um, I know everything about everything or everything about some things
I know a lot about many things, but I can't continue on that path
But what I can tell you know before us the dinosaurs were a pet project of these reptiles
Just like we would have a zoo or a public park
Put together to be a recreational place to go and admire animals and natural settings if you've ever been to
old money black nobility
Property they how they'd love their gardens
You know like, you know, if you go to some real old old money people, they invest a lot in their gardens
They have greenhouses and beautiful grounds and all that
That's what the earth was what they did
The dinosaurs, okay, they say a meteor destroyed them
Okay. Now it looked like a meteorite like here for example since you brought up the dinosaurs, that's good
We're taking a narrow swath. Okay of something that's huge
You know you how do you eat an elephant one bite at a time? So here's one bite. Okay
Now we all hopefully you myself and whoever is listening it's fairly reasonable and logical, okay, so
You have a magnet in your hand and I have a magnet in my hand and we throw them at each other
let's say your magnets the size of a beach ball and mine is the size of a grain of sand and
I throw my magnet at your magnet, you know, they're gonna
Connect and where are they going to connect on the poles?
Not at the equatorial part. So if if meteorites are magnetic, which they all state they are
And the earth is magnetic
It is nearly impossible for a natural meteorite to hit anywhere else than the North Pole or the South Pole
So we have this large hole in the Yucatan Peninsula in Mexico huge two mile wide
Hole in Arizona. They're all over the world in Russia Africa were quote-unquote meteorites hit those were not natural meteorites
Those were actually put together by the human collective the Elohim and others
Their hybrid derivations of
And when I mean a hybrid derivation of like for example, I have a friend and he's Okinawan and
His wife is Portuguese now Okinawan looks so, you know, people mistake them for Japanese, but they're not Okinawans or Okinawans, okay, and
They have a daughter. So he's Asian and she's European. So their daughter is Eurasian and I call her a hybrid
Because from a racial perspective she is a hybrid. She's not Asian and she's not European
You see what I mean by hybrid? It's very easy to hybrid eyes, by the way
Just like I have a friend and she's
from
the continent
And her husband's Italian white, right? So their child is neither. It's a hybrid you see so you have hybrid humans
Okay, so some of these hybrid humans
Decided to gather together space junk and
Throw it down on the planet around the area of Mexico and create that big swath a big Gulf of Mexico area
But whenever you see by for example meteorite strikes on the earth, you could look up in the internet internet craters meter meteorite craters
Anything that's not exactly at the North Pole or exactly hit the South Pole is not a natural meteorite
Either then you're gonna say holy shit Greek. What are you talking about?
Well, first of all, I want to just say that you've been lied to
Second of all, they don't they know this fact. I just showed you using third grade science
What do you wonder you think children are given magnets to play with around the third grade fourth grade, baby?
It was pre-k for me. Okay, there you go
So that that meteorites natural meteorites will never hit the surface of the earth other than above 80 latitude or below, right?
So North Pole or South Pole so all of these meteorite air
craters that you see on the planet are
weapons
Okay, and then if you want to discuss, you know further on how how you know
You can even tell what kind of like for example a ballistics expert can tell you
What kind of a you know explosive it was by because of his training, okay?
Just like
Forensics people that do murder cases can tell you what kind of an animal this person was mauled by right
Like if it's a lion
It's always the bet the face a bear will be the groin and the intestinal area, right?
A dog will be the limbs and the fingers right if you so if you see a body having those characteristics right away
With one second you can you'll know what animal did that to a human but the common person will be walking on says
I don't know man. He just had parts of his body bitten off
He couldn't tell right and I just gave you the small little outline that if you just remember those little rules
It's like you've just you know elevated yourself to the top 0.1% of the society
So once you see how the magnets attract and you see what's going on on the earth
You know that they were they were not meteorites per se
So that's what the dinosaurs were now by the way. I'll go out on a limb the human collective that did this
Was severely punished and their planet was wiped out here. I'm gonna go out on another limb
When you when you look at the pull what they call the Pleiades which has over
20,000 Suns and several million planets with civilizations
That is a general grouping
constellation grouping
When you look at it now with a telescope or what's been documented by science that only represents 10% of what was there a million?
years ago a
Million years ago there were 90% more planets and Suns and they were all lost in an incredible battle or war that lasted for a very
long time between the
dragons, let's say I don't like using the term Draco because
That's a very you know when people say reptilians and Draco you hear all this stuff, right?
Which ones it's it's like when you say humans
The humans aren't doing anything if you look for example at
Earth you you can't just say humans because you have so many nations that have so many different cultures in the way that they live
You have to say well Americans or Russians or Egyptians or Iraqis, right or Chinese because they're so very different the way
They're acting right? Yeah, so the same with the reptiles. I mean when I mean, who are they is like for example the
The Imperial Draco they they're in the area of Thuban
Right, which used to be the North Star now. No, it's no longer the North Star
It was the North Star about 36,000 years ago
You have
Kolasque the group called Kolasque
That runs the Milky Way
They have pretty much integrated themselves out of they're still part of the Empire
But they've integrated themselves more into a more broad-reaching way of thinking because the purpose the
thinking that the Imperial has
Imperial
Draco is their thought is to explore and dominate the entire universe by force
Or by collect by by a willing collective so when they show up if you're a willing collective there's no force involved, right?
You have others in the ancient a lot of them that
Interacted that are known as the demons like the demon Ga or more cool
Or Vortac, right? You have the theta Tauri
I mean I could go down with a 50 a list of maybe another 20 or 30. No, that's not even do it
I can send you the list and you could type it in so when you hear about
The reptilians, I just mouthed out about eight or nine different races that are very distinct
There's about 50 to 75. So when you hear about people talking about reptilians, or it would be just like someone said
Hey, I visited earth and met humans and you're like, oh humans
Okay, but they're not telling you that there's different groups here with different cultures and different, right?
So then you have to question if they just stick to humans, what do you know about them?
And who are they? Oh, well, you know, they like to eat ice cream
That's what I hear when I listen to
Yeah, yeah, that's like that's like so narrow it's almost down to stupid
So when you listen to what's being put out there in this quote-unquote community called the SSP
Whatever when I hear that it's like I told Daniel I can't listen
I have not listened to any SSP videos for more than five minutes anyone. I have to turn it off because it's just
I'm not saying that they're full of crap. But if you put it on a scale, it wouldn't weigh anything
So and it's not helping anyone
So one one thing that you know, we took a narrow swath of the dinosaurs and we led to this. So
essentially
For the past I would say half a million years when you got the moon
The moon that we have now the satellite known as the moon
Which is a dead it's a dead planet, by the way, all all planets and moons are living they have living they're living entity
But the moon is a dead one. It would be like for example, you know when you go out in the forest and you see animals
They're alive, but if someone shoots one in taxidermy and hangs it on his wall, it's it looks alive, you know
I don't know if you ever been into a place that had that they turn on the light and you see a bear growling like whoa
For a second, you're startled because it's so lifelike, but it's dead
That's our moon. It still has maintains. It's look like a planetary body, by the way
Once you start getting to more advanced cosmology, everything is a planet
What do I mean by that Suns are planets?
I know they're not fusion balls or whatever black holes are planets quasars are planets, right?
All these things are planets
Sorry, which are just larger black holes quasars, it's simply pulling it
Oh, yeah, all of the things that pulse are as quasars all of the bodies that they tell you are gas giants
For example, there are no such thing as a gas giant
Planet, for example, you could look at the Schumacher Levy comets. It's a string of pearl
meteorites that hit Jupiter in the mid 90s
If it was a gas planet, it would have gone through no matter how strong the magnetic field
It would not have captured them and you could see the surface impact that goes through the the clouds of Jupiter
There's still video they'd like they scrubbed it all but you could still find it
You could see the meteorites and let's go string of pearls
There's about seven or eight or nine meteorites going into large meteors
I should say not meteorites into Jupiter and crack and when they would crash on the surface
There would be a blob a very bright flash. All of the planets have surfaces. The Sun has a surface. It's off
It's a planet also
So, I know it's this sounds bizarre, but just know all this is welcome. I can't get this anywhere else. Please like you're not
Sorry, you're not and well, there are people that know it, but they're not speaking like for example
9-eleven was a textbook
101 nuclear demolition nuclear meaning on they're placed underground and anything on on the surface the surface reaction, you know
Justifies the object and brings it down. That's 101
That is like is if you were taking classes in electricity, you would learn
There's a positive and negative on a battery, you know real basic stuff the most basic
Nuclear demo demolition works was 9-eleven at 101. Okay, there were thousands of people involved Americans and others foreigners
Department of Energy the OST, which is the Office of Special Transportation. It's a branch of the Secret Service
EG&G, which is a they've been
Tasked since the 1940s to develop all the instrumentation
I could go on and on and on and on all these people were involved FEMA, you know everything
They were all involved in there and you know what? There's not one person
That's come public to give even a slightest breakdown of such a basic event
You know that isn't that ridiculous? Yeah. Yeah, those who speak don't know those who know don't speak
Is that there's what I've been told what you know when it comes sure
So yeah, so if that holds true, then I'll say I don't know. I'm just speaking. How about how's that?
I didn't mean it that I wasn't applying anything. No, no, of course
So from a from a cut let's go back to the cosmic inner politics
So there's a sort of a truce around the time when the moon was put in place
The the Elohim
Which you call God or gods or Yahweh and the whole collective the Elion?
They have a group of hybrids with them. Also, they're known as the Nakash and
There are the reptilian hybrids very similar to if you watch the later Star Trek's
Where in the early Star Trek's they're fighting the Klingons, but in the later Star Trek they have wharf who's like on the bridge
He's a officer right like they had a peace treaty. So now he's an officer kind of like yeah
Yeah, yeah, just kind of look at the American military
You would have never had a black man or an Asian man in the military 150 years ago. There was so prejudice, right?
So, you know would have never happened but now you do so you have a hybrid it's called they're called the Nakash
And they're in the Bible
So everything I've told you most of it is pretty well
It's not easy to access but I'm maybe that's why I'm saying it
But some of the stuff that's easy to access like I'll point out if I say some things in the Bible or give you a
Direct reference you can get it. You can look it up yourself
These Elohim through treaty and other things like that
Will dominate the earth and have been dominating the earth. They're very hands-off
Just like if you lived in somewhere in the middle of Montana
You wouldn't know what was going on in Washington DC unless you watched it on TV
You got a letter
But if you didn't watch them on TV because these Elohim are not on TV and you don't get letters
It seems like they're not around you see what I mean?
Yes, so they're going to what I've been saying they're going to sneak in because remember this solar system is under imperial rule
But they do have like for example Saturn and Jupiter are major major
Things in occult literature like, you know, Saturn is the black cube you see it in the Kabbalah right father time Kronos
Jupiter is known as Jove you always swore by Jove or Jupiter or Zeus
They're the moons of these planets
have
ambassadorship
Outposts of both the Elohim the human collective they go by several names
The Elohim is the old Judaic term. I'll use that because it's the easiest to acquire
terms like Anunnaki and other terms have been so bastardized and
Misused that I prefer not to trample a walk on something that's been so heavily trampled. It doesn't hold anything anymore
so
The truce that's in the solar system will not necessarily be broken, but you're going to have this human collective
Sneak in and take over the earth and remanage the human collective that's on this planet for the next thousand years
You will know that this is beginning when you see a Middle East Union form with a new country called a Syria
Basically a civil war in Iraq. You're going to see a monarchy installed in Israel
You're going to see a woman ruling Egypt these things when you start seeing these things happen
You'll know that you're getting to the time that I'm discussing where this particular
Society as you've known it will will go away and the new one will come under the Elohim
But the Elohim will not be doing it directly. They will be doing it
through a group of humans that they empower
If that makes any sense as a matter of fact some of these empowered humans will be ancient humans
They'll be brought back from the dead known as the resurrection
So it'll be people like Adam
What's that
No, he's too. He's a part of a different collective. He will probably be punked and
He will be given a reflective orange vest and a plastic broom
If you know what I mean
Okay
If there's that colorful is that descriptive enough?
What you laying down real quick if we get before you continue with these points you say at a time a truce at the time
The moon was put in place
By who and when roughly the mixed human collective a
Mixed group of human meaning and some reptilian well Draco based
More of the diminutive type the the Imperial Draco do not mix
Only what they're all you hear about people being hybrids of them. That's no sorry
You'll you'll be a hybrid of someone that is part of the descended from them, but never the Imperial
They're they're the most high snooty highfalutin
How else would you say?
Beings in the universe right even the Elohim will invite you in well these guys will not
So most likely the the least
The least the most distant or the closest relative you could be to an Imperial Draco will be a
Hybrid that was probably done between the Kalasch and the feline races
where the feline races see the the
Kalasch
invaded the feline in part of one of the Pleiadian and Ceres constellations and
They got such a fight back
Just like the Elohim have been fighting the Draco back
so you see this is how the Draco are when I say Draco Imperial Draco when they come to invade you and
You fight back and you bloody their nose and even threatened to destroy their strike team
They don't call in more to kill it to to to beef up their lines to defeat you they stop and they say
Wow, what a bunch of noble brave fighters. Hey instead of destroying them. We'd be better if they were on our side
They respect it. They respect the people that
Yeah
Exactly. You see that so because of that they kind of work with the
the feline races
So from that program you might have some humans that might say that they came from some kind of reptilian hybrid from that point of
You notice I'm being very specific on this
Every time there's
You know the concept of sine wave it goes up and down and you know
You have a peak and a and a lull this is how the people to talk about the fantasies
Yeah that have been going on in space you you have someone that pops up every couple of years that gives everyone all this hope
that the
dragons will be
The Draco are defeated and humans are liberated. There's no war. That's
That's that's like the Jesus nailed to a cross wearing a diaper thing. It doesn't exist, right?
It's fake, but it gets everywhere right everyone worships it
The the that will never happen
it in this universe now if you think you can escape the universe and go to another universe completely that
What might be the case where the Draco are defeated? What will happen in the future is
Just like I mentioned the feline races
Confronting the dragon races and they found the dragon the red Draco. Let's say found them to be noble and
Respected them. They did the same with the humans and to the point right now
We're the human the Elohim are some of the most technologically advanced in the universe at parity if not slightly more than the Draco
What will happen in the future is all of these races the Draco will always remain dominant because they were first here
But they were letting more of the instead of being so dark they're letting more of a lighter side
Like for example if you were in the reptilian collective
Which is over a million different races and you showed sympathy and empathy for one of your kind or another you were sent to a mental
hospital
Because sympathy and empathy is considered as a disease
They are letting more of that into their collective and have been for thousands of years and
And word has it that recently in recent in the past few thousand years the Imperial High
Command in the Draco also is allowing it because before when it was brought into some of the other races
they would destroy those races for having sympathy and empathy and the big milestone here is
Few-thousand years ago that the even the highest groups of those who dominate this universe are allowing more of a lighter side
To understand what love is what sympathy is what empathy is what peace is?
right, but peace is also a bizarre thing because
from a logic perspective
When you want peace only peace that means you have to be in a constant state of war with war
Enforcing your rule everywhere in order to have peace
You make war you're making war when you make peace you make peace
But do you have if you ask people or groups why they go to war is to make peace
Not right and when you ask them why they go to peace is to not make war
So to not do something essentially you're fighting that thing that you don't want, right?
So the the concept of peace and war again has not been explored
spiritually philosophically and on and on and on to actually develop a
Point where we could say this is a state of condition of neither peace nor war that we will exist in
It's either peace or war and that doesn't work
That's like saying black or white and I hate to tell you but most of everything is gray shades of gray
I could show you a shade of gray. That is so light. It appears to be white, but it's still gray
I could show you a shade of gray. That is so dark. It appears to be black, but it's still gray
So these are things that could be discussed in the future
But again, what will happen the various let's say the huge the main human collective and the main Draco collective
They both have the same idea, which is to explore and dominate the universe
But they will come to a crossroad and more than a crossroad to a point within each of their groups
Well, they will sense that the it's best if everyone worked together
Okay, instead of carving up territory and having truces and armistices, right?
You take over here and I take over there right? No, it will be that this is this will not happen till far into the future
This the soonest I see it ever beginning to happen is more than a thousand years from now
so I
Hope I shared because one of the messages you gave me share some things that I haven't done at all yet
And I think I might have right
Yes, and also things that you said off record without allowing me to record. So I appreciate sure. Yeah
No, sure
Since it since the clock is still ticking go ahead and fire something off maybe
You know catalyze the moment, you know what? I mean?
Yeah, I'm just super interested in our real history
You know the real American history that this stuff is not cool
You know like like you were giving me the real reasons why we did why we had the Civil War you tell me
I mean, I don't know what you can it's a trap
America was a trap. What happened was
There was a lot of stuff going on in Europe very very harsh stuff, you know, they wanted to exterminate certain people
Islam was created to prevent the spread of Christianity through the whole world, which was a good thing by the way
Because Christianity promotes ignorance and dominance and really negative stuff believe it or not
That in turned Europe inside out
But by the way, you know all of this, you know
How you destroy the all the false narratives is by using definitions, right?
I think before we've gone and this J es us character does not exist biblically or historically. It was made up just like
Oswald who shot Kennedy was made up use a Patsy
Yes. Yeah, just like just like Osama bin Laden was made up, right?
Right on and on and on like Einstein was made up and you know
But but he didn't do what they say he did right what here well
He didn't even exist the way that they say like for example, you know, there was no
crucifixion, right
That's pretty obvious whether you know it or not
I mean
It's it's really obvious because he was returned the the Roman
Governor Pontius Pilate returned him back to the Judeans to use their law. That's that's the key, right? So
There's no, you know, he's the most hate he talked if you read the New Testament
The biblical Christ is the most hateful character in the entire Bible
He hates everyone
He's he's like kind of like I'm like I call myself an equal opportunity hater. I just hate everyone
I mean, yeah, so, you know until you prove yourself, you know, like we talked about
The polionic code of law, you know, you're guilty until proven innocent, you know
Otherwise, why would they arrest you right? So I'm probable cause or whatever. So anyway
What what America was was a trap?
Basically, there was so much it was to blow off steam
They created all the corporate states, you know, they're all all the 13 colonies were corporations. You could look it up. They still are
They were brought they came over here and then you had a bunch of degenerates known as the founding fathers who wanted to join the
House of Lords and they kept appealing to the king
And he denied them so they mustered up enough money
To and they also waited for the smallpox pandemic to to reach a very high
state
when they started doing what they were doing and they had help from the French and all the other stuff and remember the
Bavarian Illuminati for formalized at the same time it all has very much
You know intertwined together
the George Washington character, which one the the one that
people talk about he died in the first week of the
Revolutionary War and they put a look-alike there that had no teeth. That's why when you look at the history
They're like, how are we going to get teeth in this guy's mouth?
Hurry up get some teeth in his mouth, right?
And when he would show up to the Freemasonic meetings and they want to do certain rituals
He flipped out because he never you know, he didn't know anything right? It was he was the look-alike
This is how sad and pathetic the American history is
You're on the brink of a civil war right now because
But not like the original Civil War that they called they was never called the Civil War until the early
Early 20th century. It was called the War of the States
And it was the federal versus the states and it was over commerce and taxation
But here, you know, what's interesting?
Do you remember a few years ago how they started doing all these protests with BLM and then Tifa and whatever else like that?
Property damage. So how they the Rolls-Royce SUV would leave bricks on the side of the road and these all these hip hoppers
No, is it true because I use this whenever I go politicking around not not that it'll make a difference
I guess in the grand scheme of things, but I try to put the money where my mouth is
Actually, sorry running for it will make more of a difference than getting the job by the way
You will bring more you will running actual the process of running, you know, like the trip. It's not getting there
It's the trip what you do while you're running will make more of a difference
But go ahead. It's true that they're all
George Soros funded and I don't know if you
I'm not gonna say this anymore. But George Soros isn't really who he's played up to be. He is
Most of the facts are correct
I'm not gonna I
No, not publicly
He's just a front man for another front man
You will never remember we started off mid-level management
Yeah, you're not gonna see okay, but look this way if you've seen their picture
You heard their voice or no or heard their name. They have no power
They are a representative
Just like for example, if you watch a Tom Cruise movie
Tom Cruise is not who he says he is in the movie
He's some actor
So you can watch a Tom Cruise movie where he plays a samurai's in Japan another one where he's a pilot Air Force, right?
You can watch him where he's a you know, he's not any of those things
Outside of the movie right so outside of whatever was reported to you that this guy is doing is not true
But if they tell you Soros is funding within the story. Yes, it is true
But overall you it laying blame which is what they want you to do is not okay, but this is my point
You could look this up
But in the early 80 it before 1860
Groups like Antifa and BLM were being sent out throughout the countryside
Raping burning pillaging stealing killing people all over the place to destabilize the country prior to the Civil War
There were black hooded men. They were black. They showed up middle of the night
They would torch barns shoot children women
Robbed steel all over the country particularly the southern like the Midland states
You could look this up, you know, Ohio, Carolina's, Virginia
Pennsylvania there were these marauding bands. They were like softening up the
The culture
Before now they say the attack on Fort Sumter or something started the Civil War. That was like a semi defunct
Fort it was a false flag and they said put some drunk a bunch of alcoholics running the place
Just blow up something there and say they were attacked
Just like the Vietnam, right? What was they that they even the Pentagon admitted? It was a false flag
They never got attacked by Vietnam, right?
Remember the bait. What is it? The whatever the awful talking? Yes Gulf of Tonga they admit
Okay, but this is what they don't admit
Do you know that the Vietnamese sunk a US aircraft carrier? You could look it up
And they sunk it in port. How did they do it?
Sponge divers can hold their breath for 20 minutes on average. They got a bunch of sponge
sponge Vietnamese sponge
Divers to go underneath the aircraft carrier and with magnets and some rudimentary waterproof devices of timers
And I mean that it looked like something out of a cartoon
Placed on the hull of the ship
Away from the anchorage, you know, which is where the ship is reinforced and blew a big hole in it and sunk
You can look this up
the Vietnamese did sink an aircraft care but the reason why it's never made public even though it's what you can find it publicly is
Because if you sink someone's aircraft carrier, you saw my battleship, right? It's a lot worse than that
It's like a punch in the eye to an imp because what do aircraft carriers represent Imperial dominance, right?
Yes
You don't put all of your greatest assets in one basket. There's no such thing as an aircraft carrier
They're called carrier groups an aircraft carrier requires about a dozen ships to support it and they're the easiest things to take out
there's constantly war games being done with aircraft carrier groups and the
Opposition generals within the what they do in the Navy
They say you'll be team a you get the carrier group and team B
You get whatever weapon you want to fight the carrier group, you know within the same US Navy
what do the
team be always pick
they
they go and buy a
$40,000 a whole about a dozen
$40,000 speedboats or $100,000 speedboats and a couple of silkworm missiles or granite missiles
and that's it and they take out the carrier group in seven minutes every time and
They've been doing the same exercise since the 1970s and since the 1970s
I'm until about five years ago. Every carrier group has been taken out
In less than 15 minutes with just a bunch of regular speed boats
Which you can go down to the dock and buy and some silk silkworm or granite missiles
Very simple rudimentary, right?
I'm looking up silkworm missile you had mentioned
Granite before and explained the granite is what they shot into the Pentagon by the way. It's a 500
Well our house or own house who makes them
There's the p700
There's a p100 p200. I shouldn't be well, actually the p700 is a 500 kiloton. It's a shipwreck missile
P700 is a 500 kiloton
Thermonuclear in it's a ramjet and rocket-powered. It has a rudimentary AI
Satellite driven you can't knock it out with an EMP
It flies in a spiral and right before it hits the target. It drops to 8 feet above or 10 feet above the waterline
It's hypersonic
As a ceramic reinforced casing it's designed to go through it through the hull of a ship now fortunately
Oh, well, the the guys who launched the p700 towards the Pentagon did not have the codes
How do we know? Well because you didn't see a nuke go off, right?
So and those were absconded the the the missile that they shot into the Pentagon was absconded from the Kursk submarine
Which went to the bottom in the year 2000?
It imploded and
It had 21 of these missiles on board and they were all when they raised the Kursk all of them were missing
That wasn't that was an inside job with the Putin Putin covered it up all the Russian generals covered it up
They got wealthy off of that. How do you think Putin's worth 250 billion?
People don't know that I see Putin's like the richest man on the planet right 200 billion or some plus a lot of people
Don't know. I don't know if you heard of this Putin Palace and one of the biggest palatials of states out in Sochi
Well, they'll do that all these guys that do and I was like, look even the American generals
Every single one has a degree in finance, right?
He looks serious and once they get into power, it's kind of like what I got a
16 or 15 years old. I worked at a convenience store and
I wasn't happy working there, but it was you know, you could make you could work anytime was 24 hours, right?
So if you want a little extra cash, you could just schedule yourself anytime during the day
And this is what the manager tells me. He says it's 350 an hour. This is like 1980, right?
It's 350 an hour and all you could steal
I was like what the manager is telling me that holy crap. What kind of a institution is this?
It's exactly how well the US generals are the worst military commanders ever this planet has ever seen or the US generals
This is very well known established fact and all the military schools in the world
All they do is abscond they they go through the State Department
They have what's called the commercial program and how many how many stockpile numbers can we change and sell these things to whoever?
I'm serious. This is this is the condition that your country is and I go to the military
This is what I'm telling you is very well known in mid mid-level and upper management in the military
The common people know nothing about this
Also, you could be in the military know nothing about this
But we are colonel and above or colonel a major or whatever. They all know this and they all want to get in on it
I know this is pretty bad, right?
Okay, Isis when Isis came out in 2014 all those brand-new Toyota's
They made sure that they got the Toyota's from a plant in Texas because the plant in Texas fits them with the bigger radiators
So they have better cooling capability for running in the desert, right?
So all the people that had like, you know, two brain cells to rub together called up Toyota and said hey
We're watching TV and there's thousands of brand-new Toyota's. Why did you give?
Isis these Toyota's, you know, they're supposedly an American enemy. He says we didn't your American State Department put the order in for them
Oh the State Department
Yeah, you the American State Department
This is this is public this is actually
Toyota
Official
Response. I don't how many people are doing anything about it. No because you can't you're an idiot
I mean people are typically moronic
Idiots, so this do you see how shocking okay going back to the Civil War?
Yes, it was not a Civil War
Basically what happened as the u.s. Was growing
It was commercial. You know this what you call the 13 colonies or the states or corporations are known as plantations
Like Rhode Island still known as a plantation. It's on their seal. You go look at it, right plantations. They call it. Yes
Yeah, it's on there. So, yeah, there are plenty. Thank you. This is the no
Yeah
Yeah, so what happened was?
Georgia, you know, Alabama, Florida
Carolinas and all that they each had collectives. So when they let's say grew cotton
Everybody brings their cotton to a cooperative and then it's sold overseas right to England and France where they were had the factories, right?
So when you're a factory in England and you want to buy cotton you get a bid of how much cotton you want to buy
And you give it to all the states and you know, Georgia wants $10 a bale South Carolina wants seven
Alabama wants five
Okay, so guess who you're gonna go with the one who is the cheapest, right?
And not only you're gonna buy from the cheapest you're eventually gonna buy all of it
Now you have to go to the next one
So when Alabama was five and Georgia was seven dollars a bale and Georgia finds out Alabama ain't got no more cotton at five
Dollars a bale. Do you think they're just gonna sell to you for seven now or they're gonna jack their price to ten
Yeah, they know you're gonna buy
Yep, and and South Carolina, which was ten dollars a bale. They gave it to ten a year ago
You think they're gonna jack it up to 20 now about the same, right?
So now all the people that are trying to price things in England their factories like wait a second
The cotton prices are crazy. You got to do something about this
Can't have that kind of
You know freedom
Right, so they went to
Graham Lincoln, he was dying a syphilis. He's been dying a syphilis for like ten years and they said listen jerk off
We're gonna back you up. You got the Freemasons and the Knights Templars
Oh, here's another thing if you go to Switzerland, you'll find a lot of mansions in the forest
It's like you'll be hiking in the forest somewhere in the mountains and there's a clearing and you're like, what the hell is this?
It's like castles and met in the middle of nowhere right compounds, right?
So you walk up to one of these outer compounds and you look inside and guess what they have
as as their flag in Switzerland the Confederate flag and
It's been there for hundreds of years. So where do you think the Confederates got their flag from?
It's a Knight Templar creation
right
Anyway
so
So that what they did was they said whatever it takes go to war create a war now
There's nobody living in Washington DC. It was a swamp, you know, they
This is the the American government started in wall on Wall Street
Okay, that's where George Washington was sworn in the look-alike right where you know per se George Washington
let's just say then they moved to Philadelphia and
They started writing a constitution like it didn't come till 13 or 14 years later when they first wrote it
We don't know who wrote it. It was sent to the Vatican for approval
Right. It didn't come back for five years
And it came back and that's the one that they put it. This is probably you could look this up
Also, they knew that when they had election of congressmen and senators they they didn't want them to stay in there very long
You could look this up and in the Constitution says if you're going to be a senator you have to be an inhabitant of the
state
Right to be us to run for Senate you have to be an inhabitant of the state that you want to run for right to
The Constitution, but then it says if you want to run again, you cannot be an inhabitant of the state. Oh
And that means you can't ever run again because if you're an inhabitant already and you want to run again
But you're an inhabitant and you can't be so that's how they put the term limit to one term, but nobody follows this
You can look at everything up I'm telling you
Promise. Yeah, so that's how they made it a one term. So that's proof
Like look I've spoken to constitutional attorneys and I bring up said, you know
It's extra Constitution says that does not be misconstrued that any Court of the United States has any power in law or equity
You know what I just said that the courts have no power in law or equity
So what are they doing? I think a constitutional attorneys are all it doesn't say that and his buddies right? Hold on
They don't want to admit it because it was under I don't even know it they don't even know it
So someone tells you they're they're a heart surgeon
They don't even know anything about the heart constitutional attorney knows nothing about the Constitution nothing zero
I mean, this is we're living in such a shit show
It's it's unbelievable I just showed you how all congressmen and senators have one term limits
right and
Actually, there was someone who said this publicly a while back to one of the senators when he was campaigning to run again
And he stopped his campaign
Because he's like, yeah, I already said I want to follow the Constitution and he actually was honorable and he did
I think it was in Arkansas
Right, so you do have some honest people that come
No, no, this is like 70s
Yeah, this is when he was he didn't you can't say that that's defamation he said he never inhaled, okay
Right, okay, so he's still not inhaling
Okay, so that's what's going on basically and after the
after the
They got whatever they needed done because they terrorized the South for 20 years, you know
They the carpetbaggers and all that stuff, right?
They kept raping and burn and there were people from all over the world, you know
For example, the Russians sent a fleet to help Lincoln. Are you aware of this? You could look it up
the Revolutionary War the fleet was sent from Poland or Prussia, but the
Lincoln needed help. So the czar the Russian czar sent a fleet. You could look that up. That's public
Probably one of the Nikolai. Yeah
So
So there we go. So what happened after that?
Lincoln is finished. We don't need you anymore. I got rid of him
You should they they were gonna have him killed but his wife shot him instead. So it's like oh great
You know
Yeah, but anyway all the witnesses and all that, you know his wife shot him right there because he was you know, anyway
You could keep going on and on and on a lot of stories, but it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter right at this point. So this is the state that you're in right now
So then what Lincoln did he put in a general order 100 and this is which means no more Constitution
No more laws. No more Congress. No more Senate the whole country runs under general
Rule 100 and no general order 100. Do you ever hear of executive order like the president made an executive order?
Oh, yeah. Okay, that's an executive order. That's fine. They can do whatever they want
That's for the executive branch and worker and employees of the government. So people apply that to themselves. I
Don't care what executive order that I'm not an employee or anything like yeah, they can make executive orders
Whatever they want mandates, it's for their workers, but when they do a general order, that's for the whole country
So it's called the Lieber code. They got Francis Lieber to write it and it's about it's called the army field manual army manual
Army, you know army procedures for the field or army field manual
Basically, the whole country's being run by the army. It's either a peaceful inhabitant or a belligerent
Okay, so that's what you're running under still right now and also if you further on to
1938 Erie Railroad versus Tompkins versus Erie Railroad
Was a precedent court case that said that all courts only work by contract
Right. Are you familiar with?
Tompkins versus Erie Railroad
1938 to it because we studied so much case law, but obviously nothing that ever matters. So Tom, they're not gonna bring that up
Tompkins versus Erie Railroad. That's why if you talk to any federal judge in private if you're reviewing a case
What the hell you're doing talking to a federal judge in private review in case say is this Erie bound or not?
that's the language they use internally Erie bound means it's contract law and
Everything they do is Erie bound unless it goes under the field manual, which it's a belligerent
And you know how doctors have billing codes right for insurance. Well, every case number is a yeah every case number
Traffic ticket whatever through the what they call the justice system is a billing code through the Chris system
Which is the Dallas Federal Reserve. It's the criminal registry
investment system
It's all the cases go through there and they're
underwritten by fidelity insurance
With why are we getting into such details doesn't matter, right? Yeah, so this is the result of the Civil War
Federal Reserve is a foreign bank, right? You know that with private shareholders. Oh, you know that the Federal Reserve
not even the shareholders the
Officials on the board have much higher security clearance than the president does
Regarding anything. What would you label that? Like what do you call that level of security clearance? Is it majestic? Is that just hype?
No. Yeah. Well, they do have different categories and it changes from group to group like the the most client
Okay, you're ready for this. This has not been ever said before, please
Hard to look up but but true the heart the highest security group within government is
The DOE Department of Energy
They have the highest most classified, it's not the CIA. It's not the FBI. It's not the
Military, it's the DOE Department of Energy now let your mind run free
What is Department of Energy do?
Think about it all the free all the nuclear all the space stuff
Earth protect, you know, there's a protection system a big, you know rail guns and energy guns to protect the earth, right?
Who do you think runs that? Okay. Okay when nukes are moved around nuclear materials moved by the OST the Office of Special Transportation
That's why on 9-11 you had a bunch of OST inspectors there. They even got caught on cameras
Where are you from something the OST?
What do you do and you hear the nuclear alarm because when the first building went down?
The nuclear alarm went off because they disbanded all the alarms that day
so anyway
The people are so stupid. I know people that were breathing in the air
Which is radioactive and they had melanomas had a read their nose removed
They had cancers and they still as there's nuclear just I don't know man. The doctor didn't say the you know, I was like
Oh my gosh
You know
They the the coroner's report by the way for 9-11
For all the people who died in the buildings everyone got a letter. It was vaporization. They were vaporized
And they changed it
Although the widows are all the close family
Everyone got five million dollars and had a had a sign an NDA that was about as thick as a telephone book
Great. I don't mean to interrupt you said it all over again because it cut off for some strange reasons say that
Oh
Well the coroner when he did the coroner's report on
9-11 everyone that died in the buildings was class was written down on the coroner's report. They were vaporized
The coroner knew or in the vaporized it cut out and the second was that all the close family members when they agreed to sign an
NDA
Non-disclosure agreement. They all got a check for five million
All the way that's where the widows are not then the one widow
Well, there's a few widows that didn't want to take the five million and got into Obama's face she died in a plane crash
Or a heart attack or cancer or whatever and there was a lot of other weird stuff going on in New York that day
and when the people saw the weird stuff they went to the police ha ha and
They filed a report and when you file a report with the police to get your address social security number
They know everything about you all those
250 it's more like 400 people that filed police reports on strange things that they saw died within two years
heart attacks car accidents
home invasions on and on and on and on
So you never want to go to?
You never want to snitch. Yeah, I didn't see nothing
They if they ask any authority asked you what you saw I said, I didn't see nothing
Right or your life is in danger
All right on and on and on because a lot of the weird stuff
It's really bizarre that had to happen for for the nukes to work, but that's another another
Topic another story, but I like leaning on 9-eleven because that is an event that you know how they have the Patriots
I'm sure you should never forget
You should never forget that you should never forget Pearl Harbor
Right that you know the chips are chained together
You know those ships that went under in Pearl Harbor that men were alive for a month knocking
SOS and the they'd have Navy SEALs that they were called frogmen at the time
They said we want to go get those men and their higher commences you go
Go near that ship to save those guys, and you'll be shot on sight
Right so don't forget pro. I don't forget the Civil War don't forget the Revolution really what it was about
Okay, the other thing about the Revolutionary War the history of the country
Was a King George he made a decree the proclamation
that
in 1772 or
1770 or 1773 don't hold me on the year
That all the colonists are to respect indigenous people you are not to invade them you're not to take their land oh
my gosh, oh
my gosh
Right well
Do you right so what did what did you know one of the nicknames for George Washington was village burner and child killer right no
Yeah
Now the whiskey rebellion was not a whiskey rebellion at all those the people that he George Washington's group
Promised that they were gonna pay for fighting and they never did
The same thing just like the tent villages that were set up in front of Washington DC
after World War one and
MacArthur and a couple other guys went in there and shot and gassed all the families and people asking for their pay from World
War one he could look that up tent city, Washington DC
1920 or whatever
And MacArthur went in there with rifles and poison gas. It was like 900 families
They wanted they just wanted their pay that they were promised
You look this up happened like 1920 or I don't know whatever
Yeah, so it's pretty nasty, it's all it's just unbelievable. You know talk about an 800 pound gorilla in the room in this country
It's not a Dutch state 800 pound gorilla
It's a 3,000 pound elephant and a hundred and fifty foot long blue whale in the room, and you still don't see it
You know here's the thing. Let's go back to 9-eleven
How many 9-eleven truthers are out there and writing books on bullshit like space weapons and high end yeah?
There are high-energy weapons for sure and all this other bullshit and explosions and all the stuff
What's that? I always hear John Lear saying it was a do a DEW
Yeah, I don't know John Lear John Lear. He worked for the company
Wants to work for the company CIA you know you never for life, right
So
Yeah, it's kind of tiring. You know I can't spend more than five minutes watching anything online
Maybe ten minutes if I'm doing something else on my hands are dirty. I can't go hit the button
It's really sad here. Here's an here
I'm gonna say something that was written 500 years ago when the printing press was mass-produced and
People could have stuff printed anywhere because before that a printing press whoo. That's such a big thing
You know you printed one page and passed it around right?
Well, they started manufacturing printing presses and made you printing material cheap. You know what the comment was
All this gossip and trash that people talk about it's now going to be mass-produced and handed to everyone
So what does the internet do?
All this trash and gossip and mind control and psyops that are right now has the opportunity to reach everyone on their devices
It's a giant re-education camp
Yes, it's about wasting your time
That's why it's you know people say life is too short. I think life is too long
You only need like 10 or 15 20 years on this stinking rock right now the way it is
Why do you want to live to like 50 60 70 or 80? That's stupid
The ink gonna make a change
Ain't got it because it's already done deal. What what needs to happen is the entire status of the planet needs to change
You see because you're in a just you're in a status right now. You're in limbo
so
so, you know, there are humans that live millions of years, you know human types and
Even if you read the ancient texts, it was very common people to live up to a thousand or more
very common
so, you know, it would be very different than you know, imagine going to like a street market and you want to buy a rug
That's handmade and you're negotiating with the price on the guy and the guy's like come on, man
It took me 90 years to weave this
Right because he lives to a thousand right? That would be a totally different world, wouldn't it?
You see yeah, that's what's coming by the way, that's one thing I didn't say when the Alahim take charge
Entropy and aging and all this stuff will be reversed
So let's say you hear in the news. The guy was a hundred years old and he died
That would be like hearing a two-year-old died
You'll be going through puberty at 35 or 40
Yeah, okay, that's fine. Yeah, I I don't I don't give up look I always say if it came in a can I'd be eating it right now
Anyway, that's pretty lascivious
Okay, well Greek is it okay it my wife wants to cook dinner is it okay if we pick up tomorrow and maybe early
Okay
Any I know you're two hours behind me. So it's for almost four o'clock where you are
Is it? Okay, if you just look anytime you call me tomorrow. Yeah, I hope you I hope this was fruitful for you
I know I like jumping over the place because everything's connected wife's right here. Yeah. Yeah. Hey wife
I just uh, if we could just do it earlier in the day, I
Will call her Josie. Okay, we'll call it. Okay. Yeah, is it? Okay, Josie not oh, she wants to prep dinner
It can't wait. No, you go for it
And this is recorded you have permission to put it anywhere you want by the way or just hold it for yourself
Okay, sounds good if we did if you want to do if you wanted to redo it
You could take notes on it and ask me questions
We could compact it down and keep it less less squirrely ages of notes
I took today that I'd love I really would like to do a part two tomorrow. Do you have it? Let's do it tomorrow
Tomorrow would be later
Instead like three hours from now would be best
For tomorrow because I'll be out and about as in three hours later than today right now for you
It's what six so about on the dot nine
Yeah, so I'm at four on the wind-up toy known as the clock right you've heard that before work schedule, yeah
Well, what about there is that what what listen what day can you do earlier?
Earlier I could do what they call Sunday
Okay, what I'll do I'm gonna I'm gonna make it up now I will text you Sunday morning when I wake up and just okay
Good. Okay. Well, that's your part two. Does this be good? I'm up when daylight daylight starts burning at 5 a.m
And I'm usually out doing gardening and working with the animals till about
637 so
Your time so it'd be my time 8 o'clock. It would be good and
Or your time 10. Okay, that's fine. I mean, yeah, okay. I'll regardless somebody I'm gonna text you Sunday morning. Okay?
Okay, that'd be great. I'll see you then. Be well, bro. Thank you very much. Great. All right. Take care