And see what that God that you pick, what information he has about that timeline.
That's a starting, this is the basic start of it.
This is like we said, if you don't give a real red fire truck or
a Ford F-150 to a four year old, you give him a toy.
And then as he gets older, there's a big gap where he doesn't.
Here's the other thing, you give a child a toy of a truck, but
he doesn't wanna play with the toys anymore at seven or eight.
But he's still too young to get the real one.
So there's a gap there where you can't give him anything
between the toy and the real truck, you feel me?
When you're 12 years old, you're still too young,
unless you're in the country, I was driving a car when I was nine.
But what I'm saying is, go to a child and give a 10 or 12 year old who's still too
young, let's say legally or whatever, to drive a truck, give him a toy truck.
What's he gonna do?
Get out of here with that.
He's in limbo.
So do you see my reference?
So you're gonna pick a God, see what laws and morality they have, and
then you're gonna go in a limbo for a while.
And then you're gonna find out really what's going on a little later.
Takes about a decade unless you work with people.
That's why people go to gurus and spiritual masters, so
they could take a shortcut.
But there is no shortcut, because you're just condensing it, right?
The shortcut is this, it's like, right now if I come to your place where you are,
Zen, or where I am here, you say, how's the room look?
Looks pretty clean.
But if I get down with a really good broom and I start sweeping and sweeping and
sweeping and sweeping, I got a nice little pile right here.
You say, I didn't see that before.
If you refine the scope to that level, yes.
I brought it all to one spot.
That's what the master of the guru does.
He takes all these things that nobody sees at the moment and
he brings it all to one spot.
It's too intense, right?
Yes, but- Yeah, go ahead.
Cosmically speaking, there has to be a bigger purpose for all this tyranny,
like we see in the SSP, for example, all the torture and enslavement.
And could it be tied to what you were hinting to prior,
that it is all meant to compartmentalize our minds and
make us, breed us better as warriors?
I would suggest that when you look at the further down the line,
way down the line, we're not given any information.
The only information that we're given is this tyranny and corruption,
the lying, cheating, stealing will go away.
And there'll be peace during that time.
But if you are disarmed and you do not have skill in fighting or
protecting or all that, you're in fear if you're confronted with the idea.
But if you are very strong and you have very strong abilities and
ordinance and you cannot be killed very easily,
you're not afraid with the idea of going to war, you see?
Not any more than I said, get up from where you are right now, walk outside.
You don't know who's out when you open the door and come back inside.
There are some people with psychological, let's say, whatever, agoraphobic,
they're terrified of opening the door and stepping outside.
But you're not, cuz you're much stronger than they are mentally.
So we're gonna be made much more mentally and physically stronger.
And it doesn't say why, but I can take a hint.
Yes, we are in a, I believe it's going to be joining them to protect
the existential, it's an existential question, the existence of this very
universe, guardians of the galaxy type thing.
We're gonna basically be, just like I said, the anarchists before.
When you go to an anarchist society, there's no, if there's a crime,
it's a big deal.
It's like if there's a rape or a murder,
the last time that happened was like 200 years ago.
And everybody is intelligent, everybody's very powerful.
There's no army because you attack the society.
You got 1,000 people living there.
They're all 1,000 warriors coming after you, right?
So, yeah, this is the society that's coming.
So, then it's gonna protect the universe.
Sorry, go ahead.
It kind of meshes with their idea that we are going to be a nexus
of the universe in about 1,000 years, a process that is going to start in about
10 years, maybe that's why we're being primed right now.
And do you know anything more about what makes us such a hotspot?
A hotspot?
No, because it's interesting from the relativistic perspective of where we are
in this galaxy, we're on the outer arm, right?
So, it's more than just the physical position.
I think all I can do is by what I've studied,
what makes us a hotspot is what we are in terms of beings to be focused on,
because we're being told so.
We're not giving any more depth in that.
I've heard from, let's just segue slightly, the idea of a chimera,
a chimera where you can merge a human with an animal, right?
If you know how to do it, and there's a technique or whatever,
you can have half horse, half human, half whatever, lion, half man, half bird.
We're the easiest to do that, to hybridize humans.
We were made to be hybridized.
We're like the Swiss army knife of the cosmos, right?
He has all the various tools.
Don't they do that stuff underground like at Dulce or down in-
Sure, sure, sure.
It's being done almost every,
there's 1,000 bases underground where these beings are.
Some of these, they're so self-sufficient, these underground bases, and
when they set them up, they just pour concrete over them,
because you're never going to come out.
They're autonomous, you know?
Yeah, we hear this, that we have the most ductile DNA of all species.
And I guess this is why we're sought after and
why we have this extreme of fear and emotion.
Yes.
Can you tell us more about how we could use our emotions in a more
constructive way?
Sure, like I think we maybe in private or
slightly brought it up the last time, the emotions are never discussed,
unless you mentioned someone who's emotionally activated.
You ever hear of people that it was not like him to be that way,
well he was very emotional, and it's accepted when you hear that, or
emotionally disturbed, or this or that.
It's not popular in public to talk about what the purpose of the emotions are.
This is something that comes from the very, I'm not gonna say, but
maybe the Tai Chi hidden schools and things like this,
that you guard this very carefully.
That the purpose of the emotion, it's the carrier, let's say, or
the tool to manifest your reason, and your logic, and your being, and
the material, and psychic, and non-physical world, let's say.
So the overcoming feeling that people get when they are emotional,
when they're overcome by their emotions, is an energy.
Now once you understand it's there for a reason, you can grab it like you grab
a wild horse and you put reins on it, and you can control it for
whatever you want to manifest.
That's a wonderful analogy.
Yeah. Yeah.
And this is one of the big taboos also in the secret societies.
If you ever walk into a very high level martial arts teaching or discussion,
and you walk in and they all stop talking and
they don't start talking until you leave,
they're discussing what we're discussing right now.
And is everyone born with this ability to
affect the surroundings just through the energy?
Yes. And you can heal or injure.
That's, well, yeah, let's do a quick example.
Do you ever hear people, I wanna give him good energy, let's give.
You have the giving energy, you have the guarding energy,
you have the taking energy, right?
Those are some basic ones.
So let's say the giving energy.
There is an emotion that's component base platform to the giving energy.
All of these energies, by the way, view them very simply.
Like for example, you go to your kitchen cupboard, you have a dinner plate,
you have a soup bowl, a salad bowl, a coffee mug, each one.
They're all made of the same materials, but
they're different shapes to hold different things.
So the giving energy, for example, how do we evoke, how do we put ourselves,
how do we bring that up?
Just like you bring up a program or a page on your computer.
Okay, simple, you don't have to use this as a very common example.
Hug, when you give someone a hug, even right now if you're alone or
driving, gesture a hug, just by yourself, don't look too crazy though.
Put your arms in front of you as if you're going to hug someone,
especially when you're standing.
You cannot help it, but feel a light sensation from your legs.
It rises through your thorax, through your solar plexus, and
it's tingling and it's slightly warming.
Just gesturing a hug, that is the giving energy.
So if you could evoke your body to feel that, and I said feeling,
now it is ready to give, to emanate.
So an example, someone says, for example, let's pray,
let's give energy to my friends, sisters, brothers, cousin, whatever who's sick.
You don't know them, you don't have to know them.
So how do we identify them?
You identify them by some personal marker.
You know my sister's brother, sister, whatever, cousin,
has some unique features to them.
So we're thinking of someone that we were asked to give this
healing energy to as unique features.
What's unique?
They have their own fingerprints, their own height,
their own social security number.
It doesn't matter how trivial or important it is.
Just think of something that's to them to identify them.
They have something unique about them, yes.
It might help if they're 70 years old and they have cancer.
Well, you say, well, did they have cancer when they were 18?
No, so you imagine what that person was like when they were 18,
and you send the image of that body, whatever the image is,
it's the feeling, over that feeling of that hug,
that giving energy that you just created over.
What if it was a birth defect?
Then you go before conception.
If it was genetic, then you have to go back to the genetic line,
even if it's 100 generations or 10 generations.
And now you're giving that energy, very powerful.
This takes practice, by the way.
You could also give a negative energy, right, to hurt someone.
But why would you do that, right?
You see, another one simply is guarding.
You know, people always say guard yourself, right,
the spiritual, guard yourself.
Well, how am I supposed to do that?
When you have to guard yourself, there's an emotion attached.
Now, if you could bring that emotion up, evoke it,
you are now in a guarding state.
Example of that is, remember, maybe you didn't do your homework,
you were very young in class,
and you get a feeling the teacher's gonna call on you,
and they do, and you get the shock in your body, right?
That's the guarding energy.
Another form of the guarding energy is denial.
That's why they tell you, don't fear, don't deny.
No, no, denial, this is where denial is helpful.
Let's say you put your hand in the cookie jar
and took a cookie when you weren't supposed to.
You weren't caught, but you were blamed for it later.
Do you say, yes, or do you say, I deny I did that?
When you deny something,
there's a certain feeling that comes up.
You can almost feel it.
It's kind of like a dull feeling,
like you wrapped a piece of plastic around your chest.
All right, everybody describes it slightly different.
And when you have that feeling, like, no,
it's even stronger.
You can also deny something that you didn't do,
but it's much stronger when you deny something
that you did do.
And this is not lying.
This is denying.
It's different.
So you evoke an emotion.
Now you have the guarding emotion in place.
And when you feel that, right,
now you're able to guard from what?
Whatever your input, your reason and logic tells you
you should guard yourself, whether it's a spirit or an ET,
a discarnate body, non-physical body, same thing,
or another human's thoughts,
or even disease, by the way, quote-unquote,
because disease is not material, it's inductive.
So I'm giving a very basic outline right here
where if you practice this every day for a few minutes,
you will be literally in a few years,
you could be like a superhero.
Superhero, like the X-Men.
Okay, here's an example.
You ever see the X-Men movies?
Like the guy who makes ice or snow
or the guy who makes things magnetic.
You ever notice before they put their superpower,
they change their emotional state slightly?
They're summoning something.
Well, also they're changing their own emotional state.
Like one, the lady who makes storms,
she's all happy and smiling,
then she gets an angry face to make the storm, you see?
Then there's another guy who does the magnets or whatever.
He gets all happy and smiley and laughy
when he's doing the magnet or whatever.
I think he says, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Like, right, you see?
So each one is different.
So once higher beings, like for example,
I don't know, like the Imperial Draco, for example,
they do not have a separate emotional rational body.
They've merged the two.
So when they wanna protect themselves,
if they wanna kill someone, they just think it
and you're dead physically, you're cut in half
because they know how to manipulate the atomic level,
you see, and vice versa.
They can heal also, by the way, you see?
So a being like that, that has merged its emotional,
not like Spock and the Vulcans
where they deny the emotion, you see?
That's the other, that's the left hand,
that's the dark side.
But an advanced being that merges the two, right?
And also they're not alien if they approach themselves
to you and have sympathy and compassion to you,
they're not alien.
They're like, you know what I mean?
Any being that has sympathy and compassion to you,
truthful, not like the fake galactic federations
that you hear about or whatever.
There's a whole bunch of fake people saying
that the colonies have been freed
and you're gonna be fine.
That's all fake, by the way, right?
The galactic federations of light, you know,
what about the galactic federation of evil
or the galactic federation of darkness?
How many people are you gonna get if you say that?
But if you say the galactic federation of light
or the aster, are these people gonna come and help you?
How many people are you gonna get?
Oh, let me see.
I got 500,000 followers already.
You start telling people that it's good and bad
and then evil if you do bad.
Oh, I've been running this channel for 10 years.
I got six followers.
Good, because that's all you're gonna get.
That's only six people that will understand this, right?
Yeah, I always thought, you know,
a level of followers on anything is not,
it doesn't hit towards altruism, you know?
If half the people knew what was going on,
on the Earth, half the people,
each one only needs to help one person
and we're all taken care of, right?
Yes, at the same time.
Yeah, but I think that these conglomerates
like the Astar Command, they put it in your face
because there are actually real versions of that,
but what they are speaking about
is something completely different,
so they're just taunting us.
But scenarios, the people that are talking
about all this stuff have been run through scenarios.
They've never gone anywhere,
but if you put a gun to their head and say,
tell me the truth now, that is,
they are telling the truth
according to what they've experienced.
That's why I'm so happy
that they call themselves experiencers
because if someone saws a woman in half on stage
and puts her back together,
the 500 people in the audience are experienced,
they will sign an affidavit under the penalty of perjury,
under the penalty of whatever,
that they saw a woman being sawed in half
and put back together, yes.
But somebody lied and they swear to it.
So they're victims.
They're not, they're super victims or whatever,
you know what I mean?
They're victims.
So you don't wanna criticize a victim
because they're a victim.
They need help.
They don't need negative criticism.
Do you see what I mean?
As a matter of fact,
most of them call themselves victims,
but they're still doing all the full picture.
Well, I still think that some of them are like that
and others are genuine,
but it's impossible to prove, I guess.
Look, all 500 people that saw the woman
being cut in half and put back together,
which one is not genuine?
Which one is?
They're all genuine.
Yeah, but some are not just in their mind,
but also physically there.
Yeah, the woman cut in half on stage
and put back together was physical.
By the way, do you know how that's done real quick?
Do you know how that's done?
No.
You get two physically fit contortional women.
The woman that showed on stage
is gonna be cut in half,
preferably taller than the one,
so the other one.
Now, where's the other one?
The other one's already in the box or in the table.
So when the woman that is presented
starts putting her legs into the box,
the woman that's already in the box
is pushing her legs out
while the woman who's going in,
you think her legs are being stretched out,
you're being fooled,
but she's actually curling them back.
So when he puts the saw blade through the middle,
it's passing the knees of the woman
used to go into the box
and the head of the woman who stuck her legs out.
And then they separate the box.
There's two women.
Then they put the box together.
And as the tall woman's coming out,
the first woman that you saw on stage,
the woman that you'll never see,
she's pulling her legs in at the same time
to give the illusion that her legs are being pulled out.
I see.
And-
See, this is similar to a scenario.
See how simple this is to do?
Well, yes.
But you also said something along the lines of
that matter is frozen light and that we can materialize.
And does that have connection with the emotion?
Materialize.
Yes, let's go back.
Maybe we mentioned the, I hate saying it, med bed.
It sounds so funny.
Notice how it's so trivial when you say med bed.
Sounds like something like happy meal, right?
Okay.
Okay, this is for the really smart people, right?
Let's say, you know, being sarcastic here.
Let's put one together, really.
Because everybody's saying the med beds are coming,
the British are coming, the med beds are coming,
the med beds are coming.
You know, they're all full of it, right?
All these people talking about med beds,
they couldn't pour piss out of a boot
with instructions on the heel, okay?
Just that's a pretty good visual if you could imagine that.
I'm not putting them down.
I'm just saying the whole thing is dumb.
If you wanna do something, let's talk about how to do it.
Why are you asking, look at the, by the way,
look at the greed behind the med bed talk.
How greedy these people are.
I'm not greedy.
You got Mrs. P, look how greedy.
Oh, are they gonna give it to us?
Are they gonna give it to us?
Yeah, you're gonna get it, all right.
Not a med bed.
So let's get some reasonably
half intelligent people together.
Maybe, I don't, you know, when I say half intelligent,
it means half wit, which is a term that's not very good.
But let's put one together.
Let's lay it out real quick in the next three minutes.
You ready?
We know that the water is not water.
We know that there is induction.
We have examples of induction constantly.
We know the human body doesn't work on absorption
or anything, it works on induction, it works on water.
Certain electrical principles.
We know that there's the emotion component.
We know that the light regenerates skin.
So let's start putting this together.
Do you know that EKGs, you know,
they could measure nerve functions and brain functions
and read it out on a graph, right?
You can read it on a plant also.
You could put that in from those devices
currently available on plants
and read the stimulations and differences
in anything alive, even bacteria, petri dish.
Do you know the, let's go back to the human part
and all the things you mentioned before.
Do you know, have you ever heard of an amputee?
He has a phantom itch.
Someone had a leg removed
and they feel like their left leg removed
and they feel a phantom itch.
They go to scratch it, but there's nothing there.
You've heard of it, Zen?
You're going, maybe you didn't, yeah.
It's called a phantom, what is there another,
there's a medical term for it, there's a Greek term, but.
Okay, that means that the energy body
of the human is still there.
The pentagram shape, the five, you know,
like you see Michelangelo draw.
And how could you be so present
that it actually fooled the individual
who knows his leg was cut off to go scratch it?
That's how strong it is.
It's not just that the leg is still there energetically,
but there's actually impulses still running through there.
Now we can measure that impulse
by attaching things to the person's body.
Actually right now,
you don't even have to attach anything.
You don't need it to do a physical DNA sample anymore.
It could be scanned.
Are you aware of this
or this information hasn't come out yet?
Okay, just like a barcode.
So this phantom itch, by the way,
for the person to feel an itch on a leg
that doesn't even exist,
could you imagine what's going on
on that missing leg that he doesn't feel?
Tremendous amount that could be read
with sensitive equipment.
So now that we know that,
we know that water can be produced through induction,
just like a water is produced underneath a rain cloud.
There's no water in a rain cloud at all.
If there was any water in a rain cloud, it would be fog.
Water is produced under the rain cloud instantly.
We know how to produce water.
We know it's induction.
We know that light rebuilds tissue.
Do you see where I'm going with this now?
Do you see how I just did?
Okay, when you work with IT,
you do a lot of bubble diagrams
and Venn diagrams, don't you?
Right?
Then you have the engineers.
This is what we wanna do,
but how do we do it, right?
With anything, even a plan, a battle plan, right?
We draw a bubble diagram, schematic.
I just gave you the whole outline.
Well, there are still some missing steps.
Further and further.
What's that?
There are still some steps technically speaking, right?
I mean, the hardware.
Yeah, well, the hardware you have, okay.
Remember how I said,
if you wanna build Tesla stuff,
a lot of people don't have success
because they go to the electronics store
and buy modern stuff.
And also they don't follow everything to a T.
They make adjustments because if you do that,
if you tell your electronics friend you wanna do this,
he says, oh, why use that?
Because we have this now.
Ah, ah, ah, screwed up.
If you wanna do Tesla stuff,
you need to find bottles, empty wine bottles,
pieces of brass, pieces of leather,
pieces of wood, right?
Junk, right?
So the way you build this is you go and find,
you go to an electronics surplus place
and you build it that way.
The reason I say this is because
if you know what a capacitor does,
a resistor, an inductor, a diode,
you're not gonna find that.
The modern capacitors and diodes are so small.
I can't even, I need a tweezer.
I can't even solder one.
It has to be wave soldered.
Where if I go, let's say,
get an old germanium diode from Mauser,
it's something I hold in my hand.
It's about the size of a piece of bubble gum.
I could work with that.
So you're gonna find the stuff that works
in old electronics salvage.
If you can find them anymore,
they're starting to really get rid of those now
because, look, I'm not that smart, okay?
And I just gave you the outline of this.
There are people that are way smarter than the Greek.
Way smarter, okay?
That are doing things.
I'm the only one that's speaking
because I'm the dummy of the group, let's say.
And there's, I don't know, there's no group.
But you see what I mean?
I'm dumb enough to talk.
There are people way smarter than me
that know what's going on,
that that's all I'm gonna say, you see?
Okay, and by how much does this type of med-bed
prolong your life?
How much can you abuse it?
The body is made or designed to go thousands of years,
at least a thousand, right?
Give you an example.
Let's, you ask me all these things that are finalities,
but it's, okay.
Let's just take something prolonging life.
You see an old person, right?
What is the characteristic of an old person?
They have wrinkly skin, right?
And they don't look as vital
as they were when they were young.
That's another way of saying,
they look like a five-pound potato in a 10-pound bag.
Where a young, pretty person is a five-pound potato
in a five-pound bag.
It's all firm and neat, right?
The reason the old person looks all wrinkly and droopy
is because their skin keeps growing,
but the rest of the body doesn't.
So as someone is getting older and older,
if you know how to slow down the growth of their skin,
well, they'll be 90 years old and look 35, won't they?
In terms of wrinkles and all that, right?
So, by the way, go look at all the cameras in China.
They have one camera for every two people.
So it's, right, 500 million cameras.
Give you $100 for each person that you see that is fat
in the public in China.
Do you see any fat people in China?
No.
Now I want you to do the same thing in America.
You're gonna give me a penny for each person that's fat.
I'm gonna be wealthy by the end of the day.
What's the difference between the two?
You see how simple it is to start going on this position?
How do you, if you wanna know how do we live longer,
how do you posture yourself?
What position do you take?
Do you see what's going on in your mind?
What's really going on?
How many times do you hear about we're gonna,
we want anti-aging?
Most of it is for vanity, so we don't look old,
not really live old.
How many times have you heard what I just said anywhere?
The reason you look old is because your skin
is growing faster than the rest of your body.
Nowhere.
Why, you know why?
Because it's simple and it's true.
So, do you know that as you keep growing,
certain parts of your body keep growing,
like your earlobes and your head?
Like if you had a, let's say you're in your 60s and 70s
and you have military uniform when you were 20,
go dig it out, put the hat you were wearing
so that fit perfectly on your head now.
It won't even, it'll sit on top of your head
like a child's hat.
Okay, when they show you Neanderthal man
and Cro-Magnon man and all that, that's baloney.
When they started digging these skulls,
they found a big cache of skulls and skeletons in France,
in the caves of France a long time ago.
They invited dentists and scientists from all over the world
and they stayed in separate hotel rooms.
They couldn't talk to each other.
And one dentist, I forgot his name.
He said, these people are exactly like us.
The only difference is they went through puberty
when they were 35.
When do we go through puberty?
9, 10, 11, 12, 13?
11, 12, 13.
Right, and these skulls and these skeletons
are 400 to 600 years old.
So when all of the various different medical people
and forensic people said the same thing,
they gave all the skeletons and skulls
down to the university in various parts of the world
to break the jaws off,
reset the jaws more forward to look more ape-like,
break the skull and reset it with a brow bone
that was more forward to make it look more ape-like.
There's your Cro-Magnon.
Okay, do you know there's no such thing as a Stone Age
and Iron Age or a Bronze Age?
It's a Stone Society, Bronze Society, Iron Society.
For example, there is a Stone Society right now.
You can go on certain islands and they use stones.
They don't even use metal.
What they tell you was the Stone Age.
If you go back or whatever, 30, 40,000 years,
whatever they tell you, they show you cavemen,
all that fake stuff.
I'll show you, let's go over a few thousand miles
and they have anti-gravity platforms
and they could, you see, Atlantis.
For example, during Atlantis,
there were other societies on the peripheral
that were living like they show you in the cavemen.
There's no such thing as a Stone Age or an Iron Age.
Is the society stone-based, iron-based, bronze-based?
Are you guys with me on this?
Yeah.
Yes, but there are some isolated cases
like the hobbits, which are only half our height
and they lived on a separate island.
And wasn't that like some sort of environmental thing
and they're a one-off?
Yes, I just suggested that to Zan John.
Zan was saying, well, what can I do to help?
I said, set yourself apart.
Well, you could take that any way you want.
If he has the wherewithal and could afford to,
go to his own island.
Yeah, of course, but don't do it in secret.
Let people know that you're around you,
that you're gonna do that.
And how are you gonna do it?
And how are you gonna do it when you're there
so that you'll become an example?
Do you see the difference?
I think so.
But just to finish with the emo thing.
Yes.
Say that you are attacked.
Someone wants to stop your heart.
Is there any type of defense against such an attack?
Yes.
Every time you train and practice the emo,
your own body, your DNA gets stronger and changes.
You can change your DNA with this, which I don't even,
now we're getting into the deeper part.
We're skipping forward.
I think when we started, when we were doing,
I call this Greek speak or the Greek talking.
Many people haven't heard it.
They're just seeing the book covers.
And some people that have heard it,
they're on the first chapter.
I'm down at 300 chapters already, you see?
So when we discuss these things,
now I gotta jump to chapter 30 or 40
when most people are still trying to catch up
on chapter two, you see?
Yeah, please don't skip ahead.
We need to understand it.
Yeah, I'm not gonna, in other words, the emo,
when you, let's just go back to the conspiratorial side,
which is true.
What's the difference between conspiracy and reality?
About a year and a half, right?
Conspiracy theory and reality, right?
Okay, so when you are starting
with any kind of physical development,
let's say any sport,
it takes you years to get really good, right?
And if you stop doing it and you get out of shape,
if you wanna get back into it,
it only takes about 30 to 90 days.
You don't have to do two years.
You have muscle memory, you see?
So every time you practice the emo on the giving,
especially the guarding,
it imprints your body and your DNA changes.
So it's doing that anyway.
It's gonna be resonating with that anyway.
Just like, for example, people that are always sad
or if you're angry, that will hurt you
and you could get cancer from it.
This was in the old traditions as well.
Don't be angry or sad all the time,
or grudges, because you could get cancer
or get sick from that.
It's called, it's beyond being psychosomatic, right?
That's because you're, that's being angry, sad,
or holding grudges is emotional, is it not?
And how can you get cancer tumors from that?
Do you see?
It's the same thing.
So why not take that feature that we have
and how come it's not being discussed at all,
at all, anywhere, not by the New Age,
not by the space cowboys and cowgirls
and not by the holistic people?
They do discuss it.
Some of the space cowboys do mention
that they are trained specifically in psionics
and they kind of-
But how do you do it?
Oh, yeah, they call it energy manipulation
and the how is not very clear yet.
Yes, in other words, how can everybody,
I listen to the stuff on the internet,
all the stuff, doctors, space cowboys,
all the holistic New Age, and I walk away saying,
all right, how does this improve my life right now?
What can I start doing?
How can I, nothing, zero, nothing, very little.
There are a lot of DIY videos, right?
If you wanna fix something,
a water pump in a 2003 whatever, Chevy whatever, yeah.
Watch the video of these, experience it.
What about when you pray for someone,
does that infringe on,
does that violate their consent or something?
That's something I heard kind of makes sense.
No, no, there's, okay, the accidental is also pre-planned,
like I have to go, a neighbor of mine's dog
got run over by a car yesterday
and they're heartbroken, right?
And it's just like for some people,
it's like a human family member dying, right?
Was that by consent?
The dog or somebody getting killed?
No.
You know, it's even worse by that.
Most people say they're sad my dog died.
You know, some of these parrots and those birds,
those tropical birds live 70 years.
I knew a woman,
they got, the parents got the bird before she was born
and she was in her 40s or 50s when the bird died, right?
That's like having, you know,
the bird is older than she was.
So these are, it's the same thing.
It's the emo is the same,
but it's not by consent, no.
We're in a free will, free fluid zone
depending on which zone you're talking about,
your own personal one, your familial one,
your neighborhood, your county or parish,
your state, your country, and then the planet.
You see?
Just like when you're going into the past,
you're actually going into the future
because everything was already started in the future
and it's replayed starting at the beginning, right?
So when you go back into the past,
it's closer to the future that is in our future.
And as we progress into our future,
we're going more into the past of the plan.
So.
But also altering it as we go along,
otherwise there would be no purpose to it.
Insignificant alters,
just like if you have a cruise ship
with 2000 people on it,
that's going from point A to point B,
because you're sitting on the toilet for three days
or playing or in the theater
or the restaurant for three days,
the cruise ship is still going from point A to point B.
It's not gonna change that.
What will change is maybe you won't meet certain people
if you're on the toilet for three days.
I'm saying this because I've heard someone
on a cruise I got off
and they were on the toilet for three days.
So what good is that?
They missed all these other opportunities.
So it's really opportunity loss.
You see.
But if you add all of these small changes together,
then maybe you can affect
what the captain of the ship does as well.
Yes, you can,
but the captain of the ship is the captain of the ship
because he's chosen based not only
would he make a good captain,
but also his strength of character.
And just one last thing about,
you mentioned about how vertically
and horizontally oriented creatures are different
because of their spinal cord alignment
and it functions as an antenna.
Can you go into that a little bit?
A little bit, that's chapter 250.
And that gets more,
that will branch out into the holography, let's say.
The med bed, I don't like call it,
I call it med bed, like hot McDonald's, happy meal.
But that's where you give little children,
happy meal, med bed, whatever.
Yeah, that branches into that.
Your spinal cord is an antenna
and it's also a stacking mechanism.
Every time energy goes through it,
it gets processed like a circuit board.
Each component processes the circuit.
So the final function is desirable.
When it's horizontal,
it's aligned to one plane, cosmic plane.
When it's vertical, it's aligned to another cosmic plane.
And about these planes,
does being on a higher one necessarily mean
a higher intelligence?
Because for example, you mentioned now,
plants only have a thought every thousand years or so.
And then I was just wondering-
Rocks.
Oh yeah, sorry.
Yeah, a plant is always in a dream state.
But the rock having a thousand year,
a thought every thousand years
is a hell of a lot more than most people I've met,
by the way, but anyway.
And does being on a higher rung
translate to higher intelligence and ability and such?
Let's just say this.
And this is not the be all end all.
What good is a highly intelligent person
that gets into an emotional road rage and kills someone
for no reason other than they were an emotional,
they couldn't control their emotions?
So my answer to that is
a highly intelligent person would be
cognizant and aware,
have consciousness and awareness
of all their faculties and control of them.
So again, they would be someone that was able to merge
their emotional capabilities and knowledge
and how to use it with their reasoning and logic together,
like an imperial Draco, for example.
And about out-of-body experiencers,
they often report visiting something
along the lines of heaven or hell.
And would you, have you any experience with this?
Yeah.
Yes.
And so there is truth to that.
And what's our relationship to that?
Minimal at this point.
If you're quote unquote stuck in this density, it's minimal.
Right.
And is the etheric or the next plane up
equivalent to the land of the dead?
Okay, the ether is the substance of this universe,
the core substance, right?
It's below the atom, you know, and all that.
So the next plane, the different densities,
like for example, when you go up to the next density
above this one, let's say the realm of the,
when the spirit leaves the body,
if you are able to stay there, distance doesn't matter.
You can go anywhere at any time instantly, right?
So everything you know about navigation is irrelevant.
And if you spend too much time there
in the realm of the dead,
you kind of get dumbed down.
If you come to this density and try to communicate,
you sound real dumb
because you detach yourself from the XYZ axis completely.
The next density higher than that
is where you start to get into the Akashic,
but not the Akashic of the past,
but the informational flow.
And then the next density higher than that
is the knowledge base.
The knowledge base starts to merge all of them down together
and can manipulate all the densities down.
But there's also second and first density
that is much lower,
which would be more like the hellish realms, right?
That we call, but the hellish realm is a real thing,
by the way, it's the underworld
where the negative beings live.
And they find us as food, they use us as food.
They're a very small percentage
of the quote unquote alien or ET races
or reptilian races, very small percentage, less than 5%.
So as you go up the density,
it's more encompassing and more merging.
In other words, they have more control,
but the next one up and the next one up,
you're pretty much in limbo.
You're in a, like you said, astral state or spiritual.
It's in your mindset, right?
The brain is an antenna.
You know, there's nothing in your brain.
It's a receiver and transmitter.
It's a transceiver, so.
And I love one of my friends to pose a question
and I am also very curious about this is,
do you know about what changes this,
you mentioned about the distinction
between soul and spirit and what are the changes
that these two undergo past physical death?
Oh, the physical death, the body and the soul are dead.
The soul is the metabolism.
Well, how do you know the soul is dead?
When someone dies, you go up to them.
There's no breath, there's no pulse
and they're starting to decompose.
That's when the absorption takes place.
All of those membranes that we showed
that are like the car tire,
they start to become porous and leak when you die.
So what the medical community is trying to tell you
is that you're dead.
And the legal community is telling you that you're dead.
Actually, if you look at older legal documents for,
they call the defendant a decedent.
You see, so everything's focused on death
in this particular stage.
So the spirit then is the mind,
but the mind, as we know it, the mind that we have,
it relies on a body or an apparatus to animate it.
It goes into disanimation.
It would be, for humans that are on this planet right now,
most humans, say what happens to the spirit after you die
is like going to the ocean with a cup of water
and dumping it into the ocean
and then trying to get it back.
Yes, you can get a cup of water back,
but is it the same cup of water you poured in?
No.
So it requires a much higher technological level of being
to sort those water molecules out
that have the memory of you and reanimate them,
whether in this time or in a future time.
That is your quote-unquote reincarnation myth,
which is not a myth, it's true,
but it's not the way people think it is.
So what you're saying is it's far above
our pre-grade right now.
That's chapters 300 or something.
It can be discussed,
but you have to learn to take control of the emotion.
Here, I'll give you another example.
If you take an average person of high intelligence,
which I don't know if that's an oxymoron,
and you show them how to go directly into the astral realm
and they survive it,
in other words, they don't have a heart attack
while they're sleeping and not wake up
because they died, too much trauma.
They won't benefit.
You have to have the emotional, right?
People talk about, when you hear people talking
about going into the astral realm or the other realms
and it's all pleasant, they're full of you know what?
Bovine excrement.
The initial thing that you see is terrifying to you.
Terrifying.
But it's interesting when you see
the most terrifying creature in the world
and he gets up and stretches their arm out
and says, how can I help you?
You look scared.
Can you get over that, right?
And it's true that most of them report
only magical experiences.
And even if they acknowledge hellish realms,
they still mention going out of body
as the best thing you can tap into.
So I guess that's already a red flag.
Yeah, if they're in a hellish realm
and they slap themselves
and they know they're not dreaming
and they're physically there,
they've been consciousness transferred
into a cloning center.
It's real.
They're still asleep in their bed,
but their conscience has been transferred
into a clone body.
And they're in some underground base here.
And a lot of people that have said that
have said that they saw celebrities and politicians
and people from the past there.
Donald Marshall.
Yeah, Donald Marshall stuff.
Yeah, so that's true.
And while we're on the topic,
do you actually know what Joshua's resurrection technique was
and where he learned it from?
That was a device, okay,
if we go back to the biblical text and look at it,
I don't suggest you,
anybody read the Bible, by the way.
Again, I'm not pushing it.
It's very interesting.
When he was raised from the dead
and put back together and perfected,
there were bodies that became animated
in the peripheral area
from the residual field that came in to do that, right?
What I mean by that is,
let's say you preheat your oven to 400 degrees
to bake something.
You know, the countertop next to it
is also going to get warm,
but it won't be 400 degrees, right?
So basically what happened when they activated what they did,
basically it's a very advanced version of the med bed
where you actually can project the device.
You don't need to be in the device.
You can project the field to do that,
was so powerful that the residual energy
animated dead bodies.
You could read it.
It's in the book of Luke.
The bodies that were recently placed in their graves
jumped out, walked around,
but they didn't resurrect.
They just fell down and died after a while,
after the residual field wore off, right?
Do I need to get more specific or?
No, that's enough of a mindset.
It goes against, okay.
Also, if you read in the text, by the way,
after the religious authorities knew who he was
and they killed him, they said,
now we have to go and silence anyone who knew him,
anyone he knew, he touched, healed,
or anything like that had to be eliminated.
And we need to create a new story, basically.
You see what I'm saying?
And about black goo,
I found it interesting that Sinamar didn't mention by name,
but said that cosmic water is black
and very energetic and dense.
And I made the correlation with black goo
and also there are accounts that describe
that it's the blood of the planets
and that drinking it strengthens you.
Do you know anything about this?
It would be more like the lymphatic fluid of the body.
You know, you have more lymphatic fluid in your body
than you do blood, right?
But they never discussed that
because things show up instantly in it.
Lymphatic, the lymphosis that also enables
all the other tissue to function correctly.
The reason why something would appear black
is not because it's black,
it's because the light cannot penetrate it, right?
We gave the example, did it appear black how?
To our human senses?
Because like I said the last time,
us three can walk into a very dark forest
where it's on a moonless, starless night,
let's say, or a dark warehouse and we don't see anything.
But if we put on night vision goggles,
we see everything just fine, don't we?
So, yeah, black would be to the human visualizing it
because the light, the visible light
does not react with it, right?
You can produce that with polarization, by the way, right?
Like polar, right?
You familiar?
Not very much, actually.
Polarizing light, you can create a,
you can have a beam of light
and run it through a polarizing film
and you'll get a black spot in the middle
or different diffraction patterns.
Yeah, so when water, water is an element, by the way,
it's not H2O.
So once you understand water and how it comes into,
create into this 3D reality from the ether,
it's a condensate.
The ether condenses into various materials,
but mostly water, yeah.
What other materials?
There is a material light,
there is a material heat
and there's a material life also.
It's a very subtle form.
What I mean by that is, for example,
have you ever heard of the term 21 grams?
Yeah, the weight of the soul.
Yeah, when someone dies,
when someone dies, you automatically,
you lose everyone, you lose at least 21 grams.
So the weight of the spirit, yeah, it's a very fine,
it's imponderable.
Like, for example,
if you look at the periodic table of elements,
you see hydrogen is number one, the first one.
Well, Walter Russell and others have shown
that there are at least seven other gases
lighter than hydrogen, but they're not discussed
because they become imponderable.
You can't put them in a container.
Can you contain someone's spirit?
Think about that.
You even, that sounds, I'm airing poetic now, right?
We just showed it's 21 grams, but it can't be contained.
It's like the eight, seven or eight elements
that are higher than hydrogen.
Could you imagine how our education system
would be different if we were able to demonstrate
imponderable materials?
Like the reason why they just show you hydrogen
is number one, as you guys know,
we can go down to a welding shop or a chemical house
and buy a bottle with compressed hydrogen gas in it.
And if we don't do anything with it
and put it in a closet for 10 years and open it up later,
it'll still have hydrogen gas in it, right?
But if I told you we can put a gas in there
that is measurable and we could see its properties,
but in 24 hours, it'll go right through the container,
even though it's three inches thick stainless steel.
What does that do to the human mind?
Well, it makes you think that the only reason
they were able to do it,
because they were not aware it was impossible, right?
You become unlimited, you see?
Could you imagine starting to work with imponderable gases
that you cannot, or imponderable fluids
that you cannot keep in a container?
How do you manage them?
And if you learn to manage them,
what kind of a different world it would be, you see?
Right, and this conversion of ether to water
is actually the founding principle
on the formation of the planets and all the bodies, right?
Yes, yes, and the ether is,
let's just say from the category,
let's take ether as one of its properties
as it has energetic properties.
We are taught that all energies go
from a high potential to a low potential, right?
Or in other words, when energy is manifested,
it always starts off high and then decays.
The ether is the opposite, it goes from low to high.
So if you have a high energetic ethereal system,
the way you feed it is by presenting it
with a low ethereal energetic system.
Let's give the analogy with two car batteries.
If you take a car battery that is brand new
and fully charged and attach it to one
that is empty, you wait a little bit
and you come back later and the fully charged battery
discharges into the empty battery
until they level out 50-50 each.
You're with me, right?
Okay, but let's say that empty battery
just has about 5% because anything below 70%
in a car battery is considered dead anyway.
Let's say it has 5%, it's not completely dead.
So let's say these are ether batteries.
We take the fully charged battery
and we connect the dead battery to it.
The fully charged battery does not go into the dead one.
What happens is whatever is left in the dead one
wants to leave and go to the fully charged one
and overcharge it.
It's the opposite movement of what we've been taught.
So that overcharging, when you have a system
that is in ethereal equilibrium
and it's presented with a system that is very low ether,
the ability for the ether to go from low to high,
in other words, is the opposite
of what energy systems we're aware of.
The moment it overcharges that other system,
we have water production.
Oops, I'm not supposed to talk about this
because now we're going to the next level of stuff.
Even Walter Russell, 100 years ago, took a vacuum chamber
and he had a spark igniter in there
and put in nitrogen gas and formed water vapor.
It was pure nitrogen gas with a spark
and also a vacuum and some ultraviolet
and he formed water vapor.
And he kept doing it.
He says, oh, that's a mistake.
The water vapor came from,
maybe there was contamination in the vacuum chamber.
No, it was a two-stage vacuum chamber
that was prepared for four days.
There's absolutely nothing in there.
It was certified, you see.
So the nitrogen gas, which is a pulsing gas,
which is, we're not oxygen breathers,
we're nitrogen breathers
and we convert the nitrogen to oxygen, right?
Shouldn't say right, but that's how it works, sorry.
Nitrogen is a pulsing gas.
And when you subject it to certain things,
yes, you create.
And that water would be very similar to the water,
not susceptible by light,
that if you presented it in the light system,
it would appear to be black.
Yeah, but oxygen still must come for something
because you'd have to regenerate and stuff.
Oxygen to a lot of the ETs, by the way,
they're warned away from us
because oxygen is very oxidizing and toxic to some of them.
That's why if you touch some of them,
your hand oils burn them very badly, right?
Urea, if you look at nitrates and urea.
Nitrates are toxic nitrogen oxygen compounds.
Oxygen is overrated.
It doesn't mean you shouldn't have it, right?
Look, for example, the halide group elements,
bromine, iodine, chlorine, fluoride, fluorine,
those are halides.
If you take those elementally or in sodium based compounds,
it hardens your pineal gland and you get hard tissue,
hardening of the arteries, it could kill you, right?
But sodium chloride, for example, in that order is a salt.
And if you don't have sodium chloride in your body,
you die again.
You need it for cell reproduction and ATP production, right?
So it's the combination of which one comes first, right?
The nitrogen always comes first, then the oxygen.
You see in this particular planet.
Now, once you start getting into seeing
how the induction process works
with the molecular level, atomic level,
because you're really never working with atomic,
you're always dealing with compounds and molecules.
As you, when you work in the field,
they call it moles, right?
You have to look at it in the order of what is your goal
and what is, when you start to have a certain reaction
or a goal that you're looking for to create
because you're synthesizing matter now,
do you have an alternative way to manage it?
What I mean by that is if you're navigating
and you're traveling with a magnetic compass
and you get to the North Pole,
you can't use that compass anymore
because as you get closer and closer,
it starts to point in a different direction
and what'll happen when you get to the North Pole,
you'll be just flying around in circles
and you'll never go anywhere, you see?
So you need an alternative method,
another reference point outside,
like maybe a geostationary satellite
beaming you locational information.
The same thing as when you start dealing
with the, what I call the happy meal,
you know, the med bed,
how the human body works, water production,
manipulation of matter, the spirit, the emotion,
all that stuff.
You can lose yourself in these things.
That's why very often they portray alchemists
and wizards as being a little crazy, right?
So you always need an outside reference system
before you start working with these things
or if you're gonna go to an advanced level.
That outside reference system usually comes
in the form of quote unquote in common terms,
a god or an ET or a higher being that manages you.
Doesn't necessarily guide you or teach you,
but if you're gonna blow something up,
they just come over and they stop you from doing it,
if that makes any sense.
Or if they see that you've been trying,
you're almost there,
but you're not gonna make any more progress,
they give you a tiny little push, right?
Give you an example.
If you have someone who likes to ride their bike a lot
and you compare them to a professional bike racer
do you know the professional bike racer
will just take off and leave them in the dust, right?
Like nothing.
But the difference between that average bicycle rider
and the professional bike racer is the amount of weight
that you would push on the average bike rider
with your pinky on his seat,
just a little bit with the tip of your pinky.
That's the only difference.
You see?
Yeah.
It's like the straw that broke the camel's back
is another analogy, right?
So these other beings, they help you like,
it's not grotesque or big,
it's very tiny, tiny, tiny little subtle movements.
So that's one reference point.
The other reference point is your own precognition.
In other words, Tesla,
in other words, you run the experiment in your mind
spiritually before you do it.
Tesla was able to design a motor with a bearing in his mind
and a month later, check the bearing for wear
and how well it's doing,
all in his mind before he even built it.
He was aided.
Oh no, he had that internal discipline through practice.
Some say that he got the inference from it.
Yes.
But once you develop a practice like that internally,
you're going to get somebody,
you're going to get attention of others
and they're going to have a little counsel
and say, should we help him or leave him alone?
Right.
Yeah, go ahead.
Kind of ties into my last question
about the Chinamar series,
because I'm assuming that you believe
that the devices and portals and everything under
which are real.
And would you say that their ultimate goal
was to facilitate this transition period that we were in,
considering that it was hidden from the surface,
first of all, technologically by,
they had to scan through the satellites
to see that there was that hemisphere there.
And then secondly,
they had to pass the ethical test of the frequency shield.
So would you say that that was put there
to mitigate this period?
Yes, but it was others because the beings
that put whatever they put there
did not want themselves to be public
and did not have like a billboard,
you know, when you pass by a store
and it says IBM or Coca-Cola,
they didn't publicize,
even though it's there and it is known to a certain degree,
I believe it was that influence came from others
based on previous agreements
that others had made with the human race,
certain of the human race
that all things will be exposed in the end.
Let me just put it this way.
The beings that may put all that stuff together
that they discovered are not happy that this is happening,
but because of previous agreements, it's being allowed.
Like, for example, I know a military colonel,
he told me even a year before 9-11,
he was told that around September of 2001,
they got to get ready for war
because some buildings are going to blow up in New York.
He was not happy when he got that news,
but he's in the military
and this came from people higher than him.
So what is he going to do, protest?
He can do that,
but does that do anything when you're in the military
or do they tell you, you know, be careful,
don't protest, right?
Right.
That's one possibility.
The other thing I said,
so when the Vatican got involved,
they will not leave you alone, right?
They will influence the output.
So, by the way, whenever you hear crucifixion,
that is propaganda, right?
Well, yes, but that's the only real thing
that you can use against it.
Everything else seems to check out.
Yes, mostly, mostly, yeah.
I don't want to get into the Vatican
because the Vatican, maybe I will real short.
You know how the censorship and how we watch TV
and nothing real gets to there, right?
That's been going on for hundreds of years, by the way.
Well, that's been the most, yeah.
We just can't do anything, you know?
Yeah, now the Vatican,
you used to be able to look this up a long time ago,
but now it's almost impossible.
The Vatican is actually, they had a website
and it says we're actually,
most people think of St. Peter's Basilica.
That's not the Vatican.
The Vatican is a small red brick building nearby
and all the state departments,
all the governments in the world
get their policies from us.
And once you join us, you cannot rebut it.
You cannot appeal it.
So basically they're saying
that we tell all the governments what to do
and once they agree, they cannot appeal.
You know, they cannot change it once we give them the order.
Okay, so they control the media.
Not that there is also other groups.
To just lean it on them is not fair.
There's different groups geographically,
different groups spiritually, above ground,
surface level, and below ground.
This is surface level.
So anything on the news that you see,
YouTube, for the past whatever, 200 years or whatever,
has been also influenced by them.
So let me just give you an idea.
They are spiritual people,
but they don't know anything
or care about the Bible at all.
They're just using that because of the Pharisees
told them, suggest they should.
It'd be a good thing to hijack.
When they came out in the 90s and so saying
that priests were molesting young boys and all this,
and there's over and over and over,
you know, not one of those stories
should have ever made it to the news
if they didn't want that to get out.
They want that to get out to their followers,
to tell the followers what their religion is really about.
Right?
Part of it is there's a certain demon,
it's the same demon in Scientology,
and the way you evoke this demonic crew
is by afflicting pain to a child through anal sex.
It's the same demon that the Scientologists have,
by the way.
So they're trying to tell the people,
look, it's not because the priests are horny
and they're not married.
No, no, no.
They know what they're doing.
They're trying to tell their followers,
are you guys ready?
And the followers, what they're doing,
the billion Catholics,
they're turning away a blind eye, you see?
So now they're at the point where the Vatican
is viewing their own believers as scumbags
because they can't even take a hint.
So what's going to happen is that system
is going to implode.
Do you see what I mean?
Because the leadership is trying to tell their believers,
if you're a quote-unquote Catholic
and you're a believer in this JES,
all you have to do is read the King James Version,
which is like the worst thing you could possibly read,
and you will see everything we're telling you is a lie.
And none of them do it.
So right away, you've got a billion people
that are A, going to be,
what are they, stupid people in big numbers
are dangerous, right?
Very, very, very dangerous group.
A billion Catholics.
I'm not blaming this on them
because the same thing goes for all the religious groups,
the Muslims, on and on and on.
So you're going to have an implosion
of quote-unquote faithful people.
And it's going to happen in the next five years.
It's going to be pretty ugly.
And yeah, just like right now,
the people that are all masked up, right?
The still masked up.
Yeah, those are the ones that are going to be
trying to cut your head off with a plastic knife
in the next decade.
So there's so much.
This is like chapter 17, what I'm talking about.
Okay.
Hey, Greg, I think this would be a good stopping point.
Is it okay if maybe we pick up next week
or something like that?
Sure.
Okay, let me hit one, two, and.