American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
American Freedom Radio
almost like, here we go, this is going to sound really abhorrent to anybody who
believes themselves Christians, but what they call the King James Version of the
Bible is pretty much the Warren Report, and all of these other texts are pretty
much the 26 volumes. That's the way I would look at it.
Sure. Well, you've got to realize the King James Version and the Bible is,
remember we said it's the most, the last thing for people to discover is what's
obvious, right? There's, the whole thing is about this one God and this Lord, you
know, in the translations that are given, and it's Dios in Spanish and other
languages, Kidios in Greek, right? That is a very low title, by the way, and it's
also erroneous to state God in one, so it's a very erroneous text. Anyone who
does a cursory study on the biblical text with an interlinear, let's say less
than a hundred hours, will discover several thousand fatal errors in the
King James Version within less than a hundred hours of research. They make
good doorstops, by the way. I've got maybe 19 of them, and when the wall shifted in
here and the office door tends to swing on its own, so you need a doorstop, but
the point is this. This is the element of paganism that's brought in
because it's the talisman in a lot of the ancient cultures where the people
were not given the information from the priesthood. They would just hand out
rabbit's foots and little charms that told them had power if they did this,
right? And that's what these versions of the Bible have become. You swear, you put
your, like putting your hand on it and swearing on it is some kind of like
osmotic power, like through osmosis or something, you know? It's ridiculous.
It's, all these texts, it doesn't matter if they're in paper form or
downloaded to a USB drive or a DVD or even read out loud, which they should be,
let's say. All reading was done out loud in the past. It's just a communication.
That's all it is, you know? If you can't communicate what's in there, it doesn't
matter. The substance doesn't matter. The actual, it's, the version itself is
irrelevant, and all of the actual text of preservation, the original texts are
irrelevant if they're not communicated, right? Well, right, and I find it
fascinating that the, what I understand, now this may be erroneous and maybe you
can correct me on this, but what I understand is the original Hebrew text
of what people might identify now as the Old Testament, right? The way that this
was communicated is you had someone who literally read it aloud to a group of
people, then you had someone else explain it, and this is where sort of preaching
came from. Yeah, it wasn't invented by the Baptists or anything like that.
It was always like that, yeah. This was the way it was done, and there might be
different preachers, but there was one particular guy who could read the text
and understood it well, and he just simply read it, and another one would
explain it or give a lesson to go along with it, and nowadays that's become
extremely convoluted. I mean, let's not even get into what's wrong with the text, but yeah,
I mean, this is the way it was communicated, so it was given in an oral
fashion, but it had been memorialized in this very literal way, right? Right, and
those that were inspired to do further than just listen to the initial
interpretation had access to it to study it further based on their specific
expertise, right? Because each, you know, the carpenter, the plumber, you know,
the shoemaker, the butcher, the baker, each had different interests within their
own trade and also within their own natural skill level to approach these
texts to see what else can be gleaned from it, but the interpretation is
something also that is, if anyone has seen the film Contact, when they
initially receive the message and there's a fellow there who can't see, and
he starts hearing some, within the rasper, you know, the snow in the picture, he
starts hearing sounds, and then they go from one level to the next
level, and they find there's more code in it, and they, you see from that film
Contact, it's very much like that, because just to throw something out, let's
just stay with the biblical text since we're on it. A more correct way
to explain it is that the language of preservation, just like you would have a
jar of pickles in your pantry, right? It means you can go and access it and it
doesn't go bad, you know? Right. The languages of preservation are Hebrew
and Greek right now, of these writings. They are originally not written in
Hebrew and Greek, but they're preserved in Hebrew and Greek, just like originally
sandwich pickles or cucumbers. Right. But once you pickle them, they change, but
they're preserved, okay? Now, but it still pretty much has its
application, so the, for example, here's, this is something where you'll throw out
a spoiler, what they call the New Testament written in Greek was actually
written in Israelite, let's say, but when it was taken to be, or let's say Hebrew
for simplicity here, but when it was taken to be recorded as public record, it was
viewed as distasteful to do so in the public record, because most of the story
of the New Testament was in regard to someone who was a convicted felon and
sentenced to death and executed. So they didn't find the story to be fit and
proper to be within the inner record, so they were told to go to the outer court
and record it there, and all of the recordings in the outer court were not
done in Hebrew, they were done in the language of the outer court, which was
known as Greek at the time. It was the Lengua Franca. That's why it's
preserved in Greek, but originally it was written or penned in Hebrew, and which
is another complicated thing, because when one says Hebrew or Chaldean, it's
the same. You can reference the origins of the Hebrew, and it's Chaldean. Chaldean
is what? Babylonian. The sages, let's say the Israelites, were not
Babylonian. They had their own language, and they've lost it. What they call
Paleo-Hebrew is actually the original Israelite language, not the modern, but
this is a very controversial, and we could do several shows on that alone, and how
language has changed, but this is just a little tidbit on that.
I think it's also valid, because this gives you an idea of exactly how complex
the very simple act of censorship becomes, in my estimation. I mean, does
that sound... Yes, but in our conversation, let's say we've had before the show, is
three problems about edification of mankind. It's not what they call
ignorance or stupidity. The first one is the cosmic censorship. The second one is
the stubbornness and rebelliousness to the information. Ignorance is never a
problem, if you have a willing participant, or a willing
container to accept the package, let's say, or someone who is willing to hear what
can be imparted. The problem is never the ignorance or even stupidity, as far as that.
It's the not wanting to hear it through some other decision. And also
there's a bad taste that's been left by religions on all of the ancient texts.
Just to change gears real quick, if you studied what they call the
Noble Quran, and you were around people that consider themselves of the Muslim
faith, or Islamic, let's say, you were trying to discuss the Quran, I assure
you, they would not be able to. They know little tidbits, and what they are
functioning under is tradition. Right, and they become angry, actually,
because I did this with an English Quran, which I understand is
not perfect by any sense, but the fact is that I sat and I read it, you know,
cover to cover, and then came back to these individuals who had lived their
entire lives calling themselves Muslims, and said to them, listen, I'm
really grateful that, because at that time it was hard to get one, and I said I'm
really grateful that you guys allowed me to read this and everything else, and I
even went through the efforts of make sure you wash your hands before you
pick up the book and everything else. I don't know if you've ever gone through
all that with it, but when you do, and then you come back to them, and you
start discussing what you've read, they pretty much reject anything that's not
part of their traditional behavior. That's the truth. Yeah, after a decade of
approaching both the major religions, Christianity and Islam, the
majority of the Christians, if you bring up something that they're not familiar
with, or don't want to be familiar with, they immediately discredit the
document. They'll tell you the Bible was just written by whatever, whatever, it
doesn't matter. There were poets, or who wrote it anyway, can't trust it. Even the
most faithful Christian will say that, by the way. What the people of the
Muslim faith do, though, they'll tell you, oh, that can't be in the Quran, because
the Quran was written to be simple. That's all they say. Now, if I
tell you I've heard that over a thousand times in each variety, that would be
small. That would be conservative. This is a very consistent trait. So the
Christians discrediting the document completely, and the Muslims consistent,
insistent about what I'm saying is not in the Quran, even though you could show
it to them right there, is because it can't be there, because they never heard
it, because the Quran was meant to be simple. There is no way that so many
people who don't know each other can say the same exact thing, unless these things
to say are being planted in their heads. Isn't that interesting? Well, and I find
that extremely interesting when we talk about Islam, because I'm telling you
that I spoke to individuals who were Pakistani. I spoke to individuals that
would call themselves Lebanese, and also with individuals who are part of the
American black Muslim movement, let's call it, and all of them gave me
just about the same reaction, although the harshness that I thought I was going
to receive from the black Muslim Americans was not there. Actually, by the
end of the conversation, it was very pleasant and parted on good terms, but
nevertheless, we ended about on the same note. It was just a lot less hostile,
which makes no sense, considering if you look at me, I mean, I look pretty much
white, and you know, the idea would be... Well, there was no racism. There was no
racism there, yeah, at all. So, it was passive in that direction, but the
interesting thing also is the lack of, how would you say, in other words, these
things have been around for so long, you know, these documents, let's call them
documents, and the people, what would you say, have an average lifespan of 70, 80,
90 on the outside, and within those, let's say, 70 years, let's subtract the first
20, and let's subtract the last 20, so you've got roughly 30 years of time to
approach any of these documents, if you profess the faith. Just about anybody to
really vehemently study. Yeah, you've got 25 to 40 years, depending on your
lifespan, if you haven't had it cut short by something sort of unforeseen.
That's about the amount of time that you have to actively, fully, and really
efficiently be able to take in the information, study it, consider it, put the
proper energy toward it. Yeah, exactly. That's 20 years plus, let's say 40 years or
20, you know, either way, but here's the thing. Let's say the documents are 900
pages, and there's 300 days in a year. If you read three pages a day, you'd be
through it in a year, just the three pages a day. So, there's no...
The thing that's fascinating to me is there's plenty of time to look into this
in detail for anyone, and no one does. When I say no one, I mean pretty much no
one, only a handful of people have ever looked at it. Right, now isn't this
part of the censorship? It gives us a bit of the how, doesn't it?
Because this seems almost insane, that no one would bother to study. I mean, people
just take it as a given, because of their bad taste in their mouths about
the organized religions, that yeah, okay, fine, the books are wrong, I got you, no
problem. They can accept that, and they can accept that there's plenty of
hypocrisy built into those systems, because it has been demonstrable over
and over again, so that they can accept. So, when you say things like, no religion
follows its own book, or I'm paraphrasing you, but nevertheless, the sentiment is
correct, no religion follows its own alleged book, you're correct, and that's
not a shocking thing. But to try and explain to people that absolutely no one
from the scholar to the preschooler in Sunday school ever bothers to
examine it, that sounds almost unbelievable, doesn't it? Yeah, but believe it,
because it's the truth. Does the truth require any believing? Now, here's the
interesting part, you ready? If you have someone who is a believer, quote-unquote,
in any of these religions, and does decide to make the dedication to study
the text, they immediately shed that title from themselves. Oh, yes. In other
words, if you're a Christian, and you study the Bible, just read by reading it,
and when you hit a roadblock, don't give it up, just, you know, discover what
that really means, and go keep moving. Or the same with the Qur'an, if you're
Muslim, or if you're Buddhist, any of the writings there, or Hindu, any of the
writings there, or Jewish, any of the writings there, you will no longer call
yourself... No, you become dispossessed from that idea, you become disabused of
wanting to be attracted to that particular grouping of individuals,
because you find it repulsive. That was exactly the word I used to you when I
told you that I sat down and very seriously considered in my young life
what they call the King James Bible, and read it cover to cover again, which I
find that almost no one who calls themselves a Christian ever does, but I
did that. Of course, I didn't do it in a day or anything like that, a little bit
slower, I didn't take the entire year that you're talking about, but I came
close, and sounds like you're ready to come back in on this conversation.
The thing is, you could never address yourself as being one of those people, so
what's very easy when you're out in public, when someone says I'm Christian,
right away it's like, oh, you've never studied your own text. If someone says I'm
Muslim, oh, you've never studied your own text. If I'm Hindu, you've never studied
anything. And if you want to take a step further, if you say I believe in
the Constitution of the United States, you've never read it, so it's very
interesting. And also, there's no Christian in the Bible, by
the way. You'll never find that, it's only used twice in a very derogatory sense as
well, so we'll leave that alone for now. Or Jew, you will not find the word
Jew in there, even though it's in the King James Version in the New
Testament only, and it's the word Judean, which is a geographic region known as
Judea and the people thereof. But anyway, it's quite accessible.
The only other similar reference you'll find is the word Judah, which refers to
either an individual or a particular family of individuals, things like that.
Through lineage, right, and that's it, as far as I can recall. It would be
almost like a surname, like if you're Smith and someone who knew your great
granddad and their family, say, well, you know, you're a Smith, you know, so
we know you from back in the day. Let's say it's a lineage. Is it a lineage or a
geographical location? In the New Testament, predominantly it was
used as a geographic location. It would be like the, there's one verse in there
that says they didn't want to do, he didn't want to do the festival of the
Jews, where actually it says he didn't want to partake in the festival of the
Judeans. So it's quite a difference. And also the letter J wasn't invented till
the year 1500. Which is a problem. We have a big problem there. Yes, and
names are exempt from language. So anyway, the cosmic censorship is
interesting. Let's tie it all back together. There's a legal, there's
something called legal precedent. You know, if someone stands up and says, I'm
going to do this, let's say in a courtroom, and no one objects, and it's
signed off as being true, it stands as true until there's an objection or an
appeal or what have you in any legal environment through their procedures
that are set up. Okay. This also holds true for any anything throughout time. So
when we look at many of the ancient documents, let's say even documents from
150 years ago, and here's the thing. And I'll say this, everything that could
have been known was known by the end of the 19th century, by the way, whether
it's physics, cosmology, medicine, you know, so wait a second, Greek, how can
you say that? Because how many times have you heard in the 20th century, look
at all these technological advancements we have? Well, we've had so much
enlightenment and advancement and things like that ever since then, Greek.
I mean, what's wrong with you? Yeah, obviously. Yeah. I mean, what are you
what are you not recognizing here? Yeah, well, what I'm this is just a little
side note. If by the end of the 19th century, what had been known would have
been applied, you wouldn't need flying machines, as you have today that require
an airfoil or a wing and a propeller, because I've never seen a bird or a
flying creature with a propeller on its nose or on its butt or a jet under its
wing. Have you? Nothing like that, no. But if they would have... Insects that flap at
pretty rapid rates that almost are reminiscent of this, but... But no propellers
or jets? No, no rotors or jets, no. Right, so if you follow the technology, let's say
let's say I'll drop the name of J.J. Thompson in, that was pretty much the
late 19th century. If that technology would have just been applied, you
wouldn't, you'd have flying machines that not only didn't require propellers or
jets, but wouldn't require fuel. Yes, I said it. So, okay. But there were, that's
why, for example, if you look, the electrical engineering had ceased to seem
to have stopped by the 1920s or 1930s. And there's a reason why. So this is very
similar also to the cosmic censorship. The who, if you want to know who is
putting the cosmic censorship, it's been memorialized. So that's going to require
homework, right? The why, it's actually explained in there, why, as well.
Because you're going to have to learn how to keep time, right? And we've also
covered, I believe, a hundred percent external input. Right, that would have
been the first episode of what we call Shelley in the Greek, I think, is the
hundred percent external input. What happens is, you know, people right now can,
most people, let's say, can, are familiar with their hands and their feet, and they
might be able to get up and walk across the room or scratch their head or see
across the room or hear things. People have become very accustomed to
their anthropomorphic shape and all their faculties, let's say, you know, what
we call a human body. But if you were a spirit right now, and you were put into
a human body, you would feel extremely awkward. It would just be as if you were,
you know, three years old and thrown into a Mack truck and told to drive it. You
would have to learn how to walk immediately, you have to learn how to see
immediately, you have to learn how to hear immediately, because these are
biological functions that are very mechanical, and we have taken our bodies
for granted, and we have also taken our thoughts for granted. You see where I'm
going with this? So, if you were dropped, if you're a pure spirit being and
dropped into a human body, you would fall to the floor, and let's say it happened
to someone else as well, and you'd look at each other, and you'd say, we'd better
learn how to walk real quick, because if someone sees us like this, they're gonna
wonder what the hell's going on. And you're gonna say, well, how do we walk? I
don't know, I've seen them do it, but let's try it. And, you know, anyone who's
been around an infant, it would look no different than a three or four or five
or six month old trying to do it. But you would hopefully, right, you see my
point? You would not be able to manifest a mechanical control of the body, you
have to learn it. And so we've taken our thoughts for granted, we think our
thoughts are our own. It's interesting. Well, you know, I hear things in my head,
or I have a thought, you know, it's an impulse in my head, and they do it, it's
my thought. Really? Really? You're sure about that? Let's go over to the
scientific side. You know, they have all these ways of sensing brainwaves, right?
You know, little electrical pads, they've got various things that they try to do.
And they eventually have come to the conclusion, anyone can do research,
even what they call the Internet, and basically all the current scientists
have come to the conclusion, well, if they're academics, they never come to a
conclusion, but let's just say the ones that tend to broach upon a conclusion
say there's nothing in your head. There's no, we can't find where memories
are, now there's parts of the brain that have damaged, the memories are not
retrievable, that's much different, that would be like an antenna. But we cannot
see the actual information or why things function in the brain the way they do. We
see neurons firing and all these pathways and things, but there's nothing
really there. We don't see the information very, you see, so it's quite
interesting. So right away, humanity thinks their thoughts are of their own,
and once they establish that they're not, then they can tune in appropriately.
And how easy would it be to jam a certain signal and allow one signal to
go in, if you're very technically savvy in radio, let's say, it wouldn't be that
hard to do. Well, right, even though people believe that, you know, radio signals are
completely, you know, uncontrollable, it's just a matter of the receiver, right? So
if you don't have the receiver oriented, you can beam a thousand radio signals
into a direction, but if you have nothing to receive it, it really amounts to
nothing. So is the alteration that, because there appears to be an
alteration, in other words, this doesn't have to be the condition, this censorship.
Is there an alteration that occurs in the receiver, or is it an alteration in
the message, or is it both? Both. It has to be. Now, also the radio that we're
taught about is, it propagates through the speed of light and waves and all
this, but this, the natural world and the spiritual cosmic world doesn't work with
those types of waves. They work with something more on the longitudinal side,
where everything is instant over any given distance, you know, and this is
also in some, I guess, in scientific circles, they call it subspace or
something, where you travel instantly to where you want to go, or communicate
instantly, and this is a reality that Tesla actually proved, and people like
Olaf Alexanderson and, you know, and J.J. Thompson with his lines of force,
this has been totally ignored, but once there's a scientific study done in
what the longitudinal wave is, or how it behaves, we'll be understanding on how
the spiritual realm works as well. And here's one thing, the gods are the gods
because they have technology that we don't have. It's all tech. Just like the
concept of, I think we mentioned once before, a few years ago there was a
stuff going around the internet about the moon is artificial, do you
remember that, Buzz? Oh god, yeah. Yeah, okay, well I was like, of course it is,
because if there's a creator, everything is artificial, because in order for
something to be artificial, you need an artificer or a creator, so if you
subscribe, let's say, to the what's called a creator or a intelligent design, then
everything is artificial, everything is made. Well, right, but let's not
confuse things here. The assertion about the moon is artificial was really that
it was a man-made or alien-made thing, and they were talking about corporeal
beings bringing something to fruition through work. That's what the
assertion was. Yeah, I got it, but I use it as an idea. The
interesting thing, we should just drop this in right here, the moon acts the way
it does is because it does not have its own orbit, it is locked into Earth's
orbit, and then once you understand that mathematically or physically
using basic physics, or you can just take a tennis ball and sit down
on the carpet on the floor at a basketball, have something orbit
another thing, now instead of having the moon have its own orbit, just lock
it into the orbit of the Earth, and then it makes sense why it behaves the way
it does, so I believe the crux of a lot of that stuff about being artificial was
its actual mechanical motion, its behavior as well, because it's the only
object that's observable that does that, and it's the only, let's say
moon, that is locked into the orbit of the planet versus having its own orbit.
There's a big difference there, and this also was described in great length, well
I would say a few pages, a few hundred words by Tesla, but no one wants to read
that, right, because then there's nothing to argue about. Well, just like with the
religions, a lot of things have now been passed down as traditional
anecdotes, but the fact is that most of the people that are discussing this
have never bothered to read. See, this is why I don't discuss Tesla, I got to be
honest with you, because I haven't read his work. I've heard about it, I have
examined people's claims about it, but that is much like someone recounting
this particular show to someone else and giving their version of it to someone
else without playing the show for them. I guarantee that some things will be
misrepresented, misunderstood, possibly, you know, for better or worse, who knows,
but either way it is distorted in some fashion when you are taking the word of
another party here, which would be a third party if you consider Tesla as the
first and you as the second. Well, there's another one as an intermediary,
you have a third party introduced, and therefore the information becomes askew,
right? Especially if you don't know what's in the punch bowl at that party.
There you go, and I love when you do stuff like that, because that's
exactly where this needs to land. Now, the who, like you said, it's going to take
some study for people to understand. I think it's very valid to say that when a
claim is made and it's not challenged, no matter on what plane we're discussing,
that's how things stand. I mean, think about this, not even
necessarily legal, criminal, actionable, forget that. We'll kind of go
with actionable. When someone decides to sue you, which did
happen to me at one point, and has happened to various other people, if
someone sues you, you've been notified that you are in danger of having a
judgment placed against you, and that person makes a claim in court and you
don't answer it, what usually happens after some process is that their claim
is validated by the courts. So, in a sense, what you're saying is the universe...
Not only by the courts, but supported by the impending society as well.
Well, right, and that's the thing, is that if you take a step back and apply it to
this, that's precisely what you're saying regarding these sorts of claims, like the
universal court, so to speak. This is the way it goes, and it doesn't matter what
legal society studies the documents or which adversary, and I do mean attorney
and adversary, both in the same breath, decides to turn it askew, twist it on its
own head, and do whatever else with it. This is the fact of the matter, and it
becomes precedent. Regardless of what they want to try and do with it later,
that's what happens, right? Yeah, and the precedent is executed. Oh yeah. You know,
it's actually taken into the physical realm, and actually the location and all
that. So, this has nothing to do with what you believe in. Now, there's an
interesting point to be made, again, regarding the censorship. The
censorship is very strong, and it's almost like, you know, being behind bars
in a way, right? But there are hints that are given. That's why I like to keep
saying the last thing left for humanity to discover is the obvious, and one of
the obvious things is words are important. No pun intended there, right? We
tend to do that a lot here. Words are important, and also the meanings of words,
and who is saying them is also very important. Meaning, is it coming from a
position of power or not, right? Right. So, who is speaking, what is being spoken, and
how it is being spoken are all extremely valuable pieces to the puzzle, right? And
look at the mentality now, where the general population of most of the
Western world, and Eastern world, I should say, most of the planet, how do
they view their leaders, by the way? Do they take what their leaders are saying
seriously, or do they actually make jokes about it? Think about it in
contemporary times. Both. Yeah. I see both. Yeah, so there's inconsistency, and there's
confusion almost, and division. There's a bipolar nature to how
leadership is being accepted, and it seems to be exponential. Exponentially
getting more convoluted as time appears to progress. Right. And let's say, apply
that notion to what we're discussing in terms of ancient documents and texts
that the religion is supposed to subscribe to. How do they take it?
Also both. It's very confusing, and there's no set mind on it. That's
absolutely true, and I guess this is why one could easily say that we are in and
unlawful atmosphere, because if there were law, one would have to abide by or
acknowledge it. Or acknowledge it, yeah. And there is no universal, well, see
there's that word, sorry to use it, but universal understanding of the way
things are supposed to be. And I say again, doesn't it tie right to the fact
that I can't find anyone who doesn't seem to believe that something is very, very
wrong on the planet. Yep, and it's temporary. Six thousand plus years
temporary? Does that sound temporary enough? Depending on your perspective, it
could be very temporary. If one accepts that time is in a relevancy to a
being who is the lawgiver, I guess that could be nothing more than a, well, a
blink of the eye at best, six days. It's defined specifically as, it would be
relatively to that being, would be relatively what six Earth days are to us.
And that's the proportion. That is not a lot, and yet that's the way it's gone.
And look at this, the first what they call one hour, according to the wind-up
toy or the digital representation thereof, is over. However, there's one more
coming up. So Greek in the second hour, I think we'll get a little more specific
on this cosmic censorship, and we'll move forward. And I want to thank all of you
guys for hanging with us tonight here on Ocelli and the Greek. We'll be right back.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us? Provide us with free education?
Well, that's obviously effective, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of
America, all the information they provide is free. What about the free
podium for broke-ass activists to speak from, then? Exploiting commonplace
corruption? They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice? Bringing light to
important information nobody else does. Oh, they never censor, hang up, or cut off
their guests? Well, that's no fun, is it? Oh, they created a fantastic alternative
media source during an era of bad, manipulative, and infiltrated mainstream
and alternative media shows and scum? Okay, well, apart from the free education, free
podium for broke-ass activists to speak from, exposing commonplace corruption,
helping vulnerable people without a voice, bringing light to important
information nobody else does, and creating a fantastic commercial-free
alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream, and alternative
media shills and scum, what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us? Donate to
American Freedom Radio today. Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American. Practically narcotic. Freedom. Oh, yes, I like it very much. Radio. You're an American institution. American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are three million edible food plants on earth, and none
have the nutritional value of the hemp plant? HempUSA.org offers you hemp
protein powder. It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100%
gluten-free. Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein,
and feeds the body the nutrients it needs. Call 888-910-4367 and see what our
powder, seeds, and oil can do for you. Only at HempUSA.org. HempUSA.org
introduces three brand-new detox formulations of micro plant powders.
Brain fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress. Total Care,
anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates, and heals the body, mind, and spirit. These products are
your alternative to pharmaceuticals. Call 888-910-4367 and like us on
Facebook. We ship worldwide. Only at HempUSA.org. Tell the truth, don't be
bullshitting people. There's enough bullshit as it is. In fact, there's just
enough. Did you know that? There's just enough bullshit to hold things together
in this country. Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation. Where would we
be without our safe, familiar, American bullshit? Land of the free, home of the
brave, the American dream, all men are equal, justice is blind, the press is free,
your vote counts, business is honest, the good guys win, the police are on your
side, God is watching you, your standard of living will never decline, and
everything is going to be just fine. The official national bullshit story. I call
it the American Okie-Doke. You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive
dialogue, with true independence. The freedom to broadcast the truth is not
free at all. So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you? The empowering
information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it provides an example
to follow. Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no
punches. The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to
deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and
loyalty. The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your
views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media. Now it's
time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of
America. Be as generous with us as we've been with you. Click on the donate banner
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics. No fear of doom. We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents the only broadcast information that would dare to underestimate the sonic energy known as Ocelli.
Second hour beginning here on Ocelli in the Greek broadcast live on American Freedom Radio dot com.
And of course I thank you regardless of where it is you decided to pick this up
whether it's further on down the stream through YouTube whatever depending on
where the show winds up being posted shared etc etc we do appreciate you
giving us a bit of your time so I did say that we're beginning the second
hour if you missed the first hour you missed an interesting discussion on the
cosmic censorship issue that that often comes up on this show and I think we've
actually broken that down pretty well although it still bears a little more
dissection or vivisection because still kind of dealing with this right now and a
quick programming note here we go this is the last time that Ocelli in the Greek
will be broadcast on what they call a Saturday night you know Saturn day of
course technically sitting here on the East Coast I'm into the Sun day of
allegedly according to the Pope's work schedule but you'll be able to find us
on Friars excuse me Friday from now on and at 8 to 10 p.m. Eastern so there you
go and of course I think that's what five to seven in the Pacific time zone
and well figure out what your wind-up toy called a clock or digital
representation thereof actually says about it and you'll be able to follow it
but you'll hear us on what they call a Friday generally speaking from now on
and it's a good reason to go to the AFR website there's on the top tabs it'll
give you scheduling other hosts as well and also a donate button that's correct
all those things even if you go to the chat which we do have at AFR as well
when you go to the chat page there is a donate button help us grow I think is
the phrase which is on that particular graphic and yes that is exactly what you
would do if you contributed something to American Freedom Radio which makes
this broadcast possible along with the two of us and well that obvious
information the most inexplicably obvious information in some cases and
well maybe not so obvious in some other cases that that we discuss here would
not be possible without American Freedom Radio so keep that in mind when you're
deciding what to do with your alleged currency ok so make censorship yeah
cosmic censorship back to it because you said it's going to be a bit of a
homework assignment to look into the who totally understood the when well that's
now and has been you said let's see 6,000 years is your estimation sure but
let's go back to the who real quick is that ok yeah absolutely ok when you say
the word army do you think of just one man in uniform
what do you think that yeah so let's say someone wanted to research army well
first of all they're going to discover there's a mass plurality involved and
because of the topical nature of the term army there you will notice other
things will notice ranks hierarchies things like that battles right there's
a very rich bit of information to say you've researched the army right I mean
there's a rules there is conduct there is well an entire system which one can
study the alleged evolution of it really truthfully there's been a change in
tactics but honestly the idea that there is a command structure and there are
individuals which conduct what is known as war prevails at all times in history
regardless of what time period society etc etc you're looking at right now
there's peacekeeping forces there's enemy there's friend and foe there's
yeah so when you hear the word God use the same thing you know it's interesting
if you go to that infinite bastion of accurate information known as Wikipedia
ha ha ha type in God and Wikipedia see what you get that's a good place to
start believe it or not and you go from there and you keep moving because most
people actually use that wiki thing you know a lot and very often it's it's like
the pocket reference guide on the Internet so that's just a quick thing so
when you look up God see what you get just like if you look up a are and why
what do you get you know you'll see those parallels and it's not we're not
saying this is about being militant or anything but it's just an analogy but
that would be the who part and you know you can't you start working that way
again it has to do with just information you know we one thing we didn't really
send home Chuck is that what is being censored cosmically information and see
here it is the what and is it all information is a specific information
yes or is it just the ability to oh I don't know hmm to internalize that
information see again here's my question that sounds like I'm asking the same
question over and over but I'm really not because is it really about the
ability to to comprehend it or is it that it is really truthfully not being
spoken it has been completely obscured from view and from and from
accessibility the second part has come first obviously you know like when when
most people wouldn't with you know they and by the way we're doing this during
what they call the holiday season which is you know and if you really want to
know where you're in such deep doo-doo just observe what's going on with that
but the censorship right the last part that I agreed yes yes that's the
perception you'll read you'll see that there's a concept of eyes to see and
ears to hear and if you're tripping on acid it would be ears to see and eyes to
hear but anyway so and by the way if you if you do get a good grip on these
ancient texts it will be like reading something about an acid trip so anyway
back to the to the thing about the information which is important besides
the perception you know we're not just the physical organs those are metaphors
being able to perceive let's just not even from a cosmic level just the
generic term information the way information is imparted and accepted
from the importer to the impart e when someone hears a bit of information it
all takes place in the imagination right like if I say Chuck I just fell
down a flight of stairs well you know you're across the country but you can
you're instantly that entire scene is played in your mind because you can
imagine I have to relate and I have to first relate what stairs are then I have
to relate to it what it would be like if someone fell down them but you know I
would imagine intentions I would visualize it yeah and I am interrupting
you a little more than usual because occasionally you know there's a reason
to do so by the way in case anybody's getting upset about that and also I just
noticed something being dropped in the chat room which I think is part of what
you're about to discuss here which is desire to comprehend is censored is the
statement that was made in the chat room and I thought that was an interesting
sort of interjection into the conversation that's where the hints are
so let's keep that in mind as well because you see we're developing an
outline here to address remember earlier I said there are hints that are being
given even though you there is a massive censorship and the desire to comprehend
is one of the hints that you can see through the cut the the censorship right
so it but it's not just about the desire it's it's it's also about the
information so first yeah like you said let's talk about the imagination in the
imagination so it's about the the act of taking one's imagination and sort of
gifting it to someone else by that which we call communication interesting
process and a little more complex than it appears because most people take it
as a given and it's not I mean it's not all of this is also there's a structure
behind that which you know that you see how this conversation can branch out
into a you know eight-year college but right but from a simple point of just
conveying any information immediately the listener or the one accepting the
information imagines it right you know if you said let's say Noah's flood well
the first thing is it's really wet right and then you go on from there right very
simple impulse reaction and once the information is given then the individual
has received the communication and just to bypass maybe some other things that
happen the next thing is the individual acts on it right the individual can act
on the imagination right in other words if let's say if you look at ancient
texts the concept of law you're made aware of a certain law and you say well
yeah okay I can see that I can you know I understand what you're saying because
if someone cannot imagine it they also say they can't understand it you ever
notice that if you bring up something unfamiliar yeah well because part of
part of the comprehension is imagination no matter what no matter how you're
receiving it even if you are taking in another form of communication such as
visually observing something right you have to be able to correlate that to
another experience another understanding like I was saying about the stairs if
you don't know what stairs are you will not understand yeah you know what did
you fall down from did you fall off of a building did you fall off of a chair your
horse I mean if I don't know what stairs are there's a problem so that's why you
say that not only are the meanings of the words important but the words
themselves become extremely important and and there you go and you have to be
objective like for example we we have a lot of branding today in a modern
culture and if anyone wants to know when we say modern we don't mean in a good
way to listen to the previous episodes you know what I mean by branding you
know these when someone wants to wipe their nose with a tissue what do they
ask for it starts with a K right and if someone wants an ear swab they ask for
something that starts with a Q right well you know why should we give them
free advertising you know or right or even when they ask for an ointment
sometimes it's based on a compound word which begins with a V and ends with an E
but truthfully that's also a brand name a brand yeah so if you were to memorial
memorialize something through the ages let's say and let's let's let's use this
name like a caterpillar bulldozer what that doesn't sound like anything but if
you describe it as a very large piece of cast iron that a man sat inside of
it and when it was animated it blew smoke and the earth rumbled and it pushed
the earth aside that's a very accurate description of what a caterpillar
bulldozer does and it's also bright yellow hmm right so you look at that
disruption to a more rudimentary level yeah it makes more sense if someone is
unfamiliar with that brand name yeah but take give someone just reading this
thing is cast of iron bright yellow man sits inside of it blow smoke and it
rumbled the earth rumbles when it moves the earth what the hell are you talking
about right so if you use the brand you're not going to get the information
and if you actually give the information what it does people all of a sudden put
it into the realm of fascination as opposed to something practical right mm-hmm
does it that sound like something that's been going on how many times do
you hear people making biblical references and and they say well what is
this supposed to mean well exactly what it is what are you talking about it's
like what came first the chicken or the egg that easy as it came first because
all things reproduce after their own car I need and say what kind of egg what if
it were a reptile in the egg that's nonsensical so things are being put in
front of us I think that would be if people have been dummy loaded for so long
like Forrest Gump says stupid is or stupid does or something so that's the
other problem but which can be simply fixed but to go back to the imagination
Chuck the in terms of the law how many times we said the law comes from your
deity right or your God right well okay what does that mean well once you get
some information you imagine it right you know if we're talking about a
subject like let's say clothing or you know food I don't like using the word
diet by the way because it has D IE in the first three letters that can't be
good so but if once that's imagined then what's the next step the next step would
be in order for it to be more tangible the individual will have to act on it
somehow or live it how many times have you heard people say well use you know
do you live what you say right do you actually do it not just say it right so
that would be the next step right just like for example you know anyone who
studies anything in any discipline it's one thing to study they're called book
smart if they don't do it it's a put-down right when someone calls someone
book smart means you don't have any practical ability which means you're
academic anyway here's the dig on academics again but so needs to be
repeated it couldn't be repeated enough we could just do digs on academics from
now told you know next ten years it wouldn't be enough because of their
weaponized stupidity but anyway the imagination aspect then is where it does
not leave and once in most people's minds and also what they are imagining
when they take in the information is not tangible any way that they can do
anything with or it's been tainted you see and this is all part of the it's
like a warfare from the adversary you see like you know an example of that
would be and I don't mean to be stuck on the biblical text or what they call the
scriptures but you know it's interesting how when the Dead Sea Scrolls let's say
the scrolls that were intact of the canonical text were discovered then they
were made top-secret you know and the reason why is because they match exactly
with the available text in their language of preservation the last thing
they want people to know is that they have valid any anyone go online and
validate that the text that they have is the text of delivery from the time
period thousands of years ago it's still congruous right so you want to keep the
doubt in people's mind if you're going to be an adversary to them you see so
this happens very often with many subjects not just the subject that we're
discussing on a cosmic level let's say the cosmic censorship but just to go
back to the overall discussion of the cosmic censorship there's something
that's written that says that if someone is tempted to do something
that's not fit and proper they're always given a way out okay and I'm
paraphrasing there I can give it to you more accurately but it's irrelevant in
other words if people are doing things that are unlawful they're always given a
way out with even within the cosmic censorship now here's the point that we
spent most of the past hour discussing we've said or particularly myself there's
no religion on the planet that does anything or knows anything that in the
text that they allegedly subscribed to in con right because you could note you
know that the word does in the Bible or the Koran but you're talking about that
talking about you know functioning okay so from that point how many quote-unquote
people he birds are these religions what is keeping them okay within their time
limit or ability from actually studying the text that they're supposed to
subscribe to almost nothing are they going to be you know is it is there any
punishment that's so dulled out if they start reading their Bible let's say if
they're Christian or the Koran if they're Muslim no but what's stopping
the people from doing it it doesn't make any sense that they're not right well
yeah that's the thing and that's why I almost want to say that we need to really
define define what you mean by cosmic because see that this is I break down
both words right we've talked about the censorship we've talked about the
functionality of it we've talked about the purpose of it the purpose of it is to
be adversarial I think because the more that you confuse people the the the
better for you to keep them from the right path with the correct idea the
reality in the literal sense of what is being related if you keep confusing the
issue so that seems to be the function but cosmic is a qualifying word for the
action of censorship so cosmic meaning what the earth and beyond it's a
planetary problem or if you want to call it a problem and if you got off the
planet it would be as well in other words you're targeted because you're
human and big then you see now you have to define humanity humanity is created
to be within the same authority of the highest authority in the cosmos and
that's the Greek term for everything out there you know meaning the world you
know the earth and beyond let's say you know all that can be perceived right okay
so this is I think we've discussed there's a curing period for mankind where
mankind has to go through a certain amount of X Y & Z to be ready for the
next step and you combine that with also the way that we've been taught to
think is far minimal in comparison to what we are actually capable of you see
how many times have you heard these scientists say we only use 10% of the
brain or something like that you know how limited we are and this has nothing
to do with the secular adversarial way that you know people are always given as
an extreme inferiority complex of how they should view themselves right you
know you look at the fashion magazines the way the science is projected to
people that you don't know but we know and all this everyone is has this
inferiority complex and this has nothing to do with that this has to do with
certain actions certain time period and the details of that believe it or not
are not given to us it could one could say if we are in an infantile state this
is commonly said by the way then one would have to suppose that we lack the
maturity and what's interesting is you know you don't do sex education to a
four-year-old because they they're not mature enough you have to wait for them
to pass puberty where that applies you see right now in that vein though when
one looks at maturity you would think that someone who okay if a five or a
six-year-old turns around and strikes someone with a stick this is actionable
they require punishment you know from the authority figure the parent the
teacher whatever but you know once they've gotten past or beyond a certain
point of maturity they are now expected to deal with greater consequences
because they understand their actions better I mean isn't this almost the
definition of what would be a lack of maturity for the species in general
sure uh-huh the maturity would be knowledge do you have the knowledge to do
what needs to be done and then carry the responsibility for it mm-hmm yeah and
this is not about there we've also discussed how people are not animals we
we share certain biological things but we're not because of the input right
we've discussed given the analogy of a puppy being raised by gorillas will act
as a group well you will not know that it was raised by gorillas as an adult
where a human would be quite easy to see that it was raised by gorillas so the
hundred percent external input is quite quite important at this time to
understand and we mentioned earlier that we've taken our thoughts for granted you
know like for what is one of the most arrogant displays of taking one's
thoughts for granted is the concept of patents or patents as they say in
Australia and other parts of the world right to do this is this is my idea and
I'm going to claim rights to it really okay it's your idea now think about it
if your thoughts are not your own basically you're you know to say that
they are and get a pat and say that this is my patent that is like the
epitome of hubris in one regard but that's that's not even to go down that
line or that line of thought because it's still quite popular you see my
example there you know yeah of course but I mean one thinks to themselves look up
boulders rolling down the hill you know it is simply a subject now to to the
physical reality that is pushing it along down that hill but at some point
it seems to me as though someone had to give it a push or some force had to be
applied to it to begin its journey mm-hmm well it's manifested here things
the things that are manifested here are very much controlled from another place
let's say the the intangible but to just to stick on the subject of the the
cosmic censorship once you understand that there is a censorship but it's it's
not completely sealed you're ninety nine point nine nine nine percent let's
say sealed off but that point zero zero one percent that's open are the hints
and then those hints are put into the imagination and then the individual has
a choice at that point once it's imagined if we're presuming that the
information that's given is correct right for so let's say in the biblical
text if you think the Christ figure was born around December 25th don't even
bother you're just gonna be wasting your time or you think there's a
crucifixion or something don't even bother you think there's like you know
long hair saying peace and love and you know look at me or you know this this is
forget it there's none of that in there in the text don't even bother going down
the road we're discussing now we've just pretty much eliminated most of our
listeners but this is not the purpose of saying that purpose of saying it is that
like I said earlier when you actually start doing the research and putting
things in in the correct order and seeing what that is really preserved in
the text it'll be like an acid trip not that what you're really reading is an
acid trip but in comparison to what you've been told and what you thought
about it you see well listen if you become accustomed to being in a dark
room long enough and then you are put into the sunlight it's extremely painful
is it not well it's not that the sunlight is bad for you it's just that
you've become accustomed to darkness and you know what I find interesting too
is that during this alleged holiday season when they were discussing because
of course I watch certain trends to see what's going on media wise as far as
dissemination goes regarding certain things like this you know what I found
fascinating is that for the first time ever I heard some individuals that were
trying to study the historical record not from a religious standpoint but just
simply examining the historical record and trying to make comparisons about
these assertions that have been made right it was really fascinating to me
and I kind of took notice that that somebody stated and I can't remember who
it was but I found it kind of startling because just went by me really quickly
that there was no evidence for crucifixion and that that actually there
is very little historical evidence to back the concept of Roman crucifixion
at that time being conducted in any way shape or form in the sense that most
people generally understand it the concept of these two erect straight bars
being put into place would be extremely cumbersome there was no machine to do so
and and this would have been problematic also the physical reality of nailing a
body to a cross in exactly that fashion is another problem well well they
actually if you read the biblical text you'll see you know in terms of that
we've actually pushed it over to the next quote quote unquote holiday these
people are going to be doing see these people I mean those that don't want to
lift a finger to measure anything or look at anything because they think it's
all being served to them by others you know yeah here look at this great this
meal is piping hot and delicious in three microwave minutes right but anyway
the the whole idea of anything that's in any of the ancient texts or even the
legal text that men subscribes to is still a secret in a mystery what
shouldn't say secret and mystery because mystery means no one knows there are
there are those that know but more more appropriately for this time period I
think we discussed there's an astronomical alignment that's given two
places the first place is in Genesis and the last place is in the last book of the
preserved text about an astronomical alignment that's of great significance
and what's interesting the more bodies involved in an astronomical alignment
the more accurate the event in other words you can zero it down not only to
it Oh a month a week or a day but within the time of day you see anyone who's ever
looked through a telescope knows that if the telescope is not in following
mechanically the the moon or whatever star you're looking at it drifts off
within a few seconds or minutes so there's an astronomical alignment that's
given and that astronomical alignment can be reckoned and if it's reckoned
according to the in common parlance the Gregorian or Julian calendar that would
have been 3 BC that alignment the month of what you call September the day of 11
and that is not open for debate and that is not open for belief or anything
that is within the text itself very accurately and it would be in the p.m.
hours it would be it's at sunset and before sunset was over the event would
have already had taken place so we're looking out of an event within what you
might call by the wind up toy between 6 and 640 so we're talking about a great
degree of accuracy in the ancient text but then we have a great degree of what
would you call it when you go online and you research these megachurches and these
quote-unquote religious internet sites and they tell you no one really knows
and there's no information in the biblical text Wow that means that oh it's
just rain even though it's yellow it's okay anyway they're telling me it's rain
but it's yellow and it doesn't smell very good but they're telling me it's
rain so I guess it's rain well I see and there you go with that with what John
Stray yeah what John Stray said in the chat room which was you know a herd
mentality that's what it preys upon and that is that that people do seem to have
a hardwired desire to follow something it's not the ignorance but it's not
ignorance it's the stubborn it's the cosmic censorship which they do have a
way out it's the stubbornness and the rebelliousness also you know people will
get into your face say well I believe this and that's it I don't want to
discuss anymore that's what I believe and in another episode we discussed how
the adversary controls all major institutions and one of the things that
the adversary has done is put on mankind the concept of rights like in freedoms
that you have a right and freedom to say what you want believe in what you want
and all that and really I thought that's what why crazy people are put in
institutions for to separate them from the rest of us because they could be
dangerous so correct excuse me not right yeah so if there's freedom here's the
thing if there's freedom of religion how do you think let's take mainstream
America Main Street mainstream America somewhere anywhere because you'll find
that mainstream Main Street America in almost any part of the country and you
ask a survey how many of you believe in freedom of religion might say most
people would raise their hand not all me but let's say most is a generous
presumption right and all of a sudden say well then we're opening a satanic
temple here how many of them would agree to that none almost right maybe one or
two or three or four but it would be an inverse show of hands right just but
you just said freedom of religion and you didn't qualify it well see that's the
thing and unqualified I mean look look let's take away the the the labels for a
moment I say well look I'm going to erect a temple here where I randomly
a sacrifice a citizen of this particular town to the local deity in order to
create stop stop that's the court building that's the standard bar attorney
but anyway sorry no it's okay I was hoping you would I'm going to a
sacrifice random citizen in order to promote just a parody oh is that that's
a goddess and they do for prosperity here's interesting part and this is a
dig on them because they deserve it not that I you know they're not going to go
away for a little while but there won't be these guys won't be around in the
future in several decades or less or a couple of decades or less but here here's
the point I was once listening to the inaugural speech of the new president of
the Bar Association he said that in order to have a strong economy you need
a strong legal system this was in the opening part of his speech hmm
interesting and the reason why people did human sacrifice was for wishes of
prosperity how many times have you heard people discuss the holidays and they say
oh well it's all commercialism now like yeah sacrificing to Moloch or ball was
about commercialism the reason they roasted children alive is because they
always made a wish of prosperity prior to it yeah that does so are you like
some freakin genius no also that was pretty pretty lucrative business for
individuals to provide those things which could grant those wishes in a
physical manifestation exactly they had to make the statues that to provide the
children the poor were encouraged to sell their children to be sacrificed
right because people didn't want to use their own it just they just had to
provide a child you know that's why you have the red the oversized red dress
character where a child sits on their lap and makes a wish of prosperity in the
marketplace known as the malls of America let's say today and you know what
else it gives me a strange sort of parallel to is what people do with the
military yeah it's it's perfectly fine to sacrifice other people's children to
this particular cause which is going to make sure to different defend these
rights and freedoms as well and therefore well yeah unqualified rights
yeah unqualified rights and freedoms yeah well unqualified rights and also
this idea of giving this sort of surrogate you know proxy sacrifice to
this mechanism I think that prevails as well I think the analogy is pretty
strong sorry I've got a serious anti-military bent in me oh no it's fine
well here's the thing there hasn't been a proper war in 2,300 years I hate to
say it leave you're correct yes so because the reason for war was is not
what we've been promote as it's been promoted but then again you know just to
harken back to yours the introduction that you gave about no matter who you
ask or when you ask them they all sense that there's something wrong right
there's something wrong going on on planet Earth no matter what culture or
who you ask or when you know if you really get a lucid or sober moment and
then out of anyone they would willingly admit to that to some degree hmm you
know so if if there's if everyone or let's say most most people will admit to
that and there's not inquiry and there isn't you know what I want you to test
yourselves to here's something I want to throw in for the listener because I've
given them a way to look at others look at others look at others when it comes to
this something being wrong now I want you to look at yourselves have you ever
encountered someone in a moment of euphoria drug-induced or otherwise who
is just far too pleasant and well I don't know happy thrilled let's say hmm
what would be a good what would be a good way to put this content with the
condition of the whole world and themselves
you Dory yeah everything everything is great everything is beautiful everything
is as it is supposed to be the world is a wonderful place and are you feeling
bile beginning to rise up in the back of your throat there you go
well why because even with that you know that someone is feeding you a line of
nonsense to be sick sickly sickly sweet I call it yeah there you go and and that
is how you know that you without examining a single thing a single world
event whatever if someone presents it to you that this is the reality around you
that everything is exactly as it should be and it's perfect and it's wonderful
and it's beautiful do you find yourself agreeing with that ever and here's the
thing Chuck if if they're if they're there in that position and they don't
inquire from a lawful perspective that renders humanity as a bunch of robots
you know the herd is in someone put in the in the text I think you mentioned
herd mentality and I don't like to say that because that gives animals a bad
name now I'm you know what I mean mm-hmm yes so we'll leave you know leave those
guys alone the animals are just fine why do I drag them into this mess no I
think you know how many times have you heard sheeple that is not correct
because sheeple are very part of sheeple sheep are very particular about their
diet if they eat a wrong diet they could get sick and die more humanity
could be more akin to they're very few sheep by the way that means that if you
heard that this was the holiday season you would get sick right based on what
they were talking about what most people have been metaphorically explained as
being pigs goats or dogs the sheep should be left out of it why the goat
will pretty much eat anything a dog will eat its vomit meaning it'll get rid of
things that are bad and go right back to them and a pig eats very violently right
you know how many people have you heard of being kicked out of their houses when
they asked show that I owe any money to the bank most people and when you kicked
out of your house by the way in the wrong time of year you you could die that
that's a reality if you have no shelter so we're looking at a level of inaccuracy
in the way people have been their characters have been described even
there so let's leave the animals alone I just wanted to throw that in because
the cosmic censorship and what people can gain information from and on is very
often give metaphorically to give more depth and richness to it within the
imagination because all information first is decided in the imagination like
if we were to say we're going on a cruise down to Bermuda and bypassing the
Bermuda Triangle of course and we're gonna sit on a sandy beach you know can
you imagine that sure right you see and now and now are reacting on it and
that's the next level so at this point all of the information is there the
censorship is yes the information and the ability for one to perceive but
there's also as we've mentioned there's an ad cosmic adversary that is preventing
people from accessing this I think from doing your own research on JFK have you
ever come across any blocking or redacting of information on through your
travels of all the years of doing that by the way on every side of any issue
that you can possibly imagine in the minutiae yes and that's just a very thin
slice of reality the JFK assassination yeah the study of six seconds of event
combined with all of the resulting things that occurred from those six
seconds yeah yeah you could say that that's a pretty thin slice even in a
human lifetime yes yes you can you say that tampering with evidence so maybe the
truth couldn't be imparted wouldn't be accurate oh well you know from the
official standpoint from those who allege to be researchers from those who
allege to give you guidance so you can understand the event wait a minute you
know that sounds again like organized religion yeah okay sorry I just came to
that realization yeah and metaphorically you see how no matter what topic we
discuss it goes back to a similar template was that always yeah there's
always a censorship there's always a misdirection there's always a magic
trick of sorts which is more trick than magic and and here's the thing you the
reality is censored by one mechanism or another distraction flat-out lie
convolution misdirection and all of these things prevail and at all times it
seems as though it's a multifaceted sort of interlocking interwoven strategy by
which all information is kept secret to some and it doesn't matter what field
you're talking about the magic tricks you know the showmanship of magic on
stage the David Copperfield's Houdini's and such I guess the technical term for
that is ledger domain or slightly you know which is an illusion production
right nothing makes a magician more nervous is when they see another
competent magician sit in the audience while they're performing because all it
takes is to break the fascination of the audience's for that musician magician
who is sitting in the audience to turn around and start telling people how the
trick was done yes because right now what's going on is when the magician
saws a lady in half and puts her back together everyone in that audience will
sign and swear to an affidavit that they saw a woman being sawed in half and put
back together on stage would they not they saw it they believe it they would
do an affidavit that they saw that wouldn't they and they would not be
lying but the magician is lying and they're swearing to it right so the the
leaders of the main institutions whether it's scientific medical religious
government on and on and on even engineering at this point are lying and
the people are swearing to it so the the circle is complete and when you catch
the liars what did they say but everybody has sworn that this is how it
is
seeing it almost leads to another strange question which is the concept of
what they call free will because if this is what is available to you and that is
all that is available to you is there any such thing as free will because if
that's all you have to work with
there is free will but it's on a micro level macro and micro and very much
distinguished distinguished in this category of discussion not within the
same thing but being different as one large movement or one large big picture
being set but the small picture is not and the analogy we've given is a
cruise ship going from London to New York with a thousand passengers everyone
all 1000 of those passengers are going to go from London to New York but while
they're on the journey on the cruise ship they have the option of being on
deck going to the theater having a meal going to their cabin taking a bath many
things to do on a cruise ship that would be the free will but the lack of free
will would be the what has been assigned for the cruise ship to everyone with the
reason why everyone got on there was to go from London to New York and the truth
is where wherever that ship does arrive regardless of what you've been told
that's where it's going to arrive and that's where everybody's going well
that's where everybody's going yeah whether it's the middle of the ocean or
it's New Jersey instead of New York or it's Florida guess what that's where
everybody's going and those things have very little to do with those little
individual decisions yeah because you could decide what you're going to do for
that four five six seven days and each individual will have a different desire
and that's why when you look around what's going on in world history and what
is going to come everyone is going to experience a certain amount of things but
within those experiences within that main experience that everyone on the
planet will see happen because simply you're on the planet and you're
manifested here you each have their your own professions your own families
your own ways of doing things your own when you go to have lunch you order
things differently on the menu but the things that we tend to be discussing on
things that are going to be coming upon this planet and society at large are
going to affect everyone it's not whether what you're going to decide for
lunch see that would be the free will gotcha well look we only have about a 10
minutes or 10 of what they call minutes left on that wind-up toy or digital
representation thereof and I'm wondering if there is a way we can put like I say
a pretty bow on this particular package I know that reference doesn't sit too
well with you but pretty bows are pretty boys just don't put him on on something
that is vulgar you know in a way but and by the way that word vulgar by the way
is what Latin is that it's called the Vulgate so anyway that's an interesting
thing if you're going to have a language of the adversary but that's another
discussion yeah I would say that we the main crux was or was the cosmic
censorship and it's a very difficult subject but I believe we've thrown in
enough elements of it that it's about information and then processed by
whoever hears the information in the imagination and then the choice of
course is whether you're going to live it or not whatever information it is
right and from this point of view it's from what hierarchy you consider going
back to what we say your law comes from your God and it's very simple if someone
says I don't have a God then where wherever you get your law from is your
substitute God whether it's a man or what we know anything else or a system
that becomes your operating system God's provide operating systems we should
make a t-shirt like that that sounds like a good idea something we could have
at Ocelli and the Greek comm at some point in the future is maybe a t-shirt
that says God provides or gods provide it would have to be plural gods I that's
why I corrected myself quickly God's provide operating systems for you so
that would be that would be a wonderful sort of thought-provoking yeah great
sure and they're also they do have names you know a name is a direct
communication a sound that someone answers to so when someone says God
that's a Teutonic Old Norse term that means the Sun when in English right so
it's quite interesting again the adversary at work and thrown in with
the censorship and and eventually people will understand that they shouldn't take
this entire human experience personally meaning the negative part of it and by
the way the more you study the more you notice the things that you thought were
positive are actually negative because there is a saying somewhere I believe
paraphrasing says that with with knowledge increasing sort of suffering
increase so you're not going to be happy camper and you're not going to make
friends learning the truth regardless of how many times people say they want it
when they actually act on it they will find themselves quite alone but yeah
these these things are about the gods they do have names and yeah this is the
next level of study just like when you say army it's just not one soldier and we
discover there are many guess what all those soldiers also have many names as
well correct yes and some of them function better than others some of them
actually achieve their goals and some of them do not there are many different
levels and layers to that particular onion so same thing applies here I
believe it's interesting just to say it this way we've gotten away so far with
12 episodes discussing these things on this level and we haven't been branded as
religious nuts or Bible thumpers or anything like that or even Satanists I'm
not saying that we should be but I believe it's because we're giving a
lucid sober explanation on this reality that can almost not be found anywhere
else and not to toot our own horn but I think sometimes you just got to say
listen folks if you're listening we've thrown together basically all of these
episodes are basically you know college course level that you know
condensing down years of college study just to a mere two hours well that's
true and actually we are just about at the end of what I believe I would count
as episode 13 and here we are you know that unlucky number allegedly you want
to give an opinion which I rarely do but historically there's many reasons why
13 is supposedly unlucky but one of the earliest accounts I found out was
across the land of Judea about 2,000 years ago when these 13 men approached a
village or a town it turned they turned the town inside out and you know what I
mean by 13 men in Judea because there were 12 and the one people keep
forgetting there was if you were approached by these folks there were
you you saw at the distance 13 men coming your way and your town or village
was never the same right absolutely correct of course you'll have to do a
little bit of homework there to find out exactly what that means although it
won't take very long if you just examine it quite plain that's one of the earliest
accounts that I've found in you there's other accounts about that number but this
is one of the earliest and I think first in time is first in line so well
there you go of course people do stick to the idea of the Friday the 13th you
know allegations about the Templars and things like that but you know it seems
as though things that get repeated more and more often also appear to to stand
up to scrutiny after after some time although well maybe I should take that
back because there's still a lot of stupidity being repeated over and over
again out there as well and what they're trying to do is memorialize the birth
let's just use place plain slave speak here of this care biblical character
and if one studies what he said he actually when he was asked did you come
to unite and he said unite I came to divide and I will divide with the sword
daughter against mother-in-law father against son and brother against brother
and then later on to paraphrase and he says I will bring terror upon you and he
also said that you have been better off to have been in Sodom and Gomorrah than
what you're going to be getting later so I don't know this is this is what's been
memorialized about this person no wonder they can't find anything that they think
they know about in anything else and that's maybe maybe that's why they're not
looking at the text it's quite shocking to see what's in there and how contrary
it is to the character that's been portrayed and the interesting part is
how many times have we said on the show that it is easier to find the nuclear
launch codes of a country's arsenal than to discuss any biblical situation
or any biblical character well that is the truth and and regardless of how
things are memorialized you know if you don't bother to read them you're not
going to learn anything so when someone approaches you about any biblical
subject ask them first do they have the nuclear launch codes and if they say no
then don't even bother listening to what they're going to say I'm serious and by
the way just for austerity the nuclear launch codes up until recently were zero
zero zero zero zero zero I kid you not and the reason why they had them as all
eight zeros was because they're supposed to change them every day but the command
said that would confuse the young boys in the silos and so let's just keep it at
zero Wow kind of like kind of like a box or something else that's programmable
when you first get it in most cases it comes with all zeros on it seems to be
the simplest thing to and the reason why we the all zeros ties in and why I use
that now this is a public joke now is because if anyone comes to you saying
that they want to discuss anything biblical at this point because I've
looked at what's out there you're going to get zero sorry guys you're gonna have
to do it on yourself and check on it well there you go and actually any
knowledge that you're going to gain is going to require some work that's the
way it is and this is the end of episode 13 and please people remember when you
go to visit Ocelli calm Ocelli in the Greek calm or American freedom radio
calm don't blame any of the websites these are merely the reports folks
thank you Greek thanks Chuck I'm telling you you gotta support American freedom
radio because this government is getting out of hand
Wall Street won't run my money the CIA are cutting into my drug running and my
gun running big pharma psychotropic drugs and making my customers commit
suicide before my hitmen can even whack them and then they get depressed and get
prescribed psychotropic drugs and commit suicide too they're trying to become the
biggest game in town when you're paying protection money you don't even get
productive I got unpaid taxes and if I can't find the money the IRS are gonna
take my tops I got a mandatory flu vaccine and now I'm autistic I'm a part
of the vaccine reaction and the doctor told me to forget about it what have I
ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully there's only one way to
get the government off our backs and that's to support American freedom radio
capiche so what are you gonna do you're gonna go to American freedom radio calm
and give them some legal tender they can't refuse
news and information you can trust this is American freedom radio freedom
freedom American freedom radio radio American freedom radio nutritious food
is real body armor it builds muscle burns fat improves digestion and feeds
the entire body the nutrients it needs did you know the US government banned the
hemp plant from growing in the United States and classified it as a schedule
one drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant people have been confused about
this plan for over 80 years and many still don't know what hemp is so now you
know hemp is not marijuana and marijuana is not him they are different varieties
of the same species hemp USA org wants the world to know these basic facts and
to help people understand that him protein powder is the best-kept health
secret you need to know about remember him protein powder contains 53% protein
is gluten-free anti-inflammatory non-gmo and is loaded with nutrients call 888
910 4367 888 910 4367 and see what our powder seeds and oil can do for you only
at hemp USA org what is the big deal about swearing to God in the first place
why does swearing to God mean you're gonna tell the truth wouldn't affect me
if they said to me you swear to tell the truth the whole truth another but the
truth to help me God I'd say yeah I'll tell you about as much truth as the
people who wrote that Bible how do you like that
swearing to God is kid stuff swearing to God doesn't mean anything swearing on
the Bible doesn't mean anything you know why because Bible or no Bible God or no
God if it suits their purposes people are gonna lie in court the police do it
all the time
yes they do it's part of their job to protect to serve and to commit perjury
whenever it supports the state's case swear on the Bible is just one more way
of controlling people and keeping them in line and it's one more thing that
holds us back as a species you're listening to American freedom radio dot
com the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate
constructive dialogue with true independence the freedom to broadcast
the truth is not free at all so what is American freedom radio worth to you the
empowering information with fun honest and pure integrity behind it provides an
example to follow friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that
pulls no punches the host sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their
duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength wisdom and
loyalty the founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your
views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media now it's
time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of
America be as generous with us as we've been with you click on the donate banner
at American freedom radio dot-com or volunteer by emailing American freedom
radio dot-com vaccine psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included no
rules no rules no taboo topics taboo topics no fear of doom no fear of doom
we are our American freedom radio American freedom radio