American Freedom Radio presents the only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as O'Joe and the Rick.
Do not attempt to adjust your listening device.
We are in control of the conversation, the sensation, and the mobilization of the sonic entity.
It is Ocelli in the Greek and we are broadcasting live from American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Ah, you know, I just thought I would throw that one in there because I was very tempted to come up with something that sounded like the old Outer Limits TV show
to try and describe this show at one point to create sort of a, oh, I don't know, a mix, a sound module.
You know, I was thinking about doing that, but honestly, you know, why?
Why go back over the old concept? Right.
Although I still still find it humorous anyway.
I'm doing great. Can you hear me? I'm coming through. All right.
Oh, yeah. Actually, you probably sound better than I do. So.
OK, that's great. Yeah. No, it's good, man. It's just it's coming together.
This is the third time we're meeting. And, yeah, last time we met, we discussed probably discussing constitution or constitutions or what condition your constitution is in.
Yeah. So, yeah. Mm hmm.
You know, and by constitution, of course, we're not talking about your general overall well-being or anything like that.
No, no. Well, maybe we are.
Anyway, getting back to it, there's always, always lots of debate in what they call the alternative media stream about the Constitution.
It's mentioned in passing in the mainstream. This is what is done all the time.
Right. Loads of arguments and pontifications about this particular document.
Is it a living document? Is it a sacrosanct document that makes sense for the current time?
Did it make sense when they first, you know, drafted the thing, et cetera, et cetera?
I mean, this is one of those things that rages on in debate regarding, well, political things that are American for certain.
And as you pointed out, I mean, there's certainly more than one constitution.
But hey, since we are broadcasting from American Freedom Radio, we could begin with the alleged constitution of the alleged United States of what was allegedly America.
And yes, I do overuse that word because, well, it's fun anyway.
You could look at all of them, Chuck. You could look at Russia.
I've been looking at Australia, Russia, United Arab Emirates.
And they all read like a business plan, like a real generic boilerplate business plan. Right.
And what does that mean? It's like someone says, give me a business plan and I'll fund you. Right.
OK, just throw something together by tomorrow. So we have something at the meeting.
That's the feeling you get when you read these documents. And they're not as profound.
They don't set a precedent. I mean, people think they do.
And here's the thing. If we're I would rather stop speaking right now and run elevator music for the next one hour and 56 minutes.
If we're going to discuss anything the way it's been discussed, because the way these things have been discussed have not helped anyone at all.
Well, that's right. It's all been counterproductive.
All of these debates about language that most people don't understand.
Again, things are quite well hidden in plain sight. And just taking a look at the it does speak like it's a draft of bullet points.
Yep. Right. It's very minor. It's actually a very minor in its intent of authority as well.
You notice most constitutions don't even have enforcement.
They say, well, if you do this, you know, then we can impeach you.
And that's about it. But they do have a lot of other they disclose quite a bit about how mundane they really are.
So, you know, with that said, can we go into the way we, I guess, always like to look at things objectively.
Imagine we just landed on this planet and we had a, you know, found out they have constitutions and such.
Not just the U.S., but, you know, we can get into that because that one's one of the most interesting ones, by the way.
But we could see we just got here to this planet. We look at the Constitution and we read it.
And we look at what they're actually how people are behaving in the legal society or the society at large and how they consider it.
And you'll see that it's in today's times, let's say today, being lawfully around the 22nd day of the eighth month by the pope's calendar, what they call October 17th, 2015.
Yeah. I didn't even bother to mention the date. Right. Because why bother?
But we did anyway. You would find that these things are relatively irrelevant in the minds of most.
Even though we said they are discussed and they have been bantered about in various communities, alternative mainstream, what have you.
And one can, again, come to the conclusion to see that there's a harsh debate if one states that they're irrelevant because you've got sides that have deified it and its writers.
And then you've got the other side that says it is irrelevant in today's date. So, yeah, we'll cover both sides.
And it's an issue that should be discussed the way I believe we're going to do it tonight. And it has never been discussed this way.
Well, right. And let's begin with that because, I mean, it does smack of being a document of dogmatic practice.
It just it looks to me like a religious document if I take a step back.
However, there's a problem here because I don't really see the deity being mentioned directly.
Right. It sort of is. If you if you if you're good with the language, you'll see justice is the deity personified personified by all of the alleged legal society buildings.
Well, right. But Greek is supposed to be a Christian nation.
Well, then, you know, do you want to open? That's a big can of worms, literally.
Yeah. But I just wanted to allude to it because this is the thing is, you know, quite, quite tightly.
Do people grip their Bibles and their constitutions in one in each hand, both with white knuckles as they as they spew quite a bit about what they believe the the coming apocalypse is going to be, et cetera, et cetera.
And generally speaking, they know nothing of the documents that they grip onto for.
Well, to borrow a popular phrase for dear life. Right.
Generally or specifically, what's interesting is, you know, if you know anyone who owns a sporting goods store, you ask them, you know, do you sell a lot of baseball bats?
And they'll say, well, you know, I happen to sell a lot of baseball bats. Why do you ask?
Well, the question is, how many of those baseball bats that you sell are actually being used for baseball?
And then they stop and think for a moment. That's a really good question. I'd say less than half.
Why? Because baseball bats make a good, effective, inexpensive club that anyone can access. Right.
So and that's how these documents are being used.
You know, it's there's a there's a well, the biblical text takes much higher precedent only by anyone with a legal or lawful mind.
And I want to define those things, too. We'll find that it has a higher claim.
Nowhere in the Constitution does it show an entity or anyone stating they created everything right, including mankind in the heavens and the earth, as it does in Scripture.
So anyone who is going to analyze these documents is going to say, wow, what these claims need to be examined or rebutted or something.
They can't just stand there. Right now, the claims that are made in the Constitution, like I said earlier, it looks like someone's drafting a business plan.
And without really getting into all that, you know, just just, you know, go to a search engine on a boilerplate business plan and then pull up any constitution of any country.
Including the US and just hold them both next to each other.
And you'll see they read very similarly. Yeah, that's true.
And in addition to that, I mean, you have an agreement being sort of ushered forward in the document to begin with.
I mean, you're supposed to be what? Endowed by your creator with these rights.
And then there's this other word that that people begin to argue about. Right.
Immediately following that. Well, that's when you hold the Declaration of Independence together with the with the Constitution, which kind of flows together.
Of course, they always leave out in terms of America or the United States.
And you have to say or because they're not the same thing.
The United States being Washington, D.C., is they've completely left out what's called the Articles of Confederation,
which formed the initial union and where it was a much more lawful precedent type of document.
So, yeah. And also when people say constitutional rights, there really are no rights in the Constitution.
That would be the Bill of Rights. So again, so again, when you when you brought up the you're endowed with rights,
let's say Declaration of Independence, Bill of Rights, U.S. Constitution, they're all thrown together.
They're distinct. But from, I'd say, the same group of people or generally the same group of people,
they've left out, I repeat myself again, they've really left out the Articles of Confederation and it's never been repealed.
But it doesn't matter. Even if the Constitution was repealed, it wouldn't change anything.
Well, that's it. And that's the thing. I mean, trying to put this in proper context,
you want to grab onto these other documents and and sort of lay out the entire field because then it makes a little more sense.
But like you said, there's a great many things left out of it.
And, you know, well, all right. Now we're going into some odd areas here.
And again, we should probably step back and become, you know, once again, the the objective observer.
Exactly. And the objectivity of it is, look, we're here now. Let's discuss what's going on.
It's so simple to say there's so much confusion. Avoid these species called the legal society.
Anyone or anything that deals with that. And we want to just maybe give a quick definition.
Do you know how many people with a show of hands know what the difference is between a lawyer and an attorney?
And most likely everyone. No one's raising their hands. Right.
Because they've interchanged those words to mean the same thing. And they don't.
And just really quickly, an attorney, let's do it by alphabetically, is someone who is appointed to handle your affairs.
Period. I've got, you know, a pig farm and I need the trough filled at three o'clock.
And can you go there and tell the guys what to do in my behalf?
I just gave you power of attorney to go feed the pigs. It's got nothing to do with law. Never did.
It represents it's there to stand in place over an appointment.
And in Western society, that's started out when you had the indentured servants or the serfs in a feudal state.
You you had no right rights of inheritance.
So what they did was when it came time to sort out your own business and get permission from the Lord, the feudal lord,
you couldn't stand before him without having an appointed attorney.
And you walked in and you explained that you're, you know, you're ready to have some things bequeathed to you to inherit.
And they looked at you and chuckled and they said, well, we get a third.
And they gave you a swift kick in the butt, kicked you out and all laughed.
They took a third of it and they said, hey, listen, next time someone dies, come back and see us again.
Right. And that's all they did. Pretty much.
Now, the lawyers, those were people that were skilled in practice of law.
They knew the law. In other words, again, the laws that were decreed to function as a society, let's say, if you could call it that.
And these were people that were would be amicus curia, I believe is the Latin term, like the next friend in court,
someone you brought in to consult you in a matter regarding the law.
And if just to show what is really going on from these particular characters that have been thrusted upon society until they start sorting out these basic things,
they will never be able to approach the whole concept of the Constitution or the lawfulness or legality of it without understanding the basis of those that are purveying it, supposedly,
because they interchange lawyer and attorney and they're not the same.
And just to add, attorneys don't know anything about law.
There's an unwritten rule even today that if you're an attorney, you're to stay away from laws.
And I've met, I'd say, more than 100 of them and try to discuss a lawful or legal matter with them, and they can't.
They always have to rush to the book, even the simplest thing.
They don't know any law and neither do the judges, by the way.
There's an unwritten rule for them not to do that.
The simple reason is that if you do study as an attorney, you will notice that no one is doing anything that's written.
And eventually you're going to call foul and you are kicked out of the club.
So it's better not to know anything and just go along with the game as the game changes, you see.
And just to back this up, if anyone wants to even go to the Harvard Law School website, go to their course catalog.
This is Harvard Law School, and you'll see their course catalog curriculum.
And all they have, it says administrative law, advanced corporate transactions, advanced clinical practice, and advanced negotiation techniques.
So when you're in the back of the alley or whatever, you know how to deal with it, right?
And that's all. There's no law at all.
Yeah, that's the thing, is that which they refer to as legal or being part of the law is really about negotiation and contracting.
Now, contracting is something that is lawful, right?
But the problem here is that it's sort of the…
Well, legal pertains.
Well, the term legal means it pertains to law.
That's why attorneys are at law and lawyers are in law.
You know, are you in the house or at the house?
Are you in the ice cream parlor or at the ice cream parlor?
Big difference.
So this is…
Now, the chances of these two definitions being sorted out and having the critters sorted out, you know what I mean?
You're not going to find any lawyers, even though the attorneys advertise themselves as such.
If you actually try to practice as a lawyer, you'll probably be thrown in prison, you know?
Yeah, most likely, or if you… yeah.
So what do you think the chances are of people actually sorting out the definition of a lawyer and an attorney in the next day, week, year, two or five?
Probably next to zero.
Oh, on a massive scale? Yeah, I would consider that very close to zero, yeah.
And they're going to say, Chuck, Greek, these are semantics.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Okay, well, you know, there's a big difference between, you know, get me a shoe and get me an ice cream cone, right?
Well, that's just semantics.
Why did you bring me the shoe?
I meant ice cream cone.
So why don't you say what you mean and mean what you say.
Oh, you mean…
It doesn't matter if we mean what we say or say what we mean.
Hmm, another discussion.
So until the legal, the law and the attorney versus the lawyer is sorted out,
you're not going to get a rational debate or outcome discussing the Constitution.
And hence going back to let's play elevator music, you know,
if we're going to talk about it the way everyone else has at this point.
Well, yeah, because that's the point, is that people start talking about it.
Immediately the next part of the conversation is usually, well, these are my rights.
I have always thought to myself, my initial gut reaction to that is, according to what?
Because where in the Constitution are you mentioned?
You're not contracted to have these rights, specifically, right?
You know, this is always, it's just a weird thing to watch it happen.
And people do grip onto it very much like they do their own Bibles,
where they think the Easter bunny is relevant and, you know,
and Santa Claus is still a good idea.
I mean, that's really what it comes down to.
This has nothing to do with that thing you're clutching in your hand, what you're saying.
And meanwhile, it also speaks to me as a document handed down by those who had control.
Because after all, you can't give something or grant something to someone
unless you possessed it in the first place.
I mean, this is an interesting kind of part of it as well, don't you think?
Like a renter or an owner.
Most people don't know that they're renting and it's right on their deed
that they're holding it in tenancy, as a tenant.
But, you know, the good example here would be what Wolfgang Goethe said about 300 years ago,
and I said something similar, but let's give a paraphrase, both of us, let's say.
You need not visit an insane asylum to discover disordered spirits
because the earth is the insane asylum of the universe.
Now, I used to always use the metaphor that coming to earth is a cross
between an insane asylum and a pig farm.
Now, you have to visit both to get a pretty good idea of how people are going to react to certain topics
that they are stubborn about keeping their own opinion or belief on
without having any reference material.
And what ends up happening is like going to a construction site and saying,
this guy is a good carpenter, and I said, why does he look so upset?
So I go up to him and I say, what's wrong?
And he says, I've been cutting this board three times already and it's still too short.
Yeah, well, there you go.
You're going in the wrong way, you know.
You're running north when you want to get to Antarctica and wondering why you're not getting there.
I mean, this is what's happening.
Yeah, and to demonstrate more insanity, according to some people these days,
if you keep running, you'll fall off the edge, right?
So anyway, yeah.
So you see, there's another example, you know, without bringing up the flat earth people.
So what does one do?
You and I can rationally discuss the Constitution in our minds,
but once you include three, four, five, or ten people, especially a Harvard graduate,
the whole thing goes to pot, goes away.
Because this is basically an insane situation.
This is probably going to kill our ratings, by the way, but I'm just saying this is not something.
But we're saying we're going to discuss it because we're going to discuss it in a practical way.
What is really going on?
And that is easy to explain.
You can explain the Constitution without reading it now, at this point at least,
because let's say we've read it, and we just look at the surroundings, how it applies.
And it doesn't.
But we can discuss what does apply, like you said earlier.
They clutched the Constitution.
I think you and I had a discussion about years ago.
It was said that when the house was burning down, they ran in and grabbed two things.
One was the U.S. Constitution, and the other was the Bible.
And that's, I guess, the myth or the culture of what people want to walk away with feeling good about.
Yeah, but I wonder sometimes if it is merely to assert their own supremacy
because they have the connection to the divine,
and without actually internalizing the meaning of these things.
Let's set the Bible for a moment because the Constitution, again, we'll go back to it,
but I think the lawyer and attorney difference is a good place to start.
That's like really getting the stuff out between your brain, like mental floss.
It's like, no, a lawyer and an attorney is not the same.
It doesn't matter how many times they put it around that you need a lawyer,
and it ends up being an attorney.
It's not interchangeable, just like the soul and the spirit are not interchangeable,
and dogs and cats are not interchangeable, two distinct creatures.
Yeah, so the biblical text is a good one because this is the future, by the way.
Right now, you can't discuss it. How do I know?
Because during the darkest time of the year, they've got this fat guy with a white beard in a red suit,
and these people have professed to be Bible believers.
So, again, you cannot discuss it as long as they're doing that en masse,
but there is going to be more of a debate about ending that practice in the future.
But on another note, people think they have the biblical text.
They don't. The King James Version is a version.
The biblical text, which is currently preserved in Hebrew and Greek,
has yet to be translated to this day.
It has not been translated outside of Hebrew and Greek.
Sorry, guys, and it's very easy to see.
You have all these versions, and all the languages are based on those versions,
and they're all based on King James.
Sorry. Sorry to tell you, but you ain't got it.
It's very easy to catalog over 5,000 mistakes in half the book already.
So you don't have it. You don't even have it.
Right. That certainly includes your Good News for Modern Man,
which is more like the Americanized edition of the King James Bible as well.
And that's not even in there.
I mean, one day we should do a show.
It'll be just reading out a list of about 500 words that are not in the Bible
that are commonly considered to be in there, you know,
like the word holy or good news or Old Testament, New Testament, God,
or this or that, you know, in singular form.
None of that is in the text of preservation at all.
So, yeah, you don't even have the text.
And, you know, then there's the ridiculous aspect of how it's turned into a talisman
or a rabbit's foot, like it's supposed to mean good luck or something like that,
like when they go to court, they tell you put your hand on the Bible
or a politician is sworn in.
Right? You ever notice that?
Oh, yeah, absolutely. It's a talisman at this point.
Yeah, rabbit's foot. Yeah.
It's what the actually, if anyone has ever read it,
you're not supposed to swear on anything anyway,
unless it's for a specific vow that is originated in a certain way.
And without getting into that,
now here's the conundrum just to show how ridiculous they are.
Let's say you go and someone says in authority, you know, a court or politicians,
you know, swear on this Bible.
No, well, see, I've got it here on a thumb drive.
I'm going to swear on this thumb drive instead.
Can I do that?
Well, no, because it's not a Bible per se, right?
Although it does contain the same information.
Yeah, because a Bible, after all, is simply a book.
You know, that's always fascinating as well to me that, you know, just the book.
It means book, they say, Biblos.
But if you actually do a little more homework on that,
you'll find that Biblos was an island in the Aegean,
and they were famous for their printing and papermaking and parchment
and, you know, pulp and parchment manufacture.
So when ancient texts were being distributed throughout the world
and you wanted a quality product, you went to Biblos and the island of Biblos,
and they had the best quality.
You could order anything, you know, animal parchment, pulp, papyrus pulp,
wood pulp, hemp pulp.
Even if you wanted something on human skin, they would offer that as well.
They had inks of blood, inks of shellfish, inks of plant.
Yeah, they were the cat's meow of the printing world back in those days,
and that's all it is.
Biblos is an island in the Aegean.
And they were so popular, it's come to mean book,
just like Kleenex means tissue, even though it's a company name, you see, or a brand.
Right, right.
So this is just a little tidbit of history.
But, again, remember, this is an insane place to be.
And why am I using strong language?
Well, because, listen, folks, when the criminality becomes high,
it requires strong language.
And the level of misdemeanor, which means bad behavior of humanity at large,
regarding any form of law or deified text or whatever,
is in a form of bad conduct and bad taste at this time still.
Right.
I mean, even when you break down the word misdemeanor,
I mean, obviously the word demeanor would speak to the condition or attitude of someone,
this kind of thing, and to miss that, you know,
obviously it means that if something is misunderstood,
then it is not being understood.
So you are outside of the demeanor that is supposed to be.
This is, you know, obvious there in the words.
Now, a lot of people might be saying to themselves,
hey, they said they were going to discuss the Constitution.
They haven't really gotten to it.
Well, do you like elevator music?
Would you like elevator music instead?
That's the thing.
We can just, you know, go quiet right now.
Yeah.
We will, though.
But here's the thing about all of them, when I say them, all of the Constitutions.
They're written as a boilerplate trust document.
They're written as a boilerplate business plan because there is a plan
and there is a business behind it, right?
Here's the thing.
This might be a little offbeat.
A lot of people in the patriot movement are complaining that the government is a corporation.
So what?
Big deal.
The question is, are they a benevolent or malevolent corporation, right?
Are they acting lawfully or are they acting unlawfully?
You see, it's not that a corporation is bad.
Yeah.
Well, see, but they would say that this is not intended to be a corporation
and it's supposed to be, that we are the sovereign people who are supposed to be in charge, right,
which is not the way a corporate structure would work.
You don't have, I mean, there are some newer types of corporate structures out there
which are run by the employees, which are run by the individuals,
but, you know, Apple is not run by iPods, though.
This is the thing.
A benevolent one to be an employee of, as I heard, this is secondhand information, is Google.
When you work at a Google campus, you show up, they'll wash your car,
they'll cook you gourmet food, they'll do your laundry while you're working.
They have massage, you know, you can do a spa during work.
It's like going to the Bellagio or something.
Right.
This is where all those, you know, infamous sort of imageries of, well, gee,
they have ping pong tables and games set up for you to engage in
just to sort of break your stress during your work day, this kind of thing.
I mean, it's still the same ideal, but a little more pleasant from a creature comfort standpoint.
So that would be benevolent from the standpoint of the employee.
Correct.
But overall, the idea of a corporation, and again, going back to the U.S. Constitution on the second section,
now, we can beat the first section to death when it talks about justice.
They're here to establish justice, by the way.
You know, in the preamble it says to, you know, the 17th word is justice.
And anyone research what that is, and it's personified,
it's the revival of the ancient goddess religion, which is very cruel.
Not because it's feminine.
It just so happens this entity, this particular god, is a very cruel god, and it happens to be a female.
Well, I'll argue with you, though, that I will argue with you on this point,
that I do believe that the most cruel things that are in creation are of the feminine.
Maybe that's just my own life experience speaking.
Well, here's the thing.
If you're at a party and you enter, let's say, a group of men speaking,
there's a certain cordiality and, you know, etiquette.
And if you're a woman and you enter a group of women speaking, it's very different.
I agree, there is a level of cruelty there that they would say things that men would never say to each other
upon the first ten seconds of meeting.
I've noticed that.
But I believe that's cultural as well.
It may be. I mean, I always...
Western culture.
Yeah, I think so.
And I always like to point to, you know, I love cartoons.
They're just a way for me to release tension because they're a way for me to engage in something
that is entirely meaningless and yet keeps me occupied.
The thing is that when I look at, like, Family Guy, and they were talking about creating TV shows,
and they said to one group of guys, go find a group of guys and get them to fight and film it.
And that's a TV show.
And then he turns to another group of guys and says, go find a group of women and get them to, never mind,
just find a group of women and they'll start fighting.
You know, there is a cultural difference between the, as you said, the cordiality that is typical in the two genders,
you know, in the two genders interacting within themselves.
But anyway, either way, I think the nature of the feminine is actually to be a bit more cruel in general.
So I don't see why this is a surprise to some people, though.
We're speaking candidly, and it might be out of what people are used to hearing.
But again, just to be objective, this is a particular spiritual entity, let's call it,
and it happens to be female, and it happens to be anti-life.
And if you don't see how the justice system has been promoting things that are promoting more death than life,
that's another discussion, I guess, how the entire society has followed it along.
And by the way, in the biblical text, even in the poor versions that you have,
there are a lot of warnings of a revival of Mystery Babylon, this goddess religion, you see.
So that is another place to see a reference on.
And personified persistently by things like the Statue of Liberty, you know, Semiramis,
the District of Semiramis, I make that joke sometimes when discussing the District of Columbia,
you know, which Columbia is also related to the feminine ancient goddesses.
You know, I mean, it's just on and on.
Yeah, Tanya is another one, Columbia.
Yeah, and that District of Semiramis is also modeled after an Egyptian necropolis, meaning city of the dead.
Right.
You know, here's the big secret, really, is that although from their mouths they say they are Christians,
from their mouths they say they're Jews, from their mouths they say they're Muslims, Hindus, Buddhists, whatever,
quite honestly and quite candidly, what we have here is the evidence of the religion of death itself
constantly being purveyed by a whole lot of these institutions, in my estimation.
Or do you think that that's oversimplifying it?
No, that's exactly what it is.
And it's sort of backwards, because let's remember, none of these religions do anything that's in any of the texts,
or know anything that's in any of the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
So what's happened is those that have structured the world religions have watched the population
and simply catered to their desires.
And they've structured these religions, all the ones above mentioned,
according to the people's behavior and geographic area.
That's why when you look at Christianity in Eastern Europe, it's different than the Christianity in Rome,
different than the Christianity in Northern Europe, different than the Christianity in Midwest U.S.,
different than the Christianity in South America.
Because all they did was look at various geographical practices that were done for thousands of years,
tweaked it a little bit with a couple of characters that you will not find in the Bible, or historically,
and now they're Christian and they put the shingle up.
And the same thing in the Middle East with the Muslim world.
The same thing with the quote-unquote Jewish world.
You have the Sephardic Jews, you have the ultra-right, they've got their base in Brooklyn here,
the Ashkenazi, based on whatever region they live in, their custom would change.
And it's the same thing with Islam.
You have all these various sects based on geographic areas, what they had been doing for thousands of years.
Because even if there was a concerted effort, let's say there were a handful of people that had read any of these texts
and tried to put them on the people, they wouldn't understand them anyway.
So they said, just do this, that, and that, and you're fine.
Just put the shingle up, and now you've got a team.
And this is the harsh reality about it.
And in the future, what's going to happen, starting actually in just a few years,
is people, when this period of tension ends, they're going to actually pick up these books and start reading them.
They're going to say, there's no Santa Claus here, there's no Easter Bunny here.
Nowhere in here does it say a woman needs to cover her face the way we do.
And nowhere here does it say that we can't have a hamburger in India.
You see?
Very interesting.
It's going to be quite a change.
Also, you know, you won't find where they have women have to wear wigs so that they don't show their hair.
You know, there is also a body.
I don't see a dress code in the Bible either, by the way.
I don't know.
Maybe I missed it.
There's no specific code, but there is a sense of covering one's private parts.
And it's the only thing you'll find in the, I'm not going to say the word, but the text of Islam,
is that the only thing regarding women's dress, there's only one little small section,
is if she's married, she needs to cover her genitalia so another man doesn't see it.
Now look, even if you're a staunch atheist and you're married,
I don't think you want anyone looking at your wife's genitalia because it's uncovered.
So, I mean, this has nothing to do with being radical or a religion of war or a religion of peace or anything.
It has to do with the most basic fundamental concept of decency.
Yeah, and plus, after all, there are sanitary concerns as well.
So, you know, it's just a practicality regardless of what your spiritual attitude might be at the end.
On this particular given day, it's kind of irrelevant.
It just seems to be a sensible thing to want to keep one's genitals covered to protect oneself and maybe others.
Right, and the reason we're saying this is the only reference in that book that they're using supposedly,
which none of them have ever read, because if they did, they wouldn't associate themselves with that group.
So what they've all done, all the religions, have taken the most negative attributes
that are listed in the books that they allegedly subscribe to and turned them into their highest practices.
Right?
Like, for example, again, in the Middle Eastern world, if anyone does some research,
the woman's image and face and body being completely covered was reserved for a certain profession in the ancient world.
And if you went out into public wearing or looking like that, you were called upon to perform in that profession.
And some call it the world's oldest profession.
Yeah, which, believe it or not, I mean, if you take a look at, you know, in what they call the Old Testament,
the story there where someone is completely covered, what's that?
Yeah, Genesis 38, for example.
Exactly, that's where I was going with it.
You know, the woman is completely covered.
What is she doing in the specific area where she meets the man?
Well, you know, look it up.
She is behaving as a prostitute.
Yes, and we are not a prostitute who would keep themselves covered in that way.
And as you said, if you're wearing the uniform, you might be called upon to perform.
That's what it was.
So they've taken their worst attributes, yeah, and glorified them as being righteous.
Yeah, this is certainly not the act of someone who is, well, let's say pious, which is an interesting word as well.
But you can refer to it as that, I guess.
And this is not what it's meant to be.
It's completely, as a matter of fact, reversed.
You know, is every woman wearing a burka supposed to be a prostitute?
Well, no, not according to the customs and practices that were put in place.
But once again, it's because they're not reading the text.
Now, somebody might say, well, this sounds like a biblical discussion as opposed to a discussion of the constitutions.
But here's the problem.
The same exact deformity in the meaning of the document, in the actual reality of the document and its application, persists, don't they?
Pretty much.
If you look across the board, though, it's with all of the religions at this point that they're doing.
They're persisting on things that they shouldn't be doing.
But let's just jump back to perhaps maybe the Constitution for just a second here.
Because as we just showed how there's a misunderstanding in the concept of the religion using a particular body of knowledge,
known as their holy book, let's say.
And by the way, you'll never find the word holy in any of those texts.
The term that's translated to holy is the word set apart, you know, in terms of setting something apart as special.
But in regard to the Constitution, the interesting part about the insanity of it when you bring it up is by going into a court.
I've seen this myself several times where people brought up a Constitution and the judge says, you cannot use that here.
And anyone that's been around these circles that study it, because you hear the horror stories, right?
The judge will say, if you mention the Constitution again, I'll put you in jail, right?
And if you watch someone being railroaded in court, for example, which is normal,
and you ask the attorney, well, why didn't you say anything, or we want to appeal this, or what are you doing here?
And he says, well, I'm here to make sure your constitutional rights are not being violated.
So this is really twisted, bizarre use of the Constitution within the legal society,
which is also preventing people from really seeing its irrelevancy in that system.
And that's all you have right now to stand on, because they always go back to the Constitution.
So if it's deemed irrelevant in practice, in other words, look at what they do, not what they say.
They stress how important these documents are, but no one seems to stress them or enforce them or put any teeth behind it.
Now, there's the popular side about, let's say, the amendments, the Second Amendment, perhaps.
That is nothing more than preventing a mob from happening.
See, the people will say, oh, wow, they're really into the thing about the guns, so we better leave it alone or we might really have violence.
So it can be used. In other words, it's too inconsistent to rely on.
But, yes, it has been used as a talking point or even to make big political maneuvers.
So it's too inconsistent.
It's like if you go to a restaurant for the first time and the meal is good and you tell your friends it was great to eat here
and you go back to patronize them again and the food sucks, it's a terrible meal.
Now you look really bad and you want consistency.
You know, you want to go there, you want it to be consistently good or consistently bad so you can know what to expect.
So what's happened in the past 200 and some odd years, no one really knows what to expect with these documents.
So that makes them very inconsistent and almost useless in that manner.
Technologically, we wouldn't be considering ourselves to be able to do much if we had, let's say,
a one out of ten chance that the lights will come on when you turn on the switch or you turn the key on an automobile, right?
We wouldn't consider it a benefit.
And it's the same with the religions, and the religions are tied into the same inconsistency.
So essentially, if we were just visiting this planet, we would say the people here are just nuts.
They're crazy.
So how do you add clarity to that?
Well, in mass, you can't.
We can discuss these things, but for sure, you can say two things.
One is what people are putting their hopes in, the religions and these political documents, is a total waste of time.
The second thing we could say is that it's not going to be a waste of time.
It's a terminal waste of time.
In other words, this false sense of hope that they have in their religion or their political documents will end in the near future.
And simply, it'll end because, very simply, they're going to actually stop what they're doing for ten minutes a day,
and they're going to actually go back and study these things on a mass level.
And that's going to be the real change.
It's going to be very simple.
Right.
And that's the beginning of it, actually.
It certainly is.
One of the persistent discussions, and I know I don't want to play the elevator music,
but one of the persistent discussions is the difference between a right and a privilege.
And I wonder if you want to kind of address that, because I always find that kind of fascinating.
You'll get different emotional responses from people based on their attitude.
I hate to use that word again, but their attitude regarding those two words in general.
Because what is a right and what is a privilege?
They're both wrong.
And they're both wrong.
It's actually backwards.
Do you want to do the worst one first or the better one first?
Well, let's do the worst first.
The worst is a right.
The reason why is because when you have freedom, which the only way to have real freedom, by the way,
and this might get us in trouble, is through anarchy.
And the term anarchy is a Greek word, and hardly anyone knows what it means, by the way.
It means arkos.
The second part means leader, and an means a without it.
And it doesn't mean no government.
It just means you have man and your god.
So each man is a king of his castle.
In order to have anarchy, you have to have a very highly educated population,
and each man would be the ruler of his domain and would be in full responsibility.
So in an anarchistic society, you would virtually have no crime, almost no crime whatsoever.
I mean, if something was stolen, there was a theft, it was like, oh, I remember when that happened ten years ago.
You have a very, let's just say, lawful society.
You can't have that.
Because you're not answering to a man-made body.
You're answering to a deity, right?
And we're not smoking anything, and we don't have imaginary friends,
but mankind will be surprised when that spiritual world starts to meld and become more overt with this one.
Okay, so there are no rights there.
So in that type of society, you have freedom as long as you don't do any harm,
because you're acting in full responsibility.
You're going to think more than once before you do anything wrong, you see?
So there you have freedom, right?
But if you do something wrong and now you lose your freedom, you go under rights.
You see, like years ago when there was a brawl at a bar or a fight, a big scene,
they arrested everyone, threw everyone in jail just to break up the fight,
and then they could sort out what happened, right?
Because if they only put a few people in jail and the other will continue fighting,
so it's to bring peace.
So everyone gets arrested and apprehended, and the ones that are liable
and have to pay back what wrong they've done, let's say, in simple terms,
they no longer have freedom and they go under rights.
Like you have a right to three hots and a cot, right?
You have a right to do this.
You have a right to do that.
So once your freedom is taken away, you go under rights.
So now you've heard of that, right?
You have a right to remain silent, right?
When was the last time you just commonly walked in public and said,
hey, how are you doing, man?
All right, good.
Just walking down the sidewalk going over to the shop over here.
Yeah, you have the right to remain silent.
What?
What are you talking about?
No one talks about that, right?
Yeah.
So, yeah, that's when you're at what you know you've lost your freedom
when you're talking about rights.
Now, privilege is different.
A privilege is where you have willingly enlisted yourself in a situation
where you've pledged an allegiance of your time or material or something,
like, let's say, going into the Navy when you have liberty, right?
When you go into port, you know,
you've actually pledged that you will be working for someone
or committing yourself to a task a good amount of your time
or a little bit of time when a leniency or a benefit or a bonus is given
where now you can be released from that task, but is the privilege.
So you're actually freer with a privilege than you are with a right.
And I know this sounds kind of twisted and crazy,
but one needs to start looking at what these things are.
You will see, for example, in the biblical text there are no rights.
You have laws, and if they're transgressed, then you balance the equation, right?
And then you go about your life freely.
There's no rights in any of the quote-unquote religious texts.
There's a concept in law that if we go back to the Constitution,
we can start meshing the Constitution and the Bible together.
But, yeah, it sounds kind of twisted because of the way it's been advertised.
Well, yeah, it sounds almost exactly adverse,
the inverse, really, of what people generally expect.
Privileges, because they think of it as this is being granted to you,
so therefore that person has power over you.
But if you have a right, then that's something that you have no matter what
because of this one little word, which I've heard pronounced inalienable
or inalienable, and therefore this is an absolute right that cannot be taken.
But that's not true either.
No, because they say they're God-given rights, and they do two fatal mistakes there.
Well, one is direct, one is indirect.
The first direct fatal mistake is they fail to tell you which God.
The second indirect mistake is if you're presuming it's the biblical God,
you won't find any rights in there.
So, again, fire up the engines, let's get off this planet.
They're all crazy.
Well, there you go, because, once again, these rights are granted to you by God,
essentially, by your Creator.
You're endowed by your Creator.
Well, that is an interesting topic, considering that it doesn't exist in the text
that most people would refer to to describe the one God.
But, of course, that's a problem anyway, because there is more than one.
It doesn't necessarily mean that the guy that we're talking about in the biblical text,
because of that claim that is made there,
I created the Earth, the Heavens, the Universe, basically.
This would be the highest of the gods, I imagine.
That's what's being imparted to you.
Although, I've got to tell you, I do consider the possibility that
this is the highest one that bothers to communicate with us.
Well, the interesting part, these are all pluralities.
And, you know, it's funny when you ask a religious people,
and when I say not religious people, I don't even mean the laymen.
I'm talking about the scholars, right, that the people go to to get this information.
Ask them any religious scholar in any religion,
what makes the highest God the highest God?
And they don't know, and if you keep pushing the issue,
they start going into convulsions as if they're going to throw up their last meal.
They don't know. None of them do.
It's fascinating when you do that.
It's very simple if you read the text in context from beginning to end, right?
You know how, especially, let's talk about the Christian concept.
They always throw a verse at you, and it's kind of like discussing a movie,
and saying, well, did you, let's say, watch this movie at 1 minute and 42 seconds?
What did you see? I'm like, no one talks like that.
You either saw the movie or you didn't.
You can't discuss it if you haven't seen the film, right?
Yeah, so in the Christian realm, at least, when you're discussing all these things,
it just goes to pot very quickly. They don't know.
They don't know anything at all about it.
And I'll spill the beans. It's very simple, and it's not my belief for anyone to agree.
Just read the work and you'll see.
What makes the head god separate from all the others is that he is exempt from death.
All the other gods are subject to death.
And let's, just in a paraphrase, supposedly his son came here and he was killed, was he not?
And resurrected, so he was subject to death.
But this is all about families.
The things in scripture, the biblical text is interesting.
They've taken everything that was plural and made it singular,
and most things that were singular and made them plural.
So of course you're confused.
But from that point of view, there are no god-given rights, period.
There's just law.
And there is no Old and New Testament.
And there is no different god here and there.
It's just a failure of communication.
And just to lead back how they have you swear on the Bible,
and you pull out a USB and you want to swear on it.
It's the same information.
So the purpose of the biblical text or any text, it's a form of communication.
And if you're not familiar with the communication, it has no value whatsoever.
Unless you're into rabbit's feet and talismans and spell casting and all that other stuff.
And even spell casting requires precision.
But anyway.
Yes, it certainly does.
And when you look at the symbols of things, that's what they are.
They're not necessarily the representation of anything that is of legitimate lineage, let's just say.
And as we go to break, I love the comment in the chat room that we got.
Greek, your Bible sounds much more interesting than the King James Version.
So I've got to love that.
Thank you.
I'm taking that as the King James Version.
And we'll continue with this discussion in the second album.
This is Oteli in the Greek.
We'll be back.
American Institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth?
And none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant.
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein, and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powders.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
American Freedom Radio is back.
We're trying to become commercial free apart from a few honorable advertisers that we would give ad space to even if they couldn't pay us.
In this quest to deliver quality radio with very few annoying ads, we are now asking the listeners like you to open up and become partners with American Freedom Radio.
We all know the economy is controlled and a new system called the peer-to-peer economy is now within our grasp.
That means if you'd like this network with its incredible hosts and incredible information to be nothing but the content you want to hear,
then you must realize that you cannot be a part of it if you're just sitting on the sidelines watching.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and pledge your support today.
Donate according to your means.
Some can only afford $1 a month while others can afford $100 a month.
Regardless of the size of your contribution, it all adds up to keeping the network owners and the radio hosts housed and fed at the end of every month.
Thank you.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape, our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape, various pain-related healthcare costs, epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com, the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules, no taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information note the sonic entity known as Ocelli.
Apparently that particular bumper piece is a little too gothic for some listeners according to the chat room.
And we are Ocelli in the Greek broadcasting live on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
And yes, if you go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com, there is a donate banner there on the front page.
And we are listener supported.
That's the first thing.
The next thing is, just to let you know, there is a website now for this show.
It is a work in progress, but you can go there and there's a few things to play with, right?
And that is at, oddly enough, OcelliAndTheGreek.com.
All one word, OcelliAndTheGreek.com.
You probably know how to spell and the Greek.
Those are pretty common words, but my last name is spelled O-C-H-E-L-L-I.
So, OcelliAndTheGreek.com.
Anyway, the discussion we were having is, you know, very much centered around the Constitution and the biblical text.
Why not? So many other people do tie them together, and they do sort of make sense with one another.
Like I said, put things in context, right?
And I find it fascinating that, yeah, you like to...
I'm sure you find it amusing on occasion to sort of watch the squirming of a biblical scholar now and then.
That's easy.
Yeah, it sure is, because I used to do it as a child.
And you know how I did it?
Now, this is going to sound really childish, but remember, I was a child.
See, that's what that means.
Okay.
I used to say, listen, if you can prove to me that this particular idea that I'm going to tell you is false,
then I'll listen to everything else you have to say.
Otherwise, I'm not buying it.
And they'd say, okay, what is it?
You know, expecting probably something very simple like, you know, show me how God exists or something like that.
No, I would say to them, well, here's the thing.
I believe that the entire world around me is nothing more than a figment of my own imagination.
And if that is the case, you're not really here except for the fact that I somehow thought you up.
And so is everything else.
And therefore, why am I not the God of this universe I observe?
Good one.
Well, you know, look, out of the mouths of seven-year-olds, right, what are you going to do?
Now you know a little bit of the background as to why, you know,
one time my mother actually tried to get me to an exorcist.
But anyway, let's put all that aside.
Actually, just for a moment, let's not, because if one just reads the text, it has nothing to do with belief,
because remember, with any piece of information you pick up, it's a road, and there's a fork in the road.
On the left, it says this is false.
So there's no reason to beat it up, just leave it alone, do something else.
The fork on the right says, well, let's say it's validatable, so let's examine it, right?
So if we examine the biblical text, it has nothing to do with what you believe in.
You will find that there is the concept of creation, and there's a theme in there that man is part of a family
that is being developed through a certain process, and mankind will join that specific family
that will no longer be subject to death, just to tie it into the previous,
our last comment on the description of the Most High, let's say.
So in essence, you are expressing verbally to this particular species the concept of what is to come.
So in one sense, it's very accurate.
But in the current sense, when we can discern that we, let's say, discern the concept of material
and the concept of mind and soul, we would say that we're not at that point yet,
but there's nothing wrong with expressing the concept.
Well, right, and as a child, I sorted that out by basically saying everything is a perception of my own experience.
Why do I know the wall is solidly there? Because I can feel it.
Well, you can imagine a feeling as well, and if one is vivid enough in their imagination
or strong enough in their own mental faculties, it seems as though you can imagine
and create all sorts of things in your own mind that actually do take on physical characteristics,
you know, like the individual who does not believe that their leg is broken
continuing to run until they realize that it's broken, or someone being shot
who does not understand that they were injured simply doesn't feel it
until they actually look down and realize that a chunk of their leg is missing or something.
I mean, this is just part of the understanding.
It's the mind which is the spirit, and what happens there with the man running
or whoever is running with a broken leg and keeps intending on running and doesn't feel it
is because of the power that's behind the mind, and becoming part of this family, let's say.
I know this sounds crazy to most people.
When you do join that spiritual realm, you'll be able to perform on those thoughts with full power.
Right now, we can have those thoughts, but we just can't quite put the power behind it.
It's kind of like the car without the gas tank, let's say, as a metaphor.
Right, and this is all part of the spiritual censorship that we find ourselves under.
Oh, yeah, and it's going to be lifted in the near future.
When I say near future, it's going to begin in the next few years.
And right now, it's just like watching people online at a movie theater or at a carnival.
They're all outside waiting.
They don't know what show they're going to.
They don't know what's going to happen next, but they know they're waiting for something.
But they're frustrated because no one likes to wait online.
This is true.
After all, and you know what's amazing about that is that truthfully, once the experience has gone through,
and you've partaken of it, it seems as though the waiting online is left quite far away from your mind.
But at the time that you're doing it, it's extremely frustrating, right?
But once you get there, it's all worth it.
Well, unless you're going to a movie nowadays, I guess maybe that's not necessarily the case.
But, hey, that's my problem.
Can we give spiritual advice just for a moment of lapse of reason here?
The advice is, you know, if you meet anyone that has an interesting life, and no matter how bad it was,
they'd say, you know, I wouldn't change a thing if I would do it over again, right?
And when the gods set us up the way they have, and we just see so much pain and destruction and frustration and suffering,
when we get through this phase, we will notice that the gods don't do anything in futility.
We will also say it had to be done this way.
We do see why it was done now, but we can't see it now.
Right.
Once you've actually survived an experience, you may say to yourself, well, it could not have happened any other way.
I am glad it did not happen any other way, and this is absolutely what was meant to transpire,
regardless of how miserable the suffering may have been.
You know, this is typical to, well, life experience in general, right?
Yeah, and the thing about life experience, again, you can have a multitude of people sitting in an audience,
watching a performer doing ledger domain or magic, sawing a woman in half and putting her back together,
and they will all leave the audience swearing that they saw that happen, and it's a lie.
You see, it's an illusion, right?
It's a deception, right?
The woman was really not sawed in half but back together.
So then experience, how much is your experience worth, you know, if you're engrossed in deception or ledger domain,
which is just sleight of hand and illusion?
So there's a lot of that going on right now,
but I believe us getting together and doing the show is probably the best way to start giving a little bit of insight
on what we've discovered that makes the objectivity worth looking into.
Well, absolutely.
So to tie back to the original concept, the original article of discussion,
the constitution or the constitutions or the constitution in general, depending on how you want to phrase it,
the fact is that the document in and of itself means what?
It's a business plan, man.
It's real simple to see.
And that's all there is to it, really.
I mean, there's nothing to fight over.
Didn't George Bush Jr.
I forgot what she was, number 42 or something like that.
He said it was just a G.D. piece of paper and upset a lot of people,
and it's okay, it's all right to get upset and all that,
but the problem is people don't have enough of a lawful or legal mind,
and we have to bunch it up together to say, wait a second, let's look at the precedent that's being set here.
This is just not your common layman saying it.
This is a man holding the highest office in that document saying that it has no value.
So it needs to be considered what is being said.
Character aside, because character aside, if he said was so heinous and so horrible,
why wasn't he, like according to the Constitution, subject to congressional hearing
and deposed from being president for treason?
He wasn't.
And even a fool can speak the truth.
I mean, that's really what it comes down to.
So long as a fool can speak, he can speak the truth.
It doesn't mean he necessarily understands it entirely.
And again, just like we said, I can clearly say what people put their hope in is hopeless,
and they will see that later.
When one reads the biblical text, for example, it says that you really don't vote anyone in.
They're all put in office, right?
And it also says that the character of the individual would be the most base of your society.
In other words, most likely the guy scooping ice cream or sweeping the street or whatever
is the type of character you will have ruling over you, not an extraordinary man.
And this is according to the biblical text, by the way.
The most basest of men will be your rulers.
And this was for the general world at large.
So whenever anyone asks me, who do you think is going to be president?
I'm like, well, the one that's the worst for the country, obviously.
Right. The most allegedly corrupt or morally bankrupt individual usually does end up in a position of leadership.
The complaint that sociopaths end up in a position of leadership is kind of accurate, but also no great surprise.
Yeah. I mean, to go back to the Constitution, there's a clause in there that discusses if any official takes bribes or so on and so forth
or has certain misdemeanors and whatever, they can be put up for treason and deposed from their position.
And, you know, that doesn't seem to be very effective, again, which renders that document not very effective.
And this is not our I'm just the purpose of this discussion, I guess, is not the belief in it.
It's what is you know, what is the report on what is going on regarding these two topics?
Because in this country, it's they clutch the Constitution and the Bible with one hand or two hands, let's say.
And they have neither. And they in both of them have lost relevancy, according to people's actions,
from the from the layman all the way up to those with authority.
And I guess that that is the only way to really give a good discussion on the state of affairs.
Because to be reasonable, we can go. Let's say that's the present state.
Let's go into the past. Has it affected anything in the past? Not really.
And what are the chances of people's perception of actually using the biblical text and the constitutional text properly in the future?
Not it's going to be the same, if not worse, probably going to get away from it even more in the in the very near future.
But but what will happen slightly more into the future?
When this frustration reaches its peak across a world global level, people will say,
we need to start looking at our own reference material because we're being told all these things and things are getting worse.
If these things are so great, why are we getting worse? So let's go see what we're supposed to be doing.
It's going to be very interesting. Yeah. But right now, the state of affairs is not good.
Yeah, that's the truth. And the fact is that, you know, the most wondrous, elaborate, beautiful piece of music ever composed could be on a piece of paper.
But if it is never played, then it is never heard. You know, this is this is what it comes down to.
So regardless of the alleged sentiment in the documentation of the, you know, of the ideas, regardless of what that is,
if it's not being applied, it becomes worthless anyway. You know, and this is the state we find ourselves in where people again,
we had the discussion about rights versus privileges.
But let's just take a moment and try and, well, dumb ourselves down for a second and imagine that rights in and of themselves were meant to be these,
you know, these absolute things that were endemic of just existing. OK, which is what people seem to take that idea as.
Let's just say that that were true. It is already rendered irrelevant, because if that were true, then there would be no reason to argue for them.
They would simply exist without contention. Right.
So because they don't because they're used improperly, they don't exist because of the concept of right is improper.
They're actually getting what they're asking for, which is kind of hard to believe, but it's actuated.
You can see it. Give you an example on a parallel course.
I've sent emails out more than 10 or 12 years ago, and I've always said this in various calls and groups, groups of people.
I said, you folks better stop saying that the masses are waking up.
You know, that's one of the popular memes and alternative media because the people are waking up.
And I said, you better stop that, because the more you say that, they're going to ramp up the police state.
And they're like, what are you talking about, Greek? I said, well, the last thing you want is ignorant masses that are awake or crazy people that are awake.
Go to an insane asylum when everyone's asleep. You feel pretty safe.
Go there at noontime when they're all around trying to get their little white cups in their meal.
You want to get out of there. So the concept of people saying that, especially in the alternative, the people are awaking.
Any rational government would say we have to ramp up and militarize the police because we have crazy, ignorant people that are now going to be mobile.
They're no longer going to be rolling around in bed. They're going to get up and start walking around.
And now we need to militarize the police. And I spoke about this more than a decade ago.
And here you go. And everyone's complaining. And I'm like, well, stop saying that you're waking up.
You have to show that you're well-informed and you're responsible before you wake up.
Right. And that has to do with an elevation in the consciousness of the masses.
And there is evidence that that's beginning to happen.
Now, that doesn't necessarily mean that it's a particularly sophisticated consciousness, you know, that is coming around, that is gaining a bit of power, you know, among the masses.
But that that's where the problem is, in my estimation, is that, you know, again, like you said, if someone is asleep, they seem much less dangerous.
And that's not just from the alleged state's position. But I mean, again, like you said, from a personal position, think about it.
We are truly immersed in the insane asylum here. And honestly, I'd rather that most of the crazy people were asleep. So, yeah.
So you see, so it's a very interesting concept, but because you could take a very, you know, that's like the whole bulk of society now at large.
Let's take a very thin slice of one of the debates or the arguments, for example, the Federal Reserve. Right.
Now, if anyone has actually interacted with the Federal Reserve and from an administrative point of view, they do interact with the public.
And you could you could find them right in the yellow pages, by the way. People are old enough to remember what that is.
You could look up, look them up and they will oblige you. They're slow and sluggish.
And they might feel they may feel you may not feel like you're being given a lot of courtesy, but you can get through to them.
And once you get through to them, you'll find out you just ask them plainly or however you want to ask them.
Does anyone owe you anything? And they're like, no, no one owes us anything.
You know, so what's this thing about the national debt?
You know, I was reading an article the other day about the U.S. taxing authority.
Agents agencies collected three and a half trillion out of the economy last year. Right.
I'd like to see that three and a half trillion. The best you're probably going to be able to do is go up to a computer where it's displayed as a number.
And I don't know. How do you get that three and a half trillion?
I think if we cut the wire on the computer, three and a half trillion electrons will pour out of the wire on the floor and we sweep them up.
Right. Is that how we get the three and a half trillion?
Well, you know, but it does. But it does.
You see, that's funny. But at the same time. Right.
There is this concept of the debt which is built into the monetary system to begin with.
And that's that's a valid point. OK, that credit system is.
But but the monetary system, the way it's set up, it's meant to be debt.
It depends on who you're talking to.
You know, there's the interface, the actual system itself from an administrative and their legal, the way it's set up, you know, within their own contracts.
And, you know, the actual machines and the gears, it's all credit.
It's it's, you know, everyone when you're born, you get a line of credit and it's based on pledging.
Right. And they create any amount of credit you was required.
But that's not you. It's hard to interface on that side.
What you do when you're interfacing is you're always interfacing with someone in the legal society.
You know, when you get, for example, a telephone bill, a gas bill, electric bill, a water bill, you notice there's a detach and send in with payment.
Right. On the bottom. Well, in a credit based economy, you can't pay for anything.
It's your signature that it's garnered from. Right.
So you're supposed to endorse that voucher a certain way and send it back in.
And it's your it settles and zeroes the debt doesn't pay for it, but it zeroes it out.
Now, you can have success with it if you know how to endorse it.
It's not a for a for V, by the way, like some people might think in the Patriot community accepted for value.
Not that way. But and they might zero it out.
Actually, they do occasionally, if not sometimes consistently, sometimes inconsistently.
But you will eventually run into a critter in the legal department and says, well, you're not doing anything wrong.
But if we do that for you, we have to do it for everyone. We have to keep up this plausible deniability.
Because how else are we going to do things where we don't have to do anything to make a living?
You see, they're skimming off of it. It's so. So, again, no one is paying any attention.
What does credit mean? You know, there's no substance.
If you have substance, credit is just simply a fancy name for collateral.
You know, you know, I'll lend you ten bucks if you give me ten bucks collateral.
You pay me back, I'll give you back the collateral. That's just a form of substance credit.
But there's no substance here. It's very clear.
There are reams of documents that state how credit is created and the level of insanity in the alternative media.
I mean, there is not one show, economic show or commentator that is discussing that this is a credit-based economy.
It's just absurd. And that's a very narrow, thin slice.
And we could talk about the medical community. I think we kind of went a little bit into how the legal society works.
We talk about the scientific community. They're all like that.
I mean, there's just nothing is real anymore other than food, clothing and shelter.
Everything else has become this magic show on stage.
Yeah, but all the means by which one can acquisition that are all of these other fictitious creations.
It's all unlawful. You know, go back. Let's go back to the Constitution for a moment.
Sort of like after the preamble in the first section, it talks about legislation and bills.
And that's the preamble really to get you into showing you that we're going to start setting up this credit-based Babylonian system.
Why do I say it's a Babylonian system?
Because after the flood, that was the empire that pretty much the Syrian Babylonian Empire worked on.
The Tontine system, T-O-N-T-I-N-E, which is an ancient system of pledging, right?
So pledging anything and everything you have or will ever have to a certain authority so you can survive within that group.
And that's how they worked. It's an ancient, ancient way of operating.
And that's the basis of the system.
But if you go to the Constitution where it talks about bills and legislation, you notice how the laws are now become bills?
Who's going to pay that bill? Aren't you supposed to pay a bill?
You know, when you go to the store and you say, you know, this is a dollar bill.
I say, yes, it is. Are you going to pay that bill or am I going to pay that bill?
Now it starts confusion. Imagine a checkout, you know, and say, well, here's a $20 bill.
OK, you know, the total comes out to $18.75, right?
OK, here's a $20 bill. OK, now he's reaching in the drawer to get some change.
And you're like, well, are you going to pay this bill or am I going to pay this bill?
And he's like, what? I'm going to get you a change.
Well, wait a second. I want to know who's going to pay this $20 bill first.
You know, anyway, I'm not going to get into that because then you can end up walking out with the bill and the change and everything you're supposed to buy.
But anyway, that sounds completely ludicrous.
You know, it does. But at the same time, yeah, it is fascinating that a bill is something that's a law.
A bill is something that is, you know, a description of services provided, which are then supposed to be, you know, paid for.
All right. And a bill is also the thing you carry around in your wallet.
And all of these things seem to contradict one another, but they don't.
It's just bizarre. It's crazy people.
And here we go. What about the bill of rights?
Who's going to pay that bill of rights?
Who's paying for the bill of rights?
You are.
Yeah, some people just might laugh that, yeah, somebody's going to pay that bill of rights.
But ask the guy who's losing a gallon of blood from the rear end how he's paying for it.
Right.
So in jail or prison or whatever unlawful type of system they, you know, they've adopted, you know, in a lawful society, there's no prison.
You have jail to create peace, you know, when there's an unruly mob.
But the concept of prison came from the East, where, you know, let's say, you know, someone murdered someone and the authorities caught them.
And they said, well, look, you see, it wasn't your fault.
You were appeasing the god of murder that day, so you have to do penance now.
So we're going to put you in this room for 15 years.
And that will settle the debt with the other deities, you know.
Yeah, that's the thing, though, is that when you look at it, I mean, when I've made the statement as well that, you know,
that we're in an unlawful society, that the entire planet is under an unlawful system in general,
you don't have to sit and dissect it or vivisect it, depending on how you look at it,
and come up with all of these different areas of particulars to explain it.
All you have to do is take a look at the fact that there would be no prison system,
there would be no long-term incarceration and this kind of thing in a lawful society.
End of story.
They just didn't exist.
They existed in the ancient times.
It doesn't exist in the biblical text, the prison.
It existed in the Babylonian society.
Well, it exists in the biblical text as historical reference.
In Egypt, for example, they had prisons in Babylon.
Yeah, like Joseph was held in the prison.
Yeah, with the baker and the winemaker, let's say,
and the Assyrians and the Babylonians would take captives there.
So, yeah, lawful societies.
And again, this is beyond what anyone wants to stretch and call belief.
If there's a body of information, whether it's considered fiction or fact,
one has to adhere to it.
Because people say, well, you're taking the Bible literally, Greek.
And I'm like, well, guess what?
It's a literal piece of information.
It's not oral.
So I have to take it literal.
It's written, is it not?
And words mean.
There we go back into the etymology, because literal, they would mean,
well, literal means that you're taking every word for word.
Well, kind of, sort of, but here's the thing.
It's not meant that literal and figurative,
these are not actually in opposition to one another,
because something that is figurative could be literal as well.
This is a complete misunderstanding.
And what the interesting part is, if you actually read any of these works,
especially the biblical work, if you read it cohesively,
it's very plain about what's figurative and what is actual,
which is interesting.
It's very difficult to discuss,
because if the people that have spent their lives studying this don't know this,
how do you expect to have a discussion with those who haven't?
And any layman can best any biblical scholar very simply by just reading the text.
And even if it's 900 pages, if you read three pages a day in less than a year,
you'll have it read.
You just have to read it through.
And you can go to any university or any biblical scholar and best them in a challenge,
because you'll find out they know nothing about the text in a cohesive manner.
They never do.
When you ask for proof of something, they quote something, usually out of context,
and quite often that doesn't even apply to what it is you've asked, like I said.
When I presented that whole idea about how the entire reality around me
could be nothing more than a figment of my imagination,
and every single thing, including the sound of your voice,
nothing more than that which I have conjured,
and therefore the entire universe is that which I have conjured,
the guy basically quoted a piece of scripture at me.
I remember I got no response a few times.
You know, just dumbfounded.
But one time I got, you know, well, here in this book says I am God, I am the Almighty.
And I said, okay, well that's great, but you see, if you go back to my point,
which I have conjured this up, then I have created that book which you are talking about.
So where is your contradiction, I ask you again.
That is just an exercise. It's a legitimate exercise that will come into fruition later.
Right now it's like we're just pondering these things
because we were actually created with that level of thought pattern.
You know, it's a very, without erring philosophical,
it is easier to find the nuclear launch codes of any country's arsenal
than to discuss the biblical text.
Right.
You know, because no one reads it.
They read it out of context.
And once, even the Koran, I'll use the term,
and any of these ancient texts, you'll see that they're very coherent.
They have different levels of priority and different claims are made in them.
But they're all very similar.
But through my travels in the past 14 years, I can't have a discussion with them
because seemingly no one has really read them.
It's just like watching a few minutes of a film and trying to discuss it with someone.
It's just not possible.
Well, there is a hierarchy in all things,
and unless you've understood the full landscape,
how can you know if there is anything much higher than what you have already observed?
This is what the problem is.
Yeah.
And the level of diversion that's been put in place in society,
all societies, to instill the diversion before one gets the original information.
Like, for example, if anyone's reading any of the ancient texts,
let's say the biblical text again,
and you get to the point, let's say in Exodus, right,
where the Israelites, let's say, left Egypt and they're ready to cross the Sea of Reeds,
and they say, oh, this is the part I'm reading right now
that I saw in the Cecil B. DeMille movie where the waters were opened and parted,
and they used Jell-O for special effects, and they walked through,
and then the waters came down.
And then they glide over that section because they think Cecil B. DeMille showed it to them, right?
But if you actually read that, it's in Exodus 15.
It's very clear, and this might piss some people off,
but if you read it with comprehension, you will see that they actually walked on ice.
And in the morning when the sun came out, the ice melted,
and pharaohs and his horses couldn't cross it,
and they fell to the bottom like a rock fell to the bottom like stone.
Interesting, right?
Now, when you're walking on ice, you're walking on water.
And as you go through the rest of the text,
you find there's another concept of someone who's walking on water.
So now you see the whole thing is so cohesive and so practical.
And what the beauty of this, though, is that whenever they make a biblical film,
there's someone that comes out of the woodwork that is going to suggest
that what they're doing according to the quote-unquote Christian story is false,
but this is really what's biblical.
And I say, well, how do you know?
Well, I actually just read the document, dummy.
And the filmmaker typically has a responsibility, and I've seen this very often,
to give a wink in the film, a clue to whoever's watching the film,
any biblical film, that what they're showing is not from the biblical text,
even though people think it is.
They'll show one specific thing that is the complete antithesis.
So if you know the story, like an example would be, again,
in the Exodus when Cecil B. DeMille did the crossing,
in the biblical text it says that everyone that came out of Egypt,
none of them were infirm.
They all walked out of there.
No one had to be carried.
In the Cecil B. DeMille film, three times they do a close-up of a man
being carried out on a stretcher.
Super close-up.
That's like wink-wink.
We're showing you the total opposite here of what's in the text.
The obvious thing that we know.
Because there's no reason to do a close-up of a guy in a stretcher
in a grandiose film like the Ten Commandments,
you know, with Charlton Heston holding up the two tombstone-like stones,
you know, when the text says he held them both in one hand.
Anyway, this is a discussion that we probably would require some serious
backup to actually describe what the biblical text really is in the future,
not now.
Right now people just don't want to hear it.
They're not ready for it.
You've got the astrotheologists.
You've got the Gnostics.
You've got the atheists.
You've got the Christians.
It's just a huge mess.
I mean, it's just, you've got to wait for it to be,
you've got to wait for everybody to just calm down and sit down.
And I'm looking for anyone who's read the text, too, to discuss it with,
which you won't find.
And just like the Constitution, the biblical text, this is how they read it.
They spend 15 minutes on it.
They don't understand anything.
They skim around.
They spend another 15 minutes, and they walk away saying,
I've read the Constitution.
I've read the Bible.
And since they all go, most humans go through,
or men and women go through this way of approaching these documents,
they all say they know it and they read it.
None of them have, or very few actually have.
So it's just waiting for this time period to pass where there's an age of reason,
and it will be coming.
And it's not only with these documents, but it's most documents.
Right.
But this is the reality of literature, you know, going back to what is literal.
The literature, this is the reality of it.
People read it allegedly, and then they seem to interpret it
as opposed to simply reading it and internalizing it, taking it at, well, face value.
There's another one of those wonderful terms, right?
You know, and this is the problem with all these things.
Yeah, and the level of, you see, the thing is they're taken out of context,
and people try to refer these things into their day and age,
even though their day and age is still, there are things that can apply,
but they just hold it in stark contrast instead of seeing, you know, what does apply.
You know, like, for example, it's very interesting, and, you know,
we do discuss the concept of keeping time.
I don't know how many people it's pissed off already,
or people just goes right over them, but it's very important.
Regarding the Constitution, if we say George Washington,
we know we had some involvement at least in the time period.
How many people by a show of hands know that George Washington actually has two birthdays,
and they're a year apart?
You could look it up.
It's a technical fact.
He has two birthdays, and they're a year apart.
And why?
Because during that time, I believe 1750,
there was a global adjustment that everyone will now adhere strictly to the Gregorian way
of timekeeping out of the Vatican versus the mixed Julian and Gregorian mix,
which was what was being used.
And when they did that, they recalculated, and he lost a year.
So he's born, I think, in 1722 and also 1721, a month apart.
You could look this up.
It's within formal records.
And the reason they did that is because when they were doing the Julian calendar,
it was strictly on the feast of Ishtar, or what they call Easter,
and then Gregorian, they shifted it over to be purely solar, you see,
versus, you know, one to have the honoring that goddess Ishtar,
which they call Easter in the Christian meme.
So, yeah, so just from that point, you know, it's very important.
I mean, right now, if we said, well, I have two birthdays, and they're a year apart,
you're insane, but this is formal record.
So keeping time is very important.
And to go back to the biblical scholar,
I have never yet met anyone that professes to be an academic biblical scholar,
believer, or anything that has come to the realization that there is no January through December,
Monday through Friday in the biblical text, or how time is reckoned.
The best I've heard is that the day starts at sundown, which is Jewish, not biblical, by the way,
because the day does not start at sundown.
So we have this bizarre avoidance of any fact that is literal, even to this day,
even with the age of computers and Internet, the most obvious things are still avoided.
So if we're going to look at the Constitution again, there's not much time reckoning in it.
But if we look at the definitions, it's quite shocking when you consider the economic state we're in.
It's a credit-based economy.
And you start noticing how in the Constitution they're converting these debts or bills into law.
So like any bill, it's like an equation that's not finished.
When you have an equation, both sides of the equal sign have to be balanced.
So when you're creating a bill, it's an imbalance.
So now the bills become the laws, and now the laws are imbalanced.
So how do these laws get settled?
Well, you get thrown behind bars, dummy.
That's how it gets settled.
And when you're behind the bars, they run a mortgage on the credit line that you have.
Man, this sounds incredible, doesn't it?
But that's what's going on.
And science fiction doesn't even touch it today.
Oh, boy.
Not yet, not yet.
That's for sure.
And science fiction, there's another term that we're going to have to take apart at some point.
Like black holes, viruses, blood pressure, it's all science fiction.
I knew you were going to go there.
And I almost am tempted to bring somebody on that I think is kind of well-versed in the Gnostic sensibilities
to have this discussion with you, because I think it would be extremely enlightening.
Yeah, you've got to remember, though, just to preempt Chuck, that who was the father of Gnosticism?
One of, or the main character, was Simon Magus, Simon the Magician.
Who was the father?
A magician, right?
And he's in the Book of Acts, very, very distasteful character in his own right.
Who was the father of Christianity as we know it?
Simon Magus.
Who was the first pope?
Now Simon is typically translated to Peter, so when you hear about St. Peter, that's Simon Magus.
Yeah, yeah, that's why I lumped in the Gnostics, the astrotheologists, the atheists, all these guys together.
This is nothing personal, but we need to sit up and we need to go back and look a little bit at the history.
I mean, how crazy does it sound by saying it's a fact that George Washington has two dates of birth, a year and a month apart?
How crazy does it sound that all of these things that are brought forward and revered
were actually the byproducts of people that were pretty much like P.T. Barnum,
have nothing to do with the biblical text at all, zero percent.
I'll give you an example.
I had a discussion a few years ago with someone who spent quite a few hours in research
from an astrotheological point of view, describing da Vinci's Last Supper painting,
and I let them go on for quite a long time, and I said,
by the way, that was supposed to be attached to describing the biblical text.
I said, there is no Last Supper in the biblical text.
Oh, there's a shocker.
Yeah, I tried to explain that.
There is no Last Supper.
Sorry, it's the Passover.
Do you know how people refuse to understand that, that that is the depiction of a Passover Seder?
And it's not.
Yeah, it's not.
There's no lamb, and that's not how it's done.
The Passover, you're to eat at what?
Standing up.
Everyone in da Vinci is sitting down.
No, I'm just saying, I'm saying to you that this is what it's supposed to be.
It's not accurate, but this is what it's supposed to be, actually.
This is what it was.
But look at it again, just like you said in the Hollywood movies,
they wink directly at those who understand.
That's da Vinci winking at you.
Well, it's like putting up a picture of John Wayne and writing Tiny Tim on the bottom.
I mean, where'd you get that?
And everyone's like, yeah, that's Tiny Tim.
Describing Lou Ferrigno as Cary Grant, even better.
And they've gotten away with it.
That's why I said that the earth has become a cross between a pig farm and an insane asylum.
I mean, I'm just waiting.
You've got to wait because when the time comes to discuss these things in a sane fashion,
which means rational, it's going to be quite fun.
And there's going to be a lot of progress with everything.
But right now, still, look, I go into commerce and I say, look, I put down a 20.
You want 15?
Okay, give me change.
But before I give you the 20, who's going to pay that bill?
And it's the confusion.
It's not difficult to confuse humans.
The hustlers, the scammers, the magicians, they've always done well.
And I see why.
I just look around.
I see how people discuss these things and they want to debate things that don't exist.
Well, that's why I've said quite a few times, mostly off the air,
but I've said quite a few times that I'm tempted to initiate the church of the Mr. Potato Head
because I feel as though it is about as valid as any other church.
So why not?
And I imagine that I might actually accrue a great deal of followers for that childhood toy.
And I'm willing to bet that zealotry will exist there as well,
just as uneducated as it does in the alleged mainstream of religious or religiosity.
Look at the word church.
It comes from the Latin word cirque, like as in Cirque du Soleil, the circus,
and its patron goddess of Cirque was Circe.
Circe, yeah.
Yeah, and she was from the Pharmaceon Island, which means poison or pharmacy.
And allegedly she had an affair with Ulysses of the Odyssey fame,
and you've heard of Latino came out of that.
That was the offspring.
So we're throwing a bunch of things here.
People are saying, oh, what did he say?
Yeah, you've heard of Latins or Latinos?
Yeah, okay.
Circe, I believe, is dead.
She was killed.
And it's basically the ancient circus.
What they did with it also is they adopted the concept of the importance of the sexual organ,
because just I think once gave the metaphor the human body might be an upside-down plant,
the brain being the root ball, the limbs are, well, the limbs,
and the seed and the flower is the genitalia.
And just like any farmer would tell you,
the most important part of the crop after it caches the bulk is making sure that he has some seed,
because if you don't have any seed, guess what?
You have nothing to plant.
There's no next year.
The species, the crop, or whatever, does not continue.
So the most important aspect of life is to maintain the seed.
Otherwise, if there was no seed, for example, with mankind, there'd be nobody here in 40 years.
So in essence, there was ancients that actually promoted the importance of the human seed.
And where does it come from?
Well, it comes from the genitalia.
So now the genitalia are the very special part of the body, so they started building shrines,
you know, the Cleopatra's needles, and all these sex temples,
and all the Illuminati, let's say, sigils, or not sigils, but you see the geometry,
you know, it's explained, it's phallic, for example, right?
Or the dome being the breast.
So the ancient job lists, the obelisks being phallic symbols, things like that, yeah.
So the typical architecture of the churches from the cathedrals on down,
you have the Gainic-shaped doors, they look like an almond shape, they come to a point,
with a round porto on top, which is the rear view of a woman when she's naked.
The two orifices.
And the spire represents two things.
This is actually from history that I've looked at that was written in the 19th century,
all the way up to the mid-20th century, of people that studied ancient culture.
And they did refer it to the architecture in these churches from cathedrals on down.
And the spire represented two things.
One was the phallic symbol, and the other one was, the spire would become narrow and to a point,
looking like it goes to infinity, to perhaps represent the Tower of Babel being accomplished.
So we have very interesting, you know, so I always tell people in passing,
you know, if you brought an ancient here in a time machine from 2,000 or 3,000 years ago,
you walk down a typical western neighborhood, he'd point at that building and say,
hey, I didn't know you had a sex temple in your neighborhood, let's go.
And you know what he'd be pointing at?
The church.
That's the typical architecture of it.
It's just like, for example, I remember going in someone's house,
and they had some children eating breakfast cereal,
and there's a particular brand that uses, I'll say the name Cheerios,
and they use a large red, what they call the heart, like a chocolate heart for Valentine's Day shape.
And I kept taking the box and covering it, or laying it down,
and one of the parents says, why do you keep doing that?
I said, because, I pulled him over, I said, that's not a heart.
That's the frontal view of a woman's genitalia.
And he was like, oh my, I see it.
I said, I don't believe it.
I said, yeah, believe it, because a heart doesn't look like that.
Right.
And you are being laughed at as a society.
Yeah, and how many, that's why, even in the computer now,
what do they call those, little emicrons or something?
Emoji.
Emoji, yeah, when someone puts that heart there,
I'm like, oh, I didn't know I was going to get hit with throbbing genitalia at the moment.
I wasn't ready for that.
And they're like, what are you talking about?
That's a heart.
And I'm like, yeah, really?
Uh-huh, do your research.
Well, and just to tie it back,
speaking of throbbing genitalia, back to the unrecoited
or undesired sexual advances that I think we end up with from the government, allegedly.
It's all based on this wonderful document that we started discussing in the first place.
But, you know, I also find it fascinating that all of that type of architecture,
where if you reexamine it from an objective standpoint,
you'll find it in the government buildings as well.
Look at the dome.
Absolutely.
In the Muslim world, the most famous and the largest mosques were the mosques and temples,
actually, to Jupiter, built by the Greeks and the Romans.
And they conquered them, and they're still standing.
And it's very, you look at the history of any of the largest mosques,
I think one's in Syria, one's, they're all over.
Not all over.
There's a handful that are considered the grandest,
and they were built with a similar architecture by the Romans to Jupiter or Zeus.
And they just simply adopted them because it was the thing to do,
and they still stand today as such.
But if you, again, the government buildings.
But, you know, the term Congress can also be related to meaning
Congress between man and a woman in that regard, exchanging seed, for example.
So these things, now this is from a mature, non-carnal point of view,
from an objective point of view,
if you have a life form that contains a seed and the continuation
in a multi-generational aspect is required to carry on the seed,
the organs that carry the seeds are very critical organs, are they not?
So they've gotten to the point where they've idolized and worshipped those organs,
and we just gave the history of the obsession of the phallic symbols
and the genitalia that's prevalent and shown throughout society
and misnamed from what they really represent in history.
Plus you won't look at a mass-produced box of chocolates the same way again,
especially in the month that they call February, right?
It's bizarre.
There you go.
It is completely bizarre.
And that's the bottom line.
So we've only got a little bit of time left, and I kind of wanted to wrap this up.
I do say to the listeners, once again, you can go to
ocelliandthegreek, all one word, dot com,
and check out what is going to develop over there.
It is a work in progress.
And I do want to thank everybody who decided to give us the time
to hear some of this information.
You may not have heard it all, but you can always try again.
And by all means, we will keep doing this until all what needs to be said is said, I think.
So anything you want to kind of leave people with tonight?
Oh, well, the donations are important to keep it going.
It's the only way by a show of hands that we know people are contributing.
We also will take calls if anyone calls.
I believe you also have a board, Chuck, there that you might be able to access.
So interaction from the listenership would be welcomed.
Not tonight.
I guess we're almost out of time, but in the future as well.
Yeah, I think in the second hour we should start to just have the phone lines open
and see where it takes us from now on and just see how that goes.
What do you think of that?
Oh, yeah, that's great.
I think it's important.
Like they asked Sarah Vaughan, what makes a great jazz musician?
She said it's the audience.
So we need to see if we're providing anything that's accommodating them.
But I think as far as I've seen, this is our third go about,
I think we're pretty much on track on talking about things and saying things that are just not being said.
Not for the sake of saying things that haven't been said, but these things are very pertinent,
and I think it's time.
I think it's time that they're aired out little by little.
And I usually just about close the show by thinking of what it is we should cover next.
I almost feel like we need to explain which gods are dead and which are not based on the evidence,
because you referenced that a few times, and you could almost call the episode God is Dead,
but which one are we talking about?
That's right, with a question mark, yeah.
That will require a little bit of research.
Believe it or not, it's not virtual.
That is pen and paper stuff.
Yeah, let's just say we could do a brief overview of that,
and this comes, folks, from actual government records of the time.
Now, this has nothing to do with what you believe in or not.
It has to do with secular historic fact that's been brought forward to this day.
We're talking about the Egyptian and Greek governments.
We're talking about the Roman governments invested very heavily in documenting the events and identifying the gods.
So, yeah, pretty interesting.
We could go down that path.
Hopefully, I have a week to get it together.
Right.
And, you know, clever handle in the chat room.
I love what you asked, and I wish I had seen it just a few seconds earlier,
because I would have asked, who is laughing at us as a culture?
And, you know, who knew that they were laughing?
You got a short answer for that, Greek?
Well, if your name is who, you better be laughing.
Like, who's on first, remember the abbot and Costello.
Otherwise, we're going to look bad.
Thanks.
Okay.
Yeah, absolutely.
We'll catch you next time.
This is Ocelli in the Greek.
See you next week.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American Freedom Radio.
Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion,
and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years,
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO, and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367,
and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
What kind of person are you?
How do you see yourself?
Are you the kind of person that lets everyone else do all the work,
just hoping that you'll be able to get some of the crumbs that fall from the table?
Or are you the kind of person that rolls up their sleeves
and does the dirty jobs that no one else wants to do?
Are you hoping that all the activists giving their blood, sweat, and tears to serve humanity
are going to solve all the world's problems?
Or are you just wondering,
is there something simple I can do to contribute?
Yes, yes there is.
Help us.
Help us do what we do.
Partner up with American Freedom Radio today
by gifting a regular amount to support the network
and your favorite hosts, bringing you less commercials and more information.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and start donating today from between $1 and $100 per month,
according to the kind of person you are.
Thank you very much for your support.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit,
and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations
to change the landscape of various pain-related health care costs,
epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders, and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer, and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.