Everybody knows the dice are loaded. Everybody rolls with their fingers crossed.
Everybody knows that the war is over. Everybody knows that the good guy's lost.
Everybody knows the fight is fixed. The poor stay poor and the rich get rich. That's how it goes.
Everybody knows the boat is sinking. Everybody knows that the captain lied.
Everybody's got this broken feeling like their mama or their dog just died.
Everybody's hands are in their pockets. Everybody wants a box of chocolates and a long-stemmed rose.
Everybody knows. Everybody knows. Everybody knows. That's how it goes.
Everybody knows.
Now, you might notice I'm in a slightly different mood.
Gotta give it a different sound when we're doing a different show, and this is episode one.
So, you're very lucky to be here today, whoever you may be listening.
Now, it is very hard to describe the Greek. It is very hard to describe Greek-speak, to be honest with you.
But you can speak to the Greek if you decide, if you dare.
And, of course, the call-in number is 218-339-8525. 218-339-8525.
And other than that, I don't have a whole lot much more to say this evening.
It is midnight Eastern time as we speak, and as the Greek is about to speak.
So, how are you doing tonight?
Doing great, Chuck. This is show number one together here, and let's get this road on the show.
That we can do as well.
Okay, mental gin. Here it comes.
So, here's the thing, Greek. It is interesting to hear you on my show, of course.
And I do enjoy it, and I'm very grateful that you have joined me on my shows.
But this will be a little different, because I'm really going to just get the hell out of your way most of the time.
Just so the listener knows.
And I'm not tired, I'm just being subdued purposely.
Well, yeah, that's one way to look at it.
But I think the listeners and the audience might appreciate bouncing things between us.
It's good to have two people to discuss these things.
I believe that having a show where we can repeatedly come on every week instead of being a guest
allows us to have a little more of an open air discussion instead of limiting it.
And I do appreciate American Freedom Radio and you for putting in the time so I could have time on the air.
Right. Well, I'll tell you what I'm going to do here is, and we discussed none of this beforehand.
We just sort of put this together for you with a general idea.
So here's the deal.
I believe that we should begin with what really attracted me to having you as a guest in the first place.
And that is the very basic observation that you're only here to take notes.
Oh, yeah.
The reason why I say that is because there's this mentality where you have to be part of a group that believes in something.
It's either sports or religion or politics.
There's this groupthink and groupaction.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
The problem is that most of these actions in the groupthink is not fit and proper or even lawful.
As one can see, if you sum up basically what's going on, you can see that humanity is in a terminal condition at this point.
And it's very gradual, of course.
But things cannot go on the way they are, no matter how gradually they are descending or degrading.
And there is a time that with all terminal things, there's something called an ending.
And giving details, perhaps, giving a little foreshadow, discussing the facts, discussing things objectively.
And you've got to have good notes to do that.
So going back to the, I'm just here taking notes.
I mean, gosh, can you be a part of any group?
I mean, look at what's going on.
Well, let's begin with sort of giving people an idea of what you mean by fit, proper, and lawful.
After all, these words are sort of subject to interpretation, right?
Well, yeah.
I'm glad you brought that up.
The word interpretation means to interpret precisely and concisely.
And there's only really one interpretation of a matter.
There are many opinions on the matter and many stories and many reports that can be given.
To actually interpret something is quite a task.
But if it's going to be branded as an interpretation, it has to be done accurately and with precision.
And unfortunately, when you look at all the subjects that people are engaged in,
from politics to science to religion to whatever subject,
there's thousands of subjects that mankind is engaged in where they have, quote-unquote, experts,
these people that are constantly learning more and more about less and less.
And the reliance on the revival of these new religions,
or actually revival of ancient religions considered new things, like science.
It's really scientism.
And anything that comes out of that scientism seems to be scienticulous.
So that's to coin Oliver Heaviside.
So we look at the religious aspects.
We look at the financial.
We look at all of these things and they're all debased.
You look at what they're supposed to be based on and they're not.
It seems to be this wave of just, yeah, degradation that's moving through.
Right. So your observation is essentially that nothing has been created anew here.
There is simply the regurgitation and debasement of what already existed.
Yeah, in name only.
What they're doing is, the core of what is being revived is actual.
But what it's being called is something different.
Like when you look at political circles, what they discuss as being rights are not rights at all.
Whenever they talk about certain rights, if you look at a certain amount of time,
the freedoms that were enjoyed before those things were coined are taken away, typically.
By a centralized power of some sort.
Whether it's corporate or public or private or government or whatever.
Because a lot of people seem to forget how all governments, as we've discussed once before, have a patron deity.
And people are ignoring these things.
There's a certain hierarchy.
They'd rather talk about what color the stripes on the flag are as a gold fringe,
but they never discuss the patron god that's behind them.
We look at the aspects of what could be called introduction to state prison or public school,
or even Harvard University.
It's just an introduction to state prison.
It's very difficult for people to break out of the subjectivity and go into the objectivity.
So I think we'll be able to enjoy that.
We have two hours, perhaps once a week, to look at the objective side of things.
Right.
And the oddity here is that you are, in a strange way, in agreement with those who would say that we are under a system now
where there are privileges which have been bestowed and then, of course, eroded upon most of the population.
But at the same time, those privileges are not understood
because the true governing mechanism that would bestow said privileges is completely obscured.
It's obscured, and it's obscured, and yet it's not.
It's actually quite clear, but it seems obscured on its face.
An example of the obscurity is, look at how the media controls the mindset week by week.
There seems to be a story every week that dominates.
Or within a certain season, like an election season, or whatever, there's this very narrow view.
It's like looking at the ground when you're walking, instead of looking ahead or up.
So when we look at the privilege, there's this concept of freedom which is only a concept.
This might air philosophical to people, but just to get down to the nuts and bolts,
Earth is a violent place.
Anyone who's ever watched any kind of an animal documentary, National Geographic or what have you,
I grew up with Mutual of Omaha sponsoring some Wild Kingdom show.
All of these natural environments are full of lions eating zebras and frogs eating flies and big fish eating smaller fish.
So the Earth in general is a violent place.
That's not a philosophical point at all. That's a reality.
Even if you have lived among a human population, excluding the animal kingdom,
one must understand that unless you're cloistered in some way,
you must have experienced the violence which is indicative of the human species as well.
And the interesting part is we were the stewards of all of this,
bestowed with a certain power over these natural mechanisms or natural things in place,
and we've abandoned that post.
So that's another part of the saga of explaining to people what their position is.
And they can see it very simply if they just listen.
The idea of the unknown has really become something that they've worshipped like an abyss.
And there's been a disregard and almost a hatred for knowledge, objectively.
Not by saying, this guy's smart, let's listen to him, or this guy's dumb, let's not.
Or you're smarter or you're more intelligent, none of that.
The universality of objectifying a situation is open to everyone because it's very simple.
So I was always thinking about if a show were to be done, looking at the standard model from back in the days
when radio used to sell soap, and then it moved on to this subliminal seduction stuff of modern advertising
to just annoying ridiculousness that fits the mindset of the people.
Right, and the days of selling soap actually are codified or still exist, I should say,
are still echoed through the idea that they still call these things soap operas on television
because literally that was their root, where they came from in the first place.
Yeah, they had a story to tell for women before women's rights were able to stay at home all day and raise children, right?
So that was that.
Back then, now it's this idea of freedom or things are free, and they're not.
I believe you wrote an article on your blog about the free media recently and how it's not really free,
and the level of dedication that's being given.
Now, a lot of people will say when you listen to what's going on, let's say, in the media,
when we say the media we're talking about the Internet radio as we're speaking on,
they'll notice that everyone is pretty much saying the same thing,
unless they have a guest that is a specialist in a certain field or is a witness
or giving testimony to their specific experiences or level of expertise.
But it's all very, very similar.
A lot of people are just dedicating their time as yourself, as the people behind the station,
and there's just what they call there are bills to pay.
Even though it's a credit-based economy, there's an influx of revenue that's required.
And I believe when you wrote that article on Zen in the Car, I believe, Ocelli,
that was very unique. It's probably the first one I've ever seen on the Internet like that.
Well, yeah, and of course you bring up a very interesting idea here that there is a credit-based economy,
and people would immediately, who are accustomed to listening to these types of shows,
say that no, we're in a debt-based situation.
But actually, it's not true.
We have been sort of conned into believing that everything is in a debt-based system.
You can't have debt when it's credit-based.
Now, if you have a substance-based economy, you can offer credit under terms.
But there's the Patriot Movement, and because of the Internet, there's a lot of spread of disinformation.
It's very simple how it works.
Money was taken away in the 1930s, pretty much in most of the Western societies.
And they said, well, how are people going to function?
Oh, that's fine. The government will set up a line of credit for each individual,
and it's established with the birth certificate.
The birth certificate creates a limited liability agreement that because there's no money,
you don't have to revolt.
We give you a credit line.
But these critters, a particular species known as attorneys, or the quote-unquote legal department,
come out with plausible deniability and ignore the fact that there is no money
and tell you that you have debt.
They tell you there is such a thing as a loan.
They tell you that there's such a thing as money.
So Henry Ford said, you know, if people found out how banking worked,
there'd be blood in the streets within a day.
And the thing that I hear all the time is the Federal Reserve, the problem, the government.
No, it's not.
No one in those systems is blocking anyone from accessing their line of credit.
It's the attorneys that are doing it.
It's the Bar Association, essentially, which has nothing to do with law
because it's based on the justice system, which is the revival of the ancient goddess religion.
So there's a mouthful right there.
Well, right.
And just to give people an idea, what would you say they could reference
to understand the basic concept behind the ancient goddess for justice?
Oh, man.
The thing is about, you know, I call the Internet, you know, zeros and ones.
It's the telegraph, you know, click, click, click, click.
You know, it's either hand or, you know, that's how the switches on these semiconductors work.
They rely on the Internet.
And the thing about the Internet is that it's subject to human input or input.
No one's inputted it on the Internet.
It's probably not on it.
You're not going to find very much about the goddess religion being revived on the Internet.
What you will find, if you spell it under justicia, Roman goddess,
you'll find that basically it's a revival of the Greek goddess Dike,
which is also the revival of Maat, or parallel, Maat, which is Egyptian.
And then that ran parallel with several Babylonian goddess religions,
which are going to be very difficult to look up on the Internet.
They have not been put on there.
A good place for anyone to go is a good university library
and look at the ancient cultures section.
Not necessarily history, but defined under ancient cultures, particularly Chaldean Hebrew culture,
which would cover the Babylonian, Persian, you know, the entire area,
from the eastern part to the western part of the Levant.
It's going to be very interesting, but it's very clear to see how it's a revival.
The goddess religions are being revived.
We're talking about the goddess religions that were predominant on the Earth 4,000 or 5,000 years ago.
Well, and the manipulation factor to the Internet is something that has always fascinated me,
because in an instant you can edit the information.
It's not immortalized in any way.
And then when it does become seemingly immortalized, it's easily erased, eradicated, or altered.
So when one does a search for the root of justice, let's just say,
you might be confronted with the concept that the Roman emperor Justinian
had introduced this concept into the modern era, right, which is a misdirection.
Justinian was, in fact, more than likely named after the lineage of, you know,
naming one after particular entities that had influenced things like that,
like you would see in any society.
So Justinian was not the originator of this concept in any way,
although he is given credit for what I believe a term they coined as moral law.
Right, which is, again, based on the ancient goddess religion.
And just to sum it up, it's a very cruel religion.
It's based on cruelty and secret practices.
I haven't gone into depth to study the details,
because just introducing the concept is just massive on its own.
An example of this, though, would be the seemingly overabundance of punishments
like the precept of punishing one to avoid a criminal act.
This kind of concept sort of runs through it, though.
Right.
You see, the ancient goddess religions were branched out into the concept of creation also.
And some of the teachings were that mankind was not male and female
when mankind was in a godlike state, according to them.
So the punishment is put on the subject if they're male or female, or man or woman.
So it really includes anyone.
It's cruel towards both women and men.
No.
Again, the revival of this religion is very interesting,
because these things are put in a positive light.
How many times have you heard the goddess in you, right?
Or the divine feminine.
This has nothing to do with feminine being bad.
They're just blazing the trail to open the mind to accept these things
once the state of this revival becomes, no pun intended, known.
Because it will be more known.
How many times have you heard Mother Earth?
All of these things that are trying to put what's going to be coming in the future
in a more acceptable light.
Just kind of like women's rights was in the 60s.
Well, and some of the groundwork, I think, is being laid as we speak, as things devolve,
because an androgynous sort of fixture in the consciousness has become acceptable
regarding one's own physicality.
You know, the concept of you can wake up one day and determine that you're female,
even though you are quite physically and irrevocably in a male body.
This kind of thing, being promoted as it has been, seems to be part of that very same agenda.
Absolutely.
The agenda is massive, and it's been going on for quite a while.
But with the religion of scientism, or science, you know,
and the upping of what they call the legal system,
which is basically they are the priests of the justice goddess.
The scientists are the priests of another aspect of it,
because the legal and the scientific systems work together with the political system
and the medical system.
The concept of promoting children being born outside of the body,
the concept of cloning, the concept of promoting male with male union,
female with female union.
And also, you know, when I say male with male and female with female,
that's usually, those terms are reserved for farm animals.
There are men and men and women and women, right?
We notice a lot of times, you know, police are looking for someone,
we're looking for a male, right?
Or is he male or female?
Or in popular culture, I've got to find myself a female, right?
Yeah, there are men and women.
Those terms are no longer used, you see.
You're just material now.
The promotion of everything that you see in contemporary culture was trending,
politically, scientifically, medically, and all this,
is a part of the goddess religion, you know?
Well, and this concept, again, is also spread through things like,
and here's the odd part, right?
You have, yes, the union of male and male,
and the union of female and female,
and of course, like you said, men and women,
these things are sort of lost because,
okay, here's one of the justifications that's often given,
that in the animal kingdom, homosexuality exists.
So therefore, it's natural because we are equated to the animal kingdom.
But I step back and I say to myself,
well, that being the concept, then that also means that things like
sex without, well, consent is also something present in the animal kingdom.
Killing an animal, another animal for invading your territory
is also something, if you were an animal, would be perfectly acceptable
if you're equating the human being to the animal kingdom.
Would it not be?
Well, here's an interesting part.
We're not animals.
From a cognitive sense, we're not.
We share the same biological features internally, organs and things like that.
Warm-blooded, cold-blooded creatures may not.
But we're not because we don't have any firmware or anything that's,
we don't have an operating system that's pre-downloaded like animals do.
If a dog was raised from when it was born by a family of gorillas
and you adopted that dog as an adult,
it would still chase a cat,
bark at squirrels and fetch a stick.
You wouldn't know it was raised by gorillas.
Would it still maintain itself as a vegetarian, do you think?
I don't think that gorillas are really strictly vegetarian.
I don't think anything is strictly vegetarian, really.
Even a lot of the predator carnivores, by the way,
also consume grasses and fruits and berries and things like that.
But the thing is, we're completely subject to external input,
where animals are not.
That's why we have schools and instruction.
And when they tell us they didn't have this type of system before,
everyone sat around the campfire and were told stories, right?
Information was passed down.
How to work with materials, how to make a fire,
all these things were passed down and taught.
Where you don't see dogs having a school,
and you don't see birds having a school.
You might see a school of fish, but that's in a different context.
So they're downloaded, fully preloaded operating system.
We don't have that, which is very interesting.
It shows that there's an incompleteness.
Here's the irony of humans or mankind.
We tend to be in a superior position materialistically,
but from being prepared from a natural sense, we're the least prepared.
You ever see when an antelope or a deer or a fawn or a horse or a calf is being born,
they're fully clothed, right?
And they're ready to go within a few hours.
Yes, see, they can even walk,
which human children cannot do for quite a while after they're born.
So we're extremely unique.
The concept of, again, the level of poverty,
mental poverty that exists on the planet today,
because let's go back to it being a global situation, is astounding mentally.
How humans or mankind have allowed themselves to be completely deceived
about the most objective and the simplest things to understand.
And I think over time we'll be able to perhaps bring these things out.
And that's why one of the reasons I don't want to get into,
let's say we're speaking about the goddess religion, right?
I don't want to get into a lot of the specifics and the history,
because that tends to dull people from really feeling obliged to study
or take notes on what we're saying,
otherwise it's not something they could repeat in a conversation or walk away with.
I think keeping it really, giving the information out in a way that
just anyone can walk away and get it and explain it.
From a very basic point of view.
There's no reason to go into details.
I think that anyone that's interested can start researching it.
And it's great that we brought up the concept of justice being a goddess religion,
because ironically, if anyone wants to research,
it's just a real piss-poor body of information on what they call the Internet.
You're going to have to find it in hard copy.
In an old, it's these things called books.
Right.
Well, many people have accused me of being absolutely antiquated and ridiculous
for asserting the idea that not all knowledge is in the interwebs.
It sounds like a cute statement, but that's what I was calling it for a while.
And I've always said that real research is not simply confined to what is in the digital matrix.
The digital matrix, the convenience, I like to say,
people are deliberately called in a condescending way sheeple or cattle.
They're not.
Now they're chickens, because they're pecking at the keyboard
and they're pecking at their devices.
If you just look at their behavior,
this is the current situation with what they call technology.
But the thing that you will find when you say things that are outside of the convention
is you will find that mankind has gotten to the position where they have a self-loathing of learning
where we just described that it is mandatory to learn.
We don't have an operating system that's downloaded when we're created or being born or after we're born.
We're the only species on the planet that must engage in the transmittal of information.
It has to be imparted.
In fact, our very lives are partially dependent upon a psychosocial interaction.
I mean, from a physical standpoint, a sense which is not excited,
a sense which is not engaged by the environment can literally become atrophied,
much like a muscle which has not been in use in the human being.
For instance, as I've noted many, many times,
newborn babies, if not exposed to light, wind up blind.
And also newborn babies, which are not held, often seem to die.
In fact, people as they age, although it's not as noticeable as the hunger for nourishment,
people as they age tend to have shorter lifespans if they are sequestered from the rest of society, in fact.
Yeah, the container needs to be massaged, needs to be touched, needs to be affected.
You know, the body, we call it a container.
And it's a very unique one.
Eventually we'll discuss maybe the anthropomorphic shape and how it is really universal.
It is the ultimate expression from an energetic and material point of view.
And these things are, when we go down this road,
the best thing to do is explain them in a way where people don't have to chase down more data on it
and walk away and they feel like they've got a pretty good roundabout idea of what was discussed.
You know, I believe that giving a lot of specific detail in history
and what people say sounds academic eventually turns people off
because there's a self-loathing that has been put on society about learning.
You know, how many times have you seen it personified in film and in art?
You know, the nerd, the bookworm, the nutty professor, right?
There's a deliberate propaganda against being learned, right?
And it's a very, very simple thing if you understand how to have good discernment and good objectivity.
Well, although it's quite often propagated that knowledge is power,
it actually appears more like weakness in theatrical presentations, right?
Because the victims of the stronger individuals,
even though they are meant to be the underdog in a lot of cases,
are the more learned, the more advanced in their knowledge, et cetera, et cetera, right?
So they're pitted against the better looking, the better placed in society.
This is one of those things that is very subtly sort of introduced on not only a subconscious level,
but a very blatantly conscious level generally, right?
Yeah, well, it's a propaganda.
It's a cosmic propaganda to keep mankind away from knowing.
Right.
And that's what I was going to show.
Yeah, that's why, again, they show that if you just look at the characters in Hollywood, for example, right?
It's always been that way where they push things that way.
And I like how you introduced the cosmic idea of it,
because you've also said on many occasions that there is a, well, a censorship, a cosmic censorship in place.
And this is part of that, I think.
Would you describe what that cosmic censorship is like on more levels than what we just discussed?
I can.
Well, the thing is, we're all subject to it, because what's interesting, when you look at ancient documents,
the biblical text, the Koran, the Rig Vedas, even some of the philosophers,
they discussed there apparently is a cosmic war going on, and we're in the middle of it.
Not very much unlike if you've discussed old stories or seen stories with older people that said,
well, I was born during the war in Europe, you know, people that were born in the 20s, 30s, and 40s,
and how difficult it was.
Pretty much mankind will discover, pretty much for the past six millennia,
they've been in the middle of a cosmic war.
And just like any war, communications and inhibiting communications and preventing communication
is one of the primary things in battle.
So the level of communication has been reduced to very base level stuff.
That's why we started off by saying, look at all the groups.
Are there any groups that you would want to be a part of?
Look at these sports people that are into sports.
There's nothing wrong with sports.
It's very good to exercise the body.
But look at to what level it has been glorified.
Look at academia, corporate institute of technology, the government, religion.
It's just beyond ridiculous at this point.
It doesn't have to be.
No, it doesn't have to be.
But doesn't it sort of smack of disinformation, which is also a rather useful tactic,
especially in a military sense.
If you can convince the enemy that you're moving to the right,
they might position themselves to deal with a move to the right while you flank them to the left.
Asymmetric.
Asymmetric warfare, precisely.
But the point here is that the idea of splitting us into groups is actually one of these mechanisms as well,
because we should recognize that we are a singular group, don't you think?
Oh, absolutely.
You see, it's the yin and yang concept, the opposite.
When something becomes very strongly polarized, it joins.
And the same happens in the opposite sense also.
When it unpolarizes, it just becomes this amorphous mass, a glob.
So either way, the tendencies that mankind have now will be the same in the future,
but they'll be of a higher quality, and they'll be more fit and proper, more life-giving,
because right now it's a culture based on the worship of death.
For example, look at something like CERN.
They're trying to find something called a God particle.
They're not even defining which God, because people have been so removed from any reality
regarding the spiritual world, they just have this generic term, God.
And they have no clue about what has been memorialized for thousands of years regarding that subject.
Before we get into CERN, though, let's just break that down a little more,
because the concept of the one God, now this will sound distasteful to some people,
and they will say, well, there is only one God.
But really what has happened here is that they've been propagandized to the point of believing that
simply because it keeps them fully distracted from actually interacting with the gods.
Absolutely. And there are many gods.
Here's the thing, when you look at the way the military is set up,
where you have the private, enlisted, 90-day boot camp, whatever they give these guys,
all the way up the ranks until you get to the highest rank.
And in the spiritual world, what they're defining as the one God would be the supreme being.
And what makes him supreme, and it's so funny, I've had this discussion for the past decade
with not just the people, in layman terms, but the academics and the biblical scholars and the religious scholars,
and the top-tier people that are supposedly holding this information,
and they cannot define God or the top being.
They just go round and round. They don't know.
And hence the purpose of this show. Maybe we can just show how simple it is.
If one were to spend a decade looking, minimum four or five years,
at what's been memorialized about the spiritual world,
you will find that the supreme being is supreme being because he's not subject to death.
All of the other spiritual entities or gods are subject to death.
And this might sound ridiculous to most people who have not looked into it yet,
because one of the definitions of a god is to be immortal,
meaning without mortality, and that couldn't be further from the truth.
And I don't like giving Hollywood references, but sometimes we have to.
It seems like if we give anything that's in a book, it's too far off most of the time.
But if you remember the film The Matrix, in the first film, I believe, they said,
well, be careful when you're in The Matrix, because if you die in The Matrix, you die in real life.
And that was brilliant. That was the best part of the film.
Because when I saw that, I just stood up and tried to explain it.
I said, pause this thing. It was on a DVD. I said, pause it. I need to explain something to you.
And everyone just looked at me like, yeah, so what?
It's kind of like giving the keys to the kingdom, and it's like, yeah, big deal.
Well, if you don't know how to turn the key, it's kind of irrelevant if it's in your hand anyway.
So that's what it comes down to.
What's interesting about that is if you look at the ancient historians,
these were historians that were supported by the governments of their times,
from Egypt to ancient Greece and Rome.
They have records, very strict records, about the death of gods, like Bacchus or Circe.
These were gods that had died, and there were supernatural phenomenon going on,
and they had priesthoods and temples, and they had direct communication back in those days,
and these gods were put to death.
In the Mahabharata, there's a story, these are the Hindi writings of Hinduism,
where a prince goes out hunting, and I'm just paraphrasing here,
and he kills, I believe, an antelope or a deer.
Well, he really screwed up that day, not because he was hunting,
but because there was a god that actually took the form of that particular animal,
and when the god had taken the form of that animal, it was mortal.
And there's a saga behind that where now the god that was killed,
the friends of that god kind of put the prince through some trouble.
You know, just as you will see when a god does take human form,
and you do kill him in human form, you have mortally wounded,
he no longer exists in the spiritual realm as well.
Very interesting.
And this sounds fantastic.
How many times have you heard the truth is stranger than fiction,
but it's still the truth?
Right.
Another odd concept to introduce here is that most people that have a deist view of things,
let's just call it, would also state that a god would have a hard time dying,
because after all, they get to exist in this afterlife that people talk about.
Yeah, that's another thing.
Remember we were talking about a credit-based economy and the concept of debt?
Well, if you agree to it, right?
But that's not how it works.
And people are going to say, look at the arrogance.
This guy is going to talk about how it works.
This is like eschatology, the meaning of all things.
What is the meaning of life?
What happens after you die?
How can one know?
Well, there's an old joke about that.
If dying was so bad, how come no one has come back to complain, right?
But anyway, yeah, it's very interesting.
What can be discussed is this, and this is the interesting thing about it.
Everyone is going to find out, right?
Everyone and everything.
And they will find out that this is indeed a created environment.
There's something called cosmic superimposition.
That's where you can create a galaxy in a light bulb if you have the right frequency, right?
Anything large superimposes.
There's a geometric shape that is part of the tools or part of the pattern.
And what people will find out is they're not going to be very happy, by the way,
when things, what's discussed as the afterlife, it's not necessarily an afterlife.
It would be called a next life.
Because let's just cut to the chase and give some truth and fact here.
When you die, you're dead.
If you look at the biblical text, it's very clear about that.
You have absolutely no consciousness of anything, and you don't come back.
Then we have to get into the definition of what a spirit, a soul, and a body is,
which there's only about maybe, again, spent a decade asking people.
Again, not the layman, but going to where the layman would go,
which would be your biblical scholars, your academics in university,
your bishops, your rabbis.
And not a one could give me a definition of what a spirit and a soul is.
Yeah, I was just going to say I guarantee there is not one of them
who can actually define what a soul is.
Right.
Yeah, it's very simple.
And if you look at the language, the soul is your breath and the spirit is your mind.
Very, very simple.
See, so this goes back to what happens when you die.
The way you know that someone is dead is that they're not breathing.
The soul dies first, and then the body decomposes.
And the spirit, which is the mind, which is completely intangible,
let's just put it this way, gets downloaded back into the master hard drive
to be reanimated later.
It's very interesting.
And people will fight you.
They will go to war and they will die to support the belief that the soul and the spirit
are the same, or that what they believe is true,
and that you either come back as this or whatever.
Now, I have not found any ancient text that says that you come back
or anyone has come back at all.
It's all because no one is looking at it.
You know, even in the Eastern texts.
I mean, this is the interesting part about the Eastern society.
Westerners tend to be a lot more forgiving.
When the Easterners find out that they've been scammed,
oh, man, that is going to be one hell of a revolution.
You know, when I say Easterners, I mean India, China, Asia at large.
Yeah, they're going to be not very happy because when they find out
all this ancestral worship that they've been doing and all this has been,
yeah, because it's in their own texts as well.
So, yeah, when you, that's why, see, what death is like sleep without dreaming.
That's why when there's a tombstone, what do they write on it?
Rest in peace.
Right.
It doesn't say you're dead in peace or you're coming back or anything like that.
Now, there will be a reincarnation or reanimation and a resurrection,
but no one has been, that has been done for anyone
except if you look at the biblical text,
there is one that was done in that fashion to be a prototype.
Well, now, there are some that would say that Lazarus rose from the dead
and that Jesus rose from the dead.
Different.
Again, there's a language problem.
Let's go back to spirit and soul to show the subtleties.
I think you had Ralph Epperson on your show a few days ago
and he discussed how the deception comes through the subtleties
and manipulation of the language.
Lazarus was killed after he was brought back.
About this, I believe Epperson is absolutely correct,
that the language in and of itself has been the course of convolution for the reality,
much like, you know, during the story of the Tower of Babel,
they said let them be confounded by their language.
I think that that is part of the reality in which we subsist at this point.
Oh, yeah.
That's why anyone that tries to be Promethean,
which would be let's do this to help mankind as a whole,
gets tasked with a torture and a punishment like Prometheus was.
The eagle will peck your liver out.
That's why you have people like Tesla or anyone else
that has to come out with a car that runs on water or whatever.
They all meet a demise.
The reason why they meet this demise,
if anyone wants to wholesale help out mankind at this point,
is going to meet their demise
because there is a terminal part of humanity that has to be manifested.
So if you want to help mankind out as a whole,
what will happen is you'll have the malevolent forces against you
because they're malevolent forces.
They don't want to see anything get better.
But you're also going to have the benevolent forces against you
because mankind has slipped so far away from reality
that they're unrehabilitatable.
So the remaking and the redoing has to come.
So the last thing you want is someone like Tesla or J.J. Thompson
or a bunch of other people showing mankind how to build flying saucers.
Right.
Yeah.
But, again, I want to go back to the concept of the subtlety of the deception of words.
It's very difficult to get across in this day and age
because right away there is such a self-loathing of knowledge.
People do not want to be called a bookworm or academic amongst their friends.
Right.
That's a nerd.
That is someone that can't speak plainly, right, they say.
Right.
So if you look at the subtlety of soul and spirit,
like, for example, if you look at the Greek paradigm that we're still in,
the soul is the pneuma, P-N-E-A-U prefix.
That's where you get pneumatic.
Pneumonia.
Yeah.
And the P-N-E-A-U means air, movement of air.
And the spirit is the psyche or the psyche.
That's where you get psychiatrist, psychotic, psyche meaning the mind.
Right.
So whenever you see the P-S-Y prefix, that is the spirit.
It's very, very simple.
So there is this virus, mental virus, because, by the way,
one day we'll maybe discuss how viruses don't exist biologically,
and that's going to be a shocker, and the audience might like that,
not because it's our opinion, but we'll just show.
We're not going to read a 900-page National Institute of Health document
to show that there's no such thing as a virus,
but there's a few things on the Internet,
maybe one brave individual out of Germany, a retired scientist,
who proved that it's just a hoax,
and everyone still says you're going to catch a virus.
But there is a virus, and it's a mental thing, just like in the computer.
It's an informational-based one.
Well, you know, much like Prometheus,
and he is not the only story, by the way,
that one can find in an ancient text or two or ten or twenty,
where someone does attempt to seemingly serve mankind
by granting them some sort of knowledge
which they previously did not hold.
Of course, Prometheus stole fire from the gods
in a very basic sense.
I'm giving the story here, Greek.
But Prometheus stole fire from the gods and gave it to man
and therefore had to be punished by the other gods, right?
He was a titan himself.
He was of the highest order.
He was a titan.
The Olympic gods came after him and then the minor gods.
But that's the Hellenistic side that people are still in.
But there are actually flesh and blood mortals
that have done endeavors to help out mankind.
You can see it right now anywhere.
The minute someone says, I have a new invention,
I'm doing this to make society better,
the clock is ticking.
That person will meet some kind of demise,
either with terminal
or they will end up sleeping on park benches,
feeding pigeons.
Right, either in a real fast sort of way,
in a fast-paced way, an accelerated way,
they will meet their demise
or they will find it later, incrementally.
So, we go to the break here.
It is Ocelli in the Greek here on American Freedom Radio.
And I advise that you stay tuned
because we may actually learn a little bit about the viruses
and other things that are attacking mankind.
Stay tuned.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth
and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you Hemp Protein Powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC,
is non-GMO,
and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp Protein Powder burns fat,
builds muscle,
contains 53% protein,
and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367
and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations
of micro plant powders, brain fuel,
for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent
that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
American Freedom Radio is back.
We're trying to become commercial free
apart from a few honorable advertisers
that we would give ad space to
even if they couldn't pay us.
In this quest to deliver quality radio
with very few annoying ads,
we are now asking the listeners like you
to open up and become partners
with American Freedom Radio.
We all know the economy is controlled
and a new system called the peer-to-peer economy
is now within our grasp.
That means if you'd like this network
with its incredible hosts and credible information
to be nothing but the content you want to hear,
then you must realize that you cannot be a part of it
if you're just sitting on the sidelines watching.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and pledge your support today.
Donate according to your means.
Some can only afford $1 a month
while others can afford $100 a month.
Regardless of the size of your contribution,
it all adds up to keeping the network owners
and the radio hosts housed and fed
at the end of every month.
Thank you.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit
and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements
of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix
and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made
in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations
to change the landscape,
various pain-related healthcare costs,
epilepsy and autism,
rising mental disorders,
and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest
99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer
and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering
intelligent debate, constructive dialogue
with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun,
honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism
that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver quality radio
in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are
American Freedom Radio.
Hey you, don't help them to bury the lie.
Don't give in
without a fight.
No, you are not tripping on acid at all.
You are listening to American Freedom Radio
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and it is still episode one
of Ocelli and the Greek.
So, where did we leave off
from the last hour?
Actually, we started to discuss viruses.
Seems odd, but you know,
I've often seen mankind itself
described as a virus
and all of these sort of attributes
sort of, well not sort of, forget sort of,
I've seen all of these attributes assigned to mankind
that sound very similar to what a virus is.
It almost seems like an apropos comparison.
It's kind of like the soul and the spirit.
They mix it up.
It's kind of like ground zero, right?
A virus.
Yeah, once again convoluted by the language, right?
Yeah, and these things have very specific meanings
and they're just used very generally
and they're turned and twisted like nice.
If anyone dares to look up the word nice
in an etymological dictionary,
which is not really just a dictionary
because a dictionary just tells you
how to pronounce the word.
That's why it's called a dictionary.
But the word nice means foolish, stupid and senseless.
So everyone is wishing themselves again
because of the self-loathing for knowledge.
There's a self-loathing for those
that want to get shit straight.
So, yeah.
Right, and of course being oblivious.
Well, what do they say?
Ignorance is bliss.
This is one of the most common statements
that you get to hear.
I assume it would be.
Unfortunately, I can't find myself
in a position of being fully and thoroughly
and unequivocally ignorant at all times.
I always have just a fraction of knowledge,
just enough to let it bother me.
The thing is not to encourage anyone
to be a bookworm or a nutty professor
or a sound academic.
Just to use a little bit of discernment
and a little bit of objectivity every day.
It goes a long way.
Unfortunately, there's a lot of reference material
that one has to have access to.
That's the unfortunate part.
Otherwise, you're going to have to take it on face value.
All of these things are specific.
It sounded exciting to talk about viruses,
but there's a couple of biomedical people
in Europe that have said,
I've never seen a virus.
I've never seen one in the laboratory.
Never been isolated.
What is it?
And they did research,
and they're, I would say, medical whistleblowers.
And if you go look at the reference material
on what they call a virus in a biological sense,
by definition of virology
virology is under toxicology.
And toxicology, the organ for toxicity,
is the liver in the body.
And years ago,
virology, the field of virology,
was under toxicology.
It was a poison.
When you have dead or decaying matter,
there's not, you know,
that's why if anyone tries to do research on a virus,
you will never, ever, ever, ever, ever find
a microscopic photograph of one.
There are always computer renderings,
just like you will never, ever find
any kind of a telescopic photo of a black hole.
These are things that do not exist.
You know, they have to make these things up.
It's part of the religion of science,
of scientism.
And unfortunately,
people have things to do.
People want to follow their own pursuits.
And if you want to know about the world around you,
you have to trust these entitled classes.
And they are not doing their job well.
Now, most of the people in the field
are ignorant of it also.
So it's the ignorant leading the ignorant.
And those that are not ignorant are pretty evil.
Exactly.
And exactly like a religion, in fact,
because quite often the priests of a religion
are also not really hip to what's going on
with the religion.
And they give a watered-down version to the masses.
The masses cling to it.
The same thing happens with the scientific community.
Do you know what the research was?
Have you actually seen it?
They don't know, but they take the proclamations
of these figureheads as, well, gospel.
All because their parents didn't tell them
it was a credit-based economy
and the U.S. Treasury has a credit line.
But could you imagine if people found out
they didn't have to work,
they just used that credit line?
Who's going to make...
They're not enough of a moral...
They don't have enough of a moral backbone
to say, I'm going to get up and sweep the streets anyway.
I'm going to get up and wash cars anyway.
I'm going to get up and bake bread anyway.
You see?
They're just going to sit home and just...
They're going to do what they want, right?
If everyone became a millionaire,
what did they say?
I'm going to do what I want.
Well, why don't you do what you want now
and watch what happens?
The term jobs...
We're going away from all these things.
I just want to throw this in.
Job is a term from the late 19th century
when people worked in a factory.
They were given a job.
It's a technical term.
When you work in a machine shop,
you're given a job.
It's usually a sketch of a part
you have to mill out or hammer out
over and over and over all day in a factory.
So when these factories were unstable,
they would shut down.
The people wanted to do some work
to get money at the time,
so they were promised jobs.
That was promised because the term job
had no meaning to anyone,
only if you worked in a factory.
You see?
And now the government and the rating...
Oh, the job rating.
It's like, who cares about a job?
What if you're working in the field?
What if you're an artist?
What if you're a musician?
Why would I want to work in a machine shop?
That's machine shop terminology.
You see?
Unless you're a machinist,
why would you want a job?
So, yeah, this is really a very confusing...
Not only is the Earth a very violent place,
it's a very confusing place.
Very misleading.
Very misleading, like you said.
You know, I personally am not a millionaire,
but I am doing exactly what I would do as a millionaire,
except not quite as much of it, right?
By creating media,
having these conversations, doing broadcasts,
things like that, of course.
If none of my time was ever taken
by the concerns of having to provide for my family,
I would do a whole lot more of this
because, truthfully, I enjoy disseminating information
and making that part of my task every single day.
Mm-hmm.
And this is, you know, the concept of democracy, right?
Deimos meaning the crowd,
which also means terror, by the way.
What are the two moons of Mars, Phobos and Deimos?
Fear and terror, fear and dread.
Well, anyway, the democratic thing is that people vote.
So, you know, how many times have you heard
people asking for money, you know,
for the price of a coffee every day
or, you know, a membership or subscribe?
You know, there are so many ways,
and you and I have discussed how it can become distasteful.
But essentially, people that are listening to us tonight
are going to at some point say,
this is pretty unique or I don't believe it
or something or other.
But one thing we can assure anyone who's listening
is no one is discussing these things.
There's really an effort being made
between the Greek and Chuck Ocelli here and AFR
to pretty much say something that needs to be said
that is just not being said.
So the three entities here,
because we're just sonic entities to people on the other side,
I've come together and we're the ones donating, really.
And it's up to the audience.
You know, how can we say,
should we keep, by a show of hands,
should we keep discussing what we're discussing?
You know, how do we see that?
We can't.
I could tell people that if they wanted to call in,
they could participate, they could make their voice heard
along with the other sonic elements here,
and they could do that if they dare.
Because after all, listen,
if you don't think that this conversation is worth having,
if you don't think that this has anything to do with your reality,
I want to hear from you.
I really do.
And you can do that at 218-339-8525.
Once again, 218-339-8525.
But really, only if you have the guts to make a statement here,
because I feel as though you're making a whole lot of statements,
and they're at least worthy of some sort of answer.
So go ahead, guys, if you want to join in.
Sorry, but as you were saying...
But how do we know what to do?
Ultimately, we're giving up our time,
because all we have is time.
You're born naked and you die naked.
They dress you up or whatever during your life, even when you're dead,
let's say, if they care enough.
All you have is time in between.
So if anyone ever says, I don't have time for that,
you can translate that into,
I really don't know how to manage my time for that,
because all you have is time.
And how you're spending your time is important.
How we're spending our time on this slot here on American Freedom Radio,
what they call Saturday,
which we can discuss also timekeeping one day.
Yeah, for two hours, by the wind-up toy known as the clock,
the Greek and Chuck O'Chelley and AFR are going to be here.
So, you know, I'm not going to be so liberal to say,
tell us what you want us to discuss,
because part of it is we're talking at you right now,
and we'd like to hear proverbially what you think.
Now, there's a sense of approval.
It'd be great if everyone that was listening would donate something right now
to the station and to Chuck.
I think you could find Chuck on his Facebook.
Would that be Charles and the O'Chelley effect on Facebook?
Yeah, you can find me on there.
Also, there's a public figure for Chuck O'Chelley,
and also there's my personal page.
But, yeah, you can find me.
And there's the radio station as well.
If you're listening right now,
there's probably on the homepage somewhere a way to donate something.
Absolutely.
It would be very interesting to see that.
There's a banner.
As a matter of fact, there's a big old banner with this sort of amorphous-looking
semi-humanoid figure that gives you a statement about the station moving.
And if you click on that,
I'm very sure that it will direct you as to how to donate with your PayPal account as well.
Yeah.
And this has been done in the circus, you know, people call it.
What you call the word church, by the way,
comes from the word Circe, or Circe, the goddess who has died.
She died, I think, on the first century B.C.
The Greeks had documented that.
And her temple was on the Pharmacopia Island.
Yes, there is an island in the island chains of Greece and Eugene called the Pharmacopia Island.
What went on there, let's see.
Yeah, so they passed around a donation, you know.
And it was done very quietly, you know,
because they knew they wanted to come back next week and they had to support,
some kind of support.
This is a very, very simple concept, you know.
The Internet, digital, is back to the telegraph, zeros and ones.
You know, the telegraph was on or off, right?
You click, click, click, click, click, click, click, right?
That's exactly how your computer is working.
You actually have revisited the initial forms of communication in the mid-19th century, you know.
And we're now wondering what is going on with the people out there.
How can they react with us?
And even a soothsayer, even a soothsayer would receive some sort of tribute for telling you the future,
whether they were a fraud or not, you know.
Most of them were.
Of course, most of them were, but then again, look at the Internet.
Most of the people doing these types of broadcasts.
And in the future, in the future, we could discuss that as well.
Well, that's pretty clear.
I mean, it's been written, and it wasn't written by a bunch of idiots.
Things are happening the way they're supposed to.
It's just not on the time frame that people expect it to.
And if we get enough objectivity and discernment, people will be able to see it very clearly.
They have to be patient to see how things will change.
But, yeah, it would be interesting to get, you know, this is our first show,
and to get some kind of input would be great if people just donated.
That's a way of saying, hey, we're passing around a donation basket.
Look, there's a reaction.
This is a virtual world.
It's kind of like being out and telegraphing a message.
You know, before telegraph and radio, the only way ships communicated, you ready, was message in a bottle.
That is not just folklore.
Yes, there were technical aspects to that, and, yeah, based on the currents.
Yeah, you had to be able to direct your bottle, after all.
Absolutely.
And there was a watchman for that, and, yeah, this is, yeah, absolutely.
So, yeah.
And I'll tell you something else.
We touched upon it in the first hour very briefly, and I turned you away from it
because I wanted to give it enough time for you to really dissect or possibly vivisect the religion of science
and how it relates to this whole CERN concept.
And I'll tell you why.
So many have integrated this into a doomsday philosophy that has, well, sort of morphed into the panic
that I take note of every once in a while when I'm reading my history,
that there are time periods where the end of the world is supposed to arrive,
and CERN has definitely evoked this continuous thematic episode in man's history
where, you know, the world is coming to an end.
There are many chicken littles, but there's very little sky falling.
You've got to interpret it the right way, and the right way is very simple.
Their scientism is coming to an end.
Here's an example.
Back in the 19th century, it was the trains, the railroad magnets, the captains of industry.
They were the corporations controlling the world.
They were the ones setting up puppet governments in Asia and in South America
because they wanted to put a train system that would go around the world except for the Atlantic, right,
up through the U.S., across the bridge, across the Aleutian Islands, into Russia,
and then once you get into Russia, you've got all of Europe.
The channel, you know, they wanted to do a bridge across the English Channel.
This was all in the 19th century.
Now it's the petrochemical companies and the pharmaceutical companies,
which are hand in hand in the military, let's say, but is controlled by them.
But then it was the railroad money that controlled the military.
That was your military-industrial complex, you see.
And when they were going out, because the advent of the automobile and other things,
their trains became very, very elaborate.
If you look at some of the later models of these engines, some of them were 12 feet tall, massive,
super-opulent passenger cars, I mean, opulence beyond belief.
Right, to the point where they created actually physical spectacles out of wrecking old trains.
Literally, this used to be an event where people paid admission to be able to witness train wrecks.
The first time it was done, actually, it was kind of disastrous
in that it caused some of the crowd to be killed and everything else.
But train wrecks actually were one of these objects of curiosity.
A spectacle is the word I was looking for.
It's a society that's been worshipping death and destruction for millennia.
By the way, what CERN is doing, anyone can do with a couple of hundred bucks
from an old neon sign shop in Home Depot.
You can do what they're doing even better and show cosmic superimposition,
which would be, if you knew what you were doing, you could have a galaxy in a bottle.
Now, Greig, that sounds almost insane.
It does.
We're talking about a 17-mile long.
Exactly.
I forget what the repair bill was on it recently, but it was a huge repair bill, extremely opulent.
I mean, so huge that it actually straddles the border of two countries, in fact.
A huge, giant thing, and you're telling me for a couple hundred dollars,
I could do what we, again, let's make a Hollywood reference,
sort of saw immortalized in the film Men in Black, where, I forget which one it was,
but there was an alien at the end playing with a marble, which actually represented our universe.
Essentially, they're not doing that.
Because in order to do a cosmic superimposition and produce something like that,
you would be working with the energy that produces life.
They are worshiping death.
What they're doing is they want to smash particles together to study them.
That's like saying we want to study goats, so we're going to blow them up.
We want to study fish, so we're going to take them apart.
And that's exactly what they do in biology, isn't it?
They take things apart.
All of the medicine is based on the study of the chemical decomposition of cadavers.
What does that have to do with the health of living people?
No, everything is dissection.
Once you remove any part of physical tissue, whether it's plant or animal,
from the host being, and it's no longer regenerative, it is now in chemical decomposition.
Ah, that's why all the drugs are based on what? Chemicals.
So you have a society that worships death.
I mean, look at their religions.
They're talking about dead people.
We have ancestral worship.
This is a society that worships death, darkness.
CERN is basically the height and end of the railroad industry,
where they had these opulent engines and cars.
There's nothing wrong with railroads, by the way.
They're very, very efficient.
It's the most efficient way to move anything on land.
But the corporate side, in other words,
the purpose of a corporation now has become to make the innocent pay for the guilty.
So there's nothing wrong with corporations.
It's just that the model that's being used today,
oh, why is it like that? Because you're in a society that worships death.
I mean, you could look at CERN.
CERN is nothing more than the opulent expression of the worship of death and destruction.
That's all it is.
And it's basically you have a legal and scientific tyranny.
It's not political.
You see, all the banking system,
anyone high up in the banking system will admit to credit-based economies, just books.
And the people have the credit.
The corporations and the governments have nothing.
How do we get them to give it up without them knowing that they have it?
Now, the groups that are benefiting from this are what's called physicists, scientists, and the legal society.
As a matter of fact, there's a TV network called C-SPAN.
And quite a few years ago, I was watching when they had the speech of the president or the chief of the Bar Association.
And in the beginning of his speech, he said,
in order to have a strong economy, you need a strong legal system.
Now, what he's talking about is their economy, not your economy.
And the same thing with the scientists.
What they're going to do is invent things that don't exist.
Ever since Einstein, you have no more what's called science, which is basically a 20th century invention.
There was no such thing as a scientist or a physicist more than 150 years ago.
And now if you go and you research some of the greats in that field from a few hundred years ago,
they call them scientists and physicists.
They were not.
They called themselves natural philosophers.
They were either vitalists who studied living things or materialists.
So this is a posthumous title which has been bestowed upon them as scientists, right?
Yeah, exactly.
And they're dead.
They're not going to complain.
If any of those men came back today, they would be in absolute horror across the board,
from the men on the street all the way up to what's going on at CERN or the halls of universities or government.
They would be in complete horror, complete horror of what's going on and what's been accepted.
But again, a little bit of objectivity is all it takes and some discernment.
Most of it is, again, not going to be on the Internet, because like I just said,
you could put in Alessandro Volta or Isaac Newton or any of these guys, Tesla.
You say, this guy was a scientist or a physicist.
No, he wasn't.
He was not.
Those words did not exist in those days.
So people have bought into it hook, line, and sinker.
The religion aspect, the Pope being in town, all the Catholics are going crazy.
It's wonderful, right?
We have some activity.
Their patriarch is in the news.
Well, if you were to study Catholicism objectively, their creed is that their believers, their followers,
believe in one apostolic church.
Right?
That's it.
It has nothing to do with the Bible.
It doesn't mention biblical texts or anything biblical or anything.
And if you look at who these apostles were, you will find that the first Pope,
well, he was made the first Pope after he died, but was a man named Simon Magus.
Simon the Sorcerer.
Lovely.
Wonderful.
That's where your Gnosticism comes from and all these other things.
So this is not a new thing, like we just harped on what's going on in the 20th century and such.
But this has been going on for thousands of years.
And the beauty of it right now is that mankind is in the credits.
The movie ended already, guys, and you're in the credits.
And all this information on who's behind the scenes and what has been going on is going to be coming out.
And that's why we're speaking.
I believe that, and I don't like using that word, that the time is not now,
but there's nothing wrong with giving a trailer of next year's movie.
People go to the movies and they see the film.
And, you know, right now people are going, they've bookmarked what they're going to listen to on the Internet, and they do so.
And here they see the Uccelli and the Greeks speaking on American Freedom Radio,
and they're like, well, okay, this guy sounds whatever.
But, yeah, whatever is, this is going to hit people pretty hard in the next few years.
So we're just giving them a precursor of the things that are going to be on the forefront.
But the interesting part of it is that they're going to take it lying down.
It's going to be normal, you know, when these major changes start to come, starting in the next few years.
It'll be shocking if we actually reveal the detail of it now.
But when they do come, the people are going to accept it.
Because when you're under so much tension and frustration that any respite or any change is good, even if it's not for the better.
Well, also, just like you said in the last hour, the people are susceptible to outside programming.
And what has happened is many things have become normal.
That if I had been speaking about them, let's just wind time back a little bit.
If I had told you 20 years ago that there would have been a massive terrorist attack on American soil,
and that it would have extremely altered that which people consider to be their freedoms,
this has actually happened.
But they might have called me crazy in 1995.
They would have left, because what the hell is a terrorist? There's no such thing.
Well, there's no terrorists here. That may be something.
There's definitions of it, but it was not in the vernacular.
It was never brought up as even an issue.
It's kind of like, now it's global warming in the 70s.
It was ice age, definite ice age by the 1990s.
But the flip that's happening, that's going to be coming, now we're getting a little bit into what's coming in the future,
is going to be accepted, just like it's accepted right now.
The future is going to be in the Middle East, what they call the Middle East.
There are going to be ten nations that are going to basically come together like the EU did,
but not in that capacity, in a different capacity.
And it will be a Middle East union, a very loose one, but they are going to be working in unison together.
And all this stuff that's going on in the Middle East right now is just strictly to denationalize the area.
What I mean by that is you cannot have, let's say using the EU as a paradigm or a model,
if France is too nationalistic and they don't get along with Germany,
and Greece is too nationalistic and they don't get along with Italy, you can't form a union.
So what you do is you go in there and you destabilize all the centralized governments,
and you put in people that are docile and complacent, and they all come together.
You can't have nationalism and sectarian fighting, or even religious fighting.
So what you're seeing now going on in the Middle East, and the reason I'm bringing this up,
is because the two main things that people are discussing in the news is the election
and what's going on in quote-unquote Syria.
But they're not talking about Yemen, they're not talking about what's going on in Saudi Arabia,
they're not talking about what's going on in Israel, because it's what they're being allowed to see.
But essentially there are nine countries right now, we're waiting for a tenth one to come on the scene,
and when this tenth one comes on the scene, yes a new country, a new old country,
it's so old everyone's forgotten about it, but their people are still here.
When they come together as a nation, then that Middle East Union will be formed.
And now you have your final new world order, your final Earth's man-made powerhouse kingdom,
let's say, or centralized part of the world will be there, and that's not going to begin for the next few years.
And the country that you're looking for is a country called Assyria, not Syria, Assyria.
And it's interesting how cosmically there's an irony how Syria is in the news a lot,
and very often when I've discussed privately and publicly the formation of a new country for the Assyrian people,
they say, you mean Syria? I mean, no, not Syria, Assyria, the Akkadian, Chaldean people.
And they're spread out throughout the entire world right now, and they do not have a country,
they haven't had a country in 2,300 years.
And the reason why they didn't have a country for so long is because in ancient times their primary resource was war.
When they wanted something, they got together and just did war, and they were real badasses.
They had the most devolved and most fearsome siege works and war machinery known to man.
And I believe cosmically if they were not put down and dissolved, we wouldn't be here right now.
But this country, this people will revive their nation, and when it is revived,
and by the way, where is Assyria? It's in northern Iraq, it's in the area of the Euphrates and the Tigris,
and it's called the Nineveh Plain. And when it forms, it's going to take a little bit of land from Turkey and Syria,
and those two areas are in contention, and Iraq.
And all those three, when you say Turkey, Syria, and Iraq, those are all places right now that are in the heat.
And the entire world will focus on this area, so the Russians being in Syria right now is nothing.
Yes, it's something, it's important, because it's showing, you know, the U.S. has been there,
and the Russians are there now, so you have the two military economic superpowers that are involved there,
almost surrendering their position.
If those that know what's coming will see that the U.S. involvement and Russian involvement in that part of the world
is not an escalation, but it's them being prepared to play second fiddle on the world stage,
not first fiddle, because first fiddle, the leading group in the New World Order, will be in the Middle East.
So there's your little future, there's your news before it's news.
And that's the purpose, actually, behind what seems to be a senseless Balkanization, that's a term I use all the time,
of places like Iraq, of the decentralization of power there, is to create a vacuum so that this nation could be formed.
It's actually a very strategically sound way to do it, much like the Third Reich rose,
because of the vacuum of power that was created that allowed the National Socialist Party to rise as it did.
On a smaller scale, that's exactly what happened.
These people will be peaceful, though. They will not rise in the nature that they were known for.
But they will be a force to be reckoned with.
And one of the main world characters is going to be a Syrian in the future.
He will be one of the most powerful people ever on the face of this Earth, who has ever lived, actually,
will come out of that group of people. And we can also discuss that in the future.
There's something that, in other words, when these things start to happen, people will just accept it.
And if you know of them now, you will not be in the frustration or in the sense of wonder.
And that something is understanding that humanity is in a terminal condition.
In other words, everything that people are looking at will not be here in the next couple of decades or less.
We'll just give them more leeway, because if we actually give them time frames, it's kind of senseless at this point.
But if you look at, for example, a few decades ago, when captains of industry and governments related to the public,
they were always discussing public works, new highways, new bridges, infrastructure, better schools,
and large ideas like the New Deal concepts, multi-generational talk.
Right now, none of them are saying anything. They're only being reactionary.
Only when something happens do they make a statement.
It's as if all of the authority of the world has retracted from making any statements beyond a decade or two.
Have you noticed that?
Oh, absolutely. Another thing I've noticed is, okay, this is going to sound really off the wall, but let's go for it anyway.
If one recalls a lot of the interpretations of a few years back of, well, the man that they call Nostradamus, Michel de Nostredame, right?
This guy, if you actually take a look at a slightly different translation from that which most scholars of his work gave,
you can actually see a very similar pattern to what you're talking about.
Yeah, I haven't studied him.
The thing is, it's one of these things that you don't want to fight against the tide.
Now, I haven't studied him, so I can't say if what he's reckoned is correct or not.
But I'll tell you, his name has been trampled through the streets by enough people that I find to be very distasteful,
that the information has become distasteful, and we don't know.
I mean, when I say we, I really can't comment on Nostradamus because of what's happened.
There are many things that comments can be made on if one can show or speak to the listener the proof of it,
but I have no proof for or against Nostradamus.
Well, I'll tell you something. I feel extremely proud of myself because that is the first time that I think I've ever mentioned something
that you did not say you had some knowledge on right away.
Yeah, I try to stick with ... this is where I focus and I recommend anyone would focus on,
where there's something substantive or it has a base to it.
Like if you see a note, and it's a note like what they call money, all right, well, go get something for it.
You can't, right? So that means it's debased.
If you see a religion with Santa Claus and they tell you they base their religion on the Bible
and you don't see any Santa Claus in there, well, that's completely debased, right?
So all of these things are debased, you know, so when you're looking at things regarding time,
the first thing you look for is are they discussing how to reckon time, right?
And right now I can tell you pretty solidly and confidently there are very few people left on the planet who can reckon time.
If you ask anyone what day it is and they say anything, January through December or Monday through Friday,
they do not know how to reckon time.
That is merely admitting that you are a papal subject, a subject of the Vatican or a subject of the Pope,
which is ... I'm not going to say there's anything wrong with that, but there's nothing right about it either, right?
So you have to be neutral on that.
And it is fascinating because most people don't realize that they are,
and that's why I constantly now at the top of my own show bring up that according to the Pope's work schedule,
it is this particular day.
Exactly. I mean, look, September means 7, October means 8, like octopus or octagon,
November means 9 and December means 10.
And they're all writing numbers, and if you discuss this with anyone,
this is the main thing that I look at regarding time.
And if you discuss this with anyone, the cognitive dissonance sets in.
It is so deep.
That's why I keep saying, oh yeah, humanity is going to take this lying down
because they haven't even realized, they don't know what day it is.
And then of course you have the ones that will throw you into la-la land
and they'll say there's no such thing as time or anything like that.
And the sad reality is, though, that if you read a true representation of what the biblical script is,
they actually give you a way to tell time, don't they?
Absolutely. All the ancient texts do.
See, simply the day starts at high noon.
That's why if you remember banking before the electronic convention,
you made a deposit after noon or an hour or so after it was counted as the next day.
And that's why when they held in common law courts, the execution was the next day.
That's why they hung you at high noon.
So the day started at noon.
For thousands of years, people settled their debts with the new moon,
which is the full moon, which rises in the east.
That's why today you still get a monthly bill.
But now they've turned the new moon into the dark one, and they've turned the day starting at midnight.
You know, the contrast here is, it used to be that you reckoned time with the light and the luminaries.
Now you reckon time in complete darkness.
Oh, because they worship death and darkness. Ah, I see.
See, and now we've tied the whole thing back together,
because as we began here at midnight, this would begin the new calendar day in the east here on the east coast, right?
A little bit earlier for you when we started.
But nevertheless, the point is that this is the reality.
We begin at the darkest point in the day, literally.
That's why to go back to the, you know, there's a self-loathing for knowledge.
People loathe those who have information or knowledge.
You know, the nerd, the nutty professor, the bookworm, the academic, you know, they're bad, right?
That's why those who do gain knowledge, what do they do?
They retract from society.
If you look at the sages, the ancient sages, where did they live?
Did they live in town? No.
They lived somewhere in the forest, or they lived somewhere in the desert, or they went away from the people.
Because when they went into town, or they went into the cities, they were in absolute horror.
You know, to give you an example, there was someone in the neighborhood that was moving out, quite popular,
and they were having a going away party, and that's what I got out of it,
and I'll tell you what's what I got out of it, because I hear a knock on the door,
and there's a woman standing there with a shaved head, and she had a low-cut shirt,
and there was a big skull tattooed on her chest, and I was in total shock.
I was in total horror to see this individual, this woman, standing in the front door,
and her mouth was moving, and I was hearing sounds, but I was in absolute horror in her appearance,
and she's telling me, oh, we're having some wonderful food, and all this, and all this,
and of course, you know, if you've got a shaved head with a tattoo of a skull on your chest,
hey, more power to you if you think that's the way to go,
but that would put myself and many others that I know in absolute horror, you see,
so the sages would have to go out, you know, that's a personal aspect of it.
No, I understand, and also, even the adaptation of certain words relating to those who are knowledgeable,
like, for instance, the word geek, right, someone who is a geek, etc., etc.,
well, that became part of the language, literally, through the idea that someone who, you know,
bit the heads off of live chickens at the circus was a geek.
This guy was definitely not part of social groups that would be in town or among the people, generally speaking, right?
Yeah, that's extreme polarization.
They're very, very, yeah, so those that want to see things go right, extremely polarized on one end,
and those that want to see things go extremely wrong, extremely polarized on the other, neither can, yeah,
there's a middle ground because mankind is mid-range.
They can't comprehend the simple and they can't comprehend the complex.
It's all mid-range stuff.
You know, it's got to be simple.
Look at sports.
All you've got to know is that this ball has to go, you know, in the goal here,
and the two different colored uniforms, you know, that's, you know,
I don't understand, you know, people chasing balls with uniforms.
I mean, there's wonderful aspects to physical, you know,
putting the body under physical exercise and the benefits of being fit,
but the level of the society has taken it to is, again, you know,
something that is not understood by those.
Well, physical, yeah, physical competition literally morphed from the comparison of one's physicality to another,
much like I've often said that I appreciate gladiatorial sports or things like weightlifting
or running a whole lot more than I do team sports, generally speaking,
because there's just a greater level of sophistication to that which is seemingly more simple,
but in all honesty is a true test as opposed to the over-complication of comparison.
Yeah, and with that, you know, every culture had its form of martial arts, you know,
and now only the Asian aspect has been popularized, you know, but every culture had, you know,
the Greeks had the pancration, and in South America, I guess in Brazil it would be the capoeira,
which looks like the dancing moves, and every culture has its high art of body movement, right?
And again, it's been centralized, you know, oversimplified, you know, Bruce Lee, you know,
but, you know, it's been, yeah, the personal aspect has been taken out.
Who was an incredible martial artist, but...
Yeah, not to discredit him or take anything away from him,
and he discovered Tai Chi, which was a form of style that could not be taught until the person, you know,
reached a certain skill level to understand what's called the Chi,
and that put him in a lot of dislike, I guess, so I've heard, but, yeah, each culture had that.
So, yeah, the interesting part is what can we say, you know, we're going to be here once a week,
we're going to try to, at least, and just discuss things that maybe people are not hearing,
and, as a matter of fact, let's just say it this way, I know they're not hearing,
and this is the place to come, perhaps, to hear these types of things.
Well, absolutely, and, of course, you won't be able to hear the Greek speak in too many other places, at least not now.
In the future, we will, there is going to have, well, I say we, who's we,
but there is going to have to be a concerted effort made to broadcast this information,
both in writing and in digital format and in terrestrial format.
I think there's going to be a need for it.
There's going to be a sobering up of society, and it's just the information has to be given.
I mean, wait until people find out that there were, for example,
the American Institute of Electrical Engineers in 1923 stated that we're only six months away
from having a self-sustaining electrical device.
Now they call it free energy, right?
The American Institute of Electrical Engineers is a mainstream, it still exists, group,
and they came out and said this in the early 20s, where is it?
They were very confident, by the way, and they had it, so where is it?
This time period is now over.
In the near future and in the coming future, there will be discussions on the reality of things,
the reality of reality, not the reality of things that are debased,
like your money, your law, your science, your religions are all debased.
It's very simple to go back and kick those institutions in the shins.
It's very easy.
I mean, they have their soft side open, and if you want to take a kick at them,
I mean, Einstein, come on.
Santa Claus, come on.
Come on, guys.
Federal Reserve note, you've got to be kidding me.
All this stuff is so easy to pick at, but the people are not ready to hear it.
They're too frustrated.
They're under too much tension.
So that can be done.
Those things should be picked on and called out for what it is.
But on the other hand, perhaps laying the ground for things to come that are substantive
and are going to be based on something real and tangible, like learning how to keep time,
learning what lawful commerce is, understanding who the gods are.
All of these things come together.
They're all the same.
Well, and that's really actually one of the more interesting aspects of what I think we're going to do here,
which is we're going to start to teach people that there is a vast amount of difference
between destroying the idols in front of the temple
and actually destroying the idea that the temple is embodied.
This is part of the problem right now, I think.
They're destroying the statues, which are easily replaced, or at least attempting to,
and in some cases quite unsuccessfully thus far.
They're too weak.
Here's the point, and the hypocrisy is too high.
For example, I've engaged people that, for example, are anti-Vatican control.
You've heard that a lot.
And I've engaged them as such.
The first thing I ask them is, what day is it today?
And guess what they say.
Something between January and December and something between Monday and Friday.
And I really feel sorry for them because they're out there bashing the Pope, right?
Yet they're admitting with their own mouth that they're the Pope's subject.
We're talking about a level of insanity and hypocrisy that it just...
I can't engage.
Which goes way beyond those that claim to be Christian and still celebrate Halloween.
Christianity is a secular thing.
The secular historians, we're talking about atheist professors now,
they have labeled the era of the past 2,000 years as the Christian era.
Christianity is secular.
Well, they call it religion, but it is a secular religion.
In other words, it's based on...
Actually, let's come out and say it.
Lower demonic entities that have existed for thousands of years.
And they're very passionate about it, and they're very ignorant about it.
But that's what makes them dangerous.
The same with every religion.
I mean, look at what's going on right now with what they call Islam.
If you read the Koran, you would never be associated with anything that's being done in the name of Islam.
Whether it's pacifist, warlike, radical, or anything.
None of them know anything.
The same with the Hindus.
The same with the Buddhists.
None of them know anything about the...
The Jews are the same.
There's no religion on the planet right now, bar none,
that does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
I mean, at all.
Yes, this is an absolute point of, once again, irrefutable reality.
And I'll tell you, we're just about to run out of time.
And I think that the second episode of Ocelli and the Greek,
I think we should focus on...
Because maybe these concepts and maybe these realities are a little too high-end for some people.
I'll tell you what I think we should do with the next episode, Greek.
I think we should focus on the human body and all of the drugs,
and maybe how that works.
How the human body works, yeah.
So perhaps if people get into their minds, know thyself,
perhaps they will know the rest of the story a little better.
What do you think?
Well, here's the thing.
If you're deceived about how your own body works,
and your body is HQ, headquarters for your soul and your spirit,
if HQ is deceived, you're going to extend that deception in everything you do.
And how could you possibly understand the universe if you don't know what's going on in your own backyard
or even in your own skull?
So why don't we do that next time?
What do you think?
Yeah, let's earmark that for the next thing to talk about.
How the human body works and what this material container is about.
And just from a simple perspective, I mean,
this is just stuff that should have been taught to us when we were just out of diapers.
Well, exactly.
But, of course, before we were out of diapers,
we had to learn how to walk and talk and everything else, unlike the other animals.
Because we're 100% subject to external input.
That's what makes us unique.
So if anyone's going to walk away from the show tonight,
the things to remember is that we are not animals because we are subject to external input.
We're the animals or not.
I mean, yes, they can be trained, but we need everything from external sources.
And the gods can also be put to death, folks.
Sorry.
And when you die, it's just like being asleep without dreaming.
That's why it says, rest in peace.
That guy standing up there at a funeral talking about all this stuff doesn't mean jack,
because what's written in stone is what's written in stone.
And what's written in stone is rest in peace.
And that's it.
So I hope you guys enjoyed this, and I hope you have learned something.
Thank you, Greek.
We will do this next week with episode two.
All right.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion, and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years, and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein, is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO, and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367, and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
What kind of person are you?
How do you see yourself?
Are you the kind of person that lets everyone else do all the work,
just hoping that you'll be able to get some of the crumbs that fall from the table?
Or are you the kind of person that rolls up their sleeves and does the dirty jobs that no one else wants to do?
Are you hoping that all the activists giving their blood, sweat, and tears to serve humanity are going to solve all the world's problems?
Or are you just wondering, is there something simple I can do to contribute?
Yes. Yes, there is.
Help us. Help us do what we do.
Partner up with American Freedom Radio today by gifting a regular amount to support the network and your favorite hosts,
bringing you less commercials and more information.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and start donating today from between $1 and $100 per month,
according to the kind of person you are.
Thank you very much for your support.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit, and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape,
various pain-related health care costs, epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders, and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer, and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.