American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli has been reaped.
As reckoned by the Pope's work schedule, it is the 22nd day of January,
which is allegedly the first month of the year, 2016,
but by my reckoning this is the 16th episode of Ocelli and the Greek,
and I'm sure that the Greek would tell us, well, give us an idea anyway,
what the actual month and day is in reality.
It appears to be the last day of the 11th month, so New Year's is coming,
believe it or not, know it or not.
Yeah, if you're looking at the moon, it's pretty close, but not tonight, let's say.
I'd say it's the 31st day of the 11th month till noon.
So, yeah, there's a lot of moon mythology about the cycles of the moon
that they're trying to compress it into some kind of scientific rationale.
It doesn't work, but when you stick with the observational, it works very well.
So, yeah, it's the end of the 11th month.
Let's see, doesn't the prefix DEC, deco, or decim mean ten?
So, interesting how some things work really well that way.
Right, I remember studying the metric system, you know,
and I do recall that that was one of those prefixes that was used all the time.
So the DEC did indicate ten of a particular unit, if I remember correctly.
And what's interesting in the months before that, it means nine,
and the month before that means eight, and the month before that means seven.
So you get four chances out of the year to figure it out,
just like when you get a multiple choice question and answer test in the educational system.
They give you four choices to figure it out, but you know only one is correct.
Yeah, interesting there.
And, of course, since you've got nine, let's see now, ten, nine, eight, and seven,
that gives you one-third of the year kind of seeming to fall on the right calendar numbers.
Then that kind of means that you've got three-quarters of what is the alleged year falling out of sync.
Well, it's not out of sync.
You know, it's interesting, if you're reading old documents, especially in English,
they will use the after, let's say after the 1700s, they will use the Pope's work schedule dating.
But within the body of the text, for example, you'll see dated, for example, June 5th, 1730.
But within the body of the text, they're talking about this fourth month, you see.
It's very interesting.
So the people knew that they were somehow subjugated, just like today.
You know, when you talk about certain authorities, they're sort of accommodated in language,
but their people's actions act as if they don't exist.
You know what I mean?
Well, right, but they explained it directly by telling you the day of our Lord.
Hmm.
Which is a Lord is a, well, from back then, yeah.
Well, that's kind of silly, but it's not.
Well, that's why I made the point, because, you know.
A Lord is a landlord, or a, it's a, yeah, it's a pretty low title, even in the human realm.
Yeah.
It means Baal, by the way, in other languages, or Kyrios in Greek.
And what's typical, the reason they did that is because when you're a serf or a slave,
you, or subjugated, you automatically assume the religion of your master.
So let's say, you know, you have, well, here's an example.
You know, if you become captured by a Muslim authority and they force you to subjugation, guess what?
You are now to practice Islam.
Or if you're subjugated by whatever group, you practice that religion.
Look at the history of slavery in the U.S.
The indigenous people from another continent that were brought over here adopted the master's religion.
You see, these are just various examples.
Well, right, and that's something that has been omnipresent throughout history.
In fact, even look to the biblical text.
One will find the description of slavery and actually the use of it.
And fact is, if you notice in the details there, the slave does always wind up being compelled to honor the gods of the master.
Some way or another, yeah.
Otherwise, they wouldn't make a good slave.
And, you know, what happens to ones that are not good slaves?
And by the way, slavery is lawful and it's also legal.
It's just something that's not discussed in this society because this society is about deceiving you.
So, yeah, up is down, black is white, war is peace.
So, yeah.
You know, and that brings me directly to the concept of cosmic censorship that we often reference on this show.
And I think that it is difficult for the listener to appreciate the depth.
You may understand censorship in a general way and that this is a sort of governing element against communication.
You can be censored because you're being told what you can say and what you cannot say.
You're being told what ideas you are allowed to impart.
You're being told what practices you may be able to engage in, et cetera, et cetera.
But I think that it is often missed that censorship goes far beyond communication and interaction.
There is more to it.
Well, you don't really feel the censorship.
People don't sense it, not even intuitively, just like you don't feel atmospheric pressure.
If you're near sea level, you have 15 pounds per square inch pushing on you.
Now, that might not sound like a lot, but if you've ever gone to the gym and picked up a 15-pound dumbbell, even if you're fit, it's not light.
If you drop it on your foot from waist high, it will break bones in your foot.
So you have one of those weights on every square inch of your body, but you don't feel it because you're in equilibrium.
You see, the body is under a vacuum.
It's under a slight vacuum, which you've adopted to.
So what I mean by that is because the people that are bringing information to the public at large are also censored.
So they don't sense anything, you see, if that makes any sense.
You know, go to a mainstream or even alternative media source or university or schooling, and the people are all saying the same thing.
So there's equilibrium.
And those that don't say the same thing are the nutters or really fringe or conspiracy.
You see what I mean?
Because now you broke that equilibrium.
Well, yes, certainly, but I mean, look, there's two interesting points to make here, though, and I wonder how you would address them.
And they're pretty simple.
One, I have no memory in my lifetime where I believed that equilibrium was observable in my life.
I feel as though I was always at a place personally.
And given that and given that experience, I say to myself, if you're able to describe this and you are aware of it.
Greek.
How does cosmic censorship affect you?
I mean, wouldn't you as someone on this planet also be subject to it?
Sure.
But there is the irony of it.
In other words, you see, it's part of it is very firm and part of it is even firmer, like six feet of steel.
There's no way you'll dig out of that.
But the other part of it is like a cheap sweater.
If you find the thread and you pull on it, it comes apart really fast.
So there's, you know, it depends on what you've maybe been granted or seen or, you know, the concept of fate.
I was asking someone about subject matter tonight and they said, why don't you talk about how you woke up?
Right. So maybe a breaking of equilibrium.
Like you mentioned, you have an equilibrium and that's real short.
It's not about waking up.
It's about what path you're on, because, for example, if you go to someone who is very indoctrinated in the system, that's their path.
Good luck, you know, or it's not going to happen.
They're not going to really venture off of that path.
But for myself, I'll give a little personal story.
When I was very young, you know, in European families, they have get togethers.
And eventually, when the adults relax, they let the children speak.
And I was probably still in my late formative years, I guess, nine or ten.
When they came up to me, I said, I'd like to know what the truth is.
And they said, about what?
I said, about everything.
And the parents and some other relatives pulled me out of the room and smacked me around real good and said, don't ever ask that question again.
And after they did that, I said, that's all I'm going to ask the rest of my life.
So that was the breaking of equilibrium for me.
And that's all it took.
But there's breaking points that everyone has.
But in essence, this is when I say cosmic censorship, it's the entire ship that is censored, you see.
But you still have certain freedoms within there to look.
But you have to realize that it's also the you have the censorship.
And then you also have the very strong influence of an adversarial force.
And we've identified that very clearly.
And from the clarity that we like to give, it might sound really strange because not only are we very clear and specific, even though some may not think so,
we also give sources where people can go and look.
I don't want to spoon feed, but this is also a time you and I come together and do this show.
And I've said repeatedly, it's not time to discuss, you know, many things.
But let's maybe discuss what can be discussed and maybe touch upon things that haven't or shouldn't be at this point.
So this is a very interesting venture of the Ocelli and the Greek thing, you know.
And I think when we bring up these topics like something like cosmic censorship, if anyone has to, you know, if you're going to wrestle with it, that's good because it's not simple.
Right. And but it does exist and it's very clear that it does exist on many levels.
No. And that's true. But, you know, still, because coming from the perspective that I come from.
Right. I mean, after all, look, unless you can relate to something based on your own past experiences,
it becomes impossible to to sort of internalize it, to really hear it.
You know what I mean? For instance, somebody who has no clue what metalwork looks like,
if you explain to them about metal and they've never seen a piece of metal which has been forged or cast,
you're going to sound like you're describing, you know, something completely fantastic that absolutely makes no sense.
There usually needs to be a linkage between common experience or common observable things in order to make that point stick at all.
Wouldn't you say? Yeah, there is. But, you know, there's an interesting film about that called Flight of the Phoenix.
As I'm going to about that is the analogy I'd like to make a bunch of guys crash a plane in the desert
and they're trying to piece together a plane to get out.
And one guy takes the lead and says, build it like this so we could fly out of here.
And then they find out at the end of the film that he's never built a plane before.
He's only been a model plane builder and they all wanted to strangle him.
And he's like, what's the difference? It's just scale. It's the same principle.
Right. So the scale that I like to give as an analogy is, you know,
go to a parking lot and point up to the sky and look at that tic-tac-toe in the sky.
You know, that's pretty deliberate. And trails like that don't form.
There's got to be particulates that are deliberately sprayed and deliberately flown in that pattern.
And some people just don't see it. That's a form of censorship, you see.
Well, right. But I often attribute that to the fact that people generally don't look up at the sky.
That's one thing. So they don't take the action to observe something, which is yet another point here.
I mean, there are many things that go on right in front of people's eyes on a daily basis.
And they don't recognize what they're really looking at or they don't recognize what they've heard.
But what if I gave you the example that I've actually said that to people that were hobby astronomers
and they still didn't want to see it, see what I was discussing or hear what I was discussing about it.
It's interesting. Right. So go to and to prove that, just go to any mainstream university that has an astronomy department.
Start talking about chemtrails. We'll show you the door. Right.
And all they do is look at the sky. So there's many levels to it.
But the thing is, being specific about it is difficult. And here's the thing.
How about we've been or myself have been as specific as I believe.
And there's a believe word which I rarely use should be discussed openly at the moment,
because we've also brought up the concept of the operating system and what is lawfulness.
And, you know, and I think the topic I wanted to discuss tonight was nothing.
What is nothing and what's interesting when you look at that, you actually find that it's there's more to it.
And it will indirectly also answer a couple of questions we've had on the e-mails,
the Ocelli in the Greek website. Oh, right. Which we should mention.
Ocelli in the Greek dot com has a contact form where we are more than happy.
And both of us have taken time to answer questions and to respond to e-mails there as well.
Just for a people's, you know, for people's chances to interact.
In case you don't like chat rooms and you'd like to simply privately send us a message,
a thought or a question that can be done there at Ocelli in the Greek dot com.
They can also click on where it says Ocelli in the Greek on the e-mail.
They don't have to fill out the contact form right above it as well.
And that will use their default e-mail. Right. Right.
That's true. So there is a way you can actually anonymously contact us if you like as well.
And, you know, it becomes one of those things you struggle with.
And, yeah, I do want to lead into that topic for certain.
But first, I'm trying to show people the noise before we show them the silence.
You know, there's a lot of possibilities and there's a lot of challenges that can be made,
say, to many of the statements that you make.
If one turns around and says, OK, you've described adherence to your God.
You've said that all people in one way or another obey the laws of their God,
whether they recognize the fact that they have a God or not.
In instances where we've discussed atheism, I find it fascinating and extremely enlightened to say that
if you're an atheist but you're absolutely obeying the laws of your locality, state and whatever,
then you have chosen to adopt the state as your God. And I believe that is correct.
And also most modern pagans, if you ask a modern pagan, which God do you subscribe to?
And they don't know. So that would also put them in the atheist.
Atheist just means Godless. You know, it would be like you're just not interested in subscribing to something.
Like if you don't know how to fly an airplane, you would be an apilot, right?
But anyway, so it just means you're without that aspect.
And what I'd like to bring forward is that divine aspect.
Now, here's the thing. Whenever you discuss the gods or anything like that,
the majority of the audience and people's minds automatically go to that R word, religion.
And what the religions have done is hijacked the memorialized information.
And they've portrayed it in the most repugnant manner, all of them.
And any sane, rational person that has any initiative to be, let's say,
sane and rational would not subscribe to any worldly religion if they examined it.
Right. So when this topic is discussed, you're like, oh, what's the Bible like?
No, because no one I've met. I've never really met anyone who's read it.
And I'm sure there are people out there who have. And the King James is not what I'm discussing.
That is a version that's very corrupted.
If you and also if you want to piece together all of the religions in one lump,
you can easily say that none of them do anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
So in essence, the world is plunged into a theism.
Correct. Correct. And that's why lack of identification.
These are very specific things. Yeah. Well, that's the other thing.
And hidden in some of these versions, though,
we do find references that that tell you what it is you're adhering to,
if you're adhering to the text and that and that becomes a little confusing.
Very confusing, because especially in English, in English.
Yeah. You're turning around and I'll throw this hint at you.
Quite often people are adhering to the God figure.
I will describe him as Zeus. Right. And they don't even realize it.
I know you can do a very simple what they call psychological experiment.
You know, if you if you if you're, let's say, addressing a crowd of people and you said,
well, I want you to describe an image after I say a word. Right.
And they'll say, fine. And you say, God. And so, OK, ask everyone, what do you see?
And they say, well, I see a guy with a beard in a toga sitting on a, you know, in a big chair.
I said, well, that's the image of Zeus in the from the Temple of Zeus in Olympia.
Or, you know, that that's not what you'll get out of any text that's been memorialized for thousands of years.
Right. The same thing if you say J.E.S.U.S.
You see a real skinny guy with long hair nailed to a cross wearing a loincloth who looks kind of white, by the way.
Yeah. But if you say Joshua to people, they don't get an image like that.
No, you see. So there's an interesting connection. This is where it's all external input.
You see their hands. How many times do people convey in a motorized wagon?
It's not an automobile because it was an automobile. You wouldn't have to put fuel in it.
And think actually are thinking about what they're doing. Oh, here comes a stop sign.
Oh, here I need to press the brake or here I need to accelerate. It's almost involuntary action.
Right. So what these religions have done and the state and any group, because, you know, there are subgroups within there.
Right. They want to get people involved in certain actions where they don't think about what they're doing.
Right. Right. Right.
OK, so when you couple that with a cosmic censorship and let's tie it back to the cosmic censorship,
there's a sense of having a lawful mind where if you know how to read with comprehension and you read something that a claim is made.
OK, and if it's not rebutted and it seems like it stands and it can be validated.
Well, guess what? It needs to be taken seriously. Right now, if you don't have a lawful mind.
Well, it doesn't matter. I think we gave like a foreclosure document as an example once.
Yes, we did. And, you know, what that leads me to and we discussed this,
there's a lawful claim which one can examine if they study the biblical text.
There is a chief deity who describes having created everything and it has not been challenged.
And I understand that. And outside of biblical as well, Mahabharata and the Koran as well.
Oh, yeah, absolutely. The same thing is described in those texts.
But here's something to consider as well.
Simply because a claim has not been rebutted does not mean that it has been validated either, in my estimation.
How do you validate it? How do you validate it? Exactly.
Well, typically it's different than verifying, right?
Verifying and validation are similar but not the same.
The easiest way to validate something like that would be in an ancient text would be by using history,
the recordation of events. Now, for example, let's not even go back to ancient times.
If you go to university right now and you read about the JFK assassination,
in every history book they have that Oswald shot him from the book depository, correct?
Correct. And we know that's not true. If we look forensically into other things,
in other words, what the culture was like, not the general culture that still is extended into today,
but the culture of the people that were involved in the incident immediately around that event.
If you start looking at that, you'll see there were so many more things,
and just things that were either obfuscated or things that were just made up.
The same with 9-11 and many other things.
When you start to go back to these ancient texts,
what you will find is you will have to find something in history that correlates with it.
Right. Now, let's go back to the JFK assassination.
If you go to the book depository window where allegedly, you know, you'll see there's no line.
You see that that could not have happened that way, according to the history that we're being given.
Now, if you look at forensic history, not necessarily, like, look at history forensically.
We're not talking about things, you know, about civilizations that were buried millions of years ago.
But just going back very carefully, you will find out that the culture of the people around those events
needs to be understood as well.
Using the JFK assassination again, what I mean by the culture is if you do some searching on what happened that day,
you will find there was a very heavy influence by the intelligence culture,
like the intelligence agencies, police authorities, politicians, other people that worked for the state.
That is a separate culture within society.
Right. They have their own way of their own allegiances and their own like subculture within the group.
Right. So when you start to address all of these ancient documents, for example,
let's look at some of the that come out of the Hindu part of the world.
You will notice there's some fantastic things that were supposedly happening a thousand years ago,
two thousand years ago, three thousand years ago that are not being discussed in secular or modern history.
Same thing in the biblical text. But when you start looking at the culture surrounding it,
you will begin to see more of the evidence.
Well, right. I mean, a lot of things are represented as having happened that are I hate to use this term,
but almost magical in a sense. There seem to be a bit more of a supernatural atmosphere that prevailed based on the reports
and the accounts from the time. Sure. Sure. Supernatural. Yes.
Like I'd like to give rocketry as an example, but that's been around for thousands of years.
You know, where you stuff a tube with chemicals and you make it go up in the air.
That's nothing to really brag about. But or an airplane, you know, people have seen things fly in the sky.
But what I mean about culture is, for example, let's take the biblical text.
If you go into the Middle East and you look at the culture, even today,
when a particular character becomes infamous or viewed in a negative light,
an effort an effort is made to eliminate any recordation of that person ever existing.
Now, this is very difficult for Westerners to comprehend because it would be akin to like, oh, Chuck is a bad guy.
So we're going to eliminate his existence. And we also have to go and destroy the birth certificate as if he was never born.
Now, if you try to go do that, well, the government won't let you do that because that's tampering with official documents.
You see what I mean? Even though they have done things like that have disappeared.
Let's say from the conspiracy side documents and people in the V.A. and such.
But this is normal in the Middle Eastern culture where you will find it going all the way back to the Egyptian times.
You will see that there are obfuscations on temple walls scraped off where inscriptions were made.
Also, a reference, if anyone wants to reference it, it still should be pretty fresh on the Internet.
I was doing research on this about Hosni Mubarak, the Egyptian president who was supposedly ousted during the Arab Spring.
And there were a few articles popping up on how there were people coming out, secular and non-secular, religious,
saying we need to wipe his name from all the records. Now, how do you how do you eliminate his existence?
I think he ruled over Egypt for a good, what, three decades plus or something, right?
So how do you they wanted to eliminate every record, you know, find every newspaper article that mentioned him and redact it.
Every, you know, all of his existence. And they were like, well, we're a little too westernized for that now, you know, was the answer.
So this is this was normal in the ancient kingdom.
Well, let me interject something, too. I know for a fact, after studying some bit of Babylonian history,
that the kings of Babylon often did this to those that defied them and that they defeated.
This was one of the commands that was given by all of these guys that we have heard about.
I mean, recently memorialized in Hollywood films like like Darius and Xerxes and people like that.
But believe it. This was not something just exclusive to them.
Babylonian kings would demand that any trace of someone who defied them,
someone who acted against their lawful command of a population, whatever, would be completely stricken from the record.
No images of them. No records of their existence were supposed to exist after they were killed,
after their uprisings were put down. I mean, that was that that's just a fact of ancient history, to my understanding.
Yeah. And it's also part of the culture, because if you displace that culture or end that custom, then that practice goes away.
You see, this is these things that we're discussing are cultural specific, just like, for example,
the intelligence services in the Western world have their own culture. Correct.
It seems to be almost beyond belief and imagination what they do. Right.
And that's why I stress all the time that there is an intelligence community which is not the same as the intelligence agencies,
that there is an interaction, a community of individuals, literally speaking,
that coalesce together based on mutual principles, et cetera, et cetera.
Trust me when I tell you people in the Mossad are absolutely interacting with people in the Central Intelligence Agency
who are acting with the secret police in any of the you know, pick a Central American country who are acting in concert with the you know,
the GRU and the former KGB guys and the you know, any of the name and intelligence service doesn't matter.
Am I whatever the hell? All of them interact in what I call an intelligence community.
It doesn't mean every single member of an agency. See, that's different than the community.
It doesn't mean every single member of an agency is part of that community,
but every single member of that community is definitely involved with one of those agencies.
Yeah, because most agencies today are extensions of the executive branch and they kind of skirt around judicial and legislative issues because of that.
But, for example, the small exception might be the CIA, which really came out of the army.
It was army intelligence after 1947, after the alleged Roswell crash to hide what the Americans were doing, still being at war with the Japanese.
You know, they told Truman, you don't want people to know that we're still at war with the Japanese, do you?
All right. So fund the CIA. And that was that.
That was so. But the interesting thing about the what they do is sometimes very difficult to imagine,
even though because of Hollywood has shown us a lot of it.
You know, recently I've heard several people trying to get a passport and how difficult it was.
You know, they had to go and get an interview and refill out the application.
And I just have to laugh. It's like I've met several people have four passports.
Five passports, you know, in different names and all this, you know, and obviously they're not your average Joe Schmo going to the passport office.
You know what I mean? So it's like, how do you pull that off?
You know, well, you know, there's a cult. There's some help you have to have.
So and it's it can manifest in with power. But going back, let's tie this all back to the cosmic censorship.
When you start to look at the claims being made, let's say in a particular text,
there is a specific area in the text, more than one area where it clearly states there will be a cosmic censorship.
And I'll actually mention how it's said.
It said, go out and close the eyes and ears of the people that these things would take place is one specific one.
And anyone could look up where that is. Right. And and then there is the concept of darkness.
All of the ancient texts warn about society or the darkness not being beneficial.
I mean, it is if you're growing mushrooms, let's say. Right. Or things like that.
It's not necessarily all evil or all bad things are in the dark.
But when the darkness in the spiritual realm overcomes a given domain, meaning the earth, things that are not going to be very good.
And if you actually look at how society is functioning, that is also true, because all the day is reckoned in the dark.
The New Year's reckoned in the dark. All of your products come from the dark. Right.
Well, right. I mean, the beginning mark of a day, according to the way the calendar is set up, is at the darkest point in the day.
So this is where you're supposed to begin the day. You can't see in the dark.
Right. So most people can't. Yeah, most people can't.
So there's the sense of what's great about this.
This is why I've spent a lot of time thinking about how to how to impart this type of information.
Is why I discuss you're in the credits part of that epoch or era, which is over 2000 years now, two and a half thousand years.
Because usually when an epoch or an year or an age ends, it starts wrapping up a quarter of the way.
Like when it's 75 percent through, it starts wrapping up and you start to see what the next age will be like.
That's why if you look at the modern age, you can go back to what's called New World Order, Age of Enlightenment, New Age thinking that started 150 some odd years ago.
You see, and it's and it's leading up to a time period that mankind is still not attained, let's say.
Right. It's still being discussed. You've heard of the term like New Age and all that stuff.
So that started a while back. Now, that's why I discuss it as being the credits portion.
And what's interesting about the credits portion is all things are revealed during this time to those who can see it.
So this is a good time to discuss these things. But the cosmic censorship is indeed coming from both sides, the positive and the negative side.
And that's pretty clear to see if we look at what's been memorialized.
Now, the thing here is to impart one's field of study.
Let's say this is not my opinion. And no, I don't believe in any of this.
I in other words, there's what is there to believe when you're imparting it.
But what I do have a personal belief in that these things are validatable and true.
And you can match these things up and you see how they actually affect reality. It's quite interesting.
Yeah, that's true. And I want to get back to this concept of darkness and the idea that a lot of people feel as though darkness is empty,
which it is no more empty than if light had been shown through it.
In my estimation, it may change in character, though. I mean, it certainly does seem to get colder when it's darker out.
It does seem to promote people to do things.
You know, a lot of things happen when it's dark out that don't happen in the broad daylight.
You know, we've heard that many, many times, right?
Nocturnal.
Yeah, that certain things occur in the nocturnal.
So there is a significant difference. But then again, there really isn't at the same time, right?
Well, let's look at it as being substantive. Some ancient texts discuss it was so dark.
One of them states it was so dark that the darkness could be felt.
OK, you might have seen in some modern sci fi films how they show like instead of being a white fog, it's like a black fog that descends.
Right. They use that a lot, especially when they now that they have computer graphics.
I've seen that a few times and I'm like, well, that's pretty accurate to how some events might have occurred along.
Eons ago, let's say. Right. If something is going to send a darkness is going to descend.
So one thing we've discussed also is that we're living in a very quiet, peaceful time, believe it or not,
even though with all the chaos that is going on, let's say it is very, very calm and peaceful time on the Earth.
If you want to discuss the contrast of the psyche or the mind of people today with, let's say,
the mind of the people a thousand years ago where 75 to 80 percent of the world's population was killed by natural disasters.
And you can go look this up. And I don't know if it's deliberate or because people don't know.
There's very little information about it on the Internet.
But between the years 800, what they reckon is 800 A.D. and 1000 A.D.,
there was tremendous carnage through the world, not by war, but by forms of pestilence and just natural disasters.
There are historians that have written about earthquakes that opened up schisms in the ground,
hundreds of miles long, hundreds of feet wide, and fires burned for 10 years,
blowing dark smoke that darkened the entire European continent.
And this is this record has been found. This is what they call the Dark Ages, for example.
So, yeah, there can be negative in that. But the Dark Ages, if one does, again, research,
try to do some research and outside of the Lancelot and Camelot and all the fairy tales that came out of the Dark Ages,
why is it that we're just given fairy tales about the Dark Ages and we're not given, you know,
we might be given some literary works from monks like Beowulf and things like that.
But why isn't that we're given any history like between 300 or 400 A.D. and 800 or 1000 A.D.?
Why is that area, that whole time blacked out?
It's a very interesting time because not only was it very interesting culturally,
how it's hidden from the modern world, but also this is where the legends of flying carpets came from.
Right. I mean, that's why that sounds pretty ridiculous, Greek flying carpet.
Yeah. But you know what? You want to hear something else ridiculous?
There's a lot of people that see things called flying saucers.
Doesn't that sound it's another household item that seems to be flying around these days, isn't it?
Well, that's true. Yeah.
So this was a very interesting. So if you actually look at what they call the Renaissance,
it was the mainstreaming or the dumbing down of what was to be accepted for us now.
But if you actually do some really good forensic research of what they call the Dark Ages,
you're going to start to see you want to talk about out of place technology and out of place artifacts.
That is a time period to look at. So this darkness thing, again, it goes both ways.
And this is you know, is it good? Is it bad? Well, you know, it doesn't sound good.
But if you actually look at that, that that time period, you will find things that are hard to find in general.
Go online, research it. You're not going to it's it's an area of history that's been blacked out.
But, yeah, the concept, again, I think this all ties back to the cosmic censorship.
What's what's great about discussing this now is just bringing the point.
I think it's I haven't really heard that used commonly or uncommonly.
It's quite original, I believe, from one perspective. But the the what we're describing is not original.
How many times have you heard in certain religious groups especially say, well, if you have eyes and ears,
it means it doesn't mean if you really have the physical eyes and ears or even if you can see with your eyes or hear with your ears.
It's not speaking about going to the eye doctor and getting an eye test or an ear doctor and getting an ear, ear test.
It's about do you can you perceive things that are, let's say, special?
Well, stress more on the you have part than the eyes and ears part, because if you have them,
if they are under your control, thusly, then it is a different story because you're able to see and to hear.
That's the way I've always taken it. Not so much a stress on the physical manifestations that they're referencing there,
but more more to the stress on the you have part, you know.
Yeah. One thing we haven't brought up and discussed here is also the concept of mastery or mastership or being a master.
That is no longer discussed. Very often you hear the term, sir, being used as being respectful.
And when people say that to me, I'm like, no, I'm not a sir.
Why are you demoting me? Because a sir is servant. That's when the Lord comes in.
Someone who has skills as a master. I remember the for example, the the what is it?
Batman. Alfred, did he call Batman, sir? What did he call him? Called him Master Wayne, didn't he?
Well, right now, interestingly, they refer to young men as masters.
And when they get older, they're called Mr. That's an odd thing.
I always thought of it as a reference to his juvenile state or it's a it's a twist.
And if anyone wants to research that part, you know, what's interesting is English.
English is not the favorite language for obvious reasons.
It's very poorly used. And I believe that I'm using that term again, that it's not benevolent.
It's not a benevolent tongue, so to speak. Right.
But from that, what I mean by mastery is this.
If you were to see someone who was a novice at doing something, a skilled trade, let's say,
they lack efficiency and economy of movement.
But if you see a master do it, he makes it look really simple because there's a set of rules that he remembers about certain things or she remembers about certain things.
And it is. And those rules have become rote. That's why.
Have you ever heard of like this is the secret recipe. Right.
And it's usually a very simple thing. It's just a very simple rule to remember to show mastery.
So what I'd like to bring forward is the operating system known as the mind works.
You where you get your rules and your laws from your God. It's very simple.
And once you see how simple that is and you find a God that has rules.
Right. Your life becomes very simple and you see how it actually does work.
But, you know, good fortune if you can find a God that has memorialized any laws. Right.
So this is up to the individual. And the thing is, I never recommend that anyone go and study these texts outwardly.
Personally, I might. Because why would I send you on a journey where you're going to try to read something you're never going to understand?
Or at least right now, it's really a very interesting thing.
And it's it's in one sense, it can be recommended to start studying.
But on the other sense, it's really close to the time period where this is going to be the subject matter.
We always tend to go back to the divine and the spiritual side of things.
We're almost at the precipice. Not quite where these things will become of great interest.
I mean, look at the political scenes right now.
Can you discuss any political topic where a religious topic is not thrown in there?
Well, no, that's becoming more and more prevalent as time goes on.
There are always these spiritual matters.
I hate even using the word religion because I have great appreciation for your characterization.
And I've kind of adopted it as well. You know, when you do something religiously, you can do anything religiously.
Religion is irrelevant.
It just means something like brushing your teeth or tying your shoelace, something you do regularly.
But the thing is that people are discussing, you know, if you look at the presidential race, the wars going on in the Middle East,
these non-secular topics are being brought up, let's say.
Are any of them accurate? Are any of them true? No.
But what it's doing is it's setting the mindset and priming in that direction, just like when you prime an engine to start it.
Is that how the engine is going to run? No, you're just priming it.
Or a pump, for example. This is prior to it going into full swing.
It's like pulling the ripcord on a chainsaw.
You see the actual saw move, but is it running? Not yet.
We're going to be going into a time period on a global level.
You know, this is why I very often have to chuckle at myself when people think that moving from one country to another is going to make their life better.
Now, if you like the cold and you live in the heat, move.
Or vice versa, but the political situation shouldn't be a reason to move unless they're really dropping bombs on you at the moment.
In which case, that's not very political anyway.
There's definitely a reason to move if your physical life is being harmed.
But the concepts that people have, people are so unaware that the entire world is going under a global system here shortly.
Not next year, not the year after, but shortly, meaning less than a decade or so.
It will be pretty much in place.
And everyone will just take it as if it's natural, like no big deal.
And it's going to be centered around the center of the earth.
Which is if you laid out a map of the earth, laid out flat, yes.
And draw a big X on it, where's the center?
And you'll find out where the center hub, because all things that go around come around.
Even in secular history, where did they tell you civilization started?
Mesopotamia.
Where do you think it's going to end?
Where the show will, the act will end.
Before a play starts, the curtains are closed.
And when the play is over, the curtains are closed.
It's very simple.
You leave the house in the morning, the car's in the garage, and you come back at night.
Where does the car go?
Back in the garage.
So this is what's happening.
But these are very big matters of the mind, and they're very simple.
That's why the mastery needs to be brought up.
The concept of mastery.
Try to master any skill.
And you'll notice that when you start to get to that level, there are these little secrets.
These little tricks of the trade.
Have you heard that?
That the novice or the hobbyist doesn't know of, if you're talking about a skill.
And then once they're known, the technique is discovered, then there's the practice.
And, like, for example, if you're a hobby, let's say you play tennis recreationally,
and you're thrown into a court with Pete Sampras, let's say a world-class tennis player,
you think, well, the ball is the same, the court's the same and all that,
but the game is so different that you might as well be playing hockey.
You can't function, even though you think you could.
So when you go to the mastership level from the novice level,
it's almost like a different game also.
That's why we keep discussing, very simply, the point that there's no religion on the planet
that does anything that's allegedly in the books that they subscribe to.
Because you have to be a novice to subscribe to a group like that, you see.
When you start to master what these things are based on, you walk away, you see.
And you start realizing the validity of these things.
The same goes with the scientific community.
If you want to study electricity and you go to university, you will leave with zero.
You will learn nothing about it, other than it hurts, and it shocks people,
and sometimes it turns people into dust if you put too much voltage on them.
But that's all. You won't know anything about electricity.
And the people that do learn about electricity put YouTubes up
and show how you could turn this motor on and unplug it and it still runs,
those are the people who know how electricity works.
Because back, I think it was in 1905,
the president of the American Electrical Engineer Society said,
there will be six months before we have an autonomous rotating device to produce electricity.
This was in 1905, and this was mainstream engineer, head of the engineering society, that said that.
This is not some guy like Tesla off to the fringe.
Where is it?
Well, there's your censorship and there's your adversary.
Oh, right, because after all, anything that would be far too beneficial is often discouraged.
Let's be kind. Discouraged, right?
So here we go.
If you're pursuing the deity that you pursue, you will serve that deity,
and that deity will put back to you what you what you approach them for.
Like, well, you know, one more thing, like there's some some kind of, quote, unquote,
constitutional crisis going on on the north, on the upper left corner of the country.
Right. If I give too many specifics, I guess people figure it out.
Well, have they ever read the Constitution? At least the first.
Why did they go past the first 17 words if they did and they still want that document?
Well, it ain't going to be a happy ending.
And I don't mean a Thai massage, happy ending.
I mean, ain't going to be a happy ending like things aren't going to work out the way you were told.
Because what if you read the first line of the Constitution, get around the 16, 17, 18 word.
It's about reviving the ancient Babylonian goddess religion, it says, to establish justice.
The reason people came here is to escape that.
And they're telling you that they're establishing it.
Yeah, and we discussed this at length in an earlier episode, I forget which number it was.
But if you look back in the archives, you'll find us discussing the Constitution and exactly what it means
relating to these concepts of liberty and justice.
These are two words which are actually revolting.
And yes, I understand the context by which people attempt to use them.
It does not mean that that is what is being invoked by the use of the language.
Well, if you need to be competent, like for example, you and I walk into a room and we say that's a blender
and it's plugged in and someone says, well, I heard that's something good.
Let me put my hand in it and turn on the switch.
Well, you better, you know, this is exactly, I used to put in the chats and I'll say it.
These guys should take up rapping like hip-hop and get into a beef and then do a shootout
because then it'll be legitimate.
Anyway, right, you've heard about rappers, you know, oh, that was shootout happened.
It was, yeah, because they had a beef, you know.
But if you're not a rapper, not into hip-hop, there's no legitimate beef to shoot
other than you're just dumb.
But anyway, let's just leave that alone.
Yeah, well, anyway, you know, we are coming close to the end of this hour.
And I think in the second hour, what I would like to address is this concept of, well, emptiness, nothingness.
What is nothing?
And, you know, I think that that will be one of the most fascinating hours we've ever done
because I am dying to hear actually what it is that you have to say.
Well, we're going to bring up that part about dying as well because that will clearly define that.
That's one of the requests we've had to discuss.
That was the joke, Mr. Greek.
Anyway, just in case somebody didn't get it because maybe I didn't either.
It's okay.
So we have a few more minutes.
And what I also want to bring up is the concept of cyber begging.
I hear that donations are what are required to keep things going.
But on the other hand, you have to remember that everyone is volunteering for this type of work.
The network and yourself and many others, and almost you could say countless others in the alternative media,
let's say, are volunteering.
Isn't that interesting?
This is all volunteer work.
And the concept of donation, there's got to be, I've always said there's got to be another way to say it,
but this has all been free.
So, you know, behind the scenes I joke about it, you know, about it's, you know, it's a form of cyber begging.
And because it's gotten to the point where when something is free or accessible,
free could be an acronym like F.R.E.E.
I think it might stand for from revenue emanated elsewhere.
So when something is free to you, that revenue had to be gotten from somewhere else.
Right. You know, even even if it's right.
Jeez. So, you know, some some effort had to have gone into it.
So the concept of cyber begging at this point needs to be either adjusted or implied
and somehow overlapped with the concept of everyone that is within the sound of our voices
and also accesses the Internet to come to, let's say, American Freedom Radio.
They have to realize that it's pretty much all volunteer work.
But there are things that require, let's say, in the legal term,
that people are being that are doing the volunteer work are being done.
D.U.N.N.E.D. or Dunning, which means they're being sent bills.
And there are things that have to be accommodated on that end in order to keep it going.
Like, what if we were to say this is the last Ocelli in the Greek show?
It just is. There's just we're not volunteering anymore because we've got to go
and flip burgers to sustain what it takes for us to come and volunteer.
Now, here's the funny thing. I know you're not on Facebook, but it almost was.
If you saw my Facebook post recently, I almost was not able to show up because of being done.
So, yeah, that's something that happened.
And I did receive support and I do appreciate all those who did that.
You guys mean the world to me because this is very important, what it is we're doing.
And I think value for value is something that needs to be honored at all times.
And that sounds like a fairly lawful concept to me, Greek.
Hmm. Yeah, well, think of it as gas in the tank.
That too.
That too. So all of those things can be done.
If you go to American Freedom Radio dot com and hit the donate button.
Guess what? You're not really donating. You're helping keep things running.
And also same prevails at Ocelli in the Greek dot com and Ocelli dot com.
All of it is appreciated and all of it keeps us going.
Stay tuned for the next hour. We discuss nothing.
What is American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us for free education.
Well, that's obviously a factor. But apart from reversing the dumbing down of America.
All the information they provide is free.
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from then?
Exploiting commonplace corruption.
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
They never censor, hang up or cut off their guests.
Well, that's no fun, is it?
Well, they created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shills and scum.
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from.
Exposing commonplace corruption.
Helping vulnerable people without a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
And creating a fantastic commercial free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream and alternative media shills and scum.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotic.
Freedom.
Oh yes, I like it very much.
Radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth?
And none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant.
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO and is 100% gluten free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
This is Rick Simpson and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
Tell the truth. Don't be bullshitting people.
There's enough bullshit as it is. In fact, there's just enough.
Did you know that?
There's just enough bullshit to hold things together in this country.
Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation.
Where would we be without our safe, familiar American bullshit?
Land of the free, home of the brave, the American dream.
All men are equal, justice is blind, the press is free.
Your vote counts.
Business is honest, the good guys win.
The police are on your side.
God is watching you.
Your standard of living will never decline.
And everything is going to be just fine.
The official national bullshit story.
I call it the American Okie-Doke.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
The network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are
American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
the only broadcast information
the sonic entity known as Ocelli.
Hour number 2 of episode 16 of Ocelli in the Greek begins now.
So, we were having a brief discussion
just before the end of the last hour
and I do promise you we're going to focus
on nothing in this hour but
perhaps you want to do a little housekeeping here
and finish up with where you were going in the first hour, Greek?
Oh yeah, it's real interesting
because I was thinking about that
today more than other times about how we volunteer.
When I say we meaning the corporate we or non-corporate we
however you want to look at it
come together to do volunteer work essentially
and it's pretty normal for people to say
hey, I do volunteer work. Okay, what do you do?
Well, I do this radio show once a week
for two hours on a minor internet radio station
and they're like, oh, really? Okay.
They expect me to say something like homeless shelter
or food bank or something like that, right?
But this is, let's just say
okay, let's take food bank. Maybe this is
thought for food.
Think about that for a minute
instead of food for thought.
That's why I tell people, you hear the word being bandied around
brainwashing. Okay, well how about washing your brain?
That doesn't sound so bad. Wash your brain from brainwashing.
How about thought for food instead of food for thought?
One sounds like a glutton, the food for thought.
Let's be more impeccable about it
and for us to be impeccable
it requires a little more impeccable support
and it doesn't mean to
start asking about things because I've heard of people
saying, oh, that's really distasteful. I kind of tune out when
people are asking for money, quote unquote, right?
It's kind of distasteful or whatever, but
on one end, let's just say it, most of the alternative
media community is broke-ass.
They're pretty broke.
There are a few people out there that do enjoy coming to the
non-center line or the mainstream
because I have to find another word for alternative as well
because there's got to be an alternative to the alternative, Chuck
and you know about that.
I describe it more as
honest media because it is not
being controlled by virtue of those
that sponsor it
and really for two reasons. One,
for the most part there is no sponsorship and secondly
those that do on occasion
sponsor it are not doing it
for the purposes of controlling it. They're doing it for the purposes
of supporting it. So this is why there is a difference.
Those that, obviously listen,
if you're a drug company and you're sponsoring
something like a news channel,
you're not going to find people going on that news channel
and saying terrible things about
the drugs you're pushing, right?
You're not going to find people that are sponsored
by McDonald's going and
telling you that that's not really food.
It doesn't happen that way, does it?
Because there's censorship.
Like here, and I'll say it, even AFR,
you'll get the best dummy loads on the internet
and we're including us for some people.
We are better, when I say we meaning
AFR, than most of the stuff only because of
the central core theme
of those who run AFR is always
the two rules are have fun and have fun.
So, I mean, you're not going to find this anywhere else.
And what's interesting, I took this so seriously
that I actually did a research on the search engine
how to beg for money successfully, right?
So I found something titled how to beg for money successfully.
It's in Hub Pages. It was written by the Pope's work schedule
on August 20th or something, 2014.
I don't really see the author's name here, but I just want to do a quick
read on this just to give people a handle on
where I'm coming from because this is what I'm struggling with
and maybe I don't have to. I'll just read this real quick. It's pretty short.
It's called Begging for Dummies. Okay.
I'm not really into begging for money. However, I've had a lot of experience
seeing beggars on the streets of New York City, so I thought I'd give a short
tutorial on how to beg for money successfully.
Besides, you never know when these tips might come in handy.
Times are hard, so pay attention.
First of all, I would like to mention some places are not good places
to set up to shop and beg for money. These are places like
parks and gyms. These areas are no good because people
who are going to them don't have any money. They are either busy running
with their headphones in their ears or they just don't have a wallet on them,
so forget about those areas. Other areas that I think would not do
as well are intersections on highways. People are in their cars and they just
it isn't easy to look the other way or
they turn up the radio and they ignore you. Interesting.
Okay. I know because I've done it.
Turn my radio up and look the other way.
Don't beg on highways. The best places to beg for money
successfully are in front of like Starbucks, high-end grocery stores, and
gentlemen's clubs. The reason these places work so well is first off,
people who are going to them have money in their pockets.
Secondly, they feel guilty about spending five bucks on a frigging cup of coffee,
a quarter pound of potato salad, or a woman who is taking off
her clothes. In case you weren't born Jewish or Catholic, guilt works.
You might be wondering about the men's clubs.
Well, studies have shown that four times as many men give to beggars
than women. Not only that men's clubs are super expensive,
at least that's what I've heard,
so if I was a beggar, that's where I'd go.
Finally, if you're going to make a habit out of begging for money,
not that there's anything wrong with that,
don't keep frequenting the same spot. People become beggar fatigued
and cynical. I know you are begging,
but that doesn't mean you have to forego all self-respect and dignity.
Hit up a new corner for a change. Be creative.
No one wants to give to a bum. You have to look like you are in
short-term jam so the people who are giving you can relate to you
and not feel like they're just throwing away their money.
That's where the bucks are, so have a good story and look decent.
They want to feel good about giving you money, and if they feel like
they are just supporting some loser,
they're not going to give you anything.
In order to beg successfully, you have to look like their brother or sister
or something they feel like they're contributing to society
instead of throwing their good, hard-won money into a black hole,
even though, let's be honest, that's probably what they are doing.
If it has come to this for you and you have to resort to begging,
I hope at least you take my recommendations and excel at it.
After all, you might be as good at that or something else.
Anyway, I just wanted to read that.
Thanks for letting me take the time to read it because I thought it was well put together
and some of the points there are things that people go through in real life
when they're in need.
In a sense, because everything here, AFR, what we're doing,
what other hosts are doing, it's all voluntary work.
In a sense, no one pushed us, no one put a gun to our head,
no one says we'd get money for doing this.
But there come times within the events that take place with trying to do these things
that you will be in need of things, money or whatever, to keep things going.
I just wanted to bring that up that it is a good idea.
Unfortunately, just like the article stated, don't beg at the same corner every time.
But we just happen to be at the same corner every what they call Friday night,
so we don't want to do it, constantly asking for it.
So give generously and give frequently if possible, and anything will help.
Right, exactly.
And truth is, no, nobody really wants to do this, but the reality is it must be done.
And it's not a matter of greed or anything like that.
I've heard it compared, and I'm glad you picked that article.
I've never read it, but definitely glad you picked it
because I've often heard it described as cyber panhandling or virtual panhandling before,
which is effectively what they were talking about.
On this end, we're on the cyber end.
This is more of a general how to beg for money successfully.
In a sense, having a beg-a-thon is good as well.
A lot of the private TV stations do it, or this one, I think it's public,
or petroleum broadcasting or something.
What is it called, PBS?
Yeah, but in this case, there come times, you know,
because everyone here is doing it on a volunteer basis.
Nothing was ever promised, but it's being done.
But again, the reason I'm bringing the point up is because matters do arise
where you're being done, and what do you do?
And you know what?
You and I are not the only ones in the room from a cyber perspective.
This is probably going to be archived, and people will hear this over and over.
So if you do hear this down the stream, you know what to do.
There you go.
So breaking away from that just because, and I don't ever like to do this,
but listen, a non-sequitur occasionally is appropriate.
It seems as though it is a non-sequitur, but who knows where we'll go.
The concept of nothing or nothingness or emptiness,
all of these things seem to be equated together.
All right, so you want to talk about nothing.
But let's talk about nothing.
Yeah, that's what we're going to do.
This was an interesting concept because when people say, you know,
what's in the box?
Nothing.
Oh, really?
And a lot of smart, wise-ass people, there's air in the box.
You know, what's interesting, we did, I think the first time we got together,
we spoke about 100% external input.
So if you really could be put into a situation of nothing,
if all of our mind is being inputted into us, isn't that something?
Isn't that something?
That's how you say it.
So the concept of nothing is very difficult for people to perceive.
And this is not philosophical, by the way,
because what this does is it offers a part of what is tangibly intangible.
Yes, the intangible can be tangible in one's thoughts.
But try to imagine nothing,
which I believe the etymology in the English just means none of something
or a no count.
What's interesting is when we go for the etymology in other languages,
let's look at more specific languages.
Let's look at, for example, the Greek, which would be tipota,
which usually an A in front of a word makes it the opposite, right, in Greek,
like theist is God and atheist would be without, okay, or atypical.
But basically tipota puts the A at the end to kind of validate something.
But what's interesting,
the word for nothing in Greek means something that is atypical
or not typical to anything that we can perceive.
Now, in the Hebrew or the Chaldean or Babylonian,
it would be a word, several words to define it,
but on a spiritual level, it would be ayin,
which literally means the beginning or the head of something very, very small
that you have to believe exists is what that word means.
So in both cases,
even when, let's say, in the Greek and the Chaldean, Babylonian, Hebrew,
those are the mainstay languages on the planet right now,
those two words basically mean something atypical or something you're not going to get a chance to perceive,
but it's still something there, which is very interesting, right?
Well, see, no thing means the lack of, I mean, I just look at the word in and of itself
and I say to myself, nothing means no thing.
And that's all there is to it.
But isn't air a thing?
If there's nothing in the box, can't you compress the air and make it into a liquid?
Well, but in that sense, even if you have a vacuum where there is no air,
you still have space.
Yeah, you have space, and space is, you know,
what's interesting is to throw this in for the techies,
is when the, during the time of the, what do you call it, the Soviet bloc,
you know, scientists, people couldn't go in and out,
and they didn't have television, and I'm not kidding about this,
they had one channel and no one watched it.
But they had these incredibly classically trained scientists, I mean, incredible,
I mean, they were trained in the classics, so they weren't diverted in many ways,
and they did incredible experiments,
like let's drill the deepest hole in the world and find out what happens.
You know, they did things like this in the Soviet Union from the 50s all the way to the 80s.
One of the things they did was in a laboratory, drew an incredibly low vacuum,
and they started probing around in there,
and they found that it was extremely energetic from an electrical perspective.
And the lower they drew the vacuum,
the more of these strange magnetic and electrical fields were developing, you see,
that were measurable.
So that's for the techie side of it.
So what's interesting here is when we look at the finest things,
when something becomes so fine and so small that it's imperceivable and intangible,
we tend to call it nothing.
But the language, the classic languages,
tell us that it's something that we need to relax about, that there's still something there,
but just believe in it, and it implies almost that you have to work with it.
If you look in a lot of the sciences, like, for example, you've heard of vitamins, okay?
Well, the word vitamin comes from vitality,
and the father of modern-day vitamin studies, or one of them that led the way,
was a man named Rudolf Hoschka,
and he wanted to find what gave food, when we consume animals and people consume food,
it gives us vitality, good food gives us vitality,
and certain foods give us different vitalities, right?
So, like, you know, like the prevention of scurvy, you got scurvy if you didn't have this,
or, you know, various conditions would arise if you were deficient of certain vital foods.
So he wanted to find out what was vital in the food.
So he would add, like, spinach extract and extracts of various plants to bacteria and fungus,
and then he would deprive others of it, and he would see conditions that would arise the same in a human.
But at one point in his studies, he figured that maybe we don't have to directly add to it,
maybe just put the two vials, the spinach extract near the bacteria,
and both in glass containers, separate from each other, and see how it would affect it.
And very often, just having the vital spinach extract next to the living organism almost had the same effect.
You see?
So he kept writing that, well, they wanted to know, well, how did that action happen?
You know, there's glass and there's air in between, and there's glass, and then there's the other thing.
How does it go through all of that?
And he tried to describe there's something called nothing that we don't understand.
Now, by the way, let me just put it this way.
If you understand and study Rudolf Hoschka, by the way, there's a cosmetic line in Europe that's named after him,
and if you're into, like, $100 lipstick and $150 face makeup, that's the stuff to get,
and it's worth every penny of it, by the way, because of its quality.
But from the other point, if Hoschka was alive today and he saw what people call vitamins,
the way they're taken and the way they're processed and all that, he would just, you know, have a conniption,
like they say back east, right?
He would just scream.
He would light his hair on fire and run down the street naked.
It's completely misunderstood.
He also discovered that once these extracts are removed and isolated,
they only have a vitality for a few days or a week or two or definitely no more than a lunar cycle.
So, you know, when people buy these vitamins and things, they've already lost their vitality.
That's why the European doctors say Americans have the most expensive urine in the world,
because it just goes in and out.
So there's many examples.
That was just a technical example, just to tie in with nutrition and things, how nothing,
there's got to be something, there's action at a distance.
Newton discussed that.
You know, what is action at a distance?
You know, doesn't it seem like things move through nothing?
So there really is no concept of nothing.
I mean, there's just the concept of nothing, but there's still something there.
The concept of an electrical generator is bogus.
Electrical generators don't generate electricity any more than a water pump generates water.
All it's doing is rotating and capturing the static field in the air, like static electricity,
and turning it into a high-pressure system through the coils and sending it down a wire.
The wire is reflecting.
So there is this concept of nothing in many ways, because there's still something there.
We cannot escape something.
There's only one place where the concept of nothing is brought to us,
and that is when we are sleeping and when we are dead, where there's no consciousness.
So in other words, consciousness and something are related.
And unconsciousness, when we no longer exist individually or whatever, nothing else exists.
And that's the true nothing that we can experience within the minds that we have currently.
Well, and there you go, because honestly, when I sleep, I am aware of the passing of time.
There is a difference between that and certain states which I can reach otherwise,
where time is not something that is tangible to me,
where there appears to be a period of nothing that connects to other periods of awareness.
But there's still something there doing it.
Well, yeah, it seems like it, but I can't really describe it.
Well, that could be a personal endeavor that you might want to be like Edgar Allan Poe and write about it,
because he, I think, tried to write about certain things like that.
But from one perspective, if you are truly restfully sleeping,
you might remember when you woke up that you did go to sleep or you're dozing off,
but there is no time.
Time is, by the way, the recordation of events.
If you don't record events, there's no time.
Like if you're really busy into something that you like doing,
you'll look at the wind-up toy known as the clock, and it's 8 o'clock in the morning.
A half hour later, you look at the clock, and it's 3 o'clock.
You're like, wait a second.
I thought only a half hour went by.
How did six hours go by, you see?
So it's just how you're perceiving things.
And I don't want to become relativistic.
This is not relativity at all.
This is just the consciousness.
I was kind of discussing this.
For example, have you ever heard of the concept of when people get into a car accident
or you know you're in an accident, all of a sudden time goes by really slow?
This is one of the examples I seize upon all the time.
Yeah.
The reason that happens is very simple is because you have cognitively,
let's say you're in the front seat and someone's in the back seat,
and they're sleeping or reading a magazine.
When you're in the front seat facing the same vantage point as the driver
and you're going 40 miles an hour and a car comes across right two feet in front of you,
you know that within two to eight milliseconds you're going to make contact.
That's a very short period of time.
But a second is a long time if you're into Olympic events.
So all of a sudden when you decide that this is going to be a car accident, time seems to stop.
The guy in the back seat who is looking at a magazine is not aware of that.
He just feels a big bang, doesn't even know what happened.
Time for him does not seem to be slow when he gets hit with the back of the driver's seat at 40 miles per hour.
He doesn't know what happened.
It's lights out.
He says one minute I'm reading the magazine, the next minute it's lights out.
But for the people that already acknowledge that they're going to be into an accident, it's just really slow.
So it's consciousness again.
So what I mean by consciousness, I hate to use that word,
and I really mean the H-A-T-A-T-E because it's been another word that's been hijacked.
Yes.
There's conscious and there's unconscious, aware and unaware.
When you are asleep, you're unconscious.
When you're dead, you're unconscious.
Now here's the other thing.
Let's just barrel this concept forward about death because we were asked about this more than once on the e-mails privately.
Can you please describe, I'm paraphrasing here, the e-mail reads as such, paraphrasing,
could you please describe what happens at the time of death or after death?
Do we lose our character, our personality, all of this?
Where do we experience them?
And the answer was that we've discussed this on the first episode.
But on another thing, this is to give a report.
Now if you think that anyone and everyone that came before you or last week is a moron because they're too old
and you're modern now because you've got the latest iPhone, you probably don't want to listen to what I have to say.
But if you think that people that lived a week, a month, a year, 100 years or 1,000 years or even 2,000 years before you
had something relevant to say that was worth memorializing, you should listen.
Because there's a lot of people that still say, you know, we're so modern now, that doesn't really work.
You see, so that's the division, that's the fork in the road.
Now let's take the fork in the road where we're going to report in part what has been memorialized for thousands of years.
What is interesting is that what you will find in all the ancient texts that death is like being asleep.
There's even texts that say that when someone had passed and now they are asleep with their ancestors, with their fathers, let's say.
It is just like sleep.
I think sleep has been referred to as the little death.
There is no dreaming.
There is no consciousness.
You're not burning in hell, Dante's Inferno, and you're not plucking a harp.
And anyone who's ever passed has not come back yet, except for a prototype, let's say.
Now, what's interesting about this, it's very simple cognitively to see that.
Can you remember any thoughts before you passed?
The answer is no.
You know, without some kind of systemic impression that is put on through hypnotherapy and coercion known as, you know, all that stuff that people do.
So what's interesting is you can go, let's say, to the mainstream funeral and this guy, this devil in a black robe with a white collar is saying,
Oh, he's with the Lord.
He's doing this.
He's doing that.
And what does it say on the tombstone?
Quite the opposite.
What's written in stone says rest in peace.
You're actually resting.
When you're sleeping, you are resting.
It is a form of rest.
There is absolutely no consciousness and no activity.
There is no time.
It is.
What's interesting about this is when this was understood by various cultures, as we brought up cultures earlier, it was reacted to in very different ways.
Like, for example, there's always mourning because we as emotional beings miss those that we love or those that or things or people and animals and things that we know and become accustomed to.
Right.
Let me present something to you, though, because it occurs to me that one could make a different observation than maybe you're accustomed to to hearing about this.
And I want you to answer this.
OK, if you recycle a piece of metal, it does not retain its shape or its purpose from its previous life unless it is then forged back into the very same thing it was recycled from.
Right. Let's just take the aluminum cans, for instance.
If you turn an aluminum can or a bunch of them into aluminum siding, it doesn't eventually retain any of its properties as an aluminum can, let's just say.
But it's still aluminum and it's still useful and it's still a as a substance recyclable.
Now, couldn't the personality, the spirit, the mind, any of these elements be recyclable since they do have substance?
Yes. Well, well, here's let me continue on the imparting the report.
The report is the specificness of the individual, the spirit, which is the mind, which makes you you.
Because remember, the body and the soul is interchangeable with everyone.
If you have the same blood type with the body parts, you know, like transplants and the soul, meaning you could resuscitate someone using your breath.
But the spirit is extremely specific. And according to ancient texts, it existed extremely discreet.
You know who you are, each individual person and also will exist after you die as an extreme distinct entity.
But it seems let me just paraphrase when someone passes from this realm and the soul dies and the body dies, meaning the breath stops and the body goes away or goes back to the base material.
The spirit is somehow downloaded into this giant hard drive that holds you for a time later on.
Not now. And you don't go anywhere else. And we have very little, if no information about that.
And that's the report that I give. And and I think it's very specific, because what it does is it allows one to act more efficiently, at least in their actions.
You know, in other words, if you hear someone saying, I saw my dead grandfather, that's not your dead grandfather.
Sorry, you're being messed with. So there's the level of efficiency.
But this is you know, you wouldn't have the movie Ghostbusters. Then you see, like the film Ghostbusters never made it to the Middle East.
It just got laughed out of the theaters. Now it might be in there, because if you try to go to a person, let's say, in the Middle East or that part of the world where you have more of an old cultural understanding of these things, they'll just laugh.
You know, those are not dead people. Those are gin. Get out of here. This is a crap movie.
Right. So it's a very interesting just like, for example, if you go to the Middle East, you won't have a move on your UFO community like we're talking about UFOs.
Those are gin. Get out of here. Well, yeah, and I understand that.
And just because you interpret something to be a particular thing does not mean that it is, you know, it's that simple.
Your observation is not necessarily completely reliable because there are distortions.
There are manipulations of what can be observable. This happens.
So but but even so, yeah, as a general cultural theme, though, because you see the film and the UFO society is other general cultural themes.
You know, they have their own problems within their own groups as well, by the way, like the hypnosis.
I've actually seen people being put under hypnosis, and that is not some kind of strange memory or whatever.
That is another being in the room entering them just like dreams.
I think we discussed how dreams are messages from other the other intangible realm.
It's we're being heavily interacted with and heavily messed with. And guess what?
We're easy to be messed with because we're ignorant of these things. And this interpretation that I'm giving is a very good one.
It can be validated as an interpretation. It's not a belief. It's just a report.
Like I say, I don't believe in these things. I've actually just reporting on what I've studied and I've validated them as being consistent throughout time.
Right, because you could look at Eastern and Old Western and Middle Eastern histories and ancient and they're all in agreement about this.
Right. And they were all isolated from each other, at least as we're told today.
Or what I mean by isolated, they had commerce and communication and intercourse.
But what I mean is they were isolated where they're not referencing directly each other.
Like the biblical text is not the referencing the Hindu text and vice versa.
They seem to be written autonomously and they're all consistent.
Right. And so it's what happens is you have consensus without collusion is very good.
And this is a much more reliable thing than, say, it's more objective because a separate groups of individuals, for instance,
if one is to observe a scientific study and you can find various groups that can recreate the very same reactions in an experiment,
you can assume that this is replicable. Right.
You can replicate it. Therefore, it's fairly reliable based on that.
So like gravity, if you're in China and you throw a brick off the roof,
it's going to go through very similar characteristics as if you're in the US or Japan or Iraq or Russia.
It's brick will pretty much fall and free fall very similarly without without having to interpret or read a report from another place.
Yeah. So these things are all being ignored, by the way, by moderns.
And I think that's why I get some joy showing up here two hours a week with you to discuss these just to give a report and say, hey, guys,
by the way, you know, you guys hear about this. In most cases, people have not.
And it's quite shameful sometimes to discuss these things, because this is part of what it should have been considered classical study.
Let's just call it that, you know. True enough.
And there's there's many, many aspects to this.
Now, it almost sounds as though we've gotten away from the concept of nothing because you explained it to some degree.
And I got to tell you, it seemed a little circular to me and maybe the listener might have missed it as well.
So I'd like to try and. Oh, absolutely.
Kick out a little more, because, look, nothing appears to be something.
Exactly. Apparently, the reason why when I first started discussing this, I got away from the English language.
Why? Because it has a certain simplicity, even though within the etymology that doesn't fulfill the concept.
Right. Because if you think of a box in space now, eliminate the box and eliminate the space where you can eliminate the box.
But it's kind of hard to get rid of the space in there because there's going to be something in that space, no matter how rarefied it is.
You see. And when we go look at the classic languages, the Chaldean Hebrew, Babylonian language or the Greek language, you know,
I haven't gone into the Eastern Asian languages or the Hindu on this, but I'm sure it's very similar.
They basically imply that there is something primordial there that is atypical.
Right. Or meaning of not of a certain type, meaning we cannot classify it.
And in another of the Chaldean or the Babylonian tongue or the Hebrew tongue.
And yes, if you're shocked, yes, Chaldean Babylonian Hebrew is the same.
If you do your research, you'll see it's the same time, just like in the lat you have the Latin, you have Italian, Spanish, Portuguese, for example.
But in that Chaldean Babylonian Hebrew tongue, you will see that the words,
the word being used for nothing actually means something very small that is chief, meaning it uses the letter A,
which means chief or head of or important, very small that you will never really grasp.
So you just have to believe that it's there. So it's.
And you factor. Right. So we cannot.
But all right. Now, what that means is that once you grasp this, nothing.
I gave the analogy of the electricity. Right. Right.
And you're not going to if you if you get a grasp, this is the point that I want to get to.
And we brought up death with this, because when you're sleeping, there is nothing going on.
And forget about dreams for a moment.
Well, if you really meditate on what sleep is and you're very tired and you've worked hard and you've gone to bed and woken up,
there's really nothingness there. It's just nothing.
By the way, if anyone says you ever heard people say Nirvana or Utopia.
Look those words up. That means Utopia means no man's land or nowhere.
And Nirvana means the same thing. It means a place where you go back to the universe where there's nothing.
Those two words. I think you want to avoid them at this point, you know.
But, you know, being an alien concept as it is to and so difficult to wrap your mind around it.
I would venture to argue that perhaps nothingness is not so bad.
Perhaps. I don't know, because quite honestly, I can't intellectually directly relate to it in a real well articulated sense.
I can't really describe it or break it down. I get a sense of it and that's it.
And it does seem as though there are no more concerns. There are no more.
So I can sort of see how the language has become convoluted with those two words.
Yes. But let's go to the other thing that I wanted to continue on.
This is the concept of bringing up nothing. And like I think I might have mentioned, it's not what we think.
It might sound circular and amounts might sound irrational because we pass it off as being very trivial.
But what happens if you learn to work with nothing? Think about that for a moment.
What do you have to say about that?
Well, if one learns to work with nothing, then you would understand the need.
You'd have to understand the nature of it in order to be able to pick it up, you know, and deal with it in the first place.
Exactly how to technically access it.
What I mean by technical access is it means you're not the only one who can do it, but you can actually show others how to do it and communicate.
OK, now. Well, how about the concept of doing volunteer work on Internet radio?
Oh, did I say that? I thought that was working with nothing.
But OK. Yeah. So excuse me.
This I left the mic open. I usually don't when I'm going to laugh on this show.
But that was necessary. Yes. OK.
So let's just discuss this point now. I brought up the concept of Rudolf Hoschka.
You know, he was adding these vital elements extracted, extracted from food to discover what we call vitamins today.
And he found out he didn't even have to add them. The sheer proximity had the same effect. Right.
There is a concept of homeopathy. It's not how much of the chemical or the substances in there.
It's how little of it. Now, now we start going into field science and field effects.
Now, there are many. Let's just say.
What would you call it when something is suppressed, suppressed, subverted, whatever science is,
that if you've done even a cursory study on the 20th century regarding health treatments,
regarding what they call free energy, things like that,
it seemed to work with devices and technical access of this nothing medium.
Right. Very interesting. Right. Like, for example, with weather work, if one wants to get it.
And I'm bringing this up because there's a lot of stuff about geoengineering.
And whenever they discuss geoengineering, it's all this brute force stuff, you know,
spraying things in the air or using harp, which is that originally was H.A.A.A.R.R.P.
is the original project name, by the way.
They people in their minds are thinking of this brute force,
but the true weather work that was done, let's say, by the kahunas and the ancients,
they use devices that if you were to examine, you would say there's nothing there.
Right. It's very interesting. And by the way, there's still people tinkering with that in modern time.
I think Wilhelm Reich and Trevor James Constable are two people worthy of noting for that.
If anyone wants to do their research. So understanding how to work with nothing.
How many times have you heard even in colloquial terms of people say they gave me nothing to work with.
Right. But they still got it done, didn't they? See.
So I think that the word the term of nothing or nothingness and not unless you're discussing it in its sheer absolute form,
which is death and everyone tastes death if they have a restful sleep, meaning sleep without dreaming.
Right. Or right now, other than that sheer absolute aspect of nothingness, which involves the individual,
there is no nothing. There's always something there to work with.
You see. And and when we brought up the concept of mastery earlier, when one becomes a master.
Well, how does he do it? You know, he didn't use anything. He pulled it out of nothing.
Well, no, there's a skill behind that as well. So this what I'm imparting here is just gently into people's minds.
There are things called fields. You know, you might have Wi-Fi or cell phone or radio waves.
You know, you don't see any of that. It's it can be tangible when you have an instrument.
Right. Right. But this concept of what we call nothing and things that we've discounted to be nothing,
there's still something there that's workable. And that is one of the things that we are being.
You know, people are talking about talking about censorship. Let's talk about a secular censorship.
Part of the existence I've noticed in society is to get people away from learning how to work with nothing.
Give you a quick example. Someone is ill. So what do they do?
They go to the doctor and all of a sudden they give them all these some things, you know, chemotherapy, let's say,
or drugs or painkillers, things to take. But do you know that traditionally?
Let's say you have a pet when the pet's not feeling well. What does it do? What does it eat? What does it drink?
Nothing. It doesn't. Yeah. Yes. So that's what I mean by learning to work with nothing.
Give you an example. I've known someone, actually more than two people,
and they were diagnosed with pretty severe cancers.
And they heard that if they go down to this place in the Caribbean, there's no radio waves there.
And this was during the time with pagers or beepers. Remember those? Right.
And none of that worked. No radio worked there. And they went there and a shaman or medicine man met them.
And this is a protected area or was, I believe, where they didn't want any radio interference.
And the people would go there and they would do nothing. They would be alone.
They would have a small hut. You either built the hut yourself or you paid for someone to build a hut.
And you ate nothing and you drank nothing. And you did an extreme fast.
And you were coached for the first three weeks on how to fast because you might have wanted to have something.
But after the coaching, after three weeks of coaching, you had to do at least five to ten or fourteen days of absolutely fasting and nothing.
And they called it starving the cancer out of the body.
So that is learning to work with nothing. You see? Think about it.
I mean, let's just go back to the Internet radio for a moment because this is something that needs to be discussed.
Chuck, you have a five-day-a-week schedule. That's ten hours a week.
And probably another ten or more hours behind the schedule. And you're volunteering.
Are you doing it for nothing? No. You're doing it because, well, you volunteer to do it.
But there's something there, isn't there? But are we working with nothing?
Are you working with nothing pretty much? Yes and no.
I mean, you get done. You know, you've got things you've got to eat.
You know, you've got people around you that rely on you.
You see, but essentially, you're doing it for nothing, right?
Essentially, I mean, everyone behind AFR is volunteered. Are they doing it for nothing? No.
You know, they're doing it for the sake of doing it. Well, more than that.
It's a pretty good venue. But are they doing it on nothing? Yeah, pretty much.
You see, I hope this whole show tied everything together.
Because learning to work with nothing is pretty amazing, you know?
Yeah, it certainly is.
And, you know, you're actually the first person I've heard talk about the concept of nothing
relating to certain diseases and things like that.
But I have some knowledge on this as well, and I've never thought to impart it to anybody.
Because, quite honestly, I figure that most people would find it insane if I explained that.
Well, yes, starving it out of your body. This is an ancient thing.
Even in the ancient texts, if you were sick and the priest deemed you sick,
you were to go outside of the city of the camp and be set apart and shut down for seven days or ten days.
Right. And, you know, you and I talked about this privately once, a long time ago,
when I was describing some of the things that I tried to study with different people in different places.
And I say tried to study because I don't feel as though I grasped enough of the knowledge
to really articulate it to anyone else.
But I did have some interesting experiences, some of which I imparted to you.
And, you know, there is something to be said for this.
And I'm kind of glad you brought it up, because it is an efficient way of dealing with some things.
Yes, it sounds like the old Abbott and Costello, who's on first.
But if you really listen to what we're trying to say here, learning to work with the intangible
will have benefits for the individual that has the peace to do it.
Because if you learn to work with nothing, it's very difficult to explain it.
And especially to the secular or technologically based moderns, they want to see evidence of it.
Right. You know, but the thing about working with nothing is you don't see what nothing is doing,
but you see its effect like the wind.
If a wind comes through and knocks all the lawn furniture down and tears a roof off, well, what did it?
You know, what's the wind? Well, let's see. Run the video tape.
Well, I don't see anything, but I see the lawn furniture being flipped over.
And you see, it's a very powerful force.
It doesn't mean that we're not talking about the abyss.
We're not talking about meditation as such as discussed.
By the way, I think we once touched on meditation.
The concept of meditation is not emptying your mind.
The only time you can empty your mind is when your body is active.
If your body is still, the mind is racing.
You see, so if you're up on a steep pitch gable roof, nailing roof shingles,
and someone says, let me tell you about my day, you're like, well, wait a second.
Let me come down. You know, I can't really focus right now.
Right. Or someone is jogging or at the gym.
They can't have a very rational discussion.
But when you're calm, this is like you can the mind.
It's an old Greek maxim. When the body is quick, the mind is slow.
And when the body is slow, the mind is quick.
When you the concept of meditation that Westerners have is an adulterated thing
that the intelligence agencies did in the 60s.
Yes, I'm signing conspiratorial.
But they said, let's get a bunch of degenerates out of India, give them new identities,
send them to the West and tell all these young white teenagers that are adopting
into drugs and things like that, that they need to sit quietly and empty their mind.
Are you kidding? That's how you drive an entire generation of people insane.
Because when you sit quiet, your mind starts to race.
So when you read about meditation, it's you get in a quiet place and let your mind go.
It's like letting the gates open at a horse race.
And anyone who's ever done this knows.
So if you've ever been tutored or taught by anyone that says you need to quiet your mind
and quiet your body, they're screwing with you and you're being messed with severely
and get away from those people.
See, whenever I have coached someone about meditation,
and I have done it several times and at several points in my life,
usually what I do is tell people to remove the clutter and to narrow what their mind is doing.
This is my goal.
This is my aim always because the more narrowed thought process is just easier to navigate
and more natural, really, because when you really focus on something.
Well, that's exactly it.
You've got before you meditate, you need to pick what you're going to meditate on.
Right.
Yeah, just don't let your mind go either,
because now you're going to be subjected to your own voices in your head that are disorganized.
And I brought up the concept of meditation because there's still this corrupted thinking about that.
So, yeah, but yes, if you do advise anyone, the easiest way to give anyone advice on meditation
is when you calm the body, the mind will start to accelerate.
And it's okay.
Take control of it.
It's like a car.
The faster the car goes, do you want to let go of the steering wheel
or do you want to be more firm on it, you see?
So be firm on a thought or a topic.
And this is what it is.
The reason I'm saying this is because you wouldn't believe even today how many,
not today, today, but in recent past, how many people say meditation is where you quiet your mind
and you go to this unknown space.
I'm like, you're a moron.
You're an idiot.
And whoever told you that needs to get away from them.
Slap them on the head with a wet newspaper.
I don't know who that's worse for, you or someone else.
When you slap someone with a wet newspaper, it gets messy for everyone.
But the point is, this is still a very corrupt, everything's been corrupted.
How many times have we said or heard that?
Including nothing.
Well, but it's true.
I believe that everything has kind of been hijacked and everything has been twisted upon itself
so that nothing represents itself in an honest fashion.
That's why I've stopped trying to use the word alternative when I refer to media
and I describe the things that are good anyway as honest media.
One way or another, it is the attempt to give someone an honest representation
of whatever's being represented.
Now, there's very few people that do that.
And you will find many of them here on American Freedom Radio, whether you disagree with them or not.
The fact is, on this venue, you will find people that are presenting something to you
that regardless of their, well, sort of shortcomings on occasion,
are doing their best to bring you an honest presentation.
It's not about the manipulation.
It's about trying to get to honesty.
And I like the word honesty.
I'm sorry.
Well, the opposite of it isn't good, so that is, but why bring it up, is one side of it.
But the other side of it is giving a good report.
Just like we just gave, let's say, yes, we did give advice on how to meditate.
Yes, and I'm pretty strong, and that's my story, and I'm sticking with it.
And if you actually have tried to meditate, you'll realize your mind starts to accelerate.
That is the story of it, right?
So why not share it?
Well, right, and that's why I thought that was extremely valuable right there,
and I stepped in to say exactly the same thing,
because coming at it from a wholly different perspective,
we did arrive at exactly the same conclusion,
which is that it is about a focus and not about this emptiness concept.
I've always found that rather strange.
There is no emptiness, yeah.
Because, yeah, once you empty your mind,
all you've really done is focused on something that you have difficulty, you know, sort of relating to.
That's all you've done.
The fear, just to go back to something that we've discussed briefly,
which was I wanted to bring up the concept of death.
The fear of death that comes in is an intuitive sense that you will be in a sense of nothingness.
There is no more.
And let me just throw this in.
You know, there's something called the abyss on the earth in an ancient text.
You can maybe figure out which one I'm discussing.
And it's a place where certain spiritual entities are imprisoned for a little while, right?
Right.
How do you imprison a spiritual entity?
What would be a, quote, unquote, punishment for them?
And it's here on the earth.
It's a sensory deprivation chamber.
There's no light.
There's no dark.
There's no smell.
There's no touch.
There's no temperature.
There's no sound.
And we can't imagine that.
But it's quite interesting when you start to  we brought up some of the things in the ancient text about, you know,
eyes to see and ears to hear and darkness that's so thick you can feel it and the abyss and nirvana, utopia.
What these things mean are not what we've been told.
And it doesn't take  these things are all arm's reach away.
And what we  you notice we're bringing up what someone might call the classics.
Modern people are lacking the classical knowledge.
And I'm not talking about Dante's Inferno and things like that.
I'm talking about knowing what came before you.
Because in order to understand something, you have to know the history of that thing first.
But that's why how many times have you heard, you know, when you  like, for example,
a completely invalidatable subject to study academically is history.
None of it is true.
So if you don't have any history, how can you understand anything?
In the Soviet Union, the people said the only thing left for us to discover is our history
because they were lied to about everything.
It's the same for the Americans, the same for the Greeks, the same for the Russians, Japanese, all around.
So how do you think a society that's operating currently on the planet is doing
when they're completely cut off from any history at all that's been truthful or honest like you mentioned earlier?
How  you know, you're not doing well.
Exactly, and it seems as though no one is immune because, after all, we are all on the same cruise ship.
Yes, see the earlier  see the earlier concept we discussed that we're all on the same cruise ship.
So no matter how many times you reorganize the chairs or change your cabin,
you are still on the very same cruise ship, and that happens to be the same rock that we are all sharing at the moment.
So, you know, we're coming down to the last few minutes here,
and I wonder how it is you'd like to cap this off because it is interesting to consider that, yeah, many things have been hijacked.
We've talked about, you know, intent, and without even mentioning the word once, we talked about intent.
We talked about the reality of nothing and how nothing seems to be something,
and a lot of somethings turn out to be nothing.
Speaking of which, you know, I think we did also read a short article about how to beg for money successfully,
and that's an unusual thing.
We never really do that.
So if people get the hint on that, what they should do is perhaps donate.
Got to find another word for that because there are things that are necessary.
I'd like to maybe bring that point up again.
This is all volunteer work, and it's distasteful for many, but I'll do it shamelessly.
AFR can use some support.
There are logistics.
There's bills that are sent.
There are expenses that are incurred for this volunteer work.
That would be the easiest way to put it, and anything and everything is appreciated.
Yes, absolutely.
So this is the end of the 16th.
It is the 16th episode, I believe.
I think so.
About Shelly and the Greek, I'm pretty sure, based on my count anyway,
that we've been on the air and done this for people on the stream live,
and I'm sure it will be replayed at some point.
And if not, you can find it on the archives,
which are also provided for you on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
So that being said, a lot of interesting stuff is going to happen tomorrow also on AFR.
Just for everybody's knowledge, there's going to be a very good episode of Angela Foreman's show,
which is going to feature Rick Simpson.
I will be present for that show just to help Angela out based on her personal situation.
Zen and the Car Radio is going to have an interesting guest, and Jordan Maxwell will also begin,
and I suggest you check the schedule often at AFR because things are changing.
There is actually more work and more interesting information being imparted at the website on a daily basis,
and, hey, there may even be a massive change in the website coming up shortly.
Just between you and me and the wall.
Okay, and I heard a Carol Rosin might be coming on as well.
She's had an Internet presence for a very long time with her disclosure work and knowing Von Braun as well,
so that is something else that's going to be coming around the pike here soon.
Absolutely right, plus Ed Opperman and a whole bunch of other people.
Oh, yeah, Ed Opperman.
And there's more to come.
And you know what, guys?
We will be back next week with episode 17 of Ocelli and the Greek,
and I hope you guys learned something tonight because I do every time I do this.
So, Greek, thank you, sir.
Okay, till next time.
I'm telling you, you've got to support American Freedom Radio because this government is getting out of hand.
Wall Street won't fall on my mummy.
The CIA are cutting into my drug running and my gun running.
Big pharma psychotropic drugs are making my customers commit suicide before my hitmen can even lock them.
And then they get depressed and get prescribed psychotropic drugs and commit suicide, too.
They're trying to become the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected.
I get unpaid taxes, and if I can't find the money, the IRS are going to take my tops.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine, and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction, and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs, and that's to support American Freedom Radio.
Capisce?
So what are you going to do?
You're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion, and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years, and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein, is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO, and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367, and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
We all know that they're not telling us the truth.
So stand up for your rights, demand the real medicine, and your right to use it and grow it.
This is Rick Sensen, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
What is the big deal about swearing to God in the first place?
Why does swearing to God mean you're going to tell the truth?
Wouldn't affect me.
If they said to me, you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth to help you, God,
I'd say, yeah!
I'll tell you about as much truth as the people who wrote that Bible.
How do you like that?
Huh?
Swearing to God is kid stuff.
Swearing to God doesn't mean anything.
Swearing on the Bible doesn't mean anything.
You know why?
Because Bible or no Bible, God or no God, if it suits their purposes, people are going to lie in court.
The police do it all the time.
All the time.
Yes, they do.
It's part of their job to protect, to serve, and to commit perjury whenever it supports the state's case.
Swearing on the Bible is just one more way of controlling people and keeping them in line,
and it's one more thing that holds us back as a species.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow,
friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.