American Freedom Radio presents the only broadcast information show of a religious outlet.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli airs in the week.
And with me is the one and only guy that calls himself the Greek.
How are you doing tonight, sir?
Doing well, Chuck.
All right.
Don't forget I'm the only Greek I know.
But it's not like you're the only one.
Right.
Either way, yeah.
So, yeah, let's just say for time reckoning it's already the 10th month and we're about in the fifth day till noon.
Just want to put that out there.
Well, yeah, I mean, allegedly it would be, well, where I'm sitting again, the 11th month and the 29th day.
But that's according to the pope's work schedule, as we have discussed many times.
But, yeah, the 10th month.
Yeah, isn't it interesting how no means nine, but they call it 11 and oct means.
Isn't October what comes before that?
Yeah, they call that the 10th and it means eight.
And decim means 10.
And, yeah, yeah.
I mean, that was the 12th, yeah.
Yeah, might as well bring it up because, you know, you never know.
I mean, maybe in the future people will be sourcing the archives and saying, hey, yeah, now that we know this guy was saying it.
So it's just one of those things, you know.
Well, yeah, I mean, this is where we're going to get into discussions of future, past and all of that.
And we're going to change gears a little bit, I guess, tonight and give it a shot discussing the geopolitical, geosocial current events of sorts.
Although, to me, there really isn't very much current.
I mean, it just seems to be the repetition of old grudges, you know, old, well, old stories being retold, et cetera, et cetera.
I don't know.
You know, that's the way it seems.
Where do you want to begin?
Well, I'm going to ask, what do you mean by grudges?
What do I mean by grudges?
Well, when you do consider, you know, the French speaking to the Russians, right, and then you take a look at where their lineage begins,
it does seem to be the repeat of things that happened in, well, alleged history in the past, doesn't it, regarding, you know, let's just say, well, all right.
Napoleonic, you mean, or how far, you mean the past?
We can go previous to that.
I mean, you can go all the way back to, well, let's think for a moment, Genghis Khan, right?
Now, you have people out there saying, why is he even bringing up Genghis Khan?
Well, if you think about it, Genghis Khan came and pretty much told these people, you know, that were connected to the Roman Catholic Church,
that one day these Arabs over here would be a problem for them, and actually reached out and asked for all kinds of things from, you know,
from what would become the Roman Catholic Church later, right, that we understand now,
in conjunction with dealing with these people that had this, well, Assyrian lineage.
Hmm, I don't know.
It just seems to be repetition.
I mean, are you catching on to that, or you think I'm just way out in left field?
That's part of the main movie, but that movie ended, now you're in the credits part.
No, it's not left field, and one of the things I've always been discussing is how people are going to start to look back,
because there was a reality that existed more than 150 years ago, so why not, you know, look at all that?
But what's interesting is that was part of a film that was wrapped up roughly 17 years ago,
and now we're 17 years into roughly less than a 40-year credit portion, and that's a mouthful right there.
I mean, this is something new.
You know, we like to look at things in the historical context, but, you know, has that context even been served up properly to us, you know?
Well, how about that, then?
Why don't we take a look at what's happening, though, because I do find it fascinating that the Russians are doing what they're doing.
I am one of the only people that I've heard say that, you know, not because I believe that Vladimir Putin's a good guy or anything,
but I do think it's been a brilliant strategic move, right, to involve himself in this ISIS crisis that's going on over there,
because I believe it's all a construct, and it's just been completely fabricated, manufactured by the various intelligence groups.
Of course, they're serving a higher purpose, and I'm sure you can get into that.
They're really fighting the war that's already been fought.
But the fact is, what we're able to observe right now is that the Russians go in,
and they take care of and push back a group of people that we have allegedly had no ability,
and when I say we, I'm talking about the United States, not you and me, and not me for sure,
but when we're talking about it, right, what are we doing?
You know, we weren't able to beat them back.
We keep dropping them all these resources.
We keep helping them out.
It seems to me as though they're more our allies than our allies anymore,
and the Russians come in who have an allegedly lesser military strength, and they immediately beat them back,
and it just seems to me again that we have something else echoing through history.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just me.
No, no, that's fine, but you've got to realize that the U.S. was getting prepared for desert-type warfare
or engagement back in the 70s and 80s.
They were painting their equipment that tan color, right?
That's right.
Yeah, so, you know, this is part, you know, again, should we say cosmic censorship?
You know, people will do things.
You know, what people fail to realize is that there is an unseen reality that affects the reality that we do see,
and it's kind of like a colony of ants.
We're only concerned about picking up this little sand pebble or this crumb and moving it back and forth,
but we really don't see, you know, anything more than an ant's eye point or a worm's eye point of view of things.
It has to do with, again, a vantage point, and the vantage point that I like discussing is essentially what's coming,
because what's interesting about it is, you know, in human history,
humans try to compile history as events that happened in the past.
Cosmic history or divine history is compiling events that are going to happen in the future, right,
because of their vantage point.
Now, would that be history, or would that be described as something else?
Well, let's just say any event that's memorialized to be communicated, whether in any format,
whether it's oral or written or electronic, is a form of memorialized information,
and history is typically memorialized events of the past.
Now, if you memorialize events in the future, that is, it's the same as events in the past,
it's just, let's say, on a different side of the timeline, you know, the positive versus negative side of a time,
of a line, let's say, zero being in the middle, you know, a very rudimentary example.
So, what's interesting, let's just, you know, hit the subject right on.
It's about Russia and Syria and ISIS, right?
It seems to be the contemporary talk right now, or the recent talk or current events.
Flavor of the week, anyway, or month, yeah.
Yeah, and it's pretty serious, because if you look at the landmasses also, you know,
the majority of the landmass of the planet is on that side of the world.
And if you look geographically, even from secular history, how there was an expansion from the
Mesopotamia or Tigris-Euphrates area outward, you know, first it went east, and then it went west,
and then it went north, and then it went south, let's say.
Okay?
What's interesting, it all being connected, and things being run in reverse, you know,
things going back to that part of the world.
So, it's not just Russia.
Like you said, it's just Russia this week, let's say, you know.
Well, you didn't quite say that, but it's meaning that this is what's going on this week or last week,
or more than a few weeks already.
The Russian engagement in that part of the world.
Let's just drop it right now.
If we just had another three minutes to speak, the reason why Syria has been in focus,
as will Iraq, is also in focus, by the way, not as much as it should be,
is because you're going to see a new country being formed in the Middle East,
and it's going to be the revived Assyria.
Not Syria.
Assyria.
A-S-S-Y-R-I-A.
And it might be called the new Assyria.
Just like you have Newfoundland or New York, or cities that are old cities renamed with the word new.
This might be called the new Assyria, and it's going to be in the northern part of Iraq,
known as the Nineveh Plains, and it was a country that existed 2,300 years ago.
And if you look at the maps of Assyria before they expanded,
because at one point they controlled the known world,
before that expansion or after that expansion, when they still existed as a nation,
you'll notice that on the maps of ancient Assyria, in their most contracted form,
still had land in modern-day Syria and modern-day Turkey.
Now, isn't Turkey in the news as well?
Interesting, right?
So this new country that will be formed in the Middle East called the new Assyria,
or Assyria revived, or however you want to put it together,
most likely it will be the new Assyria,
will actually be using or taking up, nationalistically, some land from Syria and Turkey.
Now, how do we know this?
Well, I think we might have discussed, if you want a new idea, read a really old book.
So let's just leave it at that.
So we just gave the end of the story, and we could fill in anywhere.
Now it's like paint by numbers.
When you get a paint by numbers, you get the outlines, and you don't have to be creative.
You don't have to make stuff up.
You just paint between the lines, right?
Well, yeah.
Now, people are wondering, because these kinds of things evoke the concept of Megiddo, Armageddon,
and all this other stuff, which I say is a complete contrivance,
based on a misinterpretation of the ancient text.
But then again, maybe I'm just crazy.
Well, Har means mountain. Megiddo is an area.
It's not near the southern part of that country known as Israel, or state, let's say.
It's legitimacy as a country is still being formed, by the way.
That Har means it's just a mountain.
And that implies a very specific gathering of troops to fight a particular group of people.
And those people are not really on the scene yet.
And the many situations that might, or I shouldn't say might,
many other things that have to accompany that have not taken place.
What's interesting is a lot of people borrow Biblical themes to suit their agenda,
whether they know if they have one or not.
Even just saying I'm going to borrow a Biblical theme out of context is an agenda,
even if you're doing it without knowing it.
Like, for example, the blood moon thing, right?
That comes from a Biblical context, but if you look at where the blood moons are,
or the moon will be red as blood in context, it's not solely the moon turning red.
It also is accompanied by something else in order for these things to take effect.
But they conveniently leave that part out because it doesn't get people into a frantic enough mood to listen.
Well, that's true, just like with the sun turning black.
That's exactly what accompanies.
And here's the weird thing about that, is that in reality, the sun is already black.
You can't see the sun in outer space, and that's going to really...
Why do you think there aren't, what do they call, commercial flights to outer space?
Because too many people are going to come back and say, bring me back to Earth, I can't see,
I don't feel like I'm anywhere.
They have to use what they call diffraction absorption film on the windows of the craft,
which is a fancy term for window tint.
You know that bright silver gold window tint that they put on astronauts' visors?
Without that, you can't see the sun or the stars in outer space,
because that type of light is not the type of light that we see here on Earth.
And by the way, you can't see light anyway, you only see reflected light.
So people realize this, but the sun is indeed...
And a lot of people ask, how do you know? Have you been to outer space?
That right away is the rebellious aspect of mankind, that they don't want to take in the information.
Just think about it for a moment.
But the sun being black in the biblical aspect would mean that the Earth's atmosphere is stripped away,
because the only reason you see the sun as a multicolored disk,
because it does have a different color at dawn, it has a different color at high noon,
and it has a different color at sunset.
The reason why you see the sun as a disk is because of Earth's atmosphere.
If there was no atmosphere, there would be no sun.
So it's going to be quite an interesting dynamic event to strip away the Earth's atmosphere,
where you can actually not see the sun where it was.
And these things have not yet happened.
I assure you, as I've said in the past in other places publicly,
one of the things that you will see and hear in the coming years is all things biblical.
Films based on biblical themes, books written on biblical themes,
people discussing things from biblical themes, and I assure you they're all wrong, very simply.
But the reason why they're wrong is because the text has yet to be translated out of its languages of preservation.
If you have a quote-unquote Bible in English, Spanish, Chinese, Japanese, or 180 different languages,
it's not the biblical text, just like with any other ancient text.
So that is another problem with discussing things out of context from that.
But there is going to be a greater interest in this subject,
because when these ancient texts are translated, the people will be primed for it.
And what is priming?
When you prime an engine, it's before you start it to make sure there's enough fuel in there.
So what's happening now is there's a tremendous amount of fuel being set across the planet in religious fervor,
and none of it is accurate, not even close.
Well, right, and this is what a lot of people refer to as predictive programming.
I mean, the truth is that long before you see concepts in practical, everyday life,
I mean, look, I love to point to the whole Star Trek thing, you know,
how they had things that looked like cell phones long before they became commonplace,
how they had things that looked like, well, touchpad screens and things like that long before that was even a concept.
You know, these projections and things like that, which are being worked on now,
I'm very sure will become commonplace very shortly, et cetera, et cetera.
All of these things actually come to pass after the predictive programming is issued.
You know, you get used to the idea that, and I also like to point to,
remember those toy helicopters that were very, very popular a few years ago?
Oh, yeah.
You notice that the proliferation of drones, little flying crafts, came right after they gave us toys to play with, you know?
So you can see this being repeated over and over again in the alleged society, can't you?
Yeah, and also some of the most interesting toys are just left as toys.
Like, you know, there's memory metal, where you can crumble it up and hit it with a blow dryer,
put it in the freezer, and all the creases in the metal go away.
Have you heard of this?
Okay.
And they have, in certain places, distributed this as a toy.
Now, imagine an automobile made of this.
You get a dent or a scratch, you just come out with your blow dryer, and the dent comes out.
What does that do to the auto body repair shops?
Well, yeah, and what does that do to the strange stories of alleged aircrafts that landed in places,
and there were these pieces of metal that retained their shape no matter what you did to them?
Yeah.
Where it just, you know, remembered its shape or seemed to remember its shape, you know, is something very, very strange,
because typically when we see metal that has been forged, cast, or whatever, we see it, you know, if you bend it, it stays bent.
I mean, that's just what happens.
Yeah, exactly.
So they either hide information in the public library, and they hide all the new trinkets as toys.
Well, not all of them, but so there's the geopolitical discussion.
It's a bunch of toys, and those little fighter jets do look like toys when they're up in the air, don't they?
Well, yeah, that's the fun part.
They look exactly like toys, and really, if you go to, I mean, I don't know if anybody's even got a hobby shop anywhere near them
where they live, because I am definitely in a backwards area of the country at the moment,
but, you know, in some places, I hear tell, they still have these little hobby shops where you can go and get things
that allow you to do hands-on stuff like fly little planes, little helicopters, drive little cars, et cetera, like that,
you know, from what they call remote controls.
And, hey, a lot of those toys look very much like the things that are now weaponized,
that are now being utilized for surveillance, that are now being used by policing agencies.
I mean, it seems pretty similar, really, except they have better toys for that stuff, don't they?
Yeah, they're just tools, basically, you know.
You know, you hear a lot of talk about what they call guns, you know.
What is a gun?
It's just firing a projectile, right?
Right.
So people get limited in their thinking, you know, if they're going to take the guns away, what does a gun do?
Is that the only way it can be done, or is there a million ways to do it?
So, again, there's a very narrow perception.
There's a level of control or programming or pre-programming, like you said, of how we should think of things.
Oh, right.
I mean, the entertainment industry is just what I was really referring to,
where we see concepts that are introduced as, you know, as alleged works of fiction
that somehow or another seem to come around and become reality.
You know, what was it, Brave New World?
I think it was Brave New World that featured the drug Soma, and, you know,
later on it was actually released and patented, and there's a drug called Soma now,
which is meant to keep you pretty docile, like it does in Brave New World.
You know, I know I'm going a little further back there, but, hey, it is what it is.
Like I said, the computer technology and things like that, you can see through Star Trek,
you can see concepts like Skynet and these great computer complexes that were erected for, you know,
the alleged defense and all of that.
Artificial intelligence, which I have a weird argument about that.
I believe that the Internet is essentially artificial intelligence, if you think about it.
You know, it just hasn't become completely self-aware yet,
or if it has, it's smart enough to know not to let us know it's self-aware.
Not sure which is the truth there.
But then again, I don't have the level of geekdom required to fully comprehend what's going on.
Well, maybe it's all 100% external input.
Ah, so maybe the Internet is a bit more human than we think.
It's modeled after the human.
I mean, if squirrels made computers, don't you think they would model it after squirrels?
I believe so.
Yeah, it's made, have you heard this before?
It was made in their own likeness, right?
Well, isn't that the case, yeah.
Yeah, that's the goal, I guess.
But it was interesting that people are really going to miss out on what's coming in the future,
because right now the predictive programming or all these things that are being put out right now
are just fuel for this period of tension.
A lot of the things that are in consideration now, just like the old World's Fairs,
you know, what was it, in the 30s and 50s, they said we'll have flying cars by the 90s, right?
You know, the Jetsons was supposed to be, what, the year 2000?
Okay, yeah, you don't hear any of that anymore.
You might get some films and art in that theater genre, you know, film and art, about a despotic future society,
but not as much as it used to be with the George Orwell and Aldeus Huxley.
What you're going to be seeing is a concentration of all mankind's focus in the Middle East in the next decade.
And an emergence or revival of how society on this planet was not 1,000 years ago, not 2,000 or 3,000,
but over 4,000 years ago.
That type of consciousness will be revived.
And at that point, all these things now that people have in concern will be abandoned,
and you're going to have what we discussed on, I think it was the dummy load episode,
about how there will be almost a virtually perfect society on the planet,
that people will be going about their business thinking that this is how it's going to be for the next millennia.
So to lead up to that point, again, with the concentration of everything in the Middle East,
can you remember a year or two or five or ten where the Middle East has not been in the news?
Not over the course of my lifetime.
I've got to be honest with you, because, okay, I became quite aware of the world around me in, say, 1975.
I was three years old, and I was being taught how to read via a newspaper.
Okay, I know that these are very blunt instruments, and this makes me sound extremely dated, but, you know, facts are facts.
Yeah, that's how I came to be aware of interesting things going on around the planet.
Now, they were still talking about Watergate, and they were talking about the upcoming centennial,
the bicentennial, as it were, that was going to happen in this country and things like that, and I recall those.
But I also recall the constant discussions about the things that were still going down,
the residual effects of things that were occurring because of what had happened in the 60s, right, in the Middle East.
I was being treated to discussions about Egypt and what the results were from the Six-Day War
and what Israel's real place in the world was, and then came this little thing called the Iran hostage situation.
You know, and like I said, this is from childhood.
So going on from there, there has never been a time where I could say there was even a two-year period
where the Middle East was not one of these very big areas of contention, sites of war, sites of conflict, upheaval, unrest,
everything from that point to, gee, well, the past couple of years, the Arab Spring, the invasion and occupation of Iraq,
the Syrian question, the near overthrow of the Turkish government, I mean, on and on and on and on.
Yeah, I can't think of a two-year time period where even when I was vaguely aware of world events,
that the Middle East was not at the apex of what was occurring.
Yep. And this is going to be building up with a fervor.
And if you want to go with a little bit of the predictive programming,
isn't it interesting how the thing with ISIS in the past, I don't know, maybe let's say a year, public beheadings,
now, albeit whether they're staged or not is irrelevant, the concept of being put into people's minds that people are being beheaded,
or this sort of antiquated or medieval, pre-medieval type of capital punishment, or level of cruelty,
which goes against a lot of the, let me just say the Greco-Roman jurisprudence,
is being put into the minds of people, just like, for example, the film Back to the Future in the 80s,
the doc was in trouble because he bought some radioactive material from some Muslim or Arabic terrorists, remember?
See, that was put, and then the film True Lies, remember, those were also Middle Easterners that were the villains, right?
So vilifying the people from that part of the world started in the 80s in film.
Now, what's interesting right now, what's being shown in the media is the villain beheading, okay?
Which is an ancient thing that was done during battle, right?
So this has now become normal, you know, for people to comprehend that it can happen, you see.
Because we're going back now, and this is a Greco-Roman type, when I say Greco-Roman, they're the same, type of jurisprudence, right?
And what I mean by that is what people consider to be right and wrong, right, in a legalistic way, is changing.
So, like, if you're captured by a Greco-Roman society, you don't expect to be beheaded the next day, right?
But now what's being put into the people's minds is that if you're captured by a, quote-unquote, pseudo-Assyrian, Babylonian, Middle Eastern culture, you will be beheaded.
Isn't that interesting?
How that aspect is being changed, that's being put in people's minds.
Why do I say that?
It's because for the past 2,000 plus years, this has been a Greek-type of based society in the language, in the science, in the law.
It is going to switch in the next decade, going back to more of a proto-Middle Eastern culture.
Sumerian, Babylonian, Assyrian type of jurisprudence will be considered, which is very different and foreign to the Westerner.
And this is just part of the pre-programming for that.
Now, whether the people that are putting out this know it or not, this was been written about thousands of years ago, that during a certain time period, there will be a revived ancient empire.
And when you revive an empire, when you're living under empire, every aspect of your culture is connected to that empire.
Well, see, that's fascinating.
But, you know, one might think, well, the resurrection, I shouldn't use that word.
The revival.
The revival, thank you.
The revival of this ancient culture.
I mean, outside of the endgame of the punishments being so starkly different from what we might find in Western culture.
You know, there's a whole lot more to it, though.
There's a different set of rules for everything.
And I don't think, I mean, I don't even think I have a complete grasp on what the real difference is.
I mean, I know that usury is not part of the game with these people.
It is.
May I just say that if you look at it closely, it still is, but it's not as prevalent as it is here.
Okay.
Well, it doesn't seem to be one of the main focuses, that's for sure.
I mean, you don't have the concept of, you know, store your gold with me and I'll give you a representative slip for it.
That's not the same thing, is it?
They somewhat have adopted the system.
They've just changed it.
For example, and forgive if this is not accurate, but I had a discussion with someone in that part of the world quite a few years ago.
And if you were to start a business, instead of getting a loan from the bank, the bank actually became a partner with you and your business and put their hand in the till that way.
You see?
So on paper, it doesn't look like there's actually a usury agreement, but they do have access to the till at the end of the day and as much of it as they want.
So what's interesting is there's going to be a revival of law, a law form that has been long forgotten in the future as well.
And this law form is actually a very positive law form when it's applied well, but when it's applied poorly or when it's applied in a despotic way, it could be very treacherous.
In other words, what the word treachery would mean, it would seem good, but it would actually have a negative result.
So just as if water is good if you're thirsty, but you can drown in a very shallow pool, and this is what will be applied in the future.
And not to be confused with Sharia law, by the way.
Yeah, I was just going to get to that point because I didn't want people to think that you were saying that Sharia law was a great thing.
No, Sharia law is a Freemasonic – well, I shouldn't say Freemasonic.
It's a thrown-together cultural type of law thing because if you look at, again, when we discuss this part of the world, one of the first things other than the obvious way that the fundamentalists of that part of the world dress is their religion comes up.
People think that it is a part of the world where there's a lot of fundamentalism.
And if we were to use the type of religion, let's say Islam or being a Muslim, it's supposed to be based on the Koran.
If you were to study the Koran and you were to study the culture of the people of that part of the world, you will see that they're not adhering to it at all, and they know very little of it in context.
So just like the Judeo-Christian, they would state that they are biblically based, but if you study the biblical text and study them, you will see that there's stark contrast.
As a matter of fact, it's very safe to say that they're actually doing the opposite.
It's very safe to say that.
In other words, the things that are banned in the text that they allegedly subscribe to are the order of the day, and the things that they're supposed to do, they have never heard of.
Isn't that unusual?
Yeah, mostly. That's the correct point.
And I always find it fascinating to point out that this idea of putting women in burqas and covering their faces and all this other stuff is really a uniform of the world's oldest profession, and it's kind of twisted.
Just like in the Christian realm, they do a parody to Moloch, where the child is incinerated by a bright red, placed in the lap of a bright red character.
It's very interesting how they view that as a good thing to celebrate, where it's actually abominable.
This goes across the board, though, with all concepts.
When I say concepts, I mean religions, because they're just based on concepts.
They're not founded on anything.
Well, actually, they are founded on hidden ancient rites and rituals that have persisted since post-flood days or that time period.
And all they do is change the name of the religious sect.
Like Christianity, you have all the different denominations, and Islam, you have denominations.
And if you look at these denominations, they are geographically based, you see.
And all they're doing is pursuing the ancient rites and rituals of whatever spiritual entity was in that part of the world or geography at the time.
Gee, that's funny, because that sounds a lot like what I understand paganism to be.
Exactly, yeah.
And paganism was, see, man cannot disconnect himself from the authority of a god in his mind.
Even in atheists, when you study their texts, they use the word design and creation a lot, or created a lot.
So they cannot be escaped.
The paganism aspect was that the majority of the people were separated by a priesthood who had the proprietary knowledge,
and it was necessary to keep the people functioning in their day-to-day lives.
And to get involved in the proprietary knowledge required a lot of study.
And the stronger the priesthood got, the more they sequestered the knowledge and the study,
and the more the people that didn't study fell away from it.
And then there was such a large disparity in behavior that the priests found the common people to appear repugnant to them, like almost savage.
And then the lines were drawn and the information was not shared.
But the people took upon themselves to interact with the base elemental entities of the area.
When I say elemental entities, these are spiritual entities that are indifferent to you,
meaning no matter how many offerings or how many prayers you give them, they don't really care about you at all.
That's why you see a lot of the human sacrifice.
This is the nature and the state of mankind today in the spiritual realm, when they consider spirituality.
We've discussed that as well.
So not to be confused, what's coming in the future, again back to the Middle East, is what you see now.
The various sects of Islam or the various laws that are discussed are not going to prevail in the future,
because those are not based on anything that is written.
Now, they might say, yes, these are a series of writings that those that continue the writings of, let's say, Muhammad and all this,
or in the rabbinical, in the Judeo aspect, they have their own sect of beliefs,
that if a rabbi says something and it's memorialized, it can be memorialized after a hundred years,
and they develop all these little idiosyncratic laws in Judaism.
And the same with Christianity.
They develop these little idiosyncrasies in how they do things,
from the quote-unquote people in the Jehovah's Witness Protection Program,
all the way to the Mormons, all the way to the Protestants, the Baptists,
they all have their own little quirkiness and sectarian type of belief.
And none of that is out of any of the texts that they allegedly should be subscribing to,
because anyone in these sects would say, well, if you ask them what your religion was based on,
they will say it's either the Koran or the Bible, if it's Judeo-Christian,
and you won't find what they're saying in there.
Well, yeah, and that's like I always consider the oddity of something that they call sainthood, right?
I mean, what in the world is that?
Where is the ancient texts discussion about this?
Or the biblical, yeah, or a martyr in Islam or something like that.
It's made up, but you have to, yeah, that goes back to Simon Magus,
who we could pin a lot of it on him.
He was like the, let's just say, for software you would say Bill Gates.
He necessarily didn't write the software,
but he would be considered the figurehead behind the empire of that software.
The progenitor of the system.
Pretty much, yeah.
So you would say Simon Magus or Saint Peter or the first Pope would be,
or what they call the church fathers or Gnosticism or Christianity.
All of that has come from the same place,
and then you look at all of the things that have come after that,
based on that time period of the first century A.D.,
which was just a revival of all this synchronic schizophrenia
that happened 500 years before that to grapple and throw something together.
But yeah, this is not what we're talking about.
The law form, going back to what we were discussing,
that's going to be in the future, not only in the Middle East,
but the Middle East will sort of push this or thrust it into all the cultures,
just like right now, what you hear about, quote-unquote, ISIS in the news
is thrust through all the cultures on the planet through the, quote-unquote,
mainstream media, right?
I bet if you go to Brazil or Chile or Nigeria or Russia or Canada or China,
you will see, quote-unquote, ISIS in the news if you turn on mainstream media.
So this is thrust in people's consciousness now.
Right, and it's a worldwide consideration.
Speaking of worldwide, I've got to tell you,
I'm just going to prove that I do pay attention to the chats and the Skype messages right now
and throw this in, which seems to make no sense, but I bet you we can make sense of this.
The whole flat Earth thing going around, it is so ridiculous, but let's see.
Well, that's another experiment. Can we say dummy load?
No, but not dummy load. I've got to tell you, I think it's a revival of an ancient dummy load.
How about that?
Yes, but you can't show me anywhere in any written text where a flat Earth was memorialized.
Look up Strabo. S-T-R-A-B-O, I believe.
He's like the father of modern geography or cartography and mathematics regarding cartography,
measuring curvatures and things like that.
One of the most famous ones.
It's like saying Socrates or Plato.
There are many other philosophers, but those are like the kingpins, let's say, right?
If you see renderings or statues of Strabo from, let's say, I think it was 100 B.C. or 1st century A.D.,
what do you see him standing next to?
A sphere or a globe, which is the Earth.
This is 2,000 years ago.
So where is NASA there photoshopping everything?
But here's the aspect of the flat Earth.
They might say that it comes from the biblical aspect.
I heard someone say that it's the four corners of the Earth, right?
Have you heard of that?
Yes, I've heard of that.
Of course, that's a common, one of those common phrases, actually, that you find in literature all over the place.
Sure.
The four winds, the four corners, the four, and this almost makes it seem like there might be a square.
It is not.
A square would have four corners or a rectangle of some sort, right?
Hold on.
Let's give the secret real fast because it's just you and I speaking now, right?
Everyone cover their ears.
Take a circle, okay, and I want you to put a line through it, and then I want you to put another line through it at 90 degrees,
like cutting a pie into four pieces.
Right.
Now put your finger in the middle of the pie.
Don't you see four corners there in the center?
Yes, you do.
There you go.
So that's why when you look in the biblical text, it says do not shave the four corners of your head, meaning the top of your head.
That means don't shave a round bald spot on the top of your head.
Oh, wait a second.
There are Christian monks that do that.
Oh, wow.
We weren't supposed to say that.
Okay.
Yes, because look, it still prevails.
No matter where you look, it's all backwards.
It's a bizarro world, really, isn't it?
It's a form of rationalizing things that are not modern, and remember, if you look at ancient historical writings,
right before Rome fell apart, they called themselves modern.
Right before Babylon fell, they called themselves modern.
Should I keep going?
Isn't Western society considering itself modern?
It's almost like a self-inflicted curse.
That's absolutely true.
Again, the predictive programming, and it does echo, and like Mark Twain says, history may not repeat itself, but it sure does rhyme.
And I know I'm paraphrasing, but I still think that's brilliant because it does.
Well, it's just like guns don't kill people, bullets do, or people do.
History doesn't repeat itself.
People repeat it.
Ah, there is the key, actually.
And yes, I will get into the concept of animals and stuff later.
It just hasn't come up in the conversation.
Again, I'm paying attention to the texts and things like that that are coming in, because this will fit into the story, believe me.
So we're going to discuss animals and what's wrong with what people do,
because after all, these things are prescribed for your perusal so that you might actually follow the directions in something called, well, the text.
I mean, it's there in the ancient writings, is it not?
The way that people are supposed to behave and what they're supposed to do and how we're supposed to get to this point.
Actually, the directions are all there for everyone to do what?
Well, to live a – now, what is the phrase you like to use as far as someone's life?
An efficient.
An efficient life.
There you go.
Do you remember a couple of years ago, there was this fervor about prepping and storing water, food, and rations?
What happened to that now?
Oh, it's still out there.
It's still – believe me, there are people that are dedicated still, but it does seem to have lost its – oh, I don't know.
Mass appeal?
Its trendy mass appeal, yeah.
Like, you know, it's not as big of a curiosity so that they're not doing these, you know, doomsday prepper shows like they were.
And even in alternative media, to be honest with you, although they're still running the same advertisers, you know, for your food you can keep for 30 years
and how you're going to get water if everything collapses in society, that's still going on.
But if you notice, a lot of those big businesses are not raking it in like they used to for some odd reason.
Just like the nuclear fallout shelters are not raking it in like they used to back in the 50s, right?
You know, there's a lot of this stuff going on.
Now, how efficient is it to worry, right?
I think it's written somewhere that you shouldn't worry, right?
Worry means lack of efficiency.
It's just dummy load, which again is just spinning wheels depleting energy.
It's quite crucial.
Anyone in the financial market knows that foreknowledge is critical.
What they call, you know, they punish you if you do what's called insider trading.
But that is the most coveted and the height of trading these random markets is knowing what's going to happen before it happens so you have a sense of security, right?
When you invest, right?
So having foreknowledge of what's coming on this earth is very important as well.
The only thing is that when you discuss these topics, they've been hijacked by the, quote, unquote, all those people that have been wrong in the past, right?
Someone once texted, well, those predictions, how are they going to be good for us?
Like they've been so correct for the past 100 years.
Well, it has nothing to do with that.
It has to do with, you know, can you find yourself where you are on the map?
You know, if you know how fast you're going and where you are, you know how long it's going to take to get where you're going.
It's just very basic.
And the problem now, which is not much of a problem, is that it's very difficult to discuss these things in private or public because there's a lack of study.
And, yes, it's 100% external input.
A lot of people are still going around saying, I believe, I feel, I think, or whatever.
Who cares what you believe or who cares about what you think?
Show me something that works.
Can we reference it, you see?
And you really can't.
There's a tremendous movement, or actually it was a few years ago, not as much now, but it still exists in the, quote, unquote, new age movement in many circles to tell people who they are and what to think and where we're going.
And they're all wrong, you know, when you look out there, even just cursory or in-depth study.
You know, so that's where I cite the, quote, unquote, problem because the information cannot be taken seriously when you give it in some sense of precision or accuracy.
But it doesn't matter because one should say these things because you don't want to be held accountable for not saying them later.
That's why we do the show and that's why we come out and we tell people to not worry.
There's nothing to worry about unless you like being in a hamster wheel.
And, you know, it changes.
Stop thinking of reality week by week, you know, as it's projected, you know.
And what's coming is a Middle East union that is pretty much going to be the powerhouse of the planet.
And what you're seeing right now is can we liken Syria maybe to Poland in the 1930s?
You know how they just walked everybody kind of – well, the National Socialist Party just walked through there, you know.
And that was the main – you know, there weren't a lot of – I mean, that's where there was the first like, ouch, what's going on here in Europe?
Look at Poland, you know.
The interesting thing about what's going on now with Russia in the news is it's very simple to see that it's going to be a worldwide effort in that part of the world.
And it's going to be continuous all through the rest of what they call this decade into the next decade.
So, you know, this story, yes, it is sad to see that kind of aggression.
And it's also interesting to see a world leader like Putin come onto the scene, which there's a lot that could be said about him objectively as well.
And I could share with someone that I was acquainted with that did a lot of business with the higher-ups in that part of the world.
And they were basically viewed as all being organized crime.
So, you know, that's this one person's perspective, you know, in a sense.
And, you know, what's criminal in one culture is not in another.
But when you discuss organized crime, let's say, you know, it's very relative because you could look at the Western society, how the banking and legal institutions and scientific institutions work or can be classified as organized crime as well.
I was going to say, just take a step back and you could literally categorize any organization on this planet as being part of organized crime, whether they be corporate, you know, allegedly the public sector or the governmental agencies, etc., etc.
Or even the little cliques of individuals that are regionally coalescing in order to push criminal ideals down the throats of everybody else.
I mean, really, honestly, there is a matter of domination which continues to occur all over the planet.
Just like I'm very fond of saying that it is the worship of death that is the prevailing religion across the planet.
In truth, it has nothing to do with these alleged different sects.
You know, I believe the Messiah has come.
I believe the Messiah has yet to come.
Well, I believe, you know, this guy was talking to God.
It's really all irrelevant because, in truth, your worship is actually completely dependent upon satisfying death itself.
You know, that is what I see and that's why I quite satisfactorily refer to myself as a pagan because at least that's an honest label.
You know, I don't know.
Yeah, it would be honest.
Let's just say you haven't studied and it would be an easy way to say that you don't subscribe to the organized,
or any facet of anything organized out there because of its level of hypocrisy, ignorance, or whatever, or just worshiping death.
So I get a sense of that.
I do not adhere to any religion other than, you know, brushing my teeth and combing my hair and washing, you know,
and things that I do regularly and the things that I do regularly, like, is part of your law and your law comes from your deity.
So you have to pick one and go that way.
That's just the way people work.
It's objective.
But going back to the quote unquote Russian or Putin comment,
it's that people have been getting used to this third grader or fourth grader tactics or media about the tactics and strategies in the Middle East
and Putin comes up with a fifth or sixth grade mentality.
It looks very advanced, you see.
Oh, right.
It's very much like looking at an old television show and we're just about to go into the second hour, everybody.
But just about when you go into an old television show, what you see is, well, there's a guy wearing a white hat.
There's a guy wearing a black hat.
The guy wearing the white hat is the good guy.
The guy wearing the black hat is the bad guy.
There's usually some dummy cannon fodder behind all this stuff.
Really, that's part of the scenery.
There might be, you know, some meat puppets that are sketched in there here and there, but their characters don't really have any depth.
The truth is when you take a look at that sort of very simplistic presentation versus the more, I hate to use this word again,
but the more modern style of filmmaking or television show production, things like that, it does change the perspective, the depth,
and that is certainly what we're talking about here.
Of course, Putin might be doing television in the 80s and we're still thinking about television in the 1940s and 50s.
But that's the way the world is turning, and we'll be right back in the second hour with Ocelli and the Greeks.
Stay tuned.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us with free education?
Well, that's obviously a factor, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America.
All the information they provide is free?
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, man?
Exploiting commonplace corruption?
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice?
Bringing light to important information nobody else does?
They never censor, hang up, or cut off their guests?
Well, that's no fun, is it?
They created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative, and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shows and scum?
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from,
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable people without a voice, bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream and alternative media shows and scum,
what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotic.
Freedom.
Oh, yes, I like it very much.
Radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are three million edible food plants on Earth, and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein, and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces three brand-new detox formulations of micro-plant powder.
Brain Fuel, for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit, and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape,
various pain-related healthcare costs, epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders, and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer, and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
The only broadcast would dare to under the sonic entity known as.
So the second hour begins of Ocelli and the Greek here on American Freedom Radio.
Immediately following this broadcast, apparently they will be replaying the JFK special that I did last week on the 22nd of November.
And it is not me trying to self promote by the way.
I'm being asked to tell you that.
Okay, just so everybody knows it's not what I'm doing.
But hey, at 9 a.m. Pacific, which is noontime on the East Coast, also the marathon from Saturday last, from last Saturn Day will be replayed as well.
So yeah, and following that replay of last Saturn Day's marathon here on American Freedom Radio will also be the JFK special once again.
In case you didn't catch it all.
There you go.
And again, this is not me trying to self promote.
I was part of the marathon as well.
Talked to Jordan Maxwell, which I thought was a pretty good conversation.
Also talked to Maria Heller during it.
And of course myself and my co-host here tonight had a conversation with Jack Blood last week.
So yeah, that was kind of unexpected.
And we wound up going the full two hours.
So legitimately Episode 7 was really Ocelli, Greek and Blood.
But that's okay.
We'll describe today as Episode 7.
Anyway.
7B.
7B, perfect.
He's still with me, right?
Let's just talk about Jack for a moment.
It was fun having him.
He's a radio veteran.
I mean, he sounds great.
And a lot of people recognize him.
And he's very good at what he does.
So it was really an honor to have him on.
And truthfully, he's not the style of the Ocelli and the Greek.
But it was quite a treat to have someone else on of his caliber.
Well, right.
I mean, consummate professional.
Definitely one of the guys that I look to.
And I'm happy to call him my friend as well.
You know, actually one of the people that sort of pushed me to start doing these sonic presentations, quite honestly.
And so, yes, much love to Jack from me personally.
But the thing is, yeah, that was kind of fascinating, though, to hear that contrast and the oddity between us.
Because what Jack does is he takes the news, and he very eloquently relates it to people and sort of ties things together with historical references,
takes a look at the trends, and explains to you a lot of things that are coming.
And quite honestly, although it's in a completely different style from what we're doing here today, definitely fully valid.
I really appreciate him.
But let us move a little bit more forward, because we were being asked about this concept of the animals, the raising of the animals, the use of animals.
I guess animal husbandry, this kind of stuff, the use by farmers of animals.
I mean, what does this mean for our diets, for our ability to live efficiently?
Well, okay.
Let's just say the things that one of the trademarks of doing the show is to say things that haven't been said or not being talked about.
There's many ways to go on that.
And think about this for a moment.
You know, people say, hey, I don't eat meat.
Are you a vegetarian?
Yeah, I try to be vegetarian.
Or I'm a meat eater.
You know how people say that.
You know, I eat meat, right?
Okay, well, this whole concept of meeting meat and the way people eat meat, men, women, humans, let's say.
You know, let's cover the whole gamut of the way people want to communicate the being.
Think about this for a moment.
When a predator in nature or in the natural wild or animal kingdom captures and eats its prey, you would call it a meat eater.
Okay?
And indeed it is a meat eater because it captures the prey alive and it usually kills the prey in its mouth or claws or something and immediately starts to consume it in most cases.
So it has actually transferred that life force energy into its body.
When people eat meat, they're not really meat eaters in that sense.
They're more like carrion eaters.
Kind of like vultures.
Kind of like vultures do, right?
It's carrion, yeah.
It's not necessarily very rarely.
I think it's called a geek, someone who bites the head of a chicken off a stage or something like that.
That's true.
That is a geek.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, right.
So most people when they eat meat, they're not eating, they're not doing it or it's not being done in the same context or value as it is in the quote unquote animal kingdom.
It's typically in a state of decomposition.
Now based on, depending on, it's not a discussion I'd like to have really, but when you're in touch with carrion, you render yourself with a certain field or energy that is sort of an unclean way.
You want to wash your hands.
You want to, you know, hence the, you know, the frequent washing of cutting boards and knives and hands and, you know, when people are handling these things, right?
The carrion, whether it's.
You have to.
You have to because it's carrion.
Worms, other, well, hey, worms and things like that which do feed on carrion naturally.
You want to avoid that stuff, right?
Especially.
It's in a state of decay.
It's no longer vibrant.
You see, when a lion, let's say, would tear down, take down a zebra, a pack of lions, let's say, and, you know, it's still alive.
Now, from that respect, if you were to give advice or suggestion to anyone, yes, it is far more noble to be a quote unquote vegetarian than, you see, from that respect, also from a health perspective.
But is there a more fit and proper way to handle animals?
Absolutely.
There used to be a saying that you could judge a culture by how they treat their animals and meaning their husbandry and livestock, right?
If so, if you look at a culture that has a certain amount of, let's say, reverence for the life of an ox or a cow or a chicken or a sheep or a goat and has a very quote unquote humane way of slaughtering the animal,
you'll notice that society functions very differently than one that has them all just as material and, quote unquote, you know, mechanized and in very dirty conditions that are not good for the animal.
So you can judge a culture based on the way they treat their livestock.
Well, easy case in point, right?
The way that the Native American cultures handled, you know, hunting and animals and things like this, truthfully, I can tell you from firsthand experience, not all of them, but some of them don't have an objection to, say, drinking even the fluids from the animal, the blood and stuff like that.
That does happen, but only on a fresh kill and only to honor the animal which they had hunted, you know.
Certain cultures, like when certain, depends on what covenant or culture in certain covenants, you do not, the blood is poured on the earth, on the ground, right?
So, yeah, again, that comes from your deity, believe it or not.
These are questions that, let's just throw up an interesting biblical law.
It states, for example, if a border is drawn and the people across the border decide to become your enemy, if any of the livestock cross over to your border, you are to return their livestock to them unharmed.
Wow, that's a biblical law, by the way.
And if you look at the, quote-unquote, Hatfields and McCoys, which were supposedly Christian, you know, they shot at each other's livestock, you know, and they were fighting each other.
So, a lot of these concepts are not what people think.
So, the question of how to treat animals and husbandry comes from your deity.
And every nation has a patron deity, okay?
And that's answered right there.
So, instead of looking at what people are doing, look at what's causing what they're doing.
Well, here in what's allegedly American culture, let's break it down, right?
I mean, which deity are we actually living under?
The goddess, pretty much.
Yeah, the goddess.
The goddess who is, well, what?
Semiramis, Columbia.
ISIS.
Justice.
All of them being justice, yeah.
Very cruel.
Mm-hmm.
It's a very cruel god, or in this case.
And if you don't think that there's cruelty in the society, you're not paying attention.
If you look, sticking with the animal theme, you'll see that the animals are being treated with cruelty,
and it's because of the patron deity.
And that's all we have to say about it.
I mean, when I say we, meaning, you know, in terms of discussing it,
because otherwise you're going to be going around in circular logic.
I think we've, in previous episodes, discussed how your law comes from your deity.
Mm-hmm.
It's very simple.
Yeah, there's no reason.
Like, I was on a Mitch Santel show, Remnants and Luminaries, earlier,
and a lot of the questions that were being brought up have already been answered.
It just comes from your god, and that's why science is a religion, right?
Right.
You know, medicine is a religion.
All these things have a patron deity, and it would behoove anyone to see what it's based on.
Right, and who is science's patron deity?
Do you know?
Well, that's a real interesting one,
because sometimes I like to spell science with a P-S-Y in front of it.
Mm-hmm.
It's a psy-op.
It's, again, actually the science that is purveyed in each country
is based on the country's patron deity, again.
And that's why you see all of the scientific communities right now
have kind of organized into international groups,
because right now everything is on a global level.
So, it's, again, seemingly we discuss the spiritual side of things.
Why?
Because we're spiritual?
No, not any more and not any less than anyone else,
but maybe we're discussing what's going to be on the minds of people in the future.
Well, the reality is that no matter what we're able to readily observe,
as far as these shifts, as far as these current events,
as far as these wars and rumors of wars,
and rumors of rumors of wars that exist all over the planet,
I mean, the truth is this is the stage show for the battles which have already been fought.
And people think I'm crazy when I say stuff like this,
but, I mean, really it's like the echo of what's already happened.
That's what I observe.
Well, it's like two men sitting playing chess.
The move is first structured in the mind,
and then it's manifested physically by the hand moving the piece.
And the mind would be the spiritual realm,
and the physical realm is the one that we find as being tangible.
And humans don't like to discuss or think about things that are not tangible,
because they're always called on it.
You know, prove it, show me, right?
Right.
But if we look at, for thousands of years, information on this realm,
meaning a non-tangible realm being in control,
there's always a fork in the road with any knowledge or information or subject matter.
The left fork says it's crap, it's bunked, I don't believe it.
And the right fork is that it's important and needs to be looked at.
Well, if you think it's bunked, then don't go down that road.
But if you think it's valid, and if you see validity in it,
now you've been increased by or edified by some knowledge that others don't want to have.
Oh, right.
But this becomes a question of rarefied knowledge versus, you know,
what is observed on a daily basis.
You know, and some people would say that all the concepts that we're talking about are not really relevant,
because it doesn't affect their daily lives, let's just say.
It doesn't.
But then again, you know, I ask this question all the time when they say,
well, that's not affecting me, but what's going on, you know,
at the Mexican border is affecting me, what's going on, you know, in Iraq is affecting me.
And I say, really, well, how do you even know that,
except that you're relying on these odd concepts that someone else has taught you?
The truth is, unless you have completely observed it based on your own logic,
you don't even know that the war in Iraq was nothing more than a bad TV show that's been going on for too long.
You know, you don't necessarily know that this guy Vladimir Putin exists.
He could be just an image from a video game as far as you're concerned.
The Truman Show type deal.
The Truman Show, maybe the whole planet is nothing more than a bad reality TV show
that's about to get canceled.
Of course, that sounds like a cartoon concept.
But, hey, you know, that did actually happen on a show called Futurama.
I think, no, wait, it was South Park, excuse me.
South Park was the one where it was a bad reality TV show and they decided to cancel it.
You know, the entire Earth.
Well, the thing is, it's just going to graduate to another level.
It's just that with any, let's say, qualitative discernment, you know, like quality control,
you're looking at a society that is unrehabilitatable.
So most of it is going to have to be recycled or sent to the scrap heap before it goes to the next level.
And even the ones that do go to the next level have to be completely reworked.
So, you know, people think when they say the end, it's not the end where, you know,
I was in a conversation today and someone said,
do you mean that everything is just going to be reduced back to microbial life forms on Earth?
And I'm like, no, nothing like that at all.
You're going to have the axial period of all axial periods,
which is going to be a time that is going to change everything coming in the next decade.
So it's no big deal.
Because when these things do come and they're going to be very dramatic and very major globally,
it's going to seem normal and natural, you know.
Well, much like many of the things that if you took a step back, even, you know, look at it this way.
If you went back to the 1960s and explained the society that we see,
the commonplace objects, the different interactions and things, people would think you were quite crazy.
If you went back to 1860 and explained the 1960s to them, they might think you're crazy, but maybe not so much.
You go back to 1760 and, you know, another hundred years.
Okay, this time, and yes, I purposely only chose 50 plus years the first time.
But the second time, you go back another hundred years, and it's really not all that much different, it seems.
You know, in other words, things have kind of accelerated because they're meant to.
Yes, and also there's not that much, you know.
You can take a common oaf off the street from 500 years ago or 2,000 years ago and drop him into today's society,
and within eight hours, he'd be 50% acclimated.
Within three days, he could be 99% acclimated.
You know, he'll just learn this switch here makes light, this thing does this, this thing.
People have not changed very much at all.
If you go back about 4,500 or 5,000 years and you bring someone from there into this, quote-unquote, existence we have today,
they will not be surprised at all.
You think not?
No, no, that time period is very parallel to this time period.
As a matter of fact, here, you ready to get in trouble?
Yeah, let's do it.
About 4,500 years ago, there were about 7 billion people on the planet as well.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
See, now I've never heard that before.
That's going to get us in trouble if anyone's listening, because you know what?
It's the truth.
Sorry, guys.
And there's actually very little, if not any, record of that or, you know, or evidence that people will say, hey, look how clear this is.
But what's interesting about it is back then also, people were going through puberty around 50 years old, or let's say 30, 30 to 40.
So it's quite interesting, and I could hardly wait until this becomes more public knowledge or public acknowledgement,
and it won't be for at least the better part of the next decade.
So at least this is being memorialized here, you know.
All right.
Well, that sounds interesting.
I mean, it sounds almost crazy, though, people going through puberty at 30, 40, 50 years old.
I mean, what does that say?
What was their lifespan?
Pretty long.
Actually, very long.
It would be interesting.
It wouldn't be uncommon to go to a street market, and someone would say, you know, it took me 200 years to weave this rug.
Wow.
And it would be the guy who actually made it, you know.
Yeah, quite interesting.
And, yeah, it's very important that the public doesn't know this.
They can hear it.
You know, we can say things that will come into fruition later as being a knowledge base of reality, but they can hear it,
but they don't want to know it because, you know, it's very contrary to what's being told right now.
But it has to be said.
I mean, why not?
I mean, you encouraged me to say it.
Of course.
Listen, I encourage you to say anything that's not being heard elsewhere.
Yeah, and it's not just for the sake of saying it because it's not being heard elsewhere,
but I assure you this is going to be looked at with some rationale and reasonable, you know, assessment, and will be the conclusion.
So it's very easy to come up to that information once you do some study.
So let's just throw these things out there little by little.
I mean, we gave away the four corners of the earth today.
I mean, I've never heard that discussed either.
Well, that's for certain.
And, of course, you gave them a very practical sort of way to witness it for yourself.
This is exactly what they meant by the four winds, by the way, the same kind of concept.
I mean, it's…
Well, there's a four corners region in the U.S., isn't there?
Colorado, New Mexico, Arizona.
Right, that's where you can famously stand on one point and be in four states at once or whatever.
I think they actually have some sort of thing there where you can, you know, hopscotch between them or something like that, which is kind of interesting.
Yep, and one day we'll discuss where the cosmic center of the earth is or the navel.
So if you're standing on that navel, you have the cardinal lines north, south, east, west that forms that cross.
And where that navel or that center is on the earth, right, where the cardinal lines emanate from, is the four corners of the earth.
So you could actually, you know, see four people standing in the four corners of the earth.
And it's just they're all, you know, within arm's reach of each other or inches or millimeters away.
Right, well, depending on exactly how precise you have that spot laid out.
Yeah, it's pretty close.
You could look, you could find it pretty much.
You know how the navel is a deep depression in the outer part of the body that's closed.
Where is the deepest fault line, you know, on the surface of the earth?
So you could find that just by doing a search.
We just pretty much gave that away as well.
So, yeah, that part of the earth or that part of the world, as we discussed earlier, has been in the people's minds and discussed for a very long time.
Meaning the Middle East.
And it's not going away.
And there's going to be a lot more geopolitical moves being made there.
I think once we discussed, Chuck, about how can you have a union, like let's say use the European Union as a model.
When all of the countries are too nationalistic and are fighting each other or indifferent to each other, you see.
So what you're witnessing now in the Middle East, country by country, not like dominoes, it's going to be going around here and there,
are going to become less radical, less apathetic and less national.
So they could end up working together in the next decade.
Well, right.
I mean, and this is certainly not, you're not saying that the, you know, the Calipha or the Caliphate is going to be the unifying agent over there.
You know, so just so we make that very clear, because there is this concept that the, you know, the Caliphate which is being developed
and there will be a singular like a king of the area over there is one of these things being pushed by the ISIS crisis concept.
You know, and this is completely not what we're talking about here.
No, it's not. That's not going to happen.
As a matter of fact, the, have you ever heard of the concept of the one world religion?
Of course.
Okay. Well, that's what's going to be coming in, in the future, in the Middle East.
And it's not any of the current world religions at all.
The concept of it is going to be based pretty closely, if not accurately, to the Judeo-Christian, what they are supposedly based on, but not.
It's not going to be Judeo or Christian, but it's going to be based on a certain ancient text that people are very familiar with of its existence, but have never read it.
That type of law, because what's interesting by default, if you read the Koran, in several places it has the reader acknowledge that the law of Moses is the highest law.
Okay.
So where do you find that?
But anyway, that's another story, isn't it?
It certainly is.
Yeah, so radical, you know, the way you prevent radical Islam is by having them read the Koran.
The way you prevent fundamental Christianity is by having them read the biblical text.
The way you prevent radical Judaism is to have them read the biblical text, right?
Yeah.
What do you think of the Kabbalah and the Kabbalistic...
Mishnas and things?
You have to realize that there's something called the chosen people.
You've heard that before, right?
Several times, yes.
Okay.
This is a poor translation.
You have to realize that things are chosen to serve a specific purpose.
It could be bad as well.
Like, you can choose the wind-up toy known as the clock to set your appointments, and you'll know that if everyone follows what is chosen, meaning the wind-up toy, whether it's digital or analog, you will meet at the cafe tomorrow at, let's say, 3pm by the wind-up toy, right?
Well, it's based on the agreement, isn't it?
Yeah.
Now, you have a group of people on the planet which were fortunately and unfortunately chosen to retain or be the oracles of certain information, and that's all that makes them chosen for.
And people have taken that out of context.
I even hear that in passing.
Oh, they're the chosen people.
I'm like, chosen for what?
And they don't know what.
It's all out of context right now.
But remind me of the question again that you brought up about the Kabbalistic writings.
Okay.
Yeah.
That is all strictly from the rivalry that was created.
It was rabbinical writings from the Babylonian exile.
Right.
Because basically when they were exiled to Babylon, it was like, well, if your god is so great, why are you exiled here?
Look at our priests, you know?
We're not exiled anywhere.
So they had like a little bit of a competition who could be more literary, verbose, or try to outdo one's sense of mysticism for another.
But it's all foreign.
It's based on lower – because if you look at the biblical deity, the chief deity, he claims to be the highest of authority.
And the Babylonian entities never made that claim.
They were a much lower category.
Now, this is not what anyone believes in or one's opinion.
This is just a fact in what's been memorialized.
There are many writings from that quote-unquote Judaism that are not lawful, meaning based on the biblical law.
You see, it's unlawful what they're doing for a time period yet to come.
All of the religions on the planet are operating unlawfully if they reckon their law to be in the text that they subscribe to.
Right.
All of them are.
There's not a one that isn't.
No, we've said this several times.
There's absolutely nothing that claims to be a religion on the planet that adheres to its own text regardless of what religion you identify.
It really is irrelevant because every single one, especially what they call the Abrahamic religions, those things are completely off-kilter with their own text.
But every religion, in fact, seems to be without adherence to its own laws, its own text, its own deity's desires to see them conduct themselves in their fit and proper sense, it seems to be.
None of them are fit and proper at all.
They're political.
You cut out there.
I think you were saying that they're all political.
Oh, there you are.
You're back.
Yeah, sorry, yeah.
Yeah, they're all political.
Political meaning the business of the society.
People go to these temples, places of worship for social reasons.
Well, right.
Not to be edified, yeah.
No, but that's the thing is that they're all adaptations based on, you know, kind of peer pressure from the given societal clutches that appear in different sectors.
This is why you have all these different subdivisions which are known as, well, what do they call those again?
The, you know, the different – oh, my.
What is that?
The different, you know, like –
Denominations.
There you go.
Interesting word, denomination.
Like money, yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
It's, you know – so who's the $1 bill, who's the $2 bill, and who's the $3 bill?
It seems like they're all $3 bills to me.
But, hey, that's a strange sort of jump into a joke, I guess.
But, yeah, it does appear that way because, you know, what do you say to someone who is screaming at you that, you know, this is the rule book by which I live and by which I want the entire world to live?
And, meanwhile, they have not read it, nor are they even aware of the nature of it in truth.
That is what we can observe all over the planet except in the case of those who are statists because, you know, someone who is a statist seems to be adhering to their chosen deity quite well if they're living and abiding by the law.
Oh, wait a minute.
Actually, even these people that claim to be statists will find that they are breaking the laws which are given to them by their governing deity anyway because, well, what is the point here?
We do live in a place which is unlawful.
I like to say lawless because it has no legitimate law.
So, in that sense, I think it's correct.
But, of course, you say it's an unlawful society in which we find ourselves.
Yeah, unlawful is because you're basically going against the rules of the environment or the ecos, which means the house.
You know, people are arrogant enough to think that, you know, you evolved from slime and into monkeys and to, you know.
But this is, by the way, taken from the ancient Egyptian writings where Pharaoh had commissioned texts.
I forgot which one.
I think it was an unnamed pharaoh to tell the people that they emerged from the Nile as slime, you know.
People think this evolution is amazing.
Might have been Khufu, maybe.
Maybe, yeah.
So, yeah.
So, we have a level of arrogance here that is reaching what they call high heaven, right, as they used to say.
But the aspect of people going to these, the attraction to the religious aspect is they know that there's a spiritual need.
And just like if someone wants cheese on their hamburger, they don't care if it's made with milk or not.
It looks like cheese, right?
So, you know, yeah.
It's kind of like, again, the operating system.
There was something done about a year ago.
It might even be on YouTube where evolutionists were interviewed on why they believe in evolution because you have to believe in it.
And you've got to hear some of the answers.
I mean, we're talking about, you know, an IQ of room temperature, you know.
And we're talking about academics as well, which, by the way, I like to define the term academic for people.
Should we just read that?
Because this is not an academic discussion that we're having.
No, this is certainly, yeah, this is certainly not an academic discussion.
Yeah, academic.
This is from etymology, a 1580s relating to an academy, collegiate or scholarly, which means theoretical, not practical, and not leading to a decision.
So this is what you're getting in debt for with these university morons.
And, yes, they are, all of them, not some of them.
The ones teaching and the ones going there also, and anyone who's graduated from there or left any kind of academic institution
and doesn't think that they fell into buffoonery and stupidity, well, you just haven't realized it yet, right?
And the people teaching there are the epitome of stupidity and buffoonery.
Sorry, you know, this has to be said, guys.
So, anyway.
No, and I found that funny because that was exactly the definition you sent to me when I was in the midst of arguing with someone who allegedly has a Ph.D. in two different disciplines.
Yeah, no, I love that because it was just like, well.
This is not, by the way, this is not the opinion.
The definition of academic is not the opinion of the Ocelli and the Greek show.
It is not our opinion.
This is what it actually is memorialized as.
As usual, it is the report based on what anyone can access.
Theoretical, not practical, and not leading to a decision.
Circular logic, I guess.
Yeah, that absolutely defined Jim Fetzer perfectly.
But moving forward, away from my personal problems.
But this is the thing, you know, and people wonder sometimes because I find it fascinating individuals that invest their time into going and getting Ph.D.s.
You know, they can supposedly, functionally, and literally communicate in three different languages.
They're supposed to have a particular area of discipline, also a base of knowledge, which gives them, you know, what they call liberal arts education or a general sense of the overall education that is available in a very rudimentary sense.
All of these things are supposed to be incumbent upon an individual who has graduated from an academy or a university, you know, so on and so forth, right?
I mean, it's really fascinating to understand that that's exactly what academics do.
It's a waste of time here.
You know, if you want to learn a language, do it organically.
How do you do it organically?
Well, how do people learn languages?
Well, the baby usually is brought up in speaking as an adult the language that was spoken in its formative years, right?
And how does it learn to read and write?
With coloring books.
So if you want to learn a language, download a coloring book in that native language and start coloring in the letters and start learning the words organically like a three or four-year-old would.
And guess what?
You're going to probably as an adult do it a little bit faster than a three or four-year-old, and you're going to be able to accomplish in a couple of days what a primer, you know, from let's say pre-kindergarten to first or second grade, what would take them several years, you could probably do in a few days.
And you will probably be half fluent in that language within a couple of weeks.
And you could do it all by starting by downloading a coloring book in the native country you want to learn.
And how is that?
The other thing you could do is expose yourself, just like that baby would be, to the conversational interaction in that particular tongue.
This is something else that would help you to move further because that way you could develop the conversational acumen to actually, you know, internalize it and be able to utilize it as a language, right?
Yeah, someone in chat wrote immersion, and that's pretty much the correct way to do it.
And now with the technology that's available, it can be done.
And what I have done in the past is suggested that people begin to be familiar with the languages of the part of the world that we started to bring up this geopolitical commentary about on the show.
Get familiar with those languages there, what we might call schematic languages, right?
And you would be at an advantage just like, I think, years ago here in the States.
They would say you'd be at an advantage if you knew Spanish, right?
Remember that?
That's right.
Yeah.
And prior to that, it was French and Greek a century or two ago.
I think at one point they were going to make the Langua Franca here in the U.S. back in the 1700s.
They were deciding on whether to make it Greek or French, by the way.
So, yeah, these languages would be of that part of the world, it would behoove anyone that is, quote-unquote, futuristic in mind to get familiar with those schematic tongues, which would be the, quote-unquote, Hebrew, Arabic, Farsi tongue.
You would not be at any disadvantage.
Actually, you'd be quite an advantage individual in the future within less than a decade from now.
Right.
But, I mean, there is a significant linguistic difference.
I mean, it would not be similar to the native English speaker to learn something like, you know, Spanish is not that difficult.
The Roman alphabet.
Because it contains the same alphabet exactly.
So, I mean, there is a bit of a shock to the system regarding those characters and things.
Memorization, 22 characters you've got to memorize.
But here's the thing.
The second language, especially in the aerospace industry, anyone working in any airport anywhere in the world has to know English as a second language.
That I wasn't aware of.
Okay, cool.
That is the international language for the aerospace industry, meaning airports, you know, which encompasses the entire gamut.
True enough.
All right.
Well, you know, and we have covered a lot of things here today.
I mean, we've covered the four corners of the earth.
We've covered languages.
We've covered what may or may not be fit and proper.
Although, I do want to return to the food thing a little bit because you said that somebody that, you know, purports themselves as a vegan would actually be living in a much more fit and proper way.
I wonder if you want to elaborate on that a little bit because…
Well, you're not coming in contact with carrion.
If you have a chicken sandwich that's carrion, you're not biting the head off of a chicken getting its life immediately transferred to your body, you see.
So, but nonetheless, that all comes from whatever covenant you live by or what laws you live by, and that comes from your God.
Now, if you think you're God, you should be concerned about calories, you know, because there's been a usurpation of the mind of mankind where science has come in and become the God, you know, that tells people what is good and what is not, you see.
So, what you consider to be fit and proper or right and wrong comes from your deity, not from another man.
Now, another man can share it, but you have to qualify from what deity, and that time is not yet.
I think we kind of prefaced it earlier, the future of the one-world religion, what it, we just gave a little bit of a hint of what it's going to be based on.
It is going to be a new religion or a new law or a new way of doing things, but it's going to come from a very old place, and it's not going to be malevolent.
It's going to be quite benevolent, but it will be used malevolently.
But going back to the food thing, it is more noble cosmically to, quote-unquote, be a vegetarian.
But, on the other hand, if you want to be, let's say, quote-unquote, analytical or scientific about it, if you look at any plant material very closely, you will see it's full of critters, animal life.
It's flora and fauna.
So, then we get into what defining a vegetable is, and there's an interesting book, whether you could take it with a grain of salt, it was called The Secret Life of Plants.
And, you know, when a man walked into, you know, they had the plants hooked up to EKG type machines, and when you walked in there with a scissor, the plant would register, the machine would register an impulse that the plant is noticing you with a scissor, right?
But they also have an intelligence that if you enter the room with a scissor several times and don't use it, the EKG machine doesn't go off because the plant knows you don't mean it.
You don't mean to use it.
Right, and I once saw an experiment years ago where they showed a scan of a plant, and then they cut away part of its leaf.
And then they scanned it again, they x-rayed this thing, and there was this ghost image of the leaf still there, the part that had been cut away.
I thought that was one of the strangest demonstrations I ever did see, but it appeared as though there was some sort of a manifestation of, like, physical memory that was being projected.
And don't hold me to it was an x-ray, but it was some sort of scan.
Maybe Kirlian photography?
Something like that, and it was really weird, like as if this thing remembered that you just cut off its leaf.
It shows you that maybe empty space is not empty after all.
Uh-huh, right.
See, that was the other odd sort of observation I had about it, but, you know, plants are not the very simple organisms that people think they are.
You know, that's just what I take away from all of that.
But I heard about this whole thing with these machines where they could register when somebody was coming in to pluck them and prune them.
But, of course, if you over time went in there with the same instruments, yeah, they had shears and a couple of other things.
I think they actually went in there and literally poisoned one of the plants at one point.
And then the guy comes back in with the same bottle of poison but doesn't do anything.
It seems as though the plants got upset.
Yeah, there's like kind of a – it's not the same type of mechanism that we're supposed to have, but yet –
Yeah, they're able to rationalize the activity around them.
Yeah, which, you know, where's the plant's brain, right?
Well, it's external input, man.
No, but that's my point.
See, everybody thinks that the ability for men or mankind to comprehend things on the level that it does is all having to do with the brain.
But the truth is that it's really part of an intangible grouping of things that are really, really seldom understood.
Well, what is tangible is that it keeps the ears apart.
That it does function to do for the most part.
It's a spacer.
Yeah, it definitely seems to occupy some space, yes.
Well, we discussed how could mankind be an upside-down plant where the brain is the root ball and the limbs are the limbs?
Yes.
And the sexual organs are the flower where the seed is?
Yes, sure.
And isn't it funny how you give flowers on certain holidays?
So, anyway.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Let's not let that slip right by because that is sort of a fascinating thing that you give flowers on certain holidays.
Yeah.
Now, what's interesting is that at a funeral there's an abundance of flowers, is there not?
There sure is.
But what are flowers?
It's the blossom.
It's where the seed comes from.
It's a wishful thinking, right?
Right.
So, to carry on, it's very interesting.
And I think we discussed in the container, or several times about when we discussed sexuality,
that there was an obsession of the, just like in the agriculture, there's an obsession in an unhealthy way,
but in a healthy way in agriculture that you do want to keep the seed for next year's crop.
So, if you do want to keep the seed of your family or mankind or your community going for perpetuity, let's say,
and certain secret societies and ancient societies, mystic albeit, kind of made that part of the body, let's say, with obsession, right?
That's why you see a lot of the phallic and gynic symbols, gynic meaning the female genitalia,
in a lot of the architecture in a lot of the places of worship.
So, you wonder what they're doing.
Well, yeah, there's that.
And, of course, I love when we started discussing Valentine's Day, the heart shape.
That's the thing of beauty right there.
Female genitalia, front on.
That's all it is.
Sorry, we're not making this up.
This has been put on you, and no one's noticing,
and you're being laughed at by people that are probably not laughing anymore because they're dead.
I don't think the people that came after them in these secret societies know much about it.
Some of them might, if they're paying attention.
Yeah, when I say secret societies, these were, you know, whatever you want to call them.
Some people call them masons.
Others call them this or that.
These people knew how things worked, and they put a little bit of what they did and everything they did.
A lot of the children's fables and poems came from these societies.
Like, you can name all the little children's songs.
So, yeah, these things are all tied in, and they're out there.
There's a simplicity about being efficient with your thought and your action,
but when you look at how simple it is, a lot of your energy will go to setting yourself apart from the rest.
It doesn't mean not being a part of it, but when you're in it, you're not of it.
A lot of times I see commentary about this person doing that in media or whatever,
and my reaction to that is, you know, you don't have to be like that.
Maybe that person is doing that as an example to show you what you don't want to do.
You see, like, for example, Black Friday, right?
Something like that, yeah.
And a lot of times people ask why, or, you know, let's not, or they want to go against this individual.
Let's just retract, you know, and enjoy it.
Right, right, absolutely, and I agree with that and understand it,
because, you know, I try and explain to people with some of my presentations,
people think, oh, well, you asked a question or you said something that had nothing to do with the conversation.
You know, what I might be doing is provoking a response, not only from the guest or the subject of the interview,
but, hey, from the audience as well.
Occasionally I like to throw something in just to see if they're awake, and I do it in a very subtle way, right?
The media presentation that you're interpreting, because it is your interpretation,
you know, it's not necessarily meant to be interpreted by you in the way you've interpreted it.
Now, did I just use circular logic? No, I don't think so, but by all means.
It's their version.
I guess maybe an interpretation would just be an objective transcript of the matter,
because when you leave the emotional and the delivery out, then it's not how you said it.
It's just what you said, and most people are not listening to what's being said.
They're listening to what or how it's being said.
Right, for the most part, or they're just latching on to certain keywords.
I notice that that happens with some of our shows.
People come back at me and tell me something that was said about, you know,
that they're saying about a particular show that we did, and I say to them,
what part are you listening to?
And I go back and I can vaguely understand how they drew that from that part,
but it's really funny to me, because no matter what you say, no matter what you do,
it doesn't seem as though, you know, even though people are entirely subject to external input,
it doesn't necessarily mean that the message will be received clearly when it's being said.
Well, it's like out of context with the Blood Moons or Armageddon
or, you know, just throwing things out of context because it suits someone at the moment.
Oh, right, and I introduced all those things in this conversation already.
Basically, just to give people a contrast, see, here's me letting you into my thought process,
but to give people a contrast about what is yet to come, what has already been preordained in a way.
Gee, I know that that word probably just, you know, ricocheted off of your ear like a marble off a tin plate,
but, you know, that which is preordained, let's just say, is not necessarily, you know,
something that's being prognosticated about or discussed.
How many times have you gone on any media, any media,
and seen a Middle East union being discussed with any, not even discussed,
even A, being brought up, and B, discussed in any detail, anywhere?
Nowhere else but here.
Right. I wonder why. Maybe because it's steam engine time, right?
Like it was around a long time ago, now it's time to start discussing these things.
Well, but isn't that the trouble?
Is that when it is time for it, it's time for it.
Right now, for the most part, it seems as though people are enjoying the horror movie section of the video store.
You know, that's what it's all about.
They want to be horrified. They want to be upset.
They want to be disturbed by what they perceive as happening across the planet.
They want to be afraid. They want to be very afraid.
They're not being very efficient, though, because to sit and worry about everything is really rather counterproductive.
Yeah, or listening to the rants and raves for hours on people's quote-unquote news shows or, you know, internet radio shows.
I mean, shouldn't they be saving their breath to cool their porridge, as they say in England?
You know, but it's just part of the frustration. It's part of the dummy load.
It's part of the sign of the times until the next few years when it starts to change a little bit
and the energy starts to become more proactive into understanding what's going on
instead of just discussing what's every news topic of the week.
And again, just to wrap things up, we were going to get more into the geopolitical concept
and we'll see if we get any more feedback to get into more detail about things like this in the future
because we did go into many different subjects, as we normally do, because, you know, we're not very nearsighted
and we like to go, you know, life should have variety, but we should be able to discuss things in a way that
and rational thought to things that are coming and things that are going on.
And unfortunately, because it's so difficult for people to understand that it's a credit-based economy and how it works
or to understand how the human body works and what's been put out by the medical and scientific establishment about it
and understand, let's just basic science, basic, you know, physics, basic cosmology, you know,
to start discussing these things in a true and rational sense is really going against all the grain.
And these are subjects that we touch upon on this show.
But I believe that when it's time to discuss geopolitical things, I think we should.
Well, absolutely. I just don't think the time was entirely tonight.
Although we did touch upon it, we did interweave it into the discussion.
So I want to thank everybody who decided to take the time to listen to this,
whether you caught it live or you caught it further on down the stream.
I'm not putting these on YouTube lately.
I may go back to that at some point.
But for now, I've sort of abandoned the YouTubing of it.
So you go to American Freedom Radio's archives for Ocelli and the Greek
and you can catch up on all of what we've discussed if you missed any of it.
So also, there's the Ocelli and the Greek website, which is at ocelliandthegreek.com.
You can go there and catch up a little bit, too, if you like.
And I don't know, is there anything you want to say as the time runs out on the toy
known as the clock or the digital representation thereof?
Well, first, there's never enough time. And time is all we have.
So in that respect, not really.
I think we try to keep the shows pretty much multifaceted, but the theme is typically the same.
Saying things that need to be said that aren't being said anywhere else.
Well, that is the point of this show.
So once again, everybody, please be well.
Please continue to do your own thing and try to live in a fit and proper way.
Of course, all of that and much more.
And we will see you what they call next Saturday here on Ocelli and the Greek.
Good night.
I'm telling you, you've got to support American Freedom Radio because this government is getting out of hand.
Wall Street won't loan me my money.
The CIA are cutting into my drug running and my gun running.
Big pharma, psychotropic drugs are making my customers commit suicide before my hitman can even whack them.
And then they get depressed and get prescribed psychotropic drugs and commit suicide too.
They're trying to become the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected.
I get unpaid taxes and if I can't find the money, the IRS are going to take my thumbs.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs and that's to support American Freedom Radio.
Capisce? So what are you going to do?
You're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom, freedom, American Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein, is gluten free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org
We are living in a new era. Partnerships are more important than profit and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape,
various pain related health care costs, epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders and even soldier suicides.
Crystal pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer and it saves you over one third in cost.
Crystal pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules, no taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.