It is midnight Eastern, allegedly, according to the wind-up toy, or the digital representation there, of where I sit on the East Coast.
And on a Saturn Day night, or a Sunday morning, allegedly, once again.
That means it's time for Ocelli and the Greek, and we are live on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
I'm not in my usual sort of state of mind tonight. I'm not sick as a dog. A little hungry.
But not sick as a dog like I was last week, so who knows what'll happen.
That's true. Dogs are always hungry, but anyway.
Well, to compare myself to a dog is not so bad, really. When I take a look at the human condition around me, at least dogs are, well, somewhat sensible.
And at least they get up on their hind legs once in a while.
Instead of crawling around like people do, mentally.
Right, they do protest when they're mistreated. I mean, after a while they condition themselves, right?
They seem to accept abuse and things like that, but people not only accept it, they demand it, request it, all over the place.
Maybe we'll get into that a little bit tonight, if possible, amongst other things, being the sixth show, I guess.
So, any other thoughts?
Yeah, absolutely. Well, a couple of things do sort of present themselves to me, and believe it or not, people, we don't script this at all, either.
We hardly even talk. We just meet up on the show.
This is how we do it. I mean, this is the best way to do it.
Two guys meeting in the park, or a cafe, or internet radio, and I'm, you know, same thing.
Right, so what you do is, you usually flip it forward, try and find a point of light to sort of go ahead and bat at it,
much like your friendly neighborhood domesticated cat does, right?
Following the laser pointer on the wall, and somebody places one of those red dots, and next thing you know, two hours are gone.
So, once again, here we are.
Well, looking at the text box, you know, we talked maybe about last week, perhaps talking about what happens after the proverbial end,
and maybe the concept of sexuality, but, you know, I was thinking, Chuck, before we start,
what's interesting about internet radio and mainstream or whatever, people start, you know, there's a lot of people doing shows, right?
It's just, you just need a pulse, basically, and a voice. Anyway.
Well, don't forget internet access now, that's all.
And internet access, right. And, yeah, so essentially, well, what do they do most of the time?
They listen, oh, what's in the news? So maybe I thought we should talk about the news.
Not, you know why? Because there is no news. It's a dummy load.
It's a dummy load on the system, and I was thinking of handing out dummy load awards,
but we'd have to manufacture millions of them every day.
But anyway, when we say dummy load, you know, we give a dictionary definition.
It's a noun. It's a resistive component that absorbs all the output power of an electrical generator
or radio transmitter in order to simulate working conditions for test purposes.
Oh, now, for me, what jumps right out is the idea that that could be a lot of the listeners to the Ocelli effect,
which is the other show, oh, I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said that.
No, no, it's actually everything I hear on the radio, and I mean everything.
It's just everything. This is a dummy load free two hours.
So if you, yeah, so, right, yeah, so if you're looking for dummy load, you will get withdrawal symptoms here.
Right. Now, if you are experiencing withdrawal, let me just quote one of the great prophets of our time,
Marilyn Manson, and say, you know, what he says during that one song, which is babble, babble, bitch, bitch,
party, party, sex, sex, sex, and don't forget the violence, blah, blah, blah.
There's your sad and lonely, stick your stupid slogan in and everybody sing along.
And that's about what you get elsewhere.
Or they're crying about we've got to change ourselves to change things.
No, sorry, that doesn't work.
Well, there's nothing wrong with self-improvement.
Yeah, but the reason why I'm laughing at it is, you know, if you look back in history, you know, well, you know,
it only took 80,000 people to change prohibition.
It was 100,000 women to bring women's suffrage and a million people or half a million people marched on Washington to get rights.
And I'm like, yeah, how's that serve society?
You're going still spiraling downward.
None of that stuff works.
Well, what's beautiful about prohibition is that it's provided us with many, many years of entertainment and mythology, you know,
via the Italian mafia and the mythos thereof.
So, you know, without prohibition, you wouldn't even have had a prolific organization like like the Sicilian syndicates.
That's for sure.
I mean, I don't know if you would have had the Russian mob or anything else like that.
But I'm just saying that's the one that really captures everybody's imagination.
And, hey, without that downward spiral, you wouldn't have had that.
So there you go.
No Godfather movies, no goodfellas.
No, but again, it's a dummy load.
Again, it's all dummy loading.
This is the other one is this is the one that really cracks me up.
Oh, this world leader or parliamentarian or president is bad.
We need you.
Yeah, right.
Well, here, if you ever wonder who's going to be your next leader, it's the one who's going to do more harm to your country.
Guaranteed.
Well, I shouldn't say guaranteed, but I assure you, each consecutive leader through time is worse for their own people.
Why? Because the people are getting worse.
So, you know, the other thing, no dummy load is, you know, I've got to say this.
People that are optimistic and things that are put in front of them are ridiculous.
I was out at the shops today.
And, you know, well, before I say anything about that is, you know, you hear about people.
We've got to change this.
So the next 50 years we have this and that, whatever.
You're not going to have anything like this.
I was out at the shops today.
I was walking down an aisle and I saw two guys at the end of the aisle.
And whatever exposed skin they had was about 90 percent tattooed with sharp pieces of metal sticking out of their body.
So I figured I'd turn around and walk the other way.
And then I see the back of a woman, which could be like someone's grandma.
And she turns around and she's wearing a black T-shirt with a two-foot skull on it with fire in the eyes.
You have no future on this.
You're not going to change anything.
You are going into a situation where the change is only necessary so you know how to set yourself apart from this.
And if you're going to change anything, it's another dummy load.
You can go and protest all you want.
You can go and say it's not good.
Well, okay, so what?
All right, so you change an election.
Big deal.
Ain't going to work.
Nothing is going to go the way.
In other words, the major dummy load, let's just sum it up.
The major dummy load is everything that I see people discussing, bar none, they're putting their hope in things that are completely futile.
None of those things are going to give a result that's going to take society forward.
That's why I believe you and I spoke during the end of what they call the work week,
and I said the reason why things are going to be happening the way they're going to be happening in the next two decades
is because society has reached a point now where they're unrehabilitatable.
In other words, it's kind of like the entire gradient is going down, but instead of being a slope, it's a plateau.
So it's like long steps.
Like you go down, and then you flatten out for a little while.
Then you go down the next step, and you flatten out.
Okay.
So with that said, that's why one of the most hilarious dummy loads I've seen is what a waste of time when you hear all these Internet radio,
and I have in the browser about two dozen of them that I go around and see what's going around,
and they always start off with the news, and they cannot discern that they're being mocked.
Recently, there's a lot of people losing their lives.
There's a Russian jetliner.
Why don't they get consent from the victim's families to release the black box information?
So why the questioning?
9-11, don't even want to touch that with a 10-foot pole.
None of this stuff.
People are not asking the right questions about any of it.
I mean, you look at what people are discussing as subject matter.
It's complete garbage, meaning it's a dummy load to the extreme.
So, again, this is the only place that I have seen.
The reason why we're doing this, I believe, is the motivation was let's provide the world, yes, the world,
and those beyond the planet, if they're listening as well, a dummy load free two hours, and here we are.
Well, and we still do have to give them a tip of the hat now and then,
because you have to at least provide them with the chance to understand that every one of these political leaders,
no matter what their name, their affiliation is, they're all interchangeable.
Every religion or religious practice on the planet is the worship of death, if it is worship at all.
Every legal process is unlawful, and guess what?
I've just explained the entire planet to you.
Exactly.
And it ain't going to change.
Well, here's the thing.
Why would you speak out against a leader of any people, whether it's religious, political, or what have you, even a team?
Those people are there to accommodate the needs of a certain group of people, and they tell you about it.
We're here because we were elected.
Well, how did that happen?
Well, it doesn't matter.
If people are going to say, well, it's election fraud, well, show me something in your life that's not rot and fraud.
You don't even know how to keep time.
I mean, sorry.
So the thing is, let's provide the – now we're down to maybe an hour and 50 minutes of dummy load free time.
But this is the thing.
And just one more thing.
It's not like we're going to kick anyone in the – punch anyone in the nose or kick anyone in the shins, but I really feel bad for the older people.
Years ago, I was told that you go to the older people, people with white hair and high number in years for wisdom and information.
I really feel bad.
I haven't run into anyone that is older than 50 that has one iota of anything to say that is worth listening to.
It's really sad.
And what I've done is really spent a lot of time with younger people, proving that to them, taking them around to where old folks hang out and asking the old folks,
hey, listen, I've got an 18-, 19-year-old here, a man ready to start his journey in life.
Do you have any words of wisdom?
And consistently, it's like, oh, I don't know anything.
I was just a grunt.
I did what I'm told.
Or they talk about, well, this is how you play with a woman's private parts.
Or ridiculous.
I mean, it's just I really feel my heart really goes out to the younger people.
Well, listen, playing with a woman's private parts and instruction on that particular subject matter actually might be of relevance to them.
But the other stuff.
But this is the point that I'm saying.
I mean, can we provide people, you know, this is the sixth time we've come together.
Can we say things that are just not dummy loaded?
I mean, you know, and the thing is, you know, there's probably maybe five or six people out there that are probably listening that are actually maybe, you know, really listening.
And able to acknowledge what we're putting forward.
And that's worth it.
Even if just one person is, it's worth it.
Absolutely.
And that is the point.
And, yeah, we will get to the subject matter that we sort of, you know, prefaced.
In real brief, I mean, we're talking two sentences worth of an exchange between you and I.
Both of these things are worthy of discussion.
But it does, going back to your experience at the shops, as you said, it does speak to the fact that, you know, we are dealing in a culture, a worldwide culture, in fact, that celebrates mutilation, death, the sort of removal of one's own natural identity.
And this is right on time.
Exactly what it's supposed to be.
Exactly.
It's a repeat, actually, of a long time ago.
And almost identical, but in slightly different variation thereof.
Just like listening to old vinyl.
You know, what's great about listening to a record is that it's the same record, the same turntable, the same speakers.
It's the same you.
But every time you play it, it sounds a little different.
And every time this particular thing is played, it's a little bit different.
And it has to be because we're all in a different, you know, the earth is in a different place throughout the movement of things.
And just like a record, what happens is you end up with a little extra cracks and pops and hisses because there is a bit of wear and tear on things.
After all, you're still dealing with that particular record, you know.
So here we go.
And even, yeah, it could just, yeah.
So you mentioned, if you want to dive into some topics, one was sexuality.
And I guess it's referring to it in an objective form, perhaps.
And I try and do that all the time, and nobody wants to hear it.
And I mean in private conversations, in conversations on the radio, nobody really wants to hear the objective point of view on what I see emerging currently, you know, in the field of sexuality or sexism, depending on how you look at it, right?
I mean, it's just, it is this very odd sort of thing that I see occurring, right?
You have the propagation of an amorphous, asexual, transgendered, confused-gendered, non-gendered reality being offered as the natural way of things, which absolutely makes no sense to me.
Not because of some sort of, you know, well, I believe in Leviticus it says, no, no, no.
Just from a natural standpoint, I look at it and I say to myself, well, it appears as though things that exist in the living world all have purpose.
The purpose of just about every function in one's body appears to have a logical reason, okay?
And I say to myself that sexuality in and of itself, even the interplay, the rules of attraction, let's just say, the ways that males and females interact, that whole game, you know, the dating ritual, the courting aspects of it, everything is really like a resonant part of what is the natural order of things.
Now, when you begin to, well, deconstruct it and convolute it and, you know, smear the paint from side to side, you know, eventually you combine enough colors.
You have not black, but this, you know, brown sort of useless color that doesn't represent anything in nature.
You know what I'm saying?
Baby poop.
Baby poop, there you go.
That's perfect.
Exactly.
That's the visual representation of what I see happening to sexuality in general.
And people immediately jump on me and say, oh, well, you know, you just don't like homosexuals because you were programmed not to and you don't understand that that's part of your programming.
And, no, I went through a stage like that.
I really did at an immature point in my life where I was not necessarily committed to the ideas of morality as given to me on high, but I had a, you know, a belief that it was just, you know, a bad thing for some reason.
I had a visceral reaction.
Well, Chuck, hold on.
That's part of the story.
It's not about belief or morals.
It's about being in harmony with your environment.
If your feet are on the ground.
See, what's interesting, while you were speaking, a couple of things went through my mind.
First of all, if you read the Koran and the biblical texts, which are the two major texts for the three major religions, allegedly.
I actually have to bite my tongue to say that because no one in those religions knows anything in those books.
Right.
Well, in the Koran, there are many verses that a woman is to be treated, you know, with very, very high, not to base, very high respect and honor, not to even disturb her garment.
You know, hire, you know, like an angel, pretty much.
In the biblical text, women were the chief economists.
They even had women rulers, you know, during the Deborah, the period of judges.
They were their consults.
They were very highly, highly esteemed and highly regarded.
This whole concept that people have in religious texts.
Oh, these really Abrahamic religions to treat women poorly.
Yes.
First of all, there is no such thing as an Abrahamic religion.
And second of all, the quote unquote religions that people subscribe to.
Yes, they do, because they're satanic.
Oops.
Did I say that?
Sorry.
Anyway, this is not in defense of satanists, but basically all the major religions are, by definition, that adversarial to what they're supposed to be doing.
By what they say from their own mouth.
This word satanic means adversarial, means contrary to.
Right, because Satan is literally the adversary.
The adversary.
Correct translation, yeah.
Yeah, if you say white, he says black.
You say ugly, he says pretty.
So all of the world religions are completely adversarial to the studies that are retained for them.
Now, if you want to reinvent Christianity, Islam, Judaism, Hinduism, Buddhism, and all that every day of the week, like people do the news, you can do that.
And that's what's been going on anyway.
So we're talking about a crazy group of people here on this planet for a long time.
Now, from that respect, the sexuality.
Now, from the other respect, tying it into what you said about quote-unquote homosexuality, that has nothing to do, the morality of it.
People will find out in the future.
That has absolutely nothing to do with your personal desire.
That has absolutely to do with what knowledge you have on what responsibilities are required to maintain harmony in the earth environment.
Earth meaning terra firma, your feet on the ground and the oceans and the air above you.
This is a system, you live in a system that is, when people say natural, it's artificial.
Have you ever heard of stories, by the way, they say the moon is artificial.
Have you heard that?
Yes.
Okay, well guess what?
It's all artificial.
Why?
Because in order for something to be artificial as a product, it has to have an artificer, a creator.
Need I say more?
So all things are actually artificial.
If you subscribe that there is a creator or creative force, when I say creator, that is again singular, it's plural always.
So the aspect of morality, if you look it up etymologically, I haven't, but anyone should, what it means is, I don't know.
It's probably not the way we're using it.
We're not using it properly, but the concept of law and morality and ethic means to be in harmony with your environment.
If you were, we gave the example in recent history, if you were in submerged subsurface in a submarine, you wouldn't carry a loaded firearm with armor piercing rounds around.
Because if it went off even by accident, you would be endangering everyone on the submarine.
Where if you're on a surface ship, it may not be that critical.
So you happen to be on the planet called the earth, which is a byproduct of a previous earth, let's say, reformation.
Yes, this is in all of your ancient texts.
It doesn't say, in the beginning God created the heavens and the earth.
Sorry guys, anyone with half a brain and five minutes can discover that.
Now, the other part here is, these things, the prison systems, the homosexuality, all of a sudden, it has nothing to do with your personal desire or politics.
Because mankind has been given the time to abandon this reality and go on venture in whatever reality he chooses to with direction of the adversary, let's say,
is the result of where you are as a society on the planet right now, which leads you to being unrehabilitatable at this point.
What I mean by unrehabilitatable, let's say you have a four-door sedan, six-cylinder car.
And if you go 50 miles per hour, you need 100 feet to stop.
And it works all the time.
So what you do is you take a brick wall and you measure 100 feet, you draw a yellow line.
And as long as the driver accelerates to 50 miles per hour and hits the brakes before the yellow line, you will not hit the brick wall.
So if he hits the brakes five feet from the yellow line, the car will be five feet from the brick wall on the resulting end, opposite end of the yellow line.
If he hits the brakes exactly on the yellow line, the bumper will kiss the wall.
Right now, humanity is going 50 miles per hour, and they're one inch away from the wall, and they're all looking at each other saying,
we're going to make it better.
Are you kidding? Are you kidding?
Now, this is not one of these cases where, Greek, there is no wall.
No, there is a wall, just like we give the metaphor, we're in the credits part of the world.
You know, the world already ended and no one noticed.
You're in the credits part, in terms of the movie.
You know, a really bad movie ended, and you're in the credits part.
Now, when the credits are over, what happens?
The lights come on, and this screen that was projecting all these images that took your imagination away now gets pulled up,
and you have an ugly brick wall behind it.
And that is real, where all this time that you spent in front enjoying.
So, is this fear? Is this doom and gloom?
Absolutely not, because it's unrehabilitatable.
You know, man up, woman up, you know, fess up.
If anyone has the maturity to hear this, they have the maturity to rationalize it.
Difficult without the information, and that's what we're here to give.
Well, right, and it's much like I've always rationalized death.
People have been afraid of it. They're afraid of their own demise.
They're afraid of their life ending.
They say that it is their motivation for doing many different things, that,
I'm afraid I'm going to die, or this or that, or they make it a point of,
I'm not afraid to die, I'm going to take it with...
You know, here's the bottom line.
I say that there is no point investing in that, to be afraid of it, or to embrace it, or whatever else,
because one day, no matter what, occurs on planet Earth,
no matter what I do to my body or for it, guess what?
Eventually it will cease to function and death will come.
As it will, well, maybe we'll have some time to discuss what happens after the unrehabilitated mass
known as humanity is ended and rejuvenated.
Yeah, but notice I'm not even giving any regard for what happens after.
I'm simply stating that at some point...
Well, it's good to know what happens after.
But you see, that doesn't change the original fact.
Just like you're saying, you know, there's definitely going to be a wall there.
You're going to hit it. That's all there is to it.
There's no point of rehabilitation.
There's no action I'm going to be able to take to avoid dying in a conventional sense, right?
So why should I invest any of my energies into worrying about it one way or another,
either ratcheting up my strength for it, or turning around and being afraid of it
and constantly trying to avoid the inevitable?
I mean, what is the point?
Well, there is no point, because first of all, the concept of worrying is futile,
because for someone, a worry means that you're unaided and you're here alone completely,
both cosmically and physically, which is not true.
The other aspect about dying is that if anyone's worried about that,
it tells you about whether they know how to live.
And what I mean by that, the ancient Greeks had a saying,
and it was, those that are afraid of dying don't know how to live.
And the other thing is, one of the major dummy loads on society today,
which is catching on, is the concept of reincarnation, right?
That's like the multiple timeline thing.
That's a serious dummy load.
And it tells you a lot about the people who spout that out.
Now, you can't hold them guilty for it, because people want to be part of groups
and they latch onto ideas, but there is no reincarnation.
No one has been reincarnated except for a prototype to show that it can be done,
and that's for a way later discussion, meaning in years from now, the details of that.
But that's why we started off the show tonight saying that this is just ridiculous,
how dummy loaded, and this is probably the only two hours,
and I'm saying this humbly, that anyone will find once a week that is dummy load free.
And to address the thing about death, it's very simple.
It's just like sleep without dreaming.
That's all it is.
But it's good to have instruction what happens next,
because you will be conscious when you're brought back.
And it's very good to know a lot of people are going to be in quite shock what happens next.
And this whole thing about reincarnation, that you have to be hypnotized to remember,
you're being played with.
This stuff about astral travel out of body, all that stuff is rubbish.
No one's gone out of body.
You hear all this crap, astral travel, astral meditation.
It's garbage.
No one's gone out of their body.
What happens is you're assisted.
Someone to say that I travel astrally is so arrogant to say that they're doing these things on their own.
They're not doing anything on their own.
Astral traveling, I went here, I saw my body, I saw this,
it's no different than you go down to the store and you buy a drone with a camera on it,
and you fly over a building, and you're standing on the ground watching the whole thing.
You're being assisted.
You see, so these people that always say,
well, I did this, I did these gurus and shawamis and these morons,
and these people that are looking into these other forms of what they call meditation,
they don't even know what meditation is, by the way.
We can get into that one day.
They're so arrogant that they think they're doing this.
They're so arrogant that they're going to worry about something, like you're here alone.
There's an old joke of a man praying to win the lottery, and he hears a voice one day,
and he says, you know, we've heard all your prayers about winning the lottery,
but you've got to work with us.
Go out and buy a ticket.
Right.
And I'll tell you something.
If you want to try and buy a ticket into this conversation tonight, it is free.
However, at some point in the show, I will give you,
maybe if we have time, a story about how I think we should start charging for certain things.
But anyway.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, here's the thing.
Privately, I ask people, give me your contact information because this is like therapy.
I've got to know where to send the bill.
Right.
But anyway, this is, yeah, I mean, I'm so glad we're doing this
because there's got to be at least one or two people out there that are listening,
not just hearing the sounds, because words and names and just sounds that people react to, you know,
they may not like what they're hearing, but that's good, you know.
So either way, they've got to learn to rationalize things.
But, yeah, the thing about sexuality is very simple.
If we're going to objectify it, let's objectify it very quickly.
Let's use the agriculture word.
This is an agricultural-based economy, economy meaning rules of the house.
Eco meaning house and nomos meaning law.
Which isn't really conducive to the environment, though, you know, the way that agriculture is performed.
No, no, because you're in a rehabilitated state.
Yeah.
Well, the point here is everything is on agricultural cycles.
Let's say, for example, you're being dummy loaded.
How many times have you heard these financial gurus say, oh, there's going to be a dollar collapse in July, right,
what they call July?
How many times have you heard that or whatever?
It's like, you moron, don't you know that all economic cycles build up in the spring and break down in the fall?
All of your stock market crashes happen when?
September, October.
All breaking down events happen in the fall.
All building up events start in the springtime.
No major events in the winter.
So, I mean, this is the general rule, but agriculturally meaning this.
The purpose of farming is not only to farm and produce and harvest this year, but to continue next year.
Okay.
And the way you continue next year is by having a seed, a viable seed that can be planted and reproduce the crop.
Let's divert for a second.
There's someone that says, well, you know, I think I've got this health thing.
You know, I've said, well, this sounds like you've got some kind of parasite, you know, a worm or something in your gut.
Well, what do I do to kill it?
I'm like, no, no, no, you don't try to kill the worm in your gut because it will take a thousand times more poison than you.
What you do is you disturb its breeding cycle.
So you might want to take something that's good.
If you can identify what it is, it might have a breeding cycle of 30 days, right?
So that means that, you know, in 30 days it will die of old age and then a new set comes in.
So what you do is you take something that will disturb the breeding cycle so it can't lay eggs and can't reproduce.
So then in 30 days, you know, then it will have a dead lot in your body and it passes out.
That's how it's done.
OK, so the way you go after the on a planetary scale to demise a system is to not overtly wage war, but you covertly offend and disable their ability to reproduce.
For example, Monsanto, they have plants that don't bear seeds, right?
Or bear seeds that are not fertile.
Right.
I have to go back to Monsanto.
Let's say you use that as a very narrow.
And here's the thing.
I have nothing against Monsanto.
No, but the fact is that they utilize these terminator seeds, which are no good for replanting.
Which is they're not even doing any genetic engineering.
They've got people just crossbreeding non-food grade plants that look like food grade plants and they bring it in.
There's no science behind this woo-woo-woo magic and, you know, all that stuff.
They're doing stuff that's been going on for thousands of years.
They're just divine retribution on society.
But what I mean is let's say the rule was that it was taken for granted that all seeds now are worthless.
And you have to buy seeds that are from someone who offers worthless, meaning they won't take and sprout.
You have to buy ones that do separately, right?
Right.
Well, quite simply what happens is if you can't use your seeds from this year's plants and next year's plants, you're going to have to go buy some more seeds.
So bottom line is they have created a situation where you're a reliable customer and you have to keep going back to them so that you buy your seeds again to once again plant your crop and the cycle continues.
That's what you're describing.
Yeah.
And now let's say Monsanto decides to leave the planet and go back to the planet that they came from and they said no more seeds for you guys.
We only have the formula.
So you're done.
So what you'll do is if you've saved enough stock and then nothing will grow.
Okay, so with sexuality it's the same thing.
Could it be ethereally?
What I mean ethereally is there's a common denominator between all things living.
There's something called the sacred geometry.
If you look at the length of one's arm and the sections of bones you see from the shoulder to the elbow to the wrist, the length of the fingers and the joints, there's a relationship there that is a proportion of 1 to 1.6, 1 to 1.3, and 1 to 1.1.
And these ratios occur in everything in nature, right?
Just like you see all automobiles have similar things like steering wheel and seats and things like that, right?
So you see these in common.
So the assault on humanity is so gradual that it would – but anyway, let's go back to the ethereal.
I'm running away from – my thoughts are moving faster than my mouth here.
Okay, so let's go back.
Ethereally, the human body can be in a very base level akin to an upside-down plant where the brain is the root ball, the limbs are, well, the limbs, and the genitalia is the flower and the seed.
So if you're growing plants, you're looking for a flower and a seed.
Now, the crop is very important, but you need to also preserve the ability to have flowering and seeding for more crop next year and so on and so on, repeat the process.
So that's why you see in a lot of the occulted societies the phallic symbols, the gynic symbols, the hidden sexual meanings, the sex magic people talk about.
They don't even know – when someone tells you sex magic, they don't know what they're talking about.
Those are like people on the fringe that never got it.
But anyway, I'm not going to criticize because there's people starting to talk about that again.
It's just dummy loads.
All this stuff, the ancients had discovered from this point of rationale that the human body, the most important part of the human body is the genitalia because we can say we're important as we are, but without the flower and the seed continuing, we're done.
How long are we going to live?
30, 40, 50, 100 more years, and then we're all finished.
So we have to preserve the seed to go on, just like a farmer would guard the seed.
So that's the occult obsession about sexuality, and that's why you have the sexual symbolism.
And then you have a system of a carnal lack of maturity, immature, meaning undeveloped society that views these things in a way that are out of context.
So I hope we put it into context here that the seed, the human has a seed, right?
Right.
Okay, so that's the context of sexuality.
Let's say we were pure spirit and we were observing a material world with what we call man and woman in African-American form.
We would say that their seed has to be preserved no matter how bad it is for them now, right?
So from that level, if you have a covert war against humanity, you keep them distracted with missing airplanes and all these other things, right?
And you have an agenda that's been going on for over 1,000-plus years that is going to allow them to lose sight of how important the quote-unquote seed is, right?
And get them into habits and social groups and social norms that completely discount and make the concept of reproduction irrelevant.
You see where I'm going with this?
Oh, absolutely.
It's a whole lot more detailed explanation of what it is that I say that this is part of the agenda to hamstring essentially humanity for reproductive purposes.
It is to discourage one of our primary purposes, which is to continue to reproduce.
And why is it happening?
Well, that's a whole other story, but the fact is that it is happening.
It's the goddess religion dummy load is what it is.
But this is why we see the surgical mutilation of individuals to make sure that the seed and the flower are both disabled.
It can be done chemically.
Yeah, we do see that happening.
There is chemical sterilization and castration and spaying, if you will, of the human race essentially going on right before our eyes, even though a lot of people like to claim it's not happening.
Mass abortion.
Mass abortions to literally snuff out the seed before it is allowed to even begin to blossom and could ever create any more seeds.
Then you have, in addition to that, the prevalent psychology, which is then hoisted upon the general population to encourage the idea that none of this matters,
that gender is irrelevant, that your seeds are irrelevant, that this is not part of what it is to be a human being.
As a matter of fact, you yourself can decide what and who you are, et cetera, et cetera, on a daily basis.
You can snap your fingers and change your mind.
It's all external input, man.
People think that this is what I want.
They have no clue.
People say I make personal decisions.
Really?
Do you think you're competent to make a personal decision?
I don't think so.
The majority of people are so clueless about anything around them, I mean anything, that this thing that's being hoisted that this is my personal decision, how can it be when there's nothing in your head?
It's all external, man.
It's all external influence.
Again, going back to the metaphor, if you had a young child, let's say just born, let's give it six weeks, and it was immediately adopted by a family of gorillas that breastfed it and raised it to an adult.
If you brought that human child now that is, let's say, a man of 20 to your house, first human contact, do you think he's going to sit down and speak like he just graduated from Mr. Peabody's School of the Exceedingly Clever, or is he going to act like a gorilla?
Right.
He's going to act like a gorilla.
So when people say this is my personal choice, I've got to laugh.
You have no personal choices.
It's all whatever influences have been put on you, you see.
Even if you're private, it's the arrogance of humanity that when you're in a room alone by yourself, you think you're really alone.
Boy, talk about disconnection.
The empty template, though, still does have functionality regardless of the input received that is there.
There are muscles that if not used will atrophy.
There are organs which if not utilized will fail.
It's just that simple as if you are not in one way or another accessing these different points where the input could be given to you externally.
If you're not doing that, in fact, you die.
You die, or parts of you die.
I mean, that's just – am I crazy or what?
That's the material part of it, but yeah.
You see, then it goes back to the – there was Wilhelm Reich discussed – have you heard of Wilhelm Reich or the audience of – some might, some might not.
No, he was a protege of Freud, and he came to America and discussed things about psychiatry,
and he noticed that when people were on the psychiatric couch, he noticed that some of them when they would, let's say, divulge certain information,
that he felt he was making good psychiatric progress with,
he noticed they would go into a convulsion-type movement with their physical body that resembled an orgasm, an orgasmic state.
Right.
And when I say that word orgasm, he started developing and seeing what is the function of the orgasm.
Obviously, when you say that to your average human, now, oh, an orgasm, that's sex, it feels good.
It's not just about that.
It's not just about the expulsion of bodily fluids for procreation or having fun.
He found out that there is an actual mechanism that it serves in the biological being,
and he discussed it was a release of this life force, right?
So whenever there is a release or accumulation of this life force, there's this ecstasy or pleasure.
It should be pleasurable, right?
Right.
Just like, for example, if you were to have a meal that you really like, right?
Some people have actually had food that is of their desire prepared a certain way, and it's like sex in a way.
Well, they literally describe it as orgasmic.
In fact, a lot of people.
There you go.
Yeah, because it's a life.
What does the food do, right?
It charges you with life force.
So all of these things, you know, from a mature point of view, you can see that there are commonalities, common denominators.
So what's happened is a complete corruption of the comprehension of the purpose of the genitalia, let's say, right?
It's unspoken, by the way.
Everyone knows that, you know, man and a woman have to copulate to have a child in order to have the future of humanity.
Everyone knows that.
We don't have to discuss it, right?
Well, if you keep that aspect in context with everything else that's going on socially and politically,
no one's saying, wait a second, you know, this is getting – it's pretty overt what's going on.
And then the concept of sexuality, you know, like the red light district offering those services, right?
Let's say – or, you know, now it's on the Internet or whatever.
Those types, that genre, right?
Okay.
That is different.
That is the marketing of that, just like you have the marketing of ab exercise equipment or hair regrowth or penis enlargement, right?
Or, you know, all these things.
This is marketing.
It's gone into the market, right?
Just like religion.
It's in the market.
Look at these mega churches and mega mosques and stuff.
So it's all about business.
So you've got two aspects here.
You've got the part of the business aspect that people have been fully drawn into,
and then you've got them fully drawn into the covert spiritual assault on society.
Now, these spiritual beings don't do wars like they say, oh, the longest U.S. war has been in Afghanistan.
We're, you know, 12 years or whatever, 14, 15 years.
No, it's not – they don't work like that.
It's thousands of years.
And even there's a saying, they say, it's easier to fool 7 billion people than to fool one.
Because if you fool one, you've got the 6 billion, you know, 999 million and so forth to say, hey, you know, you've been fooled.
But if you develop a plan over multiple generations to have the whole world fooled,
if one person decides I'm not going to be fooled anymore, well, guess what?
He's the nutter, right?
Right.
So this is how these elements work.
And many people have heard this in the secret society circles too, you know,
we'll gradually breathe their consciousness into this direction, and then we won't have to worry about them, you know.
So, yeah, this is – what's great is I really – what gives me pleasure,
I really like that you and I are saying these things on air at the moment,
even though it's completely irrelevant at the moment because what we are discussing is way before its time.
I'm saying this humbly.
If anyone had any wisdom at all, they would take what we're saying and file it away,
file it away for later, and bring it out where it's more relevant.
Because right now this type of rationale and this type of imparting of information is irrelevant.
What do I mean by that?
If you want to make your life miserable, listen to Ocelli in the Greek
and go out and tell your friends or family about what you heard.
You're not going to make – they're going to think you're nuts.
So file it away, and this is – you know, so.
Exactly.
And I'll tell you what else.
If you want to participate in that thing which could easily make your life miserable
if you attempt to apply all of the information contained within,
if you wish to participate in it, we do have phones open, by the way, 218-339-8525.
Again, that is 218-339-8525.
We're actually going to be willing to take calls during this part of the show.
Well, actually, for the remainder of it, if you like, depending on what you guys have to say.
We have one rule.
Don't be a dummy load.
How about that?
Sorry, I had to say that.
I've got to go to the website and do the international symbol,
the circle with the red line through it and put dummy load, no dummy load.
Right.
I mean, that's the norm, though.
I mean, if you don't want a dummy load, I heard there's a base on the moon
or somewhere under the earth, an Antarctica.
But other than that, yeah, it's really bad.
It's really sad to see how the earth has been turned into a big junkyard.
Have you ever been through a junkyard like a scrapyard?
Sure.
Yeah, exactly.
This is what they've done.
If you can see through the facade, you might see pretty streets and pretty people and pretty things,
but if you really look at where it came from, where it's going and where it is,
it's just like a movie set.
And they're built like movie sets.
Look at how they're building their houses out of compressed sawdust.
But anyway.
Right.
Well, everything is temporary at this point,
because I think in the second hour we're going to get into what it will be like at the end
or after the end or as it ends or after the now, because it already has ended.
I call it the mop-up crew, I call it.
Oh, man.
Yeah, they're going to come and mop it up.
And who's they?
It's not who you think.
It's going to be interesting.
We could talk about very clearly what's not going to happen and what is going to happen
and, again, file it away, because from what I've been hearing on the dummy loading out there,
you know, yeah, this politician is bad.
They're putting chemicals in the water.
They're spraying the skies.
What else is the common complaint?
World War III, that's my favorite.
Oh, World War III.
Yeah, sure.
Pole shift.
Oh, yeah, they need a pole shift, all right.
But, anyway.
See, and I thought we were going to get away from the sexuality discussion.
Yeah, yeah.
So the whole thing, they don't even know, they can't even define what a pole is.
And, by the way, the Earth doesn't even have poles the way they're described.
Remember the hydrofluorocarbons, the hairspray supposedly putting a hole in the ozone layer?
How does it get from that bouffant hair?
How does it get from the bouffant hairdo in a bathroom in Bayside, Queens,
all the way up to the ozone layer in Antarctica?
Well, what cracked me up about that, I told you that story, right,
what cracks me up about the tetrafluorocarbons?
Tetrafluorocarbons, yeah.
Right, fancy name for, you know, basically what comes out of an aerosol can
and what you have in your air conditioning unit.
But, anyway, back to it.
The thing was, I discovered they were screaming in the 90s that, you know,
we have a hole in the ozone layer, we have a hole in the ozone layer.
So, actually in the 80s, the late 80s.
And then in the very, like, 1990, I think it was, I was still in high school.
And we had this new kind of science which was being taught,
which was like global science or something like this.
I can't remember the exact name because I used to fall asleep during that class quite a bit.
And they started teaching us about these holes in the ozone layer
that are being made by, you know, the spray cans.
And I said, I thought it was quite laughable.
And I was told, prove it, and I won't have to worry about the class the rest of the year.
So I said, okay, fine.
And I went and found various accounts and official records
regarding holes in the ozone layer before any of these chemicals, well, were anywhere.
You know, it's all got to do, you know.
Global warming, you know, in the 70s, here's another thing.
Do you remember cars from the 70s?
Oh, yeah, but correlation is not causation is all I'm telling you.
Oh, no, it's dummy load.
It's the ultimate dummy load.
But do you remember the cars in the 70s real quick,
the speedometer had at the 55 was in red?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
They did that because they wanted you to use less fuel.
Engines were most efficient with the gearing at that speed
because there was a coming ice age by the 1990s.
Oh, right.
That's why they did that little thing on the speedometer you see in some older cars.
And, yeah.
Now, there is going to be global warming.
They're just not telling you which globe.
Serious global warming, folks.
I mean, where you walk outside your door and you could cook a chicken in three hours,
and it's going to be real harsh, and, yeah.
So, anyway, that's one of the kill shots that's going to come to the earth,
and these morons are not going to be able to figure it out,
and they're not going to tell you.
It's not a solar flare.
It's got nothing.
You have a lot of this stupidity now.
Oh, solar flares and this and that and CME effects and all that.
Yeah, yeah, they come.
The real big one was in the 19th century that took out all the telegraphs.
Yes, it took out all the telegraphs, and this is not even being discussed anymore,
and you haven't had a big one since then.
You'll get some CMEs, but it's not going to be what we might discuss later.
We're talking about an ambient temperature that will cook everything outside for a couple of weeks.
Well-deserved, of course.
But, anyway, yeah.
So to go back to the sexuality thing,
this is something that as long as we keep doing the show, we'll keep coming up,
and we can keep filling in and enhancing the concept rationally.
And what I mean rationally is, you know, mathematics, you know,
usually in popular culture, yes, I just learned enough, you know,
I'm not going to use that or, you know, it's a nerdy thing,
but the purpose of mathematics is to rationalize thought,
and that's what we're trying to do.
And just like mathematics is rational, like what I mean by that is,
let's say you walk into a shop and you say, I need some eggs,
and the storekeeper says, okay, well, I need some eggs.
Well, how many eggs do you need, right?
There's your math, right?
Because some eggs could be two or three or five dozen or a dozen.
Normally people buy a dozen, you know.
I mean, so we use math and numbers to rationally communicate, right?
You know, I have to travel, you know, how far?
Well, 100 miles.
Oh, great.
Okay.
Or one mile.
Wow, that's a totally different type of travel, right?
So numbers are really good for rationalizing thought,
and they're chock full of information.
Even though they're simple numbers, right, one to a billion or whatever,
it's just as easy to say 10 as it is to say 100 billion, you know.
And right away you give a lot of information that the mind can then reach out
with its imagination and know other things, right?
Like if I were to say, Chuck, we're going to walk a mile, you know,
I just need some comfortable shoes.
I said, Chuck, we're going to walk 30 miles.
Well, okay, now we just, you know, we've got more than comfortable shoes.
You might need a change of socks, a walking stick, food, and water.
Well, very simple.
If I told you that I punched out a 20-year-old man, you'd think to yourself, okay, fine.
Then I tell you I punched out an 80-year-old man,
you've got a completely different picture in your mind based on the fact that I've applied a number to his age.
It tells you a lot.
Yeah, but actually I know an 80-year-old that would, yeah,
that would rip your arm off and stuff it down your throat after you tried punching him.
But anyway.
Most likely, but still.
Generally speaking, if I told you that, you would think.
I know, exactly, yeah.
And he still has the same waist size as he did when he was in high school.
But anyway, my point here is when we discuss these things, we try to say a lot with a little.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
Ocelli and the Greek, second hour.
And one thing I can assure you of, and you won't find me making too many promises on this show,
but I promise you this, you will not have the distinctive feeling that a wallaby decided to vomit in your ear hole.
Anyway, moving forward, we are live on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
where we are listener supported.
So let's keep that in mind.
Folks, you can go to the chat room, by the way, instead of sending Skype messages to us while we're on air,
if you like, and you can discuss these things amongst yourselves,
or join us at 218-339-8525 if you wish, and become involved in this discussion if you dare.
Now, we discussed sexuality in an objective sense.
We objectified sexuality. Ha ha.
We turned around and looked at what the reality is relating to that,
and started to touch upon end times.
As we're winding down, we're in the credit sequence of the movie, as you like to say, sir.
And, you know, I think that might be hard for some to understand.
Hmm. How can we better...
Well, first of all, I don't think South Park's going to do an episode on it.
But anyway...
You never know. You never know. You know, you've got to watch that,
because sometimes there's these weird sort of things in there.
I haven't watched it in 15 years, and I hear they're still around, so...
Yes, they are. Yes, they are.
But the Simpsons are the longest-lasting television show in history, so what does that tell you?
Now, here's the thing. Listen, just to harp on alternative media, all of it, not some of it,
do you know why South Park probably hasn't done a show about alternative media?
Because it already is South Park.
Nice. Well, you know, and people like to point to that 9-11 episode,
where they did that some years ago, which, you know, the ultimate conclusion was,
well, unless you believe that it was a bunch of Arabs who knocked down the buildings with box cutters,
you're retarded. And that's their word, of course.
I don't mind using the word retarded, by the way, because when I think about what the word actually means,
I don't see it as offensive, but anyway...
Yeah, look, you work with epoxies, they have something called a retarder to slow it down,
so it just means to slow something down.
Right, that which retards something.
Yeah, that which retards something.
You know, something that is flame retardant is, you know, something that slows down
or is resistant to the flame spreading. Hello? Anyway.
The arrogance and disconnect of humanity at this point is the problem.
See, the information is not going to help, you know, and the awake...
I think we've harped enough on the being awake.
Please, please don't wake up. That's very dangerous.
You know, you want them called down. I mean, not killed or called, but you want a relaxing...
What was it, Soma? They used to spray Soma? What was that stuff? Brave New World.
Soma, yes.
Yeah, yeah, when you get agitated, yeah, it just relaxes you, you know.
Yeah, the population needs to stay relaxed.
The last thing you want is billions of uninformed people being activated.
I mean, even in the film called The Matrix, they had them plugged in for their energy.
That's exactly what's going on.
And look at the trouble that was created when Neo got loose, right?
Well, that's the other thing, yeah.
You've got to make sure that, you know, some people are simply not ready to be removed from The Matrix.
There's a reason for that.
Yeah, most are not, which is fine, and it's going to be that way all the way until the car hits the brick wall,
which is just a few inches away, going at 50 miles an hour.
Now, this is not doom and gloom, because the doom and gloom only comes in when you don't know how to live.
If you know how to live, you understand things, and it's just like jumping into cold water.
It's just cold for the first few moments.
And then they say, come on in, the water's fine, right?
But essentially, everything already ended, because you're in the credits part.
The age already ended.
It ended about 17-plus years ago, roughly, let's just say.
And what you're in, the final wrap-up now.
And when something is going to be wrapped up, it's the final opportunity to put in or take in,
to add or take away, let's say, things that are necessary before the movie is over completely,
or the episode is over, or the event is over, because if anything were to carry over to the next event,
you don't want any bitching and whining, right?
So, for example, if society ends in a big, horrible crash, like all these morons are saying,
then later on, someone might say, hey, we never had a chance to have a perfect society where we have, let's say,
well, let's not say perfect, but let's say, you know, liberty, meaning if you have commitments,
you are given time freely away from those commitments, and you come back to them,
so you don't feel overburdened, where you have peace and no war.
A pleasant world.
Abundance.
You know, and the thing about this environmental stuff, it's just idiots.
Anyone who hasn't done any history check-ups, talk about the end of the world.
A little bit over a thousand years ago, about 85% of the world's population was wiped off
within less than a century due to natural disaster.
And these natural disasters were ongoing every day of the week, every month, every year for about a century.
So people now are crying about this, that, you know, and oh, yeah, yeah, the environment.
They have no clue.
You can do a little bit of research on the Dark Ages and the Middle Ages,
and our friends at Google, for some reason, don't like to give this information.
Isn't that interesting?
But anyway, go read some of the writings from the, you know, from the years, let's say, 600 to 1200.
They call them the Dark Ages, okay?
It was visibly dark as well.
But I think it was over 90% of the European population died from starvation because there was no, it was just, yeah,
it was just very bad conditions.
So all this stuff now you hear about, oh, environmentally, yeah, no, natural disasters.
This is the closest you're going to get to the Garden of Eden, not until the next few years.
It's going to get better, no matter how much they're spraying or what you think is toxification.
People, again, are so arrogant that how many times have we said that they think everything was created 150 years ago, right?
So there's a flood here and a bad rainstorm.
Oh, the world's going to end.
It's geoengineering or it's bad climate change.
They have no clue of their history.
Why?
Because they're idiots.
And these are the ones propagating this, right?
And they make a living doing this.
And people send them money, what they call money, and support these morons, right?
And they keep doing this.
And they're in prominence.
And here's the thing.
Earlier, like we discussed, the sexuality, what's really done the biggest distraction in the dummy load is the commercializing of sexuality, let's say, right?
Across the board, whether it's physical or electronic or whatever, has trivialized it to the point where people have forgotten that it's about the progression or next year's crop, let's say, or next generation.
They've removed themselves from that.
Or they say, my sexual preference is my personal choice.
Really?
If you were raised by gorillas, you would be acting exactly like a gorilla.
Everything you think and believe is externally planted in you.
That's why you hear some of these people say, oh, yeah, you have to go into yourself.
You change yourself to change around you.
There's nothing in you, and there's nothing you're going to change by doing that, period.
It just doesn't work.
And why do we say that or I say that in such a stern fashion?
Sorry, guys.
It's true.
I'm sorry.
I'll have to throw in the apology for the harshness.
Well, you know what occurs to me right here is that if there were a massive, and I do mean a massive shift in this understanding, if there was a majority or even a significant number of the population that chose to conduct themselves differently, wouldn't this actually change things?
No, because if they did it properly, they would set themselves apart.
It's about setting yourself apart from it.
If everyone decided to go skinny dipping in the sewer and drink the water, would you do it because everyone is doing it or would you set yourself apart?
And if you were forced into it, you'd say, well, let me put on a hazmat suit with breathing tanks.
You see, because over a certain amount of generations, you can tell people that's a good thing to do, and you could actually breed their desire to do so.
And it would be appalling if you figured out that this is not the way it should be.
Already done, in my estimation, but good.
Yeah.
So what I mean by setting yourself apart, learn what's fit and proper.
Like, for example, if you got a job at a pet food store, they might say to you, guess what?
This label, the can on here says fish food.
Guess what?
That goes to the fish.
The dog food goes to the dogs.
The bird food goes to the birds.
Well, now, you might want to do it your way, because those rules don't matter here anymore.
The boss is gone.
I'm going to give the bird food to the fish, the dog food to the bird, and whatever, right?
And the dog will eat it, and the birds will eat it.
And see, there's nothing wrong.
The dog is eating the fish food.
The fish is eating the bird food.
And so, see, they're alive.
They're OK.
But it's not fit and proper.
It's not fit and proper.
And what is fit and proper comes from your God.
Now, let's not use that word, or your deity.
Oh, well, you know, OK, well.
So this information to an unrehabilitated...
That's why people are unrehabilitated.
They're too arrogant.
See, it's not the lack of information.
Never sympathize or empathize...
I'm sorry.
The only empathy or sympathy someone should have is if they have a lack of information.
But once you realize that it's their stern arrogance, stubbornness, and rebelliousness,
then I don't see any reason for empathy or sympathy towards people that are like that.
How many times have you heard someone say,
Well, you know, I found out, you know, this is really interesting.
You know, those things are not really contrails because, you know,
when you have a steam kettle in your... a tea kettle in your house,
you notice a steam come out.
It doesn't last for like six hours and turn into this big massive cloud that blots out the sun.
You know, they're like, Oh, wow, you know, I never noticed that.
You know, okay, that's interesting.
Well, do you want to know what there is or something?
Okay, cool.
That's all right.
That's someone you could work with.
But some people say, Well, you know, I haven't heard of that.
You know what?
I don't know about that, you know, and I don't want to know about it, and I don't care.
Right.
Whoa.
Okay.
That's what I mean by the stubborn, rebellious, arrogant.
So that is about two-thirds of the population right now in wholesale.
You might want to do some cherry picking, nitpicking, fine picking, and say about half.
Reduce it from two-thirds.
If only a handful of people out of the seven billion were like that, you're still unrehabilitatable spiritually.
Sorry.
And they've really just gravitated toward a selective area of ignorance.
You know, they've gathered an understanding from one particular source.
They've latched onto it, and that's it.
There is no flexibility in their intellect at all.
It's because of the external also.
You know, it's a spiritual.
It's a mind problem, or you want to call it a mind virus, a dummy load that's hooked up to the system.
It comes from parents, society, right?
It could actually come to when the person is alone in their state that they're injected with this, right?
Cosmically, right?
That's why we talk about the cosmic censorship.
But what people don't understand that what's been written for thousands of years,
it's all of this stuff is an all-or-nothing concept.
So if you want to turn a group of people into the positive, they have to separate themselves.
Don't try to change those that are too far gone.
You find those that are willing to change to be better, and you have to actually physically separate yourself as well.
That's why, for example, there's a folklore and mythology about the founding fathers of America
wanted to do that from the European masters, let's say, right?
And they had to do that physically.
They would not have succeeded if they tried to do it in England, right?
So they did it here from a physical distance.
So that's one aspect.
The other aspect, there's an all-or-nothing in the spiritual realm.
So let's say it's easy to fix any problem.
People say, well, how do we fix this?
How many times do you hear this on the Internet?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Or how do we fix this?
It's like, dude, what kind of question is that?
Anyone who asks that, you really have to find out, are they saying that because they really don't know and they would like to know?
Or are they in the variety that if they were shown the information, they would say, oh, I don't believe in that.
I don't want it.
I don't want to know, and I don't care.
They would probably be in the second.
Yeah, now, see, I say a lot of times that I don't know how to repair certain things because it doesn't make sense to me.
I would like to understand these things when I say that.
I would like someone to say, look, if you do X, Y, Z, it'll go away.
I would love to hear that, you know, provided that it's not something, you know, well, listen, if you amass a million people and then you don't give me something that's, you know, unattainable.
If you can give me a, you know, a basic sort of if you do this and you do this.
But this comment that I just made is expressly directed to those pontificating on the Internet to be those to go to for information on how to make things better.
This is not to the average.
So, Chuck, if you didn't know how to fix something and you want to know, that's fine as, let's say, a layperson.
But let's say you say I'm a TV repairman.
I don't know how to fix TVs and I don't want to know either.
I mean, now you're, well, now you're, you know, require the least amount of sympathy and empathy possible, right?
Right.
Because that's your job.
Yeah, you're going broke because you don't know how to do your job.
I don't feel bad for you.
And you don't want to know how to do your job either.
So this is, you know, these people are out there and they're selling books and movies and DVDs and they have places to subscribe.
The financial idiots are the big all of these financial gurus.
You know, they have all these newsletters and telling me not one of them, not one ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever says this is a credit based economy and it's unlawful.
Not none of them.
So what they're doing is they're taking, they're riding the sewer, this tide, this stinky stuff all the way down until they can't do it anymore.
Now, even though they're ignorant about what they're saying, they don't want to know anymore because they're quite happy doing what they're doing.
That's why I go back to say the society is on rehabilitatable.
Right.
It's kind of like right now.
What is going all everything that's being put out there right now at the moment at the moment, not in the near future.
It's going to change.
Everyone is basically setting up and saying, look, in case of a fire, grab that fire extinguisher.
And, you know, it's loaded with gasoline.
You know, we took all the fire retardant out.
It's full of gasoline.
Just spray it on.
It's a liquid.
It should be work the same.
You know, this is what's going on.
And very few people can see it.
And it's not you don't have to be a graduate of Mr. Peabody School of the exceedingly clever.
Anyone with a pulse and breathing should be able to rationalize this.
Unless you've been raised by the gorillas, of course.
But but the point here to go back to tie this in with sexuality in the end, you know, because, you know, the thing there's one thing to bring up these topics and to give details.
People will sometimes walk away.
You know, what was that old was that old thing?
They call it telephone or something.
It was a child in a classroom.
They told him a story.
They told him to whisper it to someone behind.
By the time it got to like five or ten people changed completely.
Right.
There's a there's a psychological concept to that, you know, a spiritual concept.
By the way, the word means the same thing.
But so the thing about discussing the end, it's not necessarily, oh, woe is us.
You know, we're going to get this.
No, this these this will happen.
No, no doubt about it.
And the reason why it's going to happen is the same reason they break.
When a horse breaks its legs severely, not all horses that break legs are shot, put down.
But, you know, you're going to be put down like an animal as a society.
You're going to be put down because the level of suffering, suffering means to take on pain willingly.
Right.
That you're going to take on.
If it continues, there'll be no life left on Earth.
And this is the interesting part.
But right now, I assure you, all these people talking about prophecies out of the Bible are wrong.
Very easy.
How do we know that these people that go on alternative media and mainstream and talk about biblical prophecies are wrong?
Ask the morons what day it is today.
And guess what they're going to tell you.
Something from January, December, Monday through Friday.
And there's none of that in these ancient texts, whether it's the Koran, the Bible, the Rig Vedas or anything.
So that's your first sign to tell that you're listening to.
Basically, someone who would have done much better by saving their breath to cool their porridge, as the English say, instead of pontificating.
But, of course, they've got the membership section.
Right.
They've got to fill up the donations and the member in the newsletters.
Yeah.
OK.
Or it's the Nazis that are going to get us still or whatever.
It's just idiocy out there, you know.
So the level of discussing what is going to happen in the end at this time, is it way too soon?
Oh, absolutely.
But there might be one person out there that might want to reference this.
And what's going to happen, like we said earlier, just to bring it back 15, 20 minutes, is when the film ends or when an event ends and the players are going to carry over to the next level, there's going to be a lot of second guessing.
Like, what if this?
We never got a chance to have a perfect society.
Right.
And that's why I got into the environmental leading, all the way to ranting on these morons on the Internet talking about what's supposed to happen and how to protect themselves when none of it works.
So the whole thing is you're going to have to be left without an excuse.
So later on, if someone, when everything is brought back, if someone says, well, we never had a chance to have a perfect society with liberty from the things we've committed to and freedoms and a great environment and no war.
So you're going to have all of that.
So later on, no one will be without an excuse.
So when you start hearing of the entire grid going down and everyone resulting to zombieism and cannibalism and ridiculous stuff like that, right, and like a Mad Max world and all this stuff, how are you going to have that if you still have a perfect, a taste of a perfect society to come for a short time in the mid-2020s?
How can that happen?
So it's all rubbish what you hear out there.
It's just astounding how the arrogance and the stupidity of mankind at this point, and I'm not talking about the layman.
I'm talking about the people speaking publicly, whether it's mainstream and print on alternative media, on their radio shows and all this.
The arrogance and the stupidity is just astounding.
So once you understand that if this is going to be done by a cosmic force and you pretty much – they work on a very high level of efficiency and they don't engage in futile tasks.
And by the way, it's always the good guys that are going to do this.
It's not the Luciferians or the Satan that's going to – or the dark forces that are going to destroy mankind.
It's the light forces, the positive, the good forces that are going to destroy mankind's society.
Because right now 100% of everything man is doing is – he's completely been subsumed into the dark side.
So anyway, there is no way that this quote-unquote end time scenario will ring through unless mankind has his way in every way, meaning in a positive way.
And that has still not come. That is your easiest way.
So the two ways to weed out the frauds is if anyone's giving any kind of event that's coming in the future, ask them what day it is.
If they tell you anything from January through December, Monday through Friday, forget it.
I mean we're talking Muppet City there.
The second thing is if they're talking about disasters that are coming now or soon and this is all disaster and rebuilding from that point on, Muppet City again.
You know, grazed by gorillas, forget it.
Now there's lots of people talking about this from religious circles, economic circles, geopolitical circles, forget it.
If you're within the sound of the sonic entity known as Achilles in the Greek, you're going to hear this other crap everywhere.
And it's going to pick up a little bit and none of it's going to come true.
It's very simple because you're going to have basically paradise on earth for a short time.
It means no war either for a short time.
And this is around the corner and not much less than about a decade roughly would say.
But it doesn't just happen with a snap of a finger.
It builds up to it and then it lasts for a short time.
And when this time comes, the high command on the planet and the world leaders will tell you this is how it's going to be from now on for the next thousand years and everyone is going to believe it.
What is there not to believe?
It will not be a propagandized perfect society like in the Soviet Union when they told you it was a perfect society and you look out your window and there's 3,000 people standing in two feet of snow and subfreezing temperatures to get toilet paper.
That's not going to be like that.
It will be the real deal for a short time.
And then glitches will come in the system and people will be asked very unreasonable things to do to bring it back and they will do it and that's the time to head for the hills.
And that's all I'm going to say about that.
It's time to come because then the rest of it gets into a lot of details.
But the thing is we spoke once about living an efficient life.
You know how much inefficiency has been put into people's lives by listening to the cartoon network idiocy on the internet about prepping and World War III and financial calamities.
Do you think anyone listening to this has lost an hour's of sleep?
Oh, I'm sure.
Yeah, you see.
So why?
Why, guys?
It's about efficiency, man.
The gods are efficient.
They don't waste.
I was working once at a construction site when I was very young and a guy was talking about efficiency and I said, well, why be efficient?
Like a stupid question.
He said, because if you're not efficient, God takes it away.
OK, and I'm using that term loosely, colloquially, even though there is no such thing as God in a singular form.
You know, right.
This is just the way they print it out.
You know, it's just it's the dummy load again.
But it's about efficiency.
And it's the way to be understood among those who have been heavily inundated with the repeated dummy loads.
You have to speak to them to get your point across, you know, because, look, if I give you the secrets of the universe in a language that you don't understand.
What have I done but barked at the moon, you know?
So, yeah, that's another point.
You know, there is no mystery.
There's a lot of secrets because to say there's a mystery, a mystery means no one knows it.
And that's like, you know, I want to kick God in the nuts, you know, like he doesn't even know it.
Right. Like patents or another thing like that.
So there's secrets like patents, you know, patents are like, oh, yeah, I came up with this idea.
Really? Really? I want to kick God in the nuts.
So I'm going to go get a patent.
I'd like to see that patent.
But that's what anyone who, by the way, anyone who goes and wants a patent is doing that when they say it's my idea.
Really? Uh-huh.
Let me see.
If you were raised by gorillas, what kind of ideas would you have?
It's all external, man.
Right.
And these morons are still going around talking about astral travel and all this stuff.
It's unbelievable.
So anyway.
And moron, by the way, just means childish and unknowing and unmisinformed and immature.
You know, it's a proper term, by the way.
And actually has a specific level of what they call IQ that's ascribed to it as well.
So I do believe the level there to, you know, extricate oneself from the moron grade is like 80, something like that, I think.
If you're below 80, I think you qualify as a moron quite scientifically.
Yeah.
Below 79 is weapons grade moron.
Oh, okay.
I was not aware of that.
But thank you.
But anyway.
But anyway, I don't like the whole concept of IQ because who is one person to say, you know, again, if we look at the ancient texts, everyone has the same intelligence.
It's the level of discernment and wisdom that rates differently.
Right.
Very strange.
Yeah.
Again, because it's all external input.
It's just like we go to a computer factory.
You see, what do they call the cases?
Then they put the motherboard.
Then there's the CPUs and the chips on the motherboard.
It's all external, man.
You know, it's the computer.
There's, you know, there's stuff in the computer, yes, but it's all fit from an external source into it.
And if you have a factory that makes a million computers a day and they all have 500 gigs hard drive and five gigs of RAM, which one is smarter than the other?
They're all the same.
It's the ones that get plugged in first and get an operating system first and programs and files first are the ones that perform.
Right.
If you plug in a computer with no operating system, it's just a space heater essentially.
That's true.
I'll tell you something.
Most people are still space heaters.
That's okay.
Most people are still just producing their carbon footprint or whatever.
That's really all their entire purpose is.
So even if you're one of them, you could donate to us.
It will make you feel better.
It's okay.
And if you're not one of them, it would behoove you to donate because this is information that you're not going to get anywhere else.
And I mean anywhere else, at least sonically at this point, all in one basket.
Let's just have a private conversation on air.
Chuck, how do you feel that you and I come on here once a week and we give out about a half a million bucks worth of information every week?
I mean for free.
Is it something we could, I don't know.
Oh, boy.
Well, it seems like this is something that is of value, right?
And at the moment, the most relatable, discernible kind of value is that which we call these little debt certificates that get circulated, these canceled checks.
Exactly.
There's no debt in them.
Yeah, they're just canceled checks.
Yeah.
Private credit.
Well, but there you go, that those canceled checks in reality shouldn't have any value, but people still utilize them for it, and therefore.
The value of it is that it's no different than when you leave the store with a gallon of milk and they say prove that you bought the gallon of milk.
You pull out a receipt.
It's just a receipt that someone has given up their body into the system.
Here, let me just throw a little diversion.
We're talking about the end, but if you want to know who's not going to be in American political office is anyone who speaks about anti-immigration and quote-unquote illegals.
The reason why they're not doing anything about quote-unquote illegals and they want them, them, parentheses, air quotes, is because every time you sign a piece of paper and get a Social Security card,
they create an exemption with $650,000, which you don't get any of.
They print notes on that and they use that.
So on one side, they don't want to come out and tell the people, well, you know, we want as many people as possible coming into the country because we just want their signature.
That's where the money's created.
If anyone tells you money's created a thin air, they're a moron.
It's not.
They're marketing your signature because your signature is the substance.
There is substance behind the money.
It's just ink.
It's, anyway.
At the end of the day, though, that's not very much substance.
No, but there is.
I mean, actually, you know, you could look at it under a microscope and that ink, depending on the magnification, is pretty tall, you know.
So anyway, if you want to know who's going to succeed or not politically is watch what they say about quote-unquote illegals coming into the country.
If someone is really, they're not going to be, the banksters will not allow that kind of policy, you see.
And most people, there's all these idiots that call themselves conservatives or patriots or whatever.
They have no, they don't want, and why do I say we use strong language?
Because when you have a high level of misdemeanor, bad behavior, it requires high level of harsh language, right?
And high criminality requires even harsher language.
So that's why I use these terms like idiot and moron and fraudster and all this stuff because the level, the cup is overfilled.
What they're doing in the malevolent sense is not only fill the cup, it's overflowed.
It's off the table and it's making a mess on the floor and I don't want to step in it.
They could fill their cups with the crap that they talk about on internet radio and whatever, all they want.
But when it starts to overflow and I start hearing emails and Skypes, what do you think of this?
I'm like, what are you talking about? This is absolutely ridiculous, you see.
So now their cups are overflowing, off the table, on the floor, and I can't walk across the internet without stepping on their garbage.
And these are the same people that have newsletters and signups and listen to me and write to me and send me money.
And if you go to them and say, hey, listen, how about this?
Oh, I don't want to know this and I don't know it and I don't care.
These are the people that most of the people in alternative media are looking at.
So, jeez louise, you know, we've got two hours to basically shotgun the whole world in this show, I guess, is what we're doing.
And it's well deserved, I think, you know, at this point.
And this ties into the end again.
It's all about how are you going to take up the next less than two decades, roughly 17 years, people's minds away from what is really going on.
Keep them disinformed and misinformed and that's all that's going on.
And when I say that, you know, I'm not addressing the mainstream.
Forget it. That's too far gone.
I'm talking about the alternative media right now.
And, you know, what people call alternative sources of information.
It's just taking up your time.
And you know what?
There's really nothing much else to do.
Take up your time.
Enjoy yourself.
Be efficient.
There you go.
If you're happy, you know, being petrified and hiding under your bed and trying to store as much ammunition as possible, you know, go right ahead.
Do that, I guess, if that's what, you know, makes you happy.
Or beans and rice.
Beans and rice.
Yeah.
Let's not forget beans and rice.
And make sure you have enough.
Oh, dear Lord, what is it?
Iodine.
Because the radiation is going to get you.
And if you swallow enough of our iodine pills, et cetera, et cetera.
You know, and hey, while you're at it, here's a little bit of natural Viagra and, you know, crunchy caffeine or whatever the hell else they're selling now.
But, you know, look, if you're not interested in enriching somebody else's pocket, if you're interested in listening to something different,
then I suggest you support American Freedom Radio and Ocelli and the Greek, which, by the way, we have the website at ocellianthegreek.com.
Yeah, it's just that simple.
Ocelli, by the way, if you can't spell it, O-C-H-E-L-L-I.
And then the rest of it is and the Greek actually spelled out.
And if you don't know how to spell that, once again, I'm not sure how you tuned into this particular station.
And please thank the nurse that handled it for you.
Now, it is interesting because all these things somebody might be saying to themselves, how does this tie into the end times as it were?
Well, it's very simple.
This stuff is actually happening right on time.
It's occurring exactly as it's supposed to, believe it or not.
This all actually, this mad, mad world makes a lot of sense, doesn't it?
It does.
I'm glad that you said it that way because it ties in perfectly to what I said about just take up your time.
It's just let the time pass and be efficient with your time.
Don't worry at all whatsoever.
The information about how it's going to come to an end and what to expect next is there as well.
And we can discuss that in any level.
But the whole subject matter, again, is whenever you get into it, there's like a mental shockwave that one suffers because how do you broach the subject in contrast to what's been said about it, right?
You have the boy who cried wolf so much.
I mean, we were supposed to all be in FEMA camps about ten years ago.
And we were supposed to be hit by comets already two years ago.
And there were financial collapses and all this.
So, I mean, it's a very difficult subject.
By now, the dollar should have collapsed.
And asteroids should have destroyed at the very least the eastern seaboard, if not the rest of the entire what they call the United States.
We should have seen multiple earthquakes.
The Earth should have actually split open.
And we should be confronted with those who live at the core of the Earth attacking us from all ends.
I mean, ant people.
And you've got to throw in the reptilians and the greys somewhere and the Pleiadians.
Oh, boy.
Well, you know, and we should have been invaded by the true alien invasion, not the one that they were blue beaming us with.
And, of course, oil should have all dried up.
What else?
Let me think.
Oh, radiation should have run out.
Viruses.
Viruses and radiation.
People don't know.
Before the 1950s, up until 1950s, places like Alamogordo, Los Alamos and other places,
when the technicians that were building nuclear arms and supplying nuclear reactors with rods,
they were walking around with five-inch disks of uranium in their pockets and all kinds of things like that.
They just knew that you didn't want to put too many of them together because it went Cherenkov blue and it went critical.
And when it goes critical, it gets hotter than those electrical stove elements is what they used to encase it in.
And then what happened was the banks all of a sudden and General Electric told all the engineers,
well, from now on, it's toxic.
You can't touch it.
You've got to stay away.
It's got to be behind lead, all this stuff.
And they're like, why?
And they're like, well, because that's what we want.
And it turned out they wanted that because they were producing so much of it and it was so expensive,
they didn't want anyone running off with it.
They didn't want people breaking in to steal it.
So what a better way to protect the inventory than to tell people it's harmful.
And it is harmful if it goes critical.
But this is – I mean, now we sound like we're crazy by saying this, right?
But anyone wants to do a very efficient two-hour investment of their time,
yes, go to that wonderful bastion of entertainment and information called YouTube
and put in nuclear scare scam, just like it sounds, nuclear scare scam.
And you hear the testimony of a man named Galen Windsor.
And I personally have run into several nuclear quote-unquote engineers
and knew someone who was probably the premier uranium mining industrialist in the country.
I have his phone on my cell phone, actually.
His nickname was the Uranium King, confirmed everything there.
But we're all going to die from Fukushima.
So ridiculous.
And then there's the viruses which are produced in the liver.
I don't know how you catch it if it can only be produced in the liver.
And this goes from the cab drivers, meaning the paramedics,
all the way up to the high levels of the castles and glossy towers of the medical community.
Everyone's convinced that it's viruses now.
So, yeah, yeah.
So have we covered a good amount of stuff that people are panicking and losing efficiency in their lives for?
I think so. I think so.
Did we get to all of it?
Well, let's see.
I guess we missed the giant takeovers, the New World Order and all that.
I guess we didn't include them in the discussion, did we?
How about New World Odor?
Because if you ever go – I remember they cleaned up Jersey the last time I came to the East Coast.
It used to have a pretty strong smell, Jersey City, Hoboken, that area.
Just part of the turnpike now.
Come on, just part of the turnpike stinks like that.
Not the whole state.
Stinkin' Lincoln.
You know, in Maine, up in Maine where they have the paper pulp factories,
I remember back in the 80s used to – Lincoln, Maine, where they used to make all the paper.
There's a lot of sulfur. It's called Stinkin' Lincoln.
That's been cleaned up too.
So I don't know what kind of odors, New World odors, we're going to get next.
Well, nothing smells worse than a place that renders fat, animal fat, dear God.
I use that metaphor as well as the car going to the brick wall.
You know, they say the horse is out of the barn.
I said, well, that horse is out of the barn, broke its leg, they shot it, and it's in the glue factory.
You're not getting it back, so move on.
You know, that term, horse is out of the barn, let's go get it.
You know, the people think politically, scientifically, religiously, they're going to fix anything.
Oh, boy.
It's time to ride something else, is what you're saying.
Yeah, the thing is, yeah, right, figure out what's fit and proper.
I mean, the thing when I say, I'm hinting, you know, when I give that metaphor,
you know, you get a job at a pet food store, and the manager says,
okay, see that can that says fish food goes to the fish, can says bird food goes to the bird,
and the dog food goes to the dog, cat food goes to the, okay, yeah, fine.
You know, I keep throwing that metaphor out there because, yeah, people are supposed to eat certain things, right?
You're supposed to wear certain things and act a certain way.
Yes, you are, right, because you're not here randomly, right?
And there are rules to this, quote, unquote, game, and you're being watched.
And this is one of the things that are going to be instilled in the future, quote, unquote, perfect society.
So just a word of advice here.
If you're in the pork business, divest.
I'm not saying tomorrow, but, you know, there's some pretty big pork futures in pork stocks, right?
If you're in the shrimp and lobster and clam and scallop business, yeah, I wouldn't be investing in that in the future
because no one's going to be eating that, or mixed fiber.
You ever go buy a shirt and it says like 80% cotton, 20% polyester?
You know how many times you've seen that?
Yeah, your clothing will no longer be made that way.
So people will discover what the rules are for being on this planet in the future very soon,
and it's going to be quite interesting.
So we just gave a little tidbit there.
I don't know if that's worth giving stock futures, but that you know, invest in.
It does sound a bit like, you know, look for things that are actually kosher is what it sounds like to me.
The word kosher means fit and proper, and it's been hijacked in the mind virus way in the Western world,
and it's also been hijacked in the religious way.
Now there's something I call the kosher Nostra.
It's the kosher mafia.
Oh, well, that's where you have to pay the rabbis in order to give their stamp of approval to whatever the hell it is.
On window cleaner.
Yeah, whatever.
Which the best window cleaner is Lenox, by the way, but anyway, just a pun or a joke,
but I hear they're getting rid of no more Windows 7 in a year and a half too.
It's all going to be Windows 10.
So yeah, I think Lenox is the way to go, finally.
But yeah, so it's all corrupt right now, and the people have to do the research on their own.
You know, I feel kind of bad, and my sympathy goes out to the quote unquote Jewish people for all the brunts and jokes
and things that have been going on not only for millennia, more than 2,000 years in the past century,
but also recently on the alternative media.
I'm not apologizing for the alternative media, even though there are people that's, you know,
the quote unquote Zionists and this and that, right, you know, whatever.
But, you know, you notice how there's a lot of Zionist bashing, Israel bashing, Jewish bashing,
but all these people doing the bashing don't realize that they've been topped by the Pope.
You know, they don't even know what date it is.
They're still on his work schedule.
So the irony here is, like, I don't want to go anywhere and counter or advise on any of the bashing that is going on out there.
I prefer to just stand aside and bash everyone else because someone's got to throw a rock to stop.
It's kind of like in film or actually in reality when there's a mob scene, someone just pulls a gun and shoots in the air.
Like, everybody stops.
You know, that's going to be coming as well.
And I think maybe the Greek going on a rant for a few minutes every so now and then to get just people to stop, you know.
Yeah, that's the best thing is the initial wave of anything that is a great disruption begins with the first stone thrown, begins with the first shot fired.
And quite often that is what actually gets people's attention.
Not necessarily that they understand what's going on, but they might actually stop what they're doing or consider doing something else.
You know, whether they were standing still and now they've been motivated to action or they have been motivated to action and they've considered standing still.
Either way, it is about the attention that is caused and creates a change, you know.
And sometimes, yeah, like you said, in a mob scene, somebody has to throw that first rock.
Somebody has to fire that first shot, even if it is up in the air and it actually doesn't do anything.
What it does, or not doesn't do anything, but what it actually does is get the attention of those around you at least.
And that can continue to ripple along the pond.
You see, because the opposite of love may not be hate, because it takes a lot of passion to love and it takes a lot of passion to hate.
The opposite of love might be apathy, you see, being just totally removed from it instead of getting sucked up into it.
But in terms of discussing the end, I think part of it was what comes after the end was what is a big void in people's minds they have no clue about.
And I think just how the end is going to come about and I think that's about all the detail I want to give is that because it's informational based right now.
There's things that are coming, but I mean informational based.
People are still being clobbered about fear and doom and gloom and things that are supposedly going to take down society.
And what I want to do is give the assurance that it's not going to happen that way.
Things are going to turn around and you're going to forget about all that right before it actually really happens.
But then there's another world that's going to come after that and that is maybe another whole other discussion.
But again, to counter the dummy load that's been put on society about reincarnation, like if someone is having a hard life it's because they were bad in a previous life and all this stuff.
I mean this is like the syncretism of Simon Magus and corrupted Asian teachings and things that are just polluting the landscape.
To the point where you cannot have a rational discussion on these topics anymore.
Typically when you try to, people just agree with you, just like explaining what cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common.
And then they walk away as if you've never said anything.
That is the trouble.
And I'll tell you what, with the last remaining eight minutes here to episode six, which I do believe we will have to dub the dummy load.
I think that would be the appropriate title to affix to this particular presentation.
Yeah, take off the dummy load.
It's not. It's going to stick around.
Well, no, but it doesn't mean I can't slap that title on it nevertheless.
So, you know, it is appropriate.
I wonder if there's anything you want to say in closing because I am reminding you that we're just about out of time.
And I'm totally wireless away from any equipment right now.
I'm making coffee.
So I'd say, yeah, no, there's not much other than we said we would discuss sexuality in the end.
And actually they do tie in very, very closely together because people have lost true perspective on both in a rational way.
Rational meaning mathematical.
How do we communicate a lot with a little and objectively?
You've got to add a sense or a sensibility to the conversation or the narrative that people can walk away and say, well, okay, this is interesting.
I don't get it.
That's why I suggested archiving.
If you listen to the show, take some notes.
There's no doom and gloom coming.
There's no pole shift coming.
Right.
As you as they're told.
Yes, it's all going to happen, but you won't notice it when it does.
It'll be as if, you know, well, you know, it'll be you'll be so caught up in other things in a positive way that you won't know when the end comes.
So so just relax about it.
It'll be like getting clubbed from the back.
You won't even know it when you're at a party.
So the the the other part was sexuality.
The objective side of it is the purpose of those organs is to what is to continue multiple generations next year's crop and so forth.
Right.
And if that's being tampered with, guess what?
Your continuation is being tampered with.
And it's been tampered with scientifically, politically, legally, socially, religiously.
What they call psychologically, psychologically, which is spiritually the P.S.
Every time you see P.S.
Y as a prefix, it means spirit.
That's the psyche or psyche.
And the pneuma P.N.E.A.U.
Prefix pneumatic of pneumonia is the soul, which is your breath.
I've heard someone on a serious dummy load concept try to define the soul recently, and I just had a laugh.
Where'd you get that?
And they got really upset when I asked because they know it's not true.
But dummy load is not true.
A dummy load is an artificial load to drain all the energy from the system.
Right.
So anyway.
And there you have described a great many other sonic entities in what they call alternative media, but not this one.
So once again, closing out Episode six, which I think is which I think is quite appropriate because six, after all, is the number of what Greek?
Mint number of men.
So, you know, it's not what it is.
It is a human number and it is to be reckoned.
And guess what?
This is what we've talked about here, exactly what the continuation is and what the end game is.
And, well, is there any reason to panic or to flee or anything else?
No, because, well, it is merely, as I said at the beginning of the show, it is merely as, you know,
avoidable as death for any individual human being.
It will come.
So why?
Why?
Oh, why waste your energy involving yourself in worry?
Right.
No one gets off this rock alive, right?
Nobody gets out alive.
Oh, Jim Morris.
Yeah.
Or the night divides the day, which is which is true in a way.
So that's absolutely true.
Remember, the majority of the people that are listening to this sonic entities known as Achilles and the Greeks still don't even know how to keep time.
So it would be kind of hypocritical on anyone's part to move forward on information that is based on a different time reckoning system.
Because especially when the two don't convert, like metric to inches or kilos to pounds, they don't convert.
There is no conversion.
One is completely arbitrary, artificial and fictional and whimsical.
And the true way to keep time is observational using celestial bodies like the earth, the sky, the earth, the moon and the sun and the stars,
which is still highly used by certain groups of people in the scientific community.
So how do we can and also in all the ancient texts.
So so I think we've done a bang up job so far in six episodes to try to communicate some things with all of like the three people listening.
And so, you know, not to pat ourselves on the back, but at least we know for sure no one at all is sonically imparting this kind of information at all right now to this date.
And what we're saying right now is going to be old hat and past hat in a decade.
Oh, yeah, you guys said it.
So what?
Big deal.
We know it now.
True enough.
And I got to tell you, I love that cricket that I was just hearing in your background there.
That was great.
You must be standing outside now.
You've got your coffee and you're outside.
So the threshold moment, let's just say I'm neither in nor out.
I'm on the threshold.
One that's an interesting thing.
Maybe this show is a threshold moment in the consciousness of people's minds, you know, and hopefully it's not like the teacher in Charlie Brown.
I think, unfortunately, it could be too many.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, we may have just spent two hours speaking to most saying what?
What?
Yeah.
And it's not about being condescending.
It's just like, you know, I'm not here to make friends.
You know why?
Because you don't have a lot of time left.
Let's get real, people.
You know.
Right.
So the cricket tells us and the wind up toy and the digital representations there tell us that we're just about done.
But once again, I want to thank you guys for tuning in and at least giving this its day in court, as it were, because once more, this is the information that you're definitely not going to receive from any other source.
And it is unique to Ocelli and the Greek.
And when we said not a lot of time left, you know, it's closed ended.
You know, it's less than two decades.
Yeah.
And make a record of that.
So, yeah.
Well, I think we'll get more into this subject with more detail.
And I think we will maybe get into more details on things on the geopolitical scene as well.
But I would say that be objective, be perceptive, be discerning and avoid the dummy load.
Right.
Because after all, what is the dummy load?
Just about everything around you, pretty much.
And there you go.
So take care of yourselves.
Be well as well as you can possibly be.
And don't worry, don't panic and avoid the dummy load.
Ocelli and the Greek are finished.
Thank you, sir.
Thanks, Trent.