American freedom radio presents the only broadcast information no other media outlet
So it is the 5th day of the second month according to the Pope's work schedule, and this is Ocelli and the Greek broadcast live on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Did say according to the Pope's work schedule, so I gotta do this, Greek, what day is it actually?
I'd say it's the end of the second week of the 12th month, so that would put us around the 15th, let's say till noon, wherever you are.
And yeah, speaking of time, I think we've been a little ahead of the curve, so yeah, you know, people wondering what we mean by time, it's just the recordation of events.
And maybe giving people a heads up on what's coming is what we've been doing and all these other things.
Might be a little too soon, but we can't say we didn't try.
Well, that's for sure, and we have arrived at episode 18 just for the sake of keeping track of things and quantitatively understanding how we've moved forward here.
There have been 18, including this one now, episodes of this particular show, and you know, I did say on social media in a couple of places, the final episode, and put a question mark there.
And I was asked immediately to explain what I meant and all that kind of stuff.
I told them, tune into the show and you'll find out.
Yeah, it's better than a Fellini film, you know.
You ever see the end of the Italian movies?
Alfine, you know, the end.
You still have credits, don't you?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
So, yeah, well, it's interesting.
I think there was a TV show and there was a comedian.
I don't want to – actually, I don't want to use his name, but he said always end it on a high note.
Now, I don't know if we're really on a high note, but I think that stopping and either taking a break or stopping just for the sake of stopping sometimes is good.
Having good measurement or good measure.
Let's go this far and stop.
And it wasn't really premeditated much in the past.
It's a fairly recent concept to just, let's just say, let's stop at 18, right?
Well, yeah, that's for sure.
So this, for all intents and purposes, though, will be the last episodic time that it arrives at a particular mark on the calendar.
You know what I'm saying?
And you can reckon it by the wind-up toy or the digital representation thereof that we call a clock.
But who knows?
You'll still be rolling around this hour every what they call weekday.
Oh, yeah, I'll just simply do my thing during this particular time slot, and that's what will happen.
And who knows?
There may be other things coming in the future regarding this type of discussion, right?
Oh, you mean like Greek-speak?
Yeah, there we go.
There'll be some more Greek-speak, everything permitting.
It'll be, let's just say, let's just not keep people wondering.
Let's just tell them what might happen.
How's that?
That's good.
I was dancing around just to see if you wanted, you know, just like you two boxers circling a ring for a moment.
You're not sure who's going to actually get it underway.
Yeah, all right.
Well, let's just say Greek-speak is still going to continue.
But how and when, no one knows.
So it'll just be showing up here and there on AFR.
And if you go to the site and expect many changes coming on AFR, all for the better,
you will know that when Greek-speak has taken place and it will be live, no one knows.
You know, round and round it goes.
No one knows where it stops and, you know, in this case, where it starts.
And neither do I.
When the impulse is there to come out and speak, it will be done on AFR.
So just keep watching.
There you go.
Stay tuned, as they say in the business, right?
Yeah, or keep listening.
Yeah, and I think that's the most accurate and complete way to describe it, wouldn't you say?
Well, for sure.
And I wanted to dispatch with that right away because that was the first question.
And, hey, here's the other fun part, is that when people tune in late, like they often do,
they'll have to go back in the archive to find out the answer to the question.
Yeah, or the presentation itself, yeah.
There you go.
And take the whole of it.
So considering that this is the last time that we are going to convene at this particular point
on that wonderful wind-up toy or digital representation thereof,
I wonder if we should wrap things up, carry it forward.
I mean, what should we do at this particular time?
Because we didn't actually have a plan for, A, ending it,
or, B, what we were going to do with the last episode.
There's no plan at all in my mind.
Well, we could run the credits, which is pretty much go back
and do you want to discuss things from behind the scenes?
Because typically the credits show you things that you didn't see on the screen
or didn't hear on the show.
But you know what, there really isn't much from that perspective
because you and I typically just show up and do the show.
Yeah, that's true.
We don't go drinking at bars together, and we don't take windy walks or anything like that.
We just say, hey, let's show up once a week and tell people things that some might not want to hear it,
some might want to hear it, and just do it.
Because you know what, they're going to hear things that haven't been said and are not being said.
So here's something very unique.
So in terms of the credits part, the only thing we could do is go back and rehash perhaps,
maybe I don't know how to do it, from 1 to 18 episodes, let's say including this one,
or categorically or what have you.
But either way, if you look at it categorically, what have we not covered, you see?
Well, a lot of specifics I think were left out of the equation.
It was meant to provoke people to examine things for themselves in my estimation.
So this is part of the purpose.
And I figure we should just throw a couple more bricks on our way out the door.
That's definitely the way to go.
But in the meantime, I would say that as per usual, it would be a good thing to just for our sake,
not even necessarily for the listener's sake, but just to, it's always good to end on a high note,
like you were saying at one point.
And I think a high note for what it is that we've done thus far would be to, well,
just give them a few more provocations for the psychological end of things.
Yeah.
It would have to be maybe viewed categorically.
Anything come to mind?
I mean, I don't have what we've done in front of us, but mentally we've discussed just the,
what was it, 100% external input?
It was her first time around.
And boy, did I sound really subdued and quiet there.
I think I've gotten more comfortable with being on radio.
I can't listen to myself.
It's very humiliating.
I guess some people like listening to themselves, but I heard the episode playing once.
I was like, I don't speak that way.
I guess it's just being new on radio perhaps.
Right.
And plus I didn't help much because I took a completely subdued position that night for sure
and thought that that was appropriate.
But you know what?
I got more comfortable with you as this went on as well because it just, you know,
it was better to have the back and forth and to sort of counterbalance some of what you say now
and then to make it just a touch more palatable to somebody who might encounter it for the first time.
You know, that was kind of what I meant to do, and I didn't do a very good job on that first episode.
But you always do a good job.
Mixed drinks, you know, I mean, I'm trying to give sometimes the liquors too hard,
and you mix it up a little with some soda and ice.
It's fine.
But I stepped on you there.
Go for it.
No problem.
Listen, you know, the thing is when we started talking about 100 percent external input,
I mean, let's revisit that concept though.
I mean, what do you mean?
So you don't actually have any thoughts or inspirations within yourself?
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah.
In short, you know, let's give the strong version of it real quick.
In essence, your spirit, your mind, your essence, what you are is defined by your spirit, your personality,
you know, aside from your physical appearance being unique as well.
That spirit is a processor, and there's constant streams coming in,
and you process these streams as they come in based on your training, you see,
and also the type of spirit that you have, right?
And also you are able to emanate.
You're also able to transmit, right, vocally, physically, and mentally.
So in a sense, that would be called telepathy, right?
So it's a telepathic form that is maybe not technically accessible, but it's constantly happening.
In other words, the brain has no function.
Just to hearken back to what the Egyptians, when they preserved the bodies through mummification,
they made special containers for every organ of the body,
but the brain was pretty much drilled out and pulled out through the nose.
And if you ask them why they didn't have a special container for it, it's because it served no purpose.
So anyway.
So your brain serves no purpose, to put a bullet point to that one.
Yeah.
Have you been outside lately?
But anyway, I'm just –
Sure.
Yeah, okay.
No, actually, it does.
You know what it really is?
It's an antenna.
It's folded up.
It's an embedded transmission line.
And you know what's interesting?
I say this because occasionally there might be some good stuff on the Internet,
and for a little while there were hidden articles, scientific articles, and real good stuff, not the garbage.
And they were saying we really can't find anything in the brain.
Yeah, there's neurons and things firing in there, but we don't see where things are being held.
But if part of the brain, let's say like a lobotomization, chemical or physical is done,
certain functions are lost, so on and so forth.
Well, just like if you have an antenna set up to do something,
and you go ahead and whack a piece off of it, guess what?
It happens to your reception.
Yeah, a couple of channels might not work anymore.
Exactly.
Yeah, and you'll be two quarters of a nickel short of a dollar.
So either way, these things are just the basic premise we try to discuss about these things.
We said the spirit and the mind.
With just redundancy, constantly discuss the soul and the spirit and the difference between those two.
And I hope that's helped anyone out there, because this also gives you a gauge.
When you have these spiritual-type people and gurus come up to you,
or you want to inquire, just ask them what the difference between the spirit and the soul is,
and watch, you get the biggest pile of dog mush thrown at you, undefined stuff.
So if something as important as the spirit and the soul cannot be defined by these, quote-unquote,
people that say they're spiritual or spiritual leaders,
guess what kind of information the rest of it's going to be about?
You know, the same pile of dog poo.
So we've been trying to hit on that, because that's important.
Yourself, your body, is made up of the fleshy part, the soul, which is the breath,
and the spirit, which is the mind.
Which takes us directly to another subject, which we covered at length, and that is the container.
But not simply the container.
We did cover a bunch of things that come right along with that subject matter.
But why did we talk about the container?
Well, it's because, yet again, much like the spirit and the soul,
and the concept, and we broke it down etymologically, as well as logically, really, for people to grasp,
the other thing that we did was break down the body and the processes
and the fallacies that are rather popular in a lot of places.
So, you know, I think, and yet, that was part of the equation you were just talking about,
because, hey, look, there was the mind, the spirit, the body.
Oh, what about the body?
Well, that's also misunderstood, too.
Completely.
And here's the motive behind that one, and we didn't mention it.
We might as well do it now.
It was a two-hour show, but the motive is, let's just say, if you're being bullied,
let's say, in a schoolyard, you know, for years and years and years,
don't you want to kick that bully in the shins at least once before you leave?
Oh, definitely, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
At least, you know, you just want to kick them in the shins.
Well, the medical industry, the purpose of this was to kick the medical industry.
When I say medical industry, everyone goes to the mainstream.
I'm talking about the alternative ones also, because they're all part of the same training.
So, you know, this is a good apple, bad apple kind of thing.
Yeah, it came from the same tree, right?
So the purpose of that show wholeheartedly initially was to just convey one point,
and the point was something very common known as the common cold.
And this has been a nuisance, meaning the common cold to many people during seasonal changes.
And the purpose of the show was really built around the concept that when people feel miserable during seasonal changes,
it's not because of little critters, all right?
It was because of what they're eating.
They're not eating seasonally.
And just to, you know, if you want to, yeah, that was, I mean, I really like how you,
that has stuck with you as well in terms of the way you've prefaced it maybe once or twice after that
on how if bacteria cause the cold, doesn't that render all refrigeration unnecessary for food preservation?
You see?
Yeah, there's a practical sort of thing right in front of your face regarding this stuff.
I mean, okay, I think about it like exactly like that is, you know, listen,
if the refrigeration is literally to not make it conducive for bacteria to grow
and therefore for your food to go bad and for things to rot and et cetera, et cetera,
if it's meant to slow down that process, not stop it, but, I mean, in a virtual sense just about stop it,
then what is the point, you know?
And we all, anybody who's listening in an area where you have electricity
and you have access to an appliance, I mean, just about anybody has a refrigerator
if you have a structure that you're living in in the Western world.
So there it is, right?
It's one of those nonsensical things, and yet every single year there is this discussion of avoiding the cold
and, you know, it became rather trendy to destroy all the bacteria
and utilize things like hand sanitizers and, you know, completely turning the world into an antiseptic mess.
It's a form of bioterrorism. Think about that word for a minute.
Yeah.
They're terrorizing the people with biological entities that have no relevancy to the condition.
It is an indirect, I mean, yeah, it's a form of bioterrorism the establishment has put on their own society.
You know, and here's the thing.
One of our credos here is why say something if someone else is saying it, right?
Right, and nobody said that.
I've never heard anybody point that out.
Yeah, and I hope it catches on, and it's interesting.
We even caught a small article about the calorie being broken
and indirectly discrediting the calorie on BBC, I believe, and it's funny how the timing works.
I just like it.
It just means the time might be more correct for these things, you know, because calories have nothing to do with food,
but I want to jump back to the common cold and all that.
Oh, right, but we will revisit that food topic because it goes logically in order here with the way we're handling this,
so don't worry.
We'll revisit food and calories in a moment, but, yeah, go right back to the refrigeration.
Yeah, and even, see, let's do it backwards like they do.
What they do is they dissect or remove cells from a living being, whether it's a plant, animal, or human,
and they remove it from the living host, and immediately after removal it starts to die or decompose,
whatever it is, cells, fluids, tissue, okay?
Yeah, right, and it's no longer in its natural environment,
and when you take something out of its natural environment, what happens?
It starts dying in one way or another, and, you know, that occurs to me that when they withdraw blood from someone,
I don't know, it seems to me like immediately, no matter how they try to preserve it,
you no longer have something that's observable in its natural environment.
I mean, it would be a whole lot more convenient to actually utilize a blood test while the blood is still in the body.
I'm just spitballing here, you realize.
Yeah, and by the way, no, that's fine, but by the way, there was a lot of live blood testing that was banned,
and they actually did away with those doctors quickly, because what they found out when they were able to,
let's say, form technical devices to maintain the blood in a more, almost like a host condition,
where it remained in a lifelike state, they would see little blue and yellow and green flashes of light within the blood,
and cells would appear out of nowhere, just too scary.
You know, you can't tell people these things just emerge like that, you know.
It just flipped them out, so, you know, you just can't tell people the truth.
You can do it through science fiction, and by the way, if anyone has an organ card,
figure out how you can donate your body to science fiction.
You'll get more out of it that way, but anyway.
Yeah, so regarding the cells, when they remove them and they go into decomposition,
they structure the entire field around the dead things or decomposed things,
and so if you are a healthy individual or healthful or athletic,
and you go to someone who is used to seeing dead and decomposition and sick people,
how are they going to examine you properly, you know?
They don't know, see, because quote unquote people that are healthy don't go to these places,
only people that are sick, so now the culture is built around that.
So if you're not sick, you're going to get sick,
but the emergence of these critters is what they're blaming it on,
but essentially, again, just to be more purposeful, to state that eating seasonally helps,
I dare anyone to try it, and if you like being miserable for sympathy, don't do it,
but let's give the quick example rehash.
If it's cold outside, your body requires a certain metabolism to adapt to the cold,
and a blood, let's say blood, you've heard of, you know,
your blood needs to be a little thicker in the cold and a little thinner in the heat, right?
Okay, that kind of stuff.
So if you are in a cold environment and you eat something that was grown in a tropical environment,
that will change your body's constituents to being in the tropics,
and you will not fare well in a cold environment, and the opposite is true.
If you're in a hot environment and you let food pass through your body,
because that's what food does, that comes from a cold environment, you will not do well,
and that's why, for example, in cold climates, you always get a hot fever,
and in hot climates, you always get a cold fever, okay?
It flips over. The fevers are opposite.
So if anyone has ever been in a situation where it's cold outside and they feel sick,
well, I bet they have bananas, sugar, coffee, what else grows in the tropics that people typically like to buy,
foods that are out of season, tomatoes, imported foods, you know, exotic foods, right?
Stop eating those things and eat things that are cross-latitude.
Take a world map and just run your hand across the latitude line where you live,
and what I mean by that is so you have variety.
So if you live in Midwest U.S. and you keep running your finger across,
you'll see like northern France and Germany, parts of China, you know, Russia,
you keep going across so you have all these different varieties or styles of cooking that you can have for variety,
you know, kind of an international, you know, it breaks things up, right?
And eat cross-latitude, and you'll see cross-latitude on the planet.
You have very similar types of foods and very similar types of diets.
Now, I've done this for many, many years, and it has a 100% success rate,
even with people that have what they may call chronic ailments like asthma or allergies
or even mild things that use the C word, you know, C-A-N word, C-E-R,
and these things kind of go away once they start to learn to eat seasonally, and it works all the time.
If you don't do it, it doesn't work, or it doesn't work.
I've also discovered from discussing this with people, because health is very important,
that if someone is sick and you show them a way to get better, they get upset
because most people are brought up in a drone-type mentality.
Go to the school, graduate, get a job, and no one pays attention to you.
You're like this blank thing that moves around in society, and the moment they get diagnosed, right?
You've heard that term, diagnosis, with the C word or something else.
They go around and tell everyone, and for the first time in their lives, they get all this sympathy.
Oh, I hope you get better.
They never got any sympathy before, so now you get rid of it.
If they figure out a way to get rid of that diagnosis or that ailment,
they realize there's no more sympathy for them.
People are emotionally starved, so you have to be careful.
The other thing is to say that it also adds to their identity
because a lot of people wind up feeling homogenized, and I do use that term for a reason,
homogenized by society in a way.
We're all seen as a sort of a collective.
You're grouped together.
You're herded together in one way or another.
Linguistically, they always talk about, well, what group are you part of, basically?
That's how you're identified so often, and here's the thing.
That becomes too wide.
It doesn't actually give you the feeling of being an individual.
So, yeah, that's another problem is now they have an identity,
which their entire life is built around the illness,
and that's something that I always try and discourage people from doing
is don't become the thing that ails you.
It is simply something that ails you.
It's not exactly who you are.
Yeah, and it's interesting to see the reaction because it is negative to be ailed by something,
but they view the sympathy as being something very original to them,
and I think that people need to be able to give that to others more openly
so this type of situation doesn't occur.
So I just wanted to, you know, just thanks for bringing that up,
or, you know, the container and emphasizing it
because this is something that anyone can take away with them.
If you eat seasonally, you will notice how your body goes into balance with the environment,
and many of the things that ail people during seasonal changes specifically will be gone,
and this works every time.
And, again, how many people in the medical establishment
Have you ever heard discussed this?
Zero. None.
Well, right, and actually I want to interject a question from the chat room
because this occurs to me that it would be logical as well.
They asked about latitude.
Yes, they get that, but what about altitude as well
because different things are cultivated at different altitudes,
so wouldn't it be also helpful to seek to be on the same altitude as well
because some things just don't grow in the mountains,
and if you live in the mountains and you're eating stuff that only grows in a valley,
wouldn't that be a problem as well?
Not really a big problem, but I would call it the fine-tuning part.
Okay.
You know, that's like the 14 shades of red, not gray,
but you know how you could say a primary color, you know, it gives you an idea,
but then, you know, the sky is blue, but is it, you know, it changes,
you know, you want to find what time of day where you're looking.
There's a fine-tuning aspect, and that's a good question.
That is part of the fine-tuning, but if you, you know, there's the rough-tuning,
you know, if you miss what we're trying to do is get people within the area where they get the general gist of it,
and then they can fine-tune it, absolutely.
It also could be fine-tuned whether you're a man or woman, child or adult, child or old person.
If you're really old, you start to be better to eat food that's more digestible.
It could also be fine-tuned for how active you are, meaning, for example,
have you ever heard the benefits of a raw diet, as in food that is not cooked?
Okay, well, that's really good.
Yes, there's a lot of vitality in raw food, but that's if you're active.
Like if you're a delivery person, you know, or into very athletic or, you know,
you're a construction worker, let's say, you're constantly active,
but if you're seated at an office all day, you eat raw food, you'll be miserable.
It'll take you a very long time to adjust because it's very difficult to digest when you're stationary.
That's why if you look at a lot of the, let's look at the animal kingdom,
even though we're not animals, they particularly eat raw food because animals are generally active.
Well, this is true, but you know what?
You bring up digestion, and that is yet another kind of topic that we covered,
which fits right in line with this, and the discussion started in a weird way,
and I'll always recall this.
We talked about the food replicators on Star Trek.
Yes, back to the science fiction element.
Remember, a lot of truth can be told to you in science fiction, you know,
and I'd love to go back over that too as we move forward here because I think that's relevant.
Are you with me?
Yep, I'm here.
Okay.
We just lost you for a moment.
You kind of broke up, but yeah, what's interesting about that is if one studies the intestines or intestines,
you will see there are many layers there, and guess what?
They're hydrophobic.
They're not porous, and look at it carefully.
Look at it objectively.
If you start reading that the intestines absorb things and you look at them, yes, it looks like it absorbs.
It looks like it might absorb something, but all of those hydrophobic layers.
Here's another example.
In many cultures, they used to use intestines and bladders of animals to hold water.
How can you do that if they're porous, if things pass through there?
Now, what's happening is what's very interesting, the body being under a biological vacuum,
and you know what's another interesting thing?
I may not want to go into it now.
As you've heard, you know, hydrochloric acid being in the stomach, right?
Well, where does that come from?
Now, that's always freaked me out, to be honest with you, because the digestive elements in the stomach, okay.
I thought about this.
Again, I always take it back to my childhood, because this is the first time when, you know,
you start to understand the order of the world and people start to put things out of the order.
You say, what is this?
Because, okay, the concept that hydrochloric acid could dissolve just about anything.
In concentrated form, yeah.
In concentrated form, right?
But somehow, there's a few things that it doesn't seem to completely disintegrate.
Well, yeah, gold and certain noble metals.
Sure, noble metals, but you could think about the durability of those things, you know,
could be observable, et cetera, et cetera.
But then when I consider to myself that there is not only hydrochloric acid,
but a series of acids in the stomach, which, you know, to the best of my knowledge,
should be able to eat wood, destroy it, disintegrate it anyway, and destroy things like cement.
I mean, you can use acetic and hydrochloric acid, right, to remove all sorts of things.
I mean, you ever try it on paint?
It does a real quick job on that.
Oil stains on concrete to circle caves for the guys that get it off the ground, you know?
Right, that was one of the things we used to use to clean spills in parking lots
because I used to work in oil and gas and stuff.
And that was one of the things that we used to use to get rid of it.
Of course, a side note, we used to use gasoline to remove paint.
But anyway, it worked real well.
But the thing is, you think about the corrosive nature of that which they tell you is contained
in something that seems as fragile as the organ known as the stomach, right?
I mean, something's out of line here.
Yeah, it is out of line.
But, you know, we also talked about, you know, how the sweat forms in the pores, right?
And we also talked about how it forms.
And not only that, we gave the analogy of when there's a rainstorm outside
and you see clouds coming in that dump millions of tons of water.
Yes, that's millions or if not hundreds of thousands of tons of water over a city, over an area.
Do you think those clouds, you know, have all that water like a sponge?
Or is that water created in real time almost instantly?
And people might say, oh, well, you know, that's the humidity in the air.
Well, you might have 25% or 30% humidity.
And then when it starts raining, it doubles.
Shouldn't the humidity go down then when it's raining if the rain is drawing it from the humidity
and there isn't that much water in the air anyway?
And here, just to throw this out, you need 15 grams of water per cubic meter of air,
according to the meteorologist, to really have a condition for rain, which is about 35% humidity.
So where is all this rain forming?
You know, where is all this rain coming from in the cloud?
There's no rain in the cloud.
There's no water in the cloud.
If there was any water in the cloud, it would sink to the earth.
So that's one thing.
And the other thing is we have these things called airplanes, right?
Escape the rain by going to the cloud, yeah.
They go through clouds and they're not drenched and dripping in water.
Yeah, and the aerodynamics don't change.
That's the other thing is you don't see a – and you would.
Listen, anything that you imagine traveling with some sort of velocity through air
is obviously going to travel affected through water.
I mean, if you don't believe me, throw a baseball over a swimming pool
and then throw a baseball into a swimming pool and you'll see what I mean.
Or even drops of water at 500 miles per hour would leave hail marks on the thin skin of an airplane.
And, yes, airplane skins are so thin that if you look at them closely, it says, don't step here.
Why?
Or if you've ever seen what's called a bird strike, a bird will go right through a plane.
But, yeah, so once people relax and understand that, yes,
things do form instantly from what's called nothing.
People have been convinced that there's such a thing as nothing.
And when they think about it, they can't because there is no such thing as nothing
because there's something everywhere.
Oh, boy.
Well, yeah, that's the other thing.
Back to the hydrochloric acid, it comes from – how could it come from something that would damage?
Well, you know, this is probably part – to get into the finer technical details, I can say I don't know.
But I can see the evidence of it, how it appears and disappears very much like a rain cloud does.
A rain cloud appears, and there's lots of rain, and then it disappears.
Here's another consideration.
I know I'm harping on this, but here's another consideration.
When a human being vomits, right, they obviously are pushing up some of their stomach contents.
It's not all food.
It contains, you know, okay, fine, somebody out there might go, okay, why are you talking about this?
But, no, there's a relative point to be had.
If you vomit up the contents of your stomach, and I don't know a human being who hasn't at some point,
you would figure that there would be a lot of damage.
I mean, yeah, you might get some irritation in your throat and your mouth,
and it doesn't taste very good and whatever.
But if you were literally vomiting up hydrochloric acid, okay, because here's why I say this.
It still is present though.
Oh, maybe.
But if you drank a diluted hydrochloric acid, you'd have observable damage.
So there is a difference in some way between the two.
Again, I don't know the technical difference per se.
Yeah, but it is something to ponder.
And let's just say, might I be holding back a little bit because do we need more than the remainder of the show to explain it,
what I've discovered about it or what can be discovered about it?
Absolutely.
I think that would be left for the future talk.
But right now, just maybe just bringing these points up, again,
because remember, we've got to kick that bully before we go, right?
That's the other thing.
And, of course, that really began with you talking about taking a blood pressure cuff machine.
I don't know if you want to go into that.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whenever I go to these grocery stores, they have a little pharmacy department.
And I asked the person in there, I said, well, where can I get one of these?
They're like, well, why?
We just rent it.
It's not ours.
And I'm like, okay, well, why do you want one?
I said, well, because I'm opening a museum on medical fakery and quackery,
and I wanted this to be one of the prime exhibits.
And they all look at me like with a stunned face.
None of them have ever said, no, it's not fake, it's not quackery.
They all intuitively know that it's a completely quacky thing.
And also I joke around.
Whenever I know I'm traveling through a town and I know there's a hospital coming up,
I have to pull over and stuff cotton in my ears because if I don't,
when I drive by, the quacking is so loud that I go deaf for about a day.
So I have to stuff the cotton in my ears.
Anyway, that's just maybe if you're in rock and roll band,
you know what I'm talking about when it's too loud and your ears ring.
But anyway, yeah, so, yeah, this is the jokes.
And no one comes by and says, well, it's not quackery.
People know intuitively.
Now here's the thing.
Let's harp on the alternative doctors a little bit because they're always still thinking,
well, the mainstream is giving bad chemicals.
Our chemicals are better.
You've got to trust us.
And there's practical advice and there's practical notions.
And when I say advice, it's not medical advice.
It's just common sense.
Like don't put your hand in the blender.
Fire burns.
How do you like that advice?
It's as basic as that.
So, yeah, I think we've used the time, not only now but also during the episode,
to convey a few things that should have and could have helped people.
And, by the way, I have gotten some feedback that since I heard eating seasonally
and, you know, colds don't occur because it's cold out,
actually someone got back and said that in one culture, I believe in the African continent,
they remove teeth from children and they do it in the wintertime traditionally
because there's less chance of infection.
So that shows me someone is listening.
And if we've affected one person, and I know it's been more than that,
we've done a pretty good presentation.
Yeah, that's for sure.
And I've heard, you know, feedback about this show as well that, you know,
people were reached about various points.
And, you know, it is heartening, let's just say, although we'll get into the heart in a little bit
because that was what we talked about last week.
It's heartening to know that at least some of what was said was heard, and that's always helpful.
And acted upon, too.
And acted upon, right.
Right.
You know, and I did bring up the whole thing about the food replicators, okay,
which somebody's going to say, well, why is he pulling this out?
Kind of relates to –
Yeah, why is he pulling that out?
Because getting into that's getting into something from nothing.
But go ahead.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, that gets into something from nothing, sure.
But it also harkens back to this discussion about food because you talked about the process, again,
without these things being porous, et cetera, et cetera.
Well, then what is the process?
I mean, if you're not – you know, digestion.
There was another keyword.
Go ahead.
It's induced through induction.
Very simple.
They have these motorized toothbrushes these days, and I think even cell phones,
and their chargers are non-contact.
You just place it in a docking station, and there's no terminal or anything there.
You know, it's all plastic.
And it's just, you know, one electrical coil next to another electrical coil,
and there's a field there.
If you put a strong magnet there, you'll feel the magnet buzzing from the 60 cycle
or, you know, coming out of the wall.
And Tesla showed how you can do remote power transmission with two synchronized,
matched devices no matter how far apart they are, and you can communicate without wire, right?
Wireless communication, right?
That's through a form of induction.
It's simple induction, really.
Another way to maybe show how esoteric induction can be,
they have these induction cookstove tops.
They're glass, and you can have a pot of boiling water, move it to the side,
put your hand right on the stove, and it doesn't – it's just room temperature.
You put the pot of boiling water right over it again, and it continues to boil, right?
The sun works through induction.
So it's a form of induction.
The food has vitality in it,
and that vitality, depending on how much vitality it has, emanates.
Here's an interesting thing.
Let's just bring this up.
If anyone really wants to do a good study, and I've always said this before,
everything that could have been known was known around the late 19th century, early 20th century.
What I mean by that, if anyone gets a good nursing book, not a doctor's book,
but a nursing book from the late 19th century, early 20th century,
they will discuss something called ptomaine rays or ptomaine effects.
Now, ptomaine is spelled P-T-O-M-A-I-N-E, and that's the Greek word for dead.
They would discuss things like if in nursing, if anything goes below the waist,
it's unsanitary, unclean.
So anything in surgery or bandages always had to be kept above the waist.
And dead bodies emanated a ray, just like through induction, that brought disease.
You didn't have to touch it, just be in its proximity.
And they were fundamental with these field effects.
So it's all field effects, essentially.
To go back to field effects, there's a guy named Rudolf Hoschka,
who was the father of modern-day vitamins.
And by the way, he would set himself on fire and run naked down the street
if he saw what people were doing with vitamins today.
And fortunately, they don't use his name,
even though there is a cosmetic line out of Europe that uses his stuff.
But he wanted to discover back in the 30s what gave food its vitality,
and he made various extracts and approached living beings.
And he noticed that eventually he didn't even have to add the extract to the life form.
He can just have them adjacent to each other.
And he's the one that figured out what's called modern-day vitamins.
So there are these things called field effects.
You know, you ever walk into a room, let's say, where that was empty,
but there were some people that just left that were arguing,
and you walk in and there's like, this room kind of feels stuffy or doesn't feel good?
They left it, you know?
Yeah, not only that, but I mean, I point to this,
that there is a practice in some pagan cultures
where you carry around vials of particular things in order to promote field effects.
And people think it's just, you know, oh, that's just silly superstition.
The holy water deal I see in the Christian paganism, yeah.
Yeah, well, there you go. I didn't separate any of them.
I just said in some pagan practices.
Oh, that's total pagan, yeah.
Christianity as it stands is paganism.
Oh, yeah, it's the highest form, actually.
It's everything put together. It's the shopping mall for paganism.
But anyway.
But like I'm saying, you see these people that even now will carry around a vial of oil
or a vial of water from a particular place and things like that.
And people think that it's just all based on hokey superstition.
I'm not telling you that all that stuff works.
What I'm telling you is that it's based upon the idea that certain things could be discovered
at a certain point to have certain field effects.
Yes, and it's all field effects to tie it back into digestion.
There you go.
Yeah, so that's the point.
And so now let's practically go through it.
Now, when one consumes food, people say, well, you get to take in or you consume medicine
or you consume a liquid or whatever.
What is happening is you're absorbing it into your body, and therefore it becomes a part of you.
Well, in a way, it certainly is part of you.
You are what you eat. That is true.
Or you are what you ate.
You are what you ate. Right.
You are what you ate. Very good.
But the thing is, it's not necessarily as though these elements are being pulled directly, let's just say.
You know, you didn't dig up the potato and extract it from the dirt,
and therefore now you have the potato from the dirt, which is now put into your body.
It's not transference in exactly the same way, is it?
No, but, you know, it's an interesting thing.
There are people that have claimed to be called breatharians where they don't eat or haven't eaten,
and they put them in laboratories or buildings that are made out of concrete and steel and electric lights,
and all of a sudden they start to starve.
And you put them back in their natural environment, and they don't have to eat again.
So you're taking it in from all nutrition and all energy comes from the environment.
And whether you have an external ecology and you have an internal ecology,
the internal ecology would be the pathway or the tunnel through the body, which is from the mouth to the anus.
That is a big tunnel way, but everything else in the body is completely sealed.
And it's under a slight vacuum condition, meaning slight negative pressure.
And some people, like I had some comments once sent to me, well, I'm not a vacuum cleaner.
I'd never said you were.
A slight negative pressure, just like if you ever leave an empty plastic bottle in the cold,
you notice how it wants to contract or people use these vacuum seal bags and they contract.
It's not even that intense of a vacuum, but nonetheless, it is a slight negative pressure.
So, yes, these things are, you know, the biological vacuum needs to be considered.
What needs to be considered is that everything is all field effects.
Also, what needs to be considered is the body is always trying to make harmony with its environment.
So why be in an environment and then bring something that is foreign to that environment into that environment to put into your body?
You see, so there's a level of harmony.
But, you know, we also maybe discussed, which we may not do, was a cooking show.
So no one's going to get my pasta fazool with lamb ragu recipe, you know, going on here, you know.
So anyway, but, yeah, I'm just joking about that.
But, you know, I was thinking one day we're doing something about how to cook.
And it sounds really funny and it has nothing to do with any of the cooking, quote unquote, shows that people have seen.
Of course, you know, if we're going to do, let's say, something on cooking or the Greek is, you know,
you've got to really listen because it's not what you think it is.
So, yeah, food preparation.
Right. And generally speaking, that was the whole thing.
And, of course, like I said, it began with the idea of the food replicator,
because how does the food replicator work in the science fiction field?
Right. Seems as though you could relate it directly to the body field effects.
You know, here's the thing.
It was just a parallel to this because we're talking about field effects.
And science fiction has been brought up more than three times or a couple of four times, let's say.
So, you know, everyone talks about you hear about all this crap.
And, well, it's kind of call it infotainment, you know, about time travel.
And they always evoke Tesla and Einstein, the Philadelphia experiment, all that, you know, you know, that stuff is it's OK.
You know, if you've got a lot of space between your ears, you've got to fill it with something.
But what's interesting is, yes, that technology is viable, but not to Tesla.
I would say somewhat to Tesla and definitely not to Einstein.
But there was a fellow named Olaf Alexanderson.
I believe it's Olaf, but Alexanderson of the Alexanderson antenna fame.
And he took the concept of radio way beyond Tesla, where not only can he do was instant communication possible,
but communications were able to be received before they were even sent.
So I'm going to stop right there because I might get myself in trouble.
But if anyone wants to look up the Alexanderson antenna, they're up in Bolinas Ridge, California.
They were set up in Sweden.
The one in Sweden, they fire up once a year.
Now, they're not set up like they were back in the days, but essentially they were, yeah, really cool.
And if that technology we're talking about early 20th century, it was developed anyhow that computers are developed.
Yeah. What's called time travel doesn't exist.
But going back to a past event, you see when people call what they say time travel, time is just the recordation of events.
So you can't travel in time unless you look at a logbook or something.
That's a stupid concept that should have never been brought forward.
But, you know, there's a lot of stupid concepts being brought forward.
But when someone says time travel, what they really mean, you know, we have to make excuses for these people is going back to a past event.
That is all entirely possible. But time travel is not possible now.
But going back, it sounds like a semantic thing.
But let's we have to say what we mean and mean what we say.
Ben wants to research the work of Alex Anderson and why he's been buried, just like so many others that came up with some really interesting basic stuff.
And I'm not talking about technology that's really difficult to make.
We're talking these guys use pieces of wood, glass, brass and steel wire, you know,
stuff you could find in the garbage and they were able to make this these kinds of things.
That's why we once discussed where have all the masters gone?
There's no more mastery, you know.
Right. And we we did touch upon that.
Of course, we are running a little lower on this first hour time wise.
But one thing I wanted to hit upon and give a couple of minutes to is, well,
it was asked about in the chat room again and I was getting to it.
But, hey, let's just jump and jump right to it.
The concept of viruses, because we were talking about bacteria and and, you know,
how people are worried about bacteria and colds and all of these wonderful things that they tell you to beware of in the wintertime,
which, again, is counterintuitive because of the atmospheric or should I say the environmental condition that that you have during a cold season?
OK, fine. But what about viruses?
I mean, viruses seem to be almost exempt, although, you know, if you don't put things into a refrigerator again,
it seems as though viruses wind up being preserved, but not really promoted.
They don't seem to grow kind of like the bacteria, or at least that's always what I've been told.
Well, this is a note. Let me preface it this way. Remember Bill Hicks?
He did the little skit on he visited the book depository where Oswald was supposedly.
And he says, look how accurate it Oswald's not even there. Right.
No, that's one of my favorite stories. Yeah, it's very accurate. Right.
OK, so Oswald sought Kennedy. There are viruses. Right.
How about the 19 Arab hijackers, which half of them were found alive later on?
You know. Yeah. So this is what viruses are. It's just an official lie.
Now, what I mean by that, let's go to the bastion of infinite knowledge known as Wikipedia.
Look up virus. What you will find they even say is that viruses are actually a part of a study known as virology.
That is a part of a study known as toxicology and all of toxicology is based on the study of the liver.
And if you keep they have five different category theoretical categories of viruses,
and you'll find out eventually doing a bit of research that what they're calling viruses is nothing more than broken up cell mitochondria.
It's no different than when it's garbage day outside.
You go over and kick someone's can on the ground and all their stuff comes out on the sidewalk.
They're your viruses. Right now. Now, here there is no such thing.
As a matter of fact, if someone wants to know such thing as described, like, for example, Oswald did exist.
Right. And the 19 Arab hijackers apparently did exist, but they did not exist in the way that we were told.
You see, that's what I mean. So. So what viruses really are there?
Actually, if someone wants to do an Internet search, put in a medical virus as a fraud.
There's a few well-written, well-written articles by European scientists that said one guy was out of Germany.
He has a Web site and he's he's now on the vaccine bandwagon like vaccines are bad.
But his whole thing was he did a very good paper on how he was studied and professionally researched viruses.
And after a few years, he says, I've never seen one. I only see computer graphics of it.
I hear about what they do. This is a fraud. Yeah, right.
And it's like black holes. You know, no one's ever seen one. It's you only see computer graphics of it. Right.
So. So it is an official story there for for official. It's a form of bioterrorism.
Do you know what I mean by that? It's like to terrorize the public to a point where they they're in a state of terror.
And then they just do whatever they're told, just like, for example, if someone cries fire in the movie theater, you're looking for the exit door.
If there's an emergency on the airplane, you just do whatever the next closest authoritative person says, like a stewardess or something.
You're going to do whatever they say. You shut down your brain.
There's no more critical thinking in an emergency or critical terroristic type situation. Right.
Just like 9-11, everyone was willing to see what was being said about it and they accepted it.
The same with Kennedy. We're hungry for this. You know, that's that's when the dummy load comes in, you know, to kill that energy.
So what's interesting is that another form of bioterrorism is that people are being terrorized by these things that don't exist and they need help.
So they go to the nearest bastion of information and they accept that as what they call gospel.
And now you're stuck with it, you know. And once people accept that, it's really hard to go against the grain.
And you being a researcher yourself have found that I don't think you've been invited by Fox News as a semi authority or authority on the Kennedy assassination lately, have you?
What are the chances of that? Right. OK. Yeah.
So astronomically not. So once these things catch on, these initial stories, you know, Pearl Harbor, Roswell aliens, all these things that are, you know, totally false as portrayed.
You cannot change that. It's going to be there. It's not written in stone, but it might as well be.
Right. And people gave me a lot of trouble for letting Liam Sheff get away with saying on my show that AIDS doesn't exist.
Well, it doesn't exist as advertised. No, it doesn't exist. It's actually a lifestyle.
Now, here's another thing. And I'm sure says I knew a guy who used to go around selling life insurance.
And they had this little thing. They want to do an AIDS test for you before they give you the policy.
They have this little thing called a postcard and they prick your finger and they stick it, you know, blood on there and send it in to see if you get accepted for it.
And I knew about this back then. So I played a trick on him. I said, I'm going to anyone that goes and eats.
If you're a meat eater or here's the thing, people say I'm vegetarian or a meat eater.
Right. Humans don't really eat meat. They're carrion eaters. They don't kill the animal and eat it as it's dying.
You know, they they kill it and the meat becomes anyway, they're scavengers.
So so what you do is if you have a rare steak, really, you know, if you like steak rare, you know, and you eat a lot of it.
If you take what's called an AIDS test within three hours, you will test positive every time.
It is true that that does happen. And of course, the false positives in those tests have done a lot of things to people's lives.
And nobody ever takes it into account that that could be something else that is part of the deception.
Well, listen, the first hour is done, but we are going to be back in the second hour for the final episode of Uccelli in the Greek.
It is number 18 here on American Freedom Radio and American Freedom Radio dot com.
Stay tuned.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us for free education.
Well, that's obviously effective, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America.
All the information they provide is free.
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from?
Exposing commonplace corruption.
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice.
Or bringing light to important information nobody else does.
Or they never censor, hang up or cut off their guests.
Well, that's no fun, is it?
Or they created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shows and scum.
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, exposing commonplace corruption,
helping vulnerable people without a voice, bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative mainstream and alternative media shows and scum,
what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotics.
Freedom.
Oh, yes, I like this very much.
Radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein, and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces three brand-new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates, and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
Tell the truth. Don't be bullshitting people.
There's enough bullshit as it is. In fact, there's just enough.
Did you know that?
There's just enough bullshit to hold things together in this country.
Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation.
Where would we be without our safe, familiar American bullshit?
Land of the free, home of the brave, the American dream.
All men are equal, justice is blind, the press is free.
Your vote counts.
Business is honest, the good guys win, the police are on your side,
God is watching you, your standard of living will never decline,
and everything is going to be just fine.
The official national bullshit story.
I call it the American Okie-Doke.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information
would dare to under
So our number two of the final episode
of Ocelli and the Greek as it has been presented thus far,
episode 18, and that is probably Odie
that you might hear barking in the background.
Anyway.
And by the way, Chuck, did we ever mention why
the numerology behind 18 is divisible by six?
You know, this will also freak out the Christian crowd.
There we go.
Yeah, actually, it's divisible by six
and you can make three sixes out of it.
Which to me are just three men standing together
because the number six is the number of man, actually.
Correct. It's the number of man. That's right.
And the reason why there are three sixes
is because by two or three witnesses, it shall be so.
So when you have two witnesses, it's so.
But when it's three, it's done.
That's why when you're reading the ancient documents,
how many times have you heard people saying,
I've said it three times
and I won't say it again.
Right. That's all you need.
So the interesting thing is, you know,
you have five fingers and a hand makes six.
You've got two arms, two legs, a torso and a head.
It makes six.
If you look at ancient documents or political documents
that have high effect, Magna Carta, Constitution,
Declaration of Independence, all those other things,
you will find there's a numeric sequences of six.
Whenever you're addressing men,
it should be divisible by six.
Isn't that interesting how it happens that way?
Well, it is. It is absolutely interesting.
And people point to the, you know,
the fact that the five pointed star
is often one of the things that is represented as,
you know, the great occult symbol.
But they often misunderstand
that there are six compartments in that configuration.
Guess what?
If you take a human body
and you imagine extending the arms outward
and the legs apart just a bit
and think about where the head lies,
that five pointed star with six compartments
is literally the representative figure for a man.
Something to consider there as well.
And of course, I always urge you to do your own research.
Find that what I just said to you is, you know,
please prove me wrong, but I doubt you will.
Yeah, when man sheds that six point perspective,
he will go to the next level,
which is not too far, by the way.
But not next week, not next year, not in ten years, but yeah.
Yeah, and in fact, you know,
there's actually more to it when you think about it.
But look, we don't want to descend into numerology
because then we'll wind up sounding like someone else
and that is not the business that we conduct here on the show.
So let us move forward with an interesting question,
again, from the chat room.
And I know where this is going to go,
so I'm just going to throw it at you
and then I'll let you hurl the bricks afterwards.
You know, what do you think we need to do about the tyranny
that we're confronted with, Greek?
You know, the tyrannical rule.
In other words, I think they're looking for your viewpoint.
Set yourself apart.
It's not there for you.
Everything is in balance.
The reason that happens is, you know,
if you bump your elbow and it hurts,
I mean, guess what, you shouldn't have bumped it, right?
But at the same time, you try to fix it.
It's not quite like that.
I don't see it as tyranny.
I don't see it as tyranny for me.
Whenever you look at leadership of anything,
whether it's a family, a corporation, or a government,
that is to impose a certain kind of order that brings balance for that system.
Sorry.
You know, I guess if this is addressing an American tyranny
or worldwide tyranny or past tyranny or just tyranny in general,
I mean, this is a huge subject on its own.
Well, certainly.
And I think a follow-up comment, it might be the same person.
I might be confusing them because it always is difficult for me to read on air, people.
But the thing is, I want solutions from the Greek, is the statement.
So you know what?
How about I just challenge you right now to say, listen, what are the solutions?
I mean, first, I guess we should identify some of the problems, which I think we've done.
But how about –
Yeah, it's simple.
Set yourself apart.
Let's use the American model.
During an election season, if – by the way, voters don't elect.
Electors elect.
When you vote, that means you are vowing that the election,
whatever the electors do during the election, you will back up.
And that's the definition of it.
Go look it up.
That's why you have to register to vote.
Voters don't elect.
But here's the thing.
During an election cycle, if absolutely no one showed up, and I mean no one,
I assure you, every government building will be empty.
Anyone could walk in and be the president.
Because what will happen is they'll say, wow,
this whole system is set up on the idea that people can vote us in.
And if no one shows up, that means that the gig is up.
But it has to be all or nothing.
You can't have five people in a town show up.
No, yeah.
I was going to say, let's –
It has to be of biblical proportion, for example.
You know what I mean?
There's that word again.
The biblical.
Well –
Which is difficult.
Well, not time yet.
But we've tried.
We can't say we haven't tried, though.
No, that's for sure.
We have tried to ask for people to consider the solutions.
But let's see.
Yeah, we don't –
This is funny.
I'm asking for solutions.
Don't rabbit trail into another topic.
Well, all right.
Yeah, let's go back to it.
Solutions are set yourself apart.
Now, it is lawful to move, actually move your physical location,
a form of –
Let me use the word, no pun intended, exodus from a place,
if it becomes unbearable to you.
But now you have to realize –
I think we once mentioned you've got to know who you are,
you've got to know when you are, and you've got to know where you are.
Well, where you are –
We try to say who you are, the soul, spirit, and the body,
when you are, lawful time.
And now we're going to say where you are.
What people fail to realize is that this entire planet
is going under a global system.
Through ancient history, let's go maybe biblical for a minute,
you'll notice all the initial stories were about events that happened to a family
or a small group or a small lineage of people.
And then these same events happened to an entire nation.
And as the story progresses, the same events happen on a global level.
So you have familial, national, and then global.
Right now you're into the global aspect.
For example, 30 years ago, if I was going to Europe, people would say,
hey, bring me the Levi jeans.
Make sure it's the one with the red label.
We'll give you $100 for it.
I remember if you go to Italy, they wanted a big Bertha club.
We'll give you $500 for it.
You know a golf club?
All right, now if you're in Europe and you want Levi jeans with a red label,
guess what?
Go to the keyboard.
Or eBay.
Yeah, you got it.
Yeah, you see?
So it's global now.
So where are you going to go?
If you think there's a hotel on the moon or a space station, go for it.
So stay put.
Mind your P's and Q's.
And here's the thing.
People say, I want to stand up for my rights.
Okay, it's good to stand up for your rights,
but it's good to sit down when they're fixing on cracking heads and busting people for it.
So use discernment.
Anyway, how many times have you heard that, stand up for your rights?
Listen, that's one of those tough things because I've got this habit of speaking out
when I find something distasteful that's occurring in front of me one way or another.
And, of course, given the situation and the way communication is nowadays,
I feel this compulsion, let's call it,
to speak out about things that I think should not be occurring because, unfortunately,
it doesn't comport with what I know to be lawful.
Lawful.
Now, I've actually taken a bit of crap for not having you lay out what is lawful and what is unlawful,
and you refer people to the biblical text, but here's the thing.
Hold on, hold on.
I have to interrupt.
Get your law from your deity.
Right.
Your deity.
And there's no such thing as one God.
There's a plurality of them, and you better do your research.
It's like if you say the word army, you expect just one soldier, or is it a multitude or a plurality?
Right.
Yeah, so continue.
Sorry.
Well, no, that's exactly where I wanted to go is that, you know,
those that are constantly screaming for liberty and justice, here's the thing.
I understand what your sentiment is, but I don't think you're reckoning properly what it is you are invoking
with the words you're choosing.
You know, and that's, yet again, one of these things that I think we covered quite well
and should cover just one more time for people.
Because I have a really profound understanding.
Listen, I do not claim to have the level of scholarship on the ancient text that you do.
But I will say this.
But hold on, Chuck.
I never claim to have a level of scholarship on it either.
What I'm trying to do is impart to people, hey, when you hear something, where did that come from?
No, I understand.
But one could say that in comparison to the average listener, you definitely have a level of understanding
of that particular text, let's just say, that is not common.
Okay?
So it's a rarefied level of knowledge.
You'll accept that, won't you?
Yeah, okay.
And eating seasonally, maybe.
Okay.
That's fine.
No problem.
We'll leave it there.
There may be more, more things that you're a master of or have a mastery of, let's just say.
Yeah, just start seeking it.
Yeah, go ahead.
But I'll tell you something.
I have a really diverse understanding of that which they call a cult,
that which they call ancient religious practices which are often identified as pagan,
although I argue that everything on this planet at this point could be easily identified as pagan.
I don't care what you call yourselves.
Yeah, no argument there.
That is a fact and the truth.
Go ahead.
But the deal is I know a lot of the roots that a lot of other people don't,
so I think it's extremely necessary to let people understand what it is they are actually intentionally invoking
when they ask for liberty and justice.
Oh, boy.
You know what?
I've heard you on that.
Why don't you give it to them then?
Well, I want us both to hit it, but here's the thing.
Yeah, okay.
Tag team it.
Yeah, definitely because it's worthy of it.
You know, all you have to do to understand that is take a look at the symbols
which are placed right in front of your face, okay?
There is a reason why the Lady Justice is, first of all, a lady,
but there's also a reason why she has a scale.
There is a reason why she is blindfolded, okay?
There is a reason why she is dressed the way she is.
She is literally the representation of one of, one of, mind you,
because there are various forms of it, of what you could easily refer to as the ancient goddess religions, okay?
And I use the word religion advisedly, I know, but in a literal sense, this was religious.
I mean, there were many practices connected to it, and justice in and of herself,
she is not the representation of a kind or equal arbiter of what is good and what is proper
and what is, well, let's say merciful.
There is no mercy and justice, by the way.
She's very cruel.
It's extremely cruel.
And then liberty and lady liberty, yeah, we can talk about the statue of liberty,
the literal representation, again, well, let's see, what's easily referable here?
Things like Samarimus, things like ISIS, not the construct that they come up with,
you know, telling you it's a terrorist organization that, you know,
any idiot can see is something that was created by the intelligence agencies
in conjunction with an organic revolt against certain practices in a particular area.
But leaving that aside, the thing is, all of this is meant to hearken back to a,
I shudder to use the word spiritual, but a spiritual order which was given to ancient people
based on the behavior of a literal goddess.
Now, this goddess, again, not the fair, kind, gentle, you know,
you're going to receive satisfaction, well, perhaps, but it depends on what you call satisfaction.
And I'd like you to discuss that a little bit and tell people that although you
and I are coming at this from different angles,
we seem to arrive at the very same conclusion regarding it.
Yeah, what I like to do is just be blunt in your face like baseball bat, you know, kind of stuff, you know.
You know, there's a kinder, gentler way always, but I think time for that is over.
People that are confessing and professing certain things, you know,
like let's go back to the word thing.
Someone says, do you have any kids?
And I say, well, I don't have any goats.
And they're like, no, you know what I mean.
I'm like, yeah, children?
Okay, so here's someone who doesn't say what they mean or mean what they say.
Do you want to go into business or partnership or even have a friend that doesn't say what they mean or mean what they say?
Not really, right?
So there's that part of element of forgiveness, let's just say, that has to be incorporated in communication.
But that's the truth.
So when people are asking for justice, they don't know what they're asking for.
But does that make it any different?
Right?
If people are asking for liberty, they don't know what they're asking for.
But does it make it any different?
You know what?
Let's throw in another one.
If people are asking for freedom, they don't know what they're asking for.
But does it make it any different?
Right?
No.
Well, no.
And that's yet again another wonderful word which is often bandied about people thinking that that means that they are allowed to make individual choices.
The word freedom, quite literally, again, you got to look back to the languages that these words were rooted in.
I mean English is the bastardization of various other languages.
Really?
Okay.
Half a million words of it.
Yeah.
Okay.
So freedom.
All right.
Let's break it in half.
You have free and dumb.
All right.
Free obviously means to be without.
Look, very simple observation.
Something that is sugar-free has no sugar in it.
Something that is, you know, supposed to be, let's say,
Devoid of it or lack of it or no presence of it.
Right.
So that's an acceptable version of what that part of the word means.
Okay.
Dumb.
D-O-M.
Okay.
Sounds to me, looks to me like the word dominos, dominorum, dominion, domination, all of these things.
And in the older days it meant the state.
Right.
Because all of these things are characteristics that obviously come along with the state.
The state dominates the situation.
The state dominates the conduct of business.
It has dominion over its people.
Right.
You know, a domicile.
I mean, all of these things actually.
You know, the dominatrix.
Okay.
It doesn't matter where you go.
If you use the D-O-M, you're talking about as someone who has control.
Correct.
Okay.
And lordship over something else.
Right.
In a formal sense it would be, guess what, the government or the state.
Oh, yeah.
We can relate it directly to that.
In a formal sense.
So the word freedom would mean no state.
And what's the funniest thing is when you hear someone that works for the state asking for freedom.
You know, that's like someone that works at Ford Motor Company saying no more cars, let's go back to horses.
Anyway.
Yeah.
You see the insanity of this?
Well, freedom actually, I mean, if you want to relate it to a word, you can relate it to the word anarchy, actually,
instead of, you know, choice or something like that.
No, it's really a really good kin to the word anarchy.
And maybe you could give them the linguistic hints as to why that works.
Well, the, well, anodomity, you mean?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, boy.
Because anarchy sounds like, yeah.
Yeah, well, but anarchy is without.
And archos means a leader.
And what that leaves is a society that is very highly educated with a system of judges when a controversy arises.
And so each man, have you heard of the castle doctrine?
So each man would be the king of his castle kind of thing.
And in an anarchistic society, their crime is extremely low because people act very responsibly in public.
Like, give an example.
Emergency, like 911, people dial that for emergencies, right?
That's a fairly new thing.
That wasn't really common until I think after the 50s or 60s, right?
It was standardized.
Before that, it was like zero operator or something, right?
Okay.
Even into the 70s, and really, honestly, it didn't get codified in a national way in this country, I would say,
until the 90s, actually, where it was available everywhere.
It might have been in places like New York City or whatever.
But a lot of other places, you were still dialing zero and talking to an operator,
and you might say, connect me to the police, this kind of thing, all the way up to the 90s, I think.
Yeah, and by the way, yeah, there's a lot of interesting coincidences with that number, 911.
But what's interesting here, just to bring up the contrast.
No, it's serious, because when they did the dedication of those buildings that went down on that day,
that was also the day that they decided on 911 being the emergency number.
But anyway, it's kind of like one of those weird coincidences, right?
But what's interesting, I found out, is that in various Western societies, especially urban ones,
when there's an announcement that 911 is no longer going to respond, people tend to riot for no reason.
Does anyone remember the blackouts in New York in the 70s and such, and the riots that took place?
Just because the power went out, and it was known that the emergency number would no longer work,
and they call that anarchy. That is not anarchy. That is the opposite of anarchy.
There is no 911 emergency. There are no police in an anarchy situation.
There's no need for that.
This is chaos, which is not anarchy.
Everything is twisted. Everything is upside down.
But just the anodominy, that is something that was brought in much later, but the AN, all that is very interesting.
Here's another interesting point.
You can learn a lot about someone by how they speak and what they say.
If someone is asking for liberty, it is taken for granted that they are indentured, and they need relief from that indenture.
Like soldiers in the Navy, they're indentured.
Much like with the goddess religion, this is not something you were swept into without volunteering to do so.
You appease the goddess because you choose to.
You have actually signed yourself over.
This is a process, actually, in many ancient cultures that adhere to the ancient goddess religion.
You willingly become a servant of the goddess.
Well, that's basically the order of how it works.
You know, it's real interesting.
For example, if you're discussing something with an atheist,
a couple approached me and wanted to have a discussion.
They say, well, Greek, you say a law comes from your deity, but I don't have a deity, ha, ha, ha.
Well, I'm like, well, do you believe in the laws of the state and the scientific results as laws of physics?
And they're like, yes, I do.
I said, well, that's easy.
Then the state is your deity, and April 1st is your holiday.
Simple.
It's by default.
But what's interesting is if someone does a little bit of research, you know how they have little decrees before a baseball game,
or I think the stupid bowl is coming up, right?
Did I say that, stupid bowl?
But anyway.
I think you did.
How they do the anthem and they announce the teams and all that.
Back in the ancient days when they allegedly threw Christians to the lions,
if you go look at the decrees that were made at the Coliseum prior to that,
they would do a short little writ, and they'd speak it out before the games would start.
And they said they were throwing the atheists to the lions, meaning people that had no, yes, you got it, deity.
Very interesting because they were the followers of various groups created by Simon Magus, Simon the Magician.
Oh, boy.
So where do you start?
You see how massive this can be.
But going back to the liberty aspect, if you're asking for liberty, my answer might be,
according to the contract or the agreement that you've become indentured under, when did they grant you liberty?
It should be specified.
You get two weeks off pay.
You get liberty when sailors go into the – you get a week of liberty, and then you'd have to go back.
So if you're crying for liberty, like unconditional liberty,
you would have never been in that situation without the conditions.
There's no such thing as unconditional liberty because in order to be in the position that you're asking for liberty,
the conditions must have been set.
Otherwise, why would you agree to it?
So it's just crazy people all around.
Do you know what I mean?
Well, right, and of course the idea was thrown around because I'm watching every once in a while,
and I don't like to go to the chat room all the time,
but since people have taken the time to engage in the discussion and pay attention there,
I do want to every once in a while turn to them.
You had this discussion many times about coming to this planet.
Well, a little misunderstanding on somebody's part that you might be from another planet.
Unfortunately, we have to report.
This is not my world.
This has been said many times, and the world is society.
The best thing to say is I'm a visitor taking notes.
That is the only stance.
This is why.
Well, but hang on a second.
What I'm trying to say is that let's make it very clear that in a literal sense,
it's not as though you're from another planet.
You were born of a woman like the majority of us, I believe, have been on this planet as far as you know.
So you're unfortunately in your mind a human being.
So let's continue on with that and explain that whole concept of giving a report
because I think that would be extremely valid as well at this point.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
If objectivity is required, you know, like going back with the blind justice,
if the evidence needs to be looked at, how is she going to look at it if she's blindfolded?
Well, yeah, there's another hint for you.
Yeah, so the element of being objective,
you cannot know about something if you don't know the history of that thing.
And unfortunately, one of the things that's been obfuscated from the minds of people is their real history.
But fortunately, there was a radio announcer back in the 50s who stated that if you want to hide something from the American public,
put it in the public library, right?
So many of these things are really not far away.
Being objective is not that difficult.
And one of the ways to present the objectivity is through metaphor.
So very simply saying that I'm just visiting this planet, taking notes,
I think removes you from a lot of the things that people look as entitlement.
You know, I think we discussed about people don't question things that they worship, right?
Like if you have someone that walks into the room and says, I have a law degree from Harvard,
and you ask him some questions that he can't answer, he says, how dare you ask me that?
I'm a Harvard graduate.
You have to worship me for that, right?
So people tend to.
Yeah.
How many times have you heard people discuss things?
Well, this is a doctor.
This person went to here.
He's done this.
He's got 30 years experience in that.
Oh, OK, that's fine.
Could it be one year's experience, 30 times over?
Right.
So all of these things that people are.
Personally, I call it image training.
And image training can be good.
And image training can be bad.
Like, for example, if you're conveying in a motorized wagon, you come to an intersection and you see a red octagon at an intersection,
no matter what language it's written in, it's been accepted internationally that you're going to stop.
Right. Right.
It's a stop sign.
So certain things like that, like and then there's the badge.
Right.
You ever notice even on television or throughout reality, in many people's experiences, it's not done anymore.
Someone of authority would flash a badge.
Mm hmm.
Right.
So these are images.
These are things that people are trained to see and react a certain way when they see that image.
And also there's a type of imagery that's created in the mind through things that they hear.
You know, if someone is this guy's a doctor and graduated from here, what he's saying is correct.
And I think we just proved that by just being probably the first to say that we should eat seasonally if you want to avoid maladies that come from seasonal changes.
And where are these other DRs or MDs discussing this in the alternative I'm talking about?
So where, you know, the thing is to convey the information, but give a metaphor that maybe shocks the individual and to stop thinking,
trying to relate what we're saying with an ad hominem aspect and start relating just directly to the information being imparted.
Right.
So definitively, just to put a cap on it, you are from Earth.
Unfortunately.
Unfortunately, it's not a good place to be.
I mean, well, look, it's a beautiful place.
There's planets, I'm sure, that are that are much more beautiful, maybe not.
But there are definitely ones that are there are not.
I mean, you could look through a telescope and see the surface of other ones.
Yeah, it's a it's a wonderful place, naturally.
But the society, the idiotic society that mankind has on it is not worth much.
It's just taking up time.
I think we discussed how humanity is in the waiting room right now.
Well, that's the other thing, you know, over and over the mentioning of how time sort of stopped in reality at one point.
That was something that we discussed and we opened many shows, not every show,
but many shows with giving you the difference between what is the Pope's work schedule and another reasonable way of reckoning time.
Obviously, you talked about how do you know what is happening or anything at all?
If you don't know who you are, where you are and when you are, you know,
these are rather useful things to know when you're considering your conditions and choosing to change them.
So by setting yourself apart from it, in other words, if you're if you got a real high paying job working in the sewer,
are you going to show up skinny dipping and drinking the water?
Are you going to ask, where's the hazmat suit and the breathing tanks get this day over with?
So one is actually partaking and the other one is setting yourself apart.
There you go. So what what can one do to set themselves apart?
You know, in a very practical sort of bullet point sense, what would you what would you say to people to set themselves apart?
Wow, that's that's how can you tell anyone what to do?
Because from one perspective, it might be interrupting their pursuit of what makes them happy.
Mm hmm. Here's the point. Here's the funny part. Your Skype is now breaking up on us a bit.
OK, you know, but but but yeah, like I was saying, you know,
it is interesting, though, to try and give people a general sense of what could be applied to set themselves apart.
You did say at various times that, look, if you're going to adhere to every single thing that you're hearing on this program,
you're probably not going to be very popular among your family, friends or anywhere.
And because that will that might set you apart. What sets one apart is are you pursuing quality or quantity?
Are you are you pursuing the familiar or are you pursuing something that, again, is based on a higher quality?
What you hear a lot about is quantity. You very rarely hear quality being discussed.
So typically things of higher quality are set apart.
If you were to, let's say, go through a parking lot of large shopping mall,
you ever notice how a Ferrari just stands out where you don't notice any of the other cars.
Right. So that's set apart in its own way. But, you know, do you really want to stand out?
You see, but these this is setting yourself apart. You know, some some of the deities say that you shouldn't.
You know, for example, if you talk to some of the priests of some of the deities like justice.
Right. Well, I think we've established that justice is a deity.
Yes. If you talk to some of their priests that are known as law enforcement and attorneys, they tell you not to be set apart.
If you ever start discussing anything that they might see controversial,
what do they typically say is you have to be just like everybody else.
Isn't that interesting? I've heard that several times in passing from people in, quote, unquote, law enforcement.
I see what's going on here. And someone might say, well, I don't have a driver's license or such and such,
as you have to get one because everyone else has one to use the to use the driving sense.
Right. You know what? You are in violation.
You can be ticketed not just for breaking the numeric. Right.
The numeric speed limit. But here's another thing. If you're not going with the flow of traffic,
even if it is not, you know, going along with the particular numeric, you know, point for the speed limit.
If you're kind of not going with the flow, so to speak, that is another problem, too.
Even if you are well within the confines of the, you know, the quantifiable, if you are not going with the flow,
if you begin to stand out, this is another reason to be punished. But of course, this is this is under the justice system.
Correct. And the thing is, do you want to stick out again? Like I think I mentioned it.
You want to stand up for your rights. It's best not to stand up when they're fixing on busting people.
You should probably just sit down when they're fixing on doing that. Right.
So there's a there's a time and a place for everything that's been said since the ancient days. Right.
But you've got to people have to sort of I say they have to.
Well, they will eventually have wake up calls. Right.
And it won't be for a while because right now humanity is affected by these axial periods.
You know, these major events that change laws or, you know, I call it the Hegelian dialectic.
Such a problem reaction solution. This is not what I'm discussing.
I'm discussing that the basic objectivity of things around them and asking for the quality that they personally seek or within a group or within a nation or within the world.
Right now, it is a time of confusion. It's a time of dabble, as they say.
Right. And yeah, because it's the waiting room period.
It's quite interesting that when when you're asked those questions, it's kind of like I'd like to be asked those questions.
What does one do to set themselves apart? But the answer to that would be, if you're listening,
setting yourself apart comes from your operating system, your deity, your God.
Where do you get your law? All these things should be answered from where you your operating system is like, you know.
So, yeah, but it's interesting to hear it. And one part of me wants to say, well, it's not time yet.
People aren't really listening if you're asking that kind of a question.
But the second part is it's really and you cannot give a direct answer because it ties back to your where you get your law form.
You see. Right. And and we did cover that quite extensively.
That's for sure. During during the previous 17 and now this being the 18th episode.
But, you know, again, we're we're in that homestretch, so to speak, of the episode.
And it's just just about 25 minutes until 10 o'clock here on the East Coast.
Right. Of what was allegedly America at one point. You know, that's where I'm sitting.
Of course, you're sitting in a different place. But, hey, you know, we're not quite reckoning time correctly anyway.
It is as it is. And, of course, I always really have a need to tell people that they need to consider their actions, you know,
and they don't for the most part. Well, consider it.
Well, hold on. Consider your thoughts because they preclude the actions, I believe that, too.
And I think that's why the media is so powerful, because it takes control of the thought.
You see, which lead to the actions and this and this is the problem.
So, you know, I think to begin with, when one looks at what are the solutions,
what are the ways to handle, you know, your daily life in a more fit and proper fashion?
And once again, you know, we talked about that, too.
I mean, could you describe what you call fit and proper for people just to, you know, again, revisit?
Oh, sure. It's very simple. There's an aspect to it that to be fit and proper is based on the environment.
And I think we used to give the naval analogy.
The type of laws you have on a surface ship are different than the type of laws you have in a submarine because the environment is different.
You don't want to be walking around with a loaded armor piercing round in a submarine,
where you could be in a surface ship because it may not be as critical if the thing goes off.
Right now, the Earth environment is quite interesting.
There are things on Earth that are fit and proper. And again, it goes back to your deity.
There is a parallel society to mankind that is almost inescapable through memorialization, through the ages.
Even in Hollywood, they show you things called gods, don't they?
And I'm not necessarily an advocate for them, but I do have to communicate the point.
The point is that what is the Earth? Who are you? Where are you? When are you?
And all of this, how to operate, and that comes from your deity again.
And there are many analogies.
You know, it is, let's say, not fit and proper to play with matches with lots of gasoline around.
You know, that is a very basic one.
So, for example, one thing to do to figure out is, will it bring harm?
And if it will bring harm unnecessarily or not rightfully, is it fit and proper?
You know, if you ask someone who is living off the grid that has a taste for meat going hunting,
let's say for a deer or something, will that bring harm to the deer?
Yes. So you can eat. See, there are many levels to it.
And without being philosophical, for mankind, it comes from your god. Very simple.
That's why, for example, people that say they don't have a god are very much interested in what the state is doing.
And the state very clearly shows they have a patron god for you, don't they?
And this is not time yet to discuss this because this axial period has not come yet.
It's being, what I mean by an axial period is how many times have you, you know,
there are certain events that happen throughout man's history that any events that come after that are based on that event.
Like, for example, 9-11 was an axial period in the political world and in the social world.
How many times have you ever heard this is a post-9-11 world, right?
Oh, I commonly talk about the post-9-11 reality.
That is an axial period.
Go ahead.
No, it was an obvious point at which a particular event had a great deal of resonance.
It traveled, it rippled, you know, the ripple effect concept ever after.
I think that without, if you were to extract that event, we would have a wholly different trajectory to various aspects of what's observable on this planet,
not just the political and not the obvious, you know, war on terror and, you know,
the resounding change in the way people are handled domestically in this country, et cetera, et cetera.
But really, the psychology, in a literal sense, was changed worldwide.
Yeah, and the acceptance of the security industry because prior to that there was the info industry with the dot coms,
and prior to that was certain technologies in the 80s, you know, where it's amazing they have wireless technology.
Remember, prior to that, it was a semi-industrial and industrial revolution before that, right?
So now you have the security industry, and without 9-11, you couldn't have the boom of the security industry,
which I was made aware of, by the way, in the 90s, that there was going to be a boom in the security industry.
Very interesting.
Didn't make any sense back then.
But the reason I refer to the axial period is what's escaped people's minds,
maybe because it's never really been there,
is that there was a massive global axial period that happened about 2,500 years ago,
so around 500 B.C., really between 500 and 600 B.C.
There are events that happened in the world that have not been emphasized,
that have actually laid the ground even on how things are today,
and it was a precursor to things that happened in the first century.
That was another axial period in that part of the world that gradually spread to the rest of the world.
When I say the first century, that's when a lot of the major changes,
especially when Christianity came about, right?
So that was another axial period very close to that, and we haven't had any since.
9-11 would be probably the next one that would be on a global level.
There's going to be axial periods to come that are going to change mankind's thoughts
to the point where they are going to no longer think or seek things that they seek today,
even the day that we are speaking right now.
And these things are going to air back to things of old.
And this time period is coming, and we're not too far away.
We're looking this period is going to start in what they call the spring of 2018, roughly.
Roughly, yeah.
Yeah, that's why very often I'm like, it's not time yet.
It's not time yet.
What does he mean by that?
So there you go.
Yeah, and I even, again, coming from a different perspective,
would say that there is a great deal of change, which I can anticipate,
and I believe it will be, well, I would say it will begin in the winter of 2017
and maybe a lot of table setting before the meal is served.
But I think that that's when you'll be able to market, you know,
on that thing we call the Pope's work schedule.
And really quickly, why not tell people once again why I keep saying that's the Pope's work schedule,
just one more time.
It's very simple because that's what it is.
It's not a timepiece.
You can't keep time with it, folks.
It is the Pope's work schedule.
That's why you call it the work week, and that's why you call it the weekend.
You cannot reckon time with it.
Put aside all this crap about 365 and a quarter leap year days, whatever,
to go around the sun and Monday through Friday and all that stuff, that is a ruse.
There are 28.756915 whatever days in a lunar month.
It's all crap.
It's just junk.
It's a work schedule.
That's why, for example, for those of you that do that parody of human sacrifice known as birthday cake,
every year you'll notice it's a different day of the week.
It's not because the earth goes around the sun differently or anything like that.
It's because it's a work schedule.
It's totally arbitrary, and no one is paying attention.
Well, and here's another fascinating thing.
Talk about people not paying attention.
Built right into it in plain sight, you have an homage, if you will, to various deities.
Wait a minute.
I thought that if you have an homage to various deities in a collective place,
that could be considered a pagan construct.
Your calendar, in fact, is a pagan construct.
Well, why do I say that?
Take a look at what they call these days of the week.
All right.
Today is a Friday.
Well, that's shortened.
It's Friar's Day.
Saturday is what they will call it in a few hours, right?
That's actually Saturn Day, you know.
And the Sunday being Kyrios or the Lord Day.
And then Monday, Totten's Day, which Totten could be death in German.
And then Woden on Wednesday.
Woden, you know, he flies through the sky with staghorn creatures.
He knows who's good and bad, and you worship Woden by bowing down to a tree.
That's why trees are made of Woden.
Aren't trees made of Woden?
And then, of course, right after that you have Thor's Day.
Thor, yeah.
Another guy has got a big hammer.
And the way you worship Thor is by slaughtering a winged creature.
That's why what they call Thanksgiving has to be on a Thor's Day.
Thursday, yes.
Because don't they slaughter a winged creature?
It has nothing to do with cowboys and Indians or pilgrims and Indians or anything like that, folks.
You guys need to maybe look a little deeper.
Just a bit.
And I always encourage people to do that because if you don't know the meaning behind the things
that are actually part of your daily existence, and if you don't understand the words you're speaking,
sometimes, you know, I always loved that old axiom that people have, you know, changed over time.
But it is often better to allow people to believe that you are a fool as opposed to opening your mouth and proving it.
Well, now that works in a social way.
Sure, it does.
But I think that it's extremely relevant to mention to people that, you know,
it's not just other people that may be hearing the words you speak,
but sometimes through the words you speak, you are also garnering the attention, invoking, if you will,
the sentiments of all that can hear you.
And, hey, there may just be individuals who are not represented in a corporeal sense, if you will.
Let's throw something in there, Chuck, on that, which we haven't.
What's interesting, a little bit of study, and of course, you know,
these ancient primitive savages didn't know what they were writing about.
What's interesting, unless you're part of the family of the high command in the spiritual realm,
even though you are a spiritual being, which makes the weakest of the spiritual beings are much more powerful
than even an army of men, by the way, they cannot read minds.
The angelic beings don't know what you're thinking.
You have to write it or speak it.
That's why you speak it, in fact.
You know, notice, you could not simply think it, and therefore, I mean, you can transmit it, though.
We've been through that.
Yes, it can be secret.
Well, yeah, if you think it and don't speak it, they cannot read the mind.
It has to be written.
That's why, for example, some ancient texts, when someone was told to write something down,
he was writing it for a spiritual entity to see, not another man.
That's been misunderstood.
So what's interesting about this is that they can put thoughts into your mind,
but they can't extract them, so be careful.
And again, the reason why there is the pagan practice, which is still commonly utilized today,
of writing something on a piece of paper and then burning it.
Yeah, believe it or not, you write it so that it's now red, and the act of burning,
well, fire in and of itself has its own particular attraction when it comes to, well,
not only moths and people, for it is a useful thing.
I mean, it can keep you warm.
It can consume things that are undesirable and turn them into something more useful,
like the remnants thereof, which can be utilized for fertilizer, stuff like that, believe it or not.
Yes.
It goes back to the ether, fire chain.
And, you know, another thing is you can write something down and put it in water
and then drink the water.
So, you know, this is actually something you'll find in the Old Testament.
Yes, you will.
All of these practices are represented there.
And quite honestly, when you take a look, again, at the ritualization of various things,
I mean, anywhere from taking your communion, right,
when you sit there and take that piece of bread or whatever it is they stick on your tongue nowadays
and you take your sip of wine, you know, the blood in the body and all that,
that's one thing that one could look at.
And you say, well, obviously there's symbolism built into there and so on and so forth.
But, I mean, going back to the most common sort of cultural practice
that does not seem to have any sort of religious or, should I say, spiritual significance,
I mean, hey, people celebrate their birthdays with a birthday cake.
And one of the most remarkable things, as we approach the near end of this show,
is to go full circle right back to one of the first conversations I had with you
where consideration of the following three things, and I'll let you add on to it,
and then I guarantee you we'll run right out of time.
One of the first spiritual things that you and I discussed
that I thought was extremely worthy of consideration.
What do birthday cakes, you know where I'm going.
Cannibals, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
Now what the hell is he talking about?
Now he's gone over the edge. Birthday cakes, I mean, that's just a nothing.
Cannibals, birthdays, and dolls.
Cannibals, they couldn't have anything to do with eating a piece of frosted cake.
And dolls, they're toys you give them to kids.
And I was recently, just real quick, I want to add this one aspect,
and then I'm going to shut up and I want you to do it.
Real quick, I was on a primarily Christian roundtable discussion,
and they were talking about the intentionality and Satan
and all these different things, and I said, you know what,
I bet you that not a one of you has ever sat and considered
why the practice of giving a child a doll that very often resembles a child
has come into existence.
What does that mean?
Every single ritualized thing in your culture has its roots in something.
Has anybody ever considered what that's for?
The whole table, believe me, all these people who wanted to pray and discuss
and quote Bible verses went very quiet as I explained the following.
It is a practice which harkens back to after having sacrificed one of your children
when the other children in your family ask where that child has gone,
you give them this to comfort them to replace their sibling.
That is where that practice came from.
Or it's an effigy of a child.
Well, and there you go.
It would be an effigy of a child, but what I'm saying is to make it very relatable.
Yes, that's exactly the gesture that they're performing,
whether they know it or not, like it or not.
That's what it looks like.
If you're looking from another world, let's say.
And you know what?
I read in more than one place that ignorance of the law does not make you immune
to breaking that law, and it is written in a lot of places.
But anyway, I'll shut up now.
I want to make sure we cap this with birthday cakes, cannibals, and dolls.
And before we start, the spiritual realm, the beings there,
do love children more than even parents love their children.
It's kind of hard to imagine because the love of a parent is very high.
So even gesturing, sacrificing them is pretty nasty stuff.
So, okay, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
In the ancient Mesopotamian communities, they spoke a Chaldean Hebrew language,
which is similar, like saying Latin language in Europe, which covers many others.
But it was Chaldean.
And they were told to worship these lords or balls in that tongue.
And the priests of these balls or lords were known as the Qahans.
And the way they told people they would gain prosperity, so this was commercial,
is by bringing a child and having it sacrificed,
and everyone partook in some of the blood and some of the flesh of the child.
And that's why we call the eating of human flesh Qahanballism, or cannibalism for short,
which literally means a cannibal is a priest of the Lord.
And there are plenty of them in every neighborhood these days, by the way,
call themselves priests of the Lord.
Now what's interesting, as Chuck mentioned, when the family went home,
children said, where's my brother, where's my sister?
So the altar boys of these priests of the Lord would make these little effigies
or dolls to give to the children in the meantime.
So now you know the origin of why dolls were made to be given to children.
Okay.
And the interesting part is these guys were run out of town eventually
because they didn't really get prosperity from doing this, but it did satisfy these lords.
And they said, well, in order to stay around,
let's stop telling the people to kill their children and eat them,
because it became a little distasteful, not much,
because it was still readily accepted by Moloch worship.
So they told people to find the next child that would be in line,
place them in a high chair with a pointy hat like they wear and bake a loaf of sweet bread
and place lights and have the child blow the lights out, which symbolizes blowing the life out.
And to show that this does bring prosperity,
anyone attending the ceremony would bring presents for the child.
Now, what does that sound like?
So, yeah, so you've got the gesturing of human sacrifice, you know, being brought.
People will do anything if they think it brings them joy.
You know, people talk about love.
You've got to have love.
I'm like, what are you talking about love?
I mean, because you'll find a lot of love at the National Pedophile Convention.
Is that what you're talking about, love?
What kind of love are you talking about?
Yes, and believe it or not, we talk about pedophiles.
The reason why you say it that way is because a pedophile sounds more like somebody who likes feet.
Exactly, yeah.
It's pedo, not pedo.
Right.
Everyone says pedo.
So I don't know.
I still don't know.
I try to see what they're saying, but anyway.
Yeah, I understand.
But, again, I tell you, consider the words and the actions you take,
and we are just about out of time on the very last episode that we're going to do in this fashion.
So Ocelli and the Greek is just about over, but I do tell you,
you've got to keep tuned and keep a watch on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
because other information and forms of presentation will end up being there.
I just have no idea when, how, how many, nothing else like that.
Just like real life, it's going to unfold as it does.
Also, if you go to Ocelli.com, in my membership section,
the complete archive for the show 1 through 18 is not there yet,
but by the end of this week it will be there, as well as an extra episode,
which we recorded only for Ocelli.com.
But like I said, keep an eye on American Freedom Radio.
We're going to do this.
At some point there will be more Greek speak.
And, Greek, what's your final words?
Well, thank you for listening, everyone.
See you again.
I've done the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected.
I get unpaid taxes, and if I can't find the money, the IRS are going to take my tops.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine, and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction, and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs,
and that's to support American Freedom Radio.
Capisce?
So what are you going to do?
You're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom, freedom, American Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion,
and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States,
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years,
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts,
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367.
888-910-4367.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
We all know that they're not telling us the truth.
So stand up for your rights, demand the real medicine, and your right to use it and grow it.
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
What is the big deal about swearing to God in the first place?
Why does swearing to God mean you're going to tell the truth?
Wouldn't affect me.
If they said to me, you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth, so help me God,
I'd say, yeah!
I'll tell you about as much truth as the people who wrote that Bible.
How do you like that?
Huh? Huh?
Swearing to God is kid stuff.
Swearing to God doesn't mean anything.
Swearing on the Bible doesn't mean anything.
You know why?
Because Bible or no Bible, God or no God,
if it suits their purposes, people are going to lie in court.
The police do it all the time.
All the time.
Yes, they do.
It's part of their job to protect, to serve,
and to commit perjury whenever it supports the state's case.
Swearing on the Bible is just one more way of controlling people and keeping them in line,
and it's one more thing that holds us back as a species.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow,
friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.