American Freedom Radio presents the only broadcast information no other media outlet
would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocellus has entered the rink.
You may recognize it as, or the date or anything else, this is Ocelli and the Greek, a decidedly
different show which does air via our friends at American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Good evening.
How are you doing tonight, Greg?
Hey, Chuck, as good as can be, of course.
And just throw in for those that tend to go the organic route, it appears it might be
the 29th of the 8th month, or the 29th day of the 8th month, let's put it that way, from
noon to noon.
Just, you know, because the earthy, crunchy people think they're a more organic approach
instead of what's put out by the guy with the funny fish hat.
Right, and according to the Pope's work schedule, right as I speak it is the 25th day of October,
which is the 10th month, according to the Pope's work schedule, one more time, and in
other parts of the U.S. it would be the 24th day of that same alleged 10th month.
But again, that's the guy with the funny fish hat's schedule.
And I thought octo meant eight, like octopus or octagon.
Yeah, much like a stop sign, you know, that's an octagon, right?
I mean, that's what that's a representation of.
So that's an eight-sided figure, I think.
I don't know.
And well, yeah, and so everyone's, you know, when you take a multiple-choice question-answer
test, they give you four possible answers and, you know, you either do your homework
or you guess.
But you notice that four months out of the year they actually tell you what month it
is pretty close, you know, like octo meaning eight, nova meaning nine, dessa meaning ten,
and let's not forget septem meaning seven.
And no one's guessing, no one's doing any homework.
Can we say everybody's failing?
Well, I don't know.
I don't believe in grading because grading is very degrading.
But if you're that degraded that you haven't noticed what the hell's going on with even
time yet, I don't know what to say at this point.
But anyway, let's carry on.
That's what we'll say.
Hey, and eventually when we get into that 12th month, according to the Pope's work schedule,
that would be desi, deca, whatever, December.
That should be the 10th month, according to its name.
Absolutely.
A little confusing, isn't it?
Yeah.
And it comes out, you ever heard of that game Simon Says, right?
Ah, yes.
Yeah.
And he was the father of what we call, historians define the era that we're living in, which
is the Christian era.
So yeah, these things cross over, man.
It's remarkable.
Look, you know, you just landed here, you know, or I just landed here, anyone just comes
to this planet.
I mean, it takes like 15 minutes to figure it out.
Maybe a day or two tops.
And it's interesting when you listen to people speak on, you know, what's called the alternative
radio or the, you know, whatever communication is going on mainstream or such.
And you constantly hear, now more than ever, how do we fix it?
What's going on?
Why are there so many problems?
I mean, it takes like a day max to figure it out.
Just look around and see, are things the way they're supposed to be?
Are things the way that people say they should be?
Absolutely not.
Just put things in order.
If September means seven, why don't you number it as such?
I mean, you got to start somewhere, you know, I call it, people have been what's called
dummy loaded.
And just to, let me just define that real quick.
It's an engineering term for electrical engineering.
When you design a really large system with a lot of current going through it, they notice
all these anomalies that, you know, arcing and sparking, things get hot, you know, things
blow up.
So they decided to put hookup motors in the system that absolutely just spinning and doing
nothing to soak up that extra current that comes through the lines that they can't define
using their ridiculous Einsteinian physics.
So, or resistors on large motors, because they used to pull the switch and they didn't want
to shut off.
So they dummy load them.
They put devices in there that just soak up the energy to prevent an explosion.
So the society has been dummy loaded, you know, with the world's religions, all of them,
the science you see, the obsession with these secret societies, you know, you hear a lot
of people trying to explain to us Freemasonry and the Illuminati symbolism and all that,
you know, more dummy loading.
And then you have the UFO community, you know, more dummy loading.
And when I say this, it sounds like, well, Greek, you know, you're making this general
statement, you know, well, generally, yes, you know, 99% of those things that I mentioned
are dummy loads on society, sucking the energy out only to keep the circuit going so it doesn't
blow up.
And, you know, oh, right.
Much like the interesting observation, at least it's interesting to me for some reason.
You know, the fact is that there are such secret societies, then how is it you know
about them?
I always ask that question to people that want to take a great deal of my time up, breaking
them down and dissecting every single aspect of them.
If they're so extremely secret, then how is it that you're even discussing this with me
unless you are part of that society?
And that upsets people.
Yeah, well, here's a you want to know a really big secret?
Go ahead. A really big secret in nature.
Cold rises and heat goes down, folks.
That's that's a really don't tell anyone.
By the way, that's an odd concept, because we've always been taught that heat rises,
you know. Yeah, well, in art, in systems that produce heat and cold with chemical
decomposition, you know, when you burn wood or you use the type of electricity we're
using to make cold or, you know, music moving free on through pipes for air
conditioning, that'll make a cold because all that's based on chemical decomposition.
Whenever this is breaking down or going towards the death cycle, the heat rises and
the cold goes down.
But the biggest secret that we shouldn't really discuss because is that in nature,
cold rises and heat descends, just like you should have a cool head and warm feet.
And that's that's that's like the biggest secret.
Why? Because everyone's got access to it and no one is paying any attention.
How do I know no one's paying any attention to that?
I don't hear people demanding that engineers develop devices that make an ascending
cold in a descending heat, have you?
So people are quite happy with a hot head and cold feet, aren't they?
Apparently. And the odd thing there is that it used to be explained to me that the
molecules of air expand when they are heated.
So what happens is there's less of them.
And because they're less heavy, they rise, you know, sort of like why does wood float
on water almost?
You know, one of these kinds of concepts.
And I say to myself, well, yeah, that makes a bit of sense.
But if it doesn't work, but it doesn't work, you know, it's well, if you hit the
molecule, what kind of heater are you using?
You know, they're probably doing it in a lab.
You have a quackademic, you know, in there.
And yeah, it's there's two sides to it, you see.
And they're they're focusing on the the dead side.
And that's the that's part of the dummy load, you know, to suck away the energy.
You know, let's talk about, you know, how corrupt the government is.
Well, you do have a representative government, people, all of you.
Sorry. You know what that means.
If the government's corrupt, guess who else is the masses?
Well, yeah, I mean, that's been one of the most startling statements recently being
heard by some people for the very first time is that, quite honestly, people have
actually gotten what it is they've asked for their own ill-conceived actions
lead to that representation, the alleged larger, you know, the higher part of the
pyramid or whatever.
But hey, let's not get too straight into that odd symbolism, because that's just
another pointless discussion.
I got to tell you, I put out on social media that we were doing Episode four
tonight and I put into the graphic the
phrase God is dead and a question mark.
And you know what? I expected a lot more of a reaction.
Meaning, did you get any reaction?
I got nothing from the general public, to be honest with you.
It's exactly what one should predict, because the term God is erroneous in the first
place. So you can't say God is dead as a definitive
point, because there is no such thing as God in a singular form.
It is plural.
Right. Hence the question mark.
You see, that's why I did that.
But I expected the usual sort of defensive, offended
posture that generally comes out of your more fundamentalist style
Christians that, well, at least that's how most people describe them, you know,
and or any group or any group that believes that there is a singular
God which is in charge of every single thing.
And there is no other divinity besides the one that they
don't even know the name of, nor do they know the nature of, nor
do they have any real knowledge of the scripture of, regardless of the fact
that they identify themselves as being a, well, a subject
to this said one singular God.
Right. And since that
concept of singularity is not found, their allegiance is basically
to something that doesn't even exist.
So think about that, how twisted it could be.
But in reality, we can say
we tend to not want to look at things that have come before us.
The reality of it is most people are functioning.
They may not say it, but they're functioning as if everything sprang
into existence about a century ago.
Why? Because they don't go further back than that in their knowledge base.
So what do you do with that?
Well, you know, first thing it beckons is we've got to go a little further back.
We've got to go maybe like two or three centuries.
Right. Maybe a little further.
Maybe four centuries, maybe five, maybe six, maybe ten, maybe.
OK, it's not that hard. Right.
And when we start looking further back, we find
there's tremendous mention of the gods in literature,
in culture, in custom, in architecture.
And now there isn't, you know, look at the ancient temples
made of stone with facades and depictions of these anthropomorphic
beings called gods, let's say.
And today, look at the major structures are just sleek glass towers.
What happened? Right.
They are actually absolutely absent of any divinity.
And what's fascinating there is, you know, the temples were not
the only places that were adorned with the depictions of the gods.
Seemingly everything actually had,
you know, a ceiling, a mosaic, a carving, a statue,
et cetera, et cetera.
I mean, when you examine all these ancient cultures, actually,
the representation of the gods seem to be everywhere in one form or another.
And nowadays, as you very, very succinctly
point out, we have modern structures
that are devoid of any of these representations.
Truly. And here we go with a odd statement,
but truly like a godless representation in the architecture,
which is a great deal more temporary
than the older, you know,
allegedly less technologically advanced structures
that we see in in ancient history. Right.
Yeah. And they're made of glass and glass is a silicate based,
which most glasses basically melted sand.
So there are towers made of sand. Mm hmm.
And anybody who's built a sandcastle on a beach knows about how far that goes.
Right. Right. And this from the spiritual point of view,
they are made of sand.
And from an engineering point of view, they are made from sand.
You could research how glass is made.
And there's hundreds of trucks loaded with sand
delivering sand to large glass factories.
Where? Yeah. Yeah.
So it's an interesting concept, just as it's not unusual
if someone is traveling on the earth and goes through these
quote unquote areas where they're building houses for people.
If you look at them going up or being built,
especially after the frame is put up there, it looks like sawdust.
They're building their houses out of compressed sawdust. Mm hmm.
Right. This is like a board particle board, which, you know, truthfully,
although a lot of people have to utilize it in their furniture
because it's what's affordable.
But the truth is that the the valuable
and attractive furniture, the furniture that one would have
if price were no object doesn't contain this pressboard nonsense
because we all know it's temporary.
We all know that a simple injury to it causes it to crumble and fall apart.
Exposure to elements of any kind.
I mean, from moisture or, you know, greater temperature, whatever.
All of these things are extremely corrosive,
to use a phrase, to anything that's built of this crap.
And meanwhile, all of our modern structures, you know,
these great achievements allegedly in our architecture nowadays
are actually constructed.
I mean, we think about them in a grandiose fashion regarding,
you know, steel frames and everything else.
But the reality is that the majority of the building
that is meant to stand is air.
And then when you subtract away all of the other flimsy materials,
including the glass,
the steel frame really doesn't even get to stand all that long.
And meanwhile, we look at structures that are thousands of years old,
made of stone and mud, you know.
Yeah. Or or just yeah, that's part of the
what I'm trying to allude here as is a metaphor.
For when you consider that the from a universal level,
there's perfect harmony.
And when you look at a galaxy in a photograph,
let's say a real telescope, not a one that's provided to you,
let's say by NASA or whatever, if you ever get a chance to see it,
you're for yourself or a cell under a microscope.
You see there's a harmony for these things to exist.
So right now it's easy to perceive that mankind with this furniture
made of sawdust and towers made of sand.
They have a life, a very short lifespan, right?
They're they're made that way
because there's no reason to make them last a long time
because that is part of the universal harmony where a thousand years ago,
they built things to last a thousand years, a hundred years ago.
They made them to last a hundred years.
And now they're making things to last a better part of a decade, if not two.
And this is not because we're sloppy or not paying attention.
It's because it's part of the universal harmony.
These things will not be here or there's no reason for it to be,
to have longevity built into it.
You see, and this is the part that people lack paying attention.
But there's this two week myopic view of the universe right now.
You know, what is trending, you know, in the alternative media or mainstream?
What's in the news?
And they and they're not paying attention to what is actually being manifested.
You know, and again, the is the topic of the gods.
Yes, plural is a very large one.
But again, we have a society on this planet.
That has been dummy loaded big time with distractions, science,
religion, secret societies, UFOs,
you know, beliefs, movements, trends.
Those are all dummy loads. Very simple
to to discern how they're, you know,
they're spinning their wheels and they and they have to be dummy loaded.
You know, they have to be worn out so they can go to sleep.
It's a it's a very interesting thing that in the future,
when people start to look in the near future, I should say,
when they start to look to see that there is a little bit more history
and there's a little bit more that can be discerned from that,
they will discover a plurality
beyond this material.
Existence that they're locked into right now.
What I mean by plurality, meaning that there is another society
that is a non material, non corporeal, and and it affects
part of the plurality is that that group affects the material world
and it will become more overt in the future in plural form.
And, you know, part of what we wanted to discuss
was perhaps bringing people up to speed in a nutshell,
as one can do sonically on what we call radio.
Just a brief overview of the history of these things.
But at the same time, you have to address the dummy load, the distraction.
Right. So that's what makes it so difficult to discuss this.
But if we were to end the show right now,
we'd have to say there there is no such thing as God.
It's it's gods and there is a society of them.
And the chief god, the head god,
what makes him the head god is that he is not subject to death.
All the others are.
And it's as simple as that.
And and actually the highest quality document to review
this is the biblical text, but not the King James, of course,
because, you know, there's no Sunday or Monday and there's no. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It's pretty bizarre document, by the way.
But you have to realize
the the level of mentality that people blindly follow
these things as icons.
They know nothing about what they're doing at this point still
on within their little groups, whatever whatever part of the world
they are, whatever religion or science or group they think there are secret or not.
They don't know much about what they're doing.
And that's what makes it scary.
You see.
Well, the other thing is that it's seemingly an insurmountable subject
when one begins to look for the proof and the details, because after all,
it would actually not be something that we could possibly
even remotely compress into a two hour presentation.
It seems as though we're starting off slow here tonight,
but there is a reason for it to try and simply relate to you a,
you know, a an accounting of what there is to be understood
regarding this is impossible in a short presentation.
Yes. You know, you presented to me earlier today before we went on air
a list of, well, 500,
500 gods that are noted that have died now.
Right. Somebody says, well, gee, you know, that's just a misunderstanding.
That is the superstitions of primitive peoples that you're talking about.
But no, it's actually not based on the superstitions.
It has something to do with a lot of things that are a whole lot more secular
than the superstitious tribal beliefs of individuals, doesn't it?
Oh, absolutely. You know, when we say secular, it would be, you know,
walk down the street, go to a university, pick up a textbook.
You know, these guys are self-professed atheists. Right.
So, you know, we're not going into a building where they're telling you
to bow down to a tree with Santa Claus and the Easter bunny. Right.
These are people that, you know, and they still do this, by the way.
The, you know, atheists partake in those holidays, which is unusual.
It shows you how crazy this world is.
But so they have, in short,
secular historians have cataloged over 3000 spiritual entities by name.
Right. And over 2000 of those spiritual entities were classified as gods.
Meaning of of of a certain power where they can actually communicate
and impart to man, where the other ones were more like elementals.
Elemental meaning like certain aboriginal people, meaning first people.
According to history, let's say the in the Americas,
they found totem, what they call totems or totem poles.
Right. For certain elemental deities.
And that would be within that 3000.
But the 2000 plus were classified as gods.
And this is by non-religious historians.
Right. By going through records and memorializations.
And then there are many events through history where, for example,
people navigating what's called the Great Sea in ancient texts,
which would be the Mediterranean
reporting events and hearing voices and captains being summoned to the deck
because this particular god was going to be killed tonight.
And a spectacle was to be seen.
And these things were recorded by testimony in, quote unquote,
government records of the day now.
And it was seen by many.
So, you know, we could start discussing the ancient society in there.
And you can't discuss any ancient society
without bringing up the customs and culture and the religions
that they had, quote unquote, religion, meaning something you do regularly,
which is acknowledging these gods. Right.
Like people say, you know, I'm very religious
because I like to comb the hair and brush the teeth and tie the shoelaces.
Often you see.
So religion just means something you do on a regular basis.
Why? Because your law comes from your deity, from your god.
And it's not traffic law or tax law.
It's how you operate your how you construct your life.
You know, what do you eat? What do you wear?
How you do business, how you raise a family, how you keep time.
All that comes from your deity.
Now, in fairness, though, some people behave
as if their deity is the government or the legal society.
They behave as if that in and of itself is their deity.
So therefore, their lives are governed by their religious practices
that have to do with adhering to the edicts handed down by that deity.
Correct. You know, and that's what they're doing.
Yeah. If you had to just spend 15 minutes or a day on this planet
and give a good report on what's going on here, pretty much you can very,
very objectively say it's I mean, it's obvious that the world right now
is under what's called it's ruled, it's ruled, it's rules and laws
come from the ancient goddess religion personified
through iconography and statuary
as the goddess of justice
throughout the whole world.
You know, let's go to that bastion of infinite knowledge, Wikipedia.
Right. OK.
It's fantastic. Yeah.
And put in and put in justice and scroll down and they will show you all the statues
of dozens and dozens of countries.
I mean, Iran has one.
Russia has one.
Every country right now has a goddess statue personifying law.
Very simple. So this planet right now is under the goddess religion
and very simple, you know, and this has also been discussed
in the the biblical text and others.
There's a a malicious or malevolent female entity that will conquer
the spiritual side or the mind of man during a certain era.
And it's not she's malicious or malevolent because she's female.
It's just a malicious or malevolent entity.
And it happens to be female.
Right. Just like if you were held up, someone pulled a gun on you
with a ski mask on the way to the shops and you know, you didn't know,
you know, you give me your wallet and you do, otherwise I'll kill you.
And then later on, you apprehend them and pull the mask off.
And it's a woman.
And if you tell people, well, this woman pulled a gun on me,
does that make you anti-feminine?
No, it just so happens they're a woman.
You see, you see, this is the problem with discussing these things with a with a
when you have a carnal minded
society or someone that you're trying to express these this information to,
because carnally minded meaning, oh, if if, you know, male bad thing,
all males are bad, you know, female did a bad thing.
So all females are bad, very, you know, base is there's no, you know, it's it's
the way it's very difficult to discuss these things because the way people hear it
is, well, the apple is red.
Oh, the car is red. So the car is an apple.
You know, they're they're associated with the car.
So the justifications are very, very base.
Again, that's why society has been it's very easy to dummy load it
with all the religions that you see, not some of the religions,
all of the religions right now, all of the science that you see,
the secret societies that you see is a dummy load
and all the UFO stuff that's being discussed is a major dummy load.
Right. And here's and here's, you know, and quite intentionally,
am I being a bit sarcastic when I say the justification for this
is that you can very easily
manipulate a population by giving it such broad strokes to work with.
I mean, it is very loose association by which all things seem to be driven.
After all, the adherence to the scripture as it stands
is from the king and therefore a whole lot of the laws
which also govern people's behavior and their religiosity in truth
also comes from some king in the past.
You know, they're adhering to this as opposed to following.
They're they're they're really truthfully idolaters in a way,
because they're following the laws given to them by someone
that is not a god directly.
And they haven't gone to the source on any of this, have they?
No, not at all.
And that's another thing that define we can do this in short.
You know, there are three bloodlines on this planet.
One is discussed.
The other two are not.
I mean, the other two or one is completely known.
Let's say the other one is discussed and the third one
is completely not discussed and not known.
And this comes from the biblical text.
Very simply, have you ever heard it?
I'll use the colloquial term first.
And the sons of God took the daughters of men
and they became the giants.
Right. This is in Genesis.
Totally erroneous.
That is not what it says at all in the text.
And there's actually big movements on that.
What it actually states, if you actually did a translation,
it would be the sons of Elohim or the sons of God's plural,
let's say, took the daughters of Adam.
And then came the Nephilim, which Nephilim etymologically means
the the many breathing or the Nefesh, meaning soul
or a new type of breathing creature. Right.
The word giants is not in the Bible or the biblical text.
It's Nephilim.
It became giants when they did
the Greek translation of the Old Testament.
They put in gigante instead of Nephilim,
where you get giant from only there as.
Yeah, because they became, let's say,
colored with and fascinated with all of these Nephilim being very large.
And by description, if you go to the Book of Kings gives you,
you know, how tall they were and how large their weaponry
or how large the beds that they slept in.
So they so they went back and revised it and used the Greek word gigante.
But the word gigante is not in the text.
So let's go back.
It's not the daughters of men.
It's the daughters of Adam.
So it's a specific bloodline, you see.
And the sons of gods are very simply understood.
If you actually look at the context as a whole, these are beings.
In other words, the gods do reproduce.
Right. And these they're not you hear in a lot of the the culture
and alternative, it's the fallen angels.
Right. That took.
No, it's not fallen angels.
So that is completely the angels cannot intermix with man.
But the sons of gods or the gods can.
Angels are different species.
And then we have cherubim.
You see, there's so many different species in that world.
It's kind of it's kind of like we visited earth and came back and said,
yeah, I saw a dog and I saw a man and a woman.
And that's all there was on earth. Are you kidding?
You're you've left out, you know, a million other groups of creatures here.
Right. Mm hmm.
So anyway, from that perspective,
the sons of gods is a whole other discussion
and a whole other field of study,
which I assure you is not being addressed at all.
At all. And and they are here
and just throw in something.
This is just for curiosity's sake.
Maybe we can continue or not.
If you read the text, it says that one day is a thousand years
and a thousand days is is is a well date
for them is a thousand years for us and a thousand years for us is a day for them.
So they have a very long lifespan, a very long lifespan.
So if you are one of these sons of gods
and you lived in, let's say, in a city or a town
and you appeared as like a middle aged man
a hundred years go by, you haven't aged a day and everyone's starting to wonder,
why isn't this guy aging?
You know, you're going to problem on your hands.
You've got to move to another town and reintroduce yourself, you see.
Right. Very interesting concept.
And if you actually look into some folklore in history,
there's a strange people that move from place to place and never seem to age.
Hmm. But let's you know, but, you know, we can't discuss that
from the text that's been memorialized because, you know,
greys and reptilians and fallen angels and evolution
and the bunny Easter Bunny and Santa Claus.
You see, those are all the dummy loads that are put on looking in this direction.
And you know what I find interesting right there, though,
just in the statements you were just making, is that the introduction
of the concept of calling a race of individuals giants
when they were really a separate race
that happened, that happened to wind up being larger.
They weren't simply giants by race.
But, you know, if all of a sudden we were having human children
that tended to grow to be eight feet tall,
they would be giants in the literal sense.
But they would still be humans by race.
They would still be classified as human beings.
They would just happen to be larger.
Well, they're a mix.
And another another characteristic is the technical term is polydactyl.
They got six fingers and six toes on each hand and each foot.
And there's many.
So that that that's what we call a heretic.
I don't like to use the word genetic, but hereditary trait.
And every year there are many people born
with six fingers and six toes and they're surgically removed,
you know, so they could blend in, you know.
So there is evidence of that particular bloodline.
And the giants and that group called the Nephilim are actually the hybrid
of the sons of God and the line of Adam.
When you look at, for example, the creation,
see the creation story.
Both the creationists and the evolutionists are wrong.
They're both wrong.
Because if you look at the the actual text, it's a remaking.
It's a remodel.
It's not it's not an initial.
There's very little information about the initial creation.
All of the the creation that is taking place
in the text is a remodel or a remaking.
So it's just fascinating when you can look at it
and then find in secular science, you know, that the evidence supports it.
You know, when you look at things like the flood and
their support in secular science.
Right. And when it happened also.
And there's also secular support that there was a solar system
wide destruction about 13000 years ago in the solar system,
which is where the remaking started in the book of Genesis, for example.
Right. Because there's a each the six days of creation,
each one represents a thousand year period.
And you see, Adam came on the sixth day and that was about 6000 years ago.
So at 13000 years ago, roughly would be the biological,
the biblical timeline for a massive solar system wide catastrophe,
which is explained in great detail in Genesis, verse two and one verse.
But which, of course, you know,
you start discussing the text, you lose the majority of the people.
But the concept here is to just give the concept.
Well, right. And what is missing from the text or from people's interpretations?
I always again, this is one of my childish
viewpoints about it is that, OK,
we say that the earth was created.
We say that, you know, the heavens were created.
We say that all these things on the earth were created, et cetera, et cetera.
Where in there is the space to put these things created?
You know, well, that's that's beyond that's information
that's beyond the information that we have in the ancient texts at this point.
And and from I hate to give personal opinion, but I'll give it just
very seldom I do this is because we just simply lack the maturity
to go to that point.
I call that the space between the space because there's only one dimension
and that space and then everything is within that space.
And, you know, you've heard this is a three dimensional world.
And here's the fourth dimension, the fifth dimension,
that those are just coordinates in space that were developed by engineers
to communicate in drawings, you know, top view, side view, front view,
3D drawing. Right.
That's it has nothing to do with the physical reality.
It's just simply communication.
And just as time is simply a communication.
And the thing and the thing about humanity
as a whole, understanding these things has to grasp
a has a very has to have a very firm grasp on these basic tools
on what space is, what matter is and what time is
to be able to approach what's been memorialized.
Now, if you think these old texts that were memorialized
and we still have them preserved to this day
lack validity because they were ignorant and primitive back then,
then you should leave it alone. Don't waste your time.
That's why I never suggest anyone go and read them,
because you won't understand anything in there
unless you understand space, matter and time
in the perspective preserved in the text, you know.
And that's why I think tonight I heard someone say, well,
this is a different society now.
You know, we live in a different society now from 200 years ago.
Let's say I think the topic was the founding fathers of the US,
which I don't like using that term.
But, you know, the early birth of the country, let's say.
And someone said that we live in a different society.
Actually, you're not in different society.
A more accurate term is that you are descendants of that society.
There's no quantum jump where they were there 200 years ago.
Let's say. And all of a sudden you appeared out of nowhere.
Now you see there's a lineage and people have been ignoring these lineages.
Most people can't go back more than a century in their family tree
where the ancients were able to go back more than several centuries.
It was very common to go back a thousand years or two thousand years.
And now they can't because they've been cut off
and not only cut off from who they are, who they come from,
but they're cut off from the information as well.
And there's going to be a revival in what the topic that we're all these
various topics within the topic of the show and coming in the next few years.
I assure you that.
But it's going to seem to just come out of nowhere and blossom.
It has to.
Right, well, and the other the other interesting thing that occurs to me
as you're discussing this is I say to myself, because of the limitations,
however, you want to classify those limitations,
but because of the limitations of mankind in general,
there is always the argument that we have simply not been given
the knowledge because we cannot receive it.
So therefore, in my mind,
there could be a great deal more to the saga of the gods
that not a single one of us on this rock will ever have access to because we are
in such a limited state.
In other words, for instance, the idea that there is one Supreme God.
There actually may be many more.
I mean, we are not necessarily privy to the entire collection of gods.
I mean, there could be a thousand of them.
Right. But to have the right, let's say,
to go there, you have to have already have a pretty good handle on what you've got.
You see, it's these things are not gotten through the imagination or through osmosis.
A lot of people think that if they, let's say, get a physics textbook,
that's three inches thick, if they put it under their pillow,
they'll get all the information from Osmo.
It doesn't you know,
where you might read one page and think you've got the whole thing requires
study, and a lot of people say they don't have time to do that or don't want to.
So that's where you step back and say, well,
if you can succinctly compress the information and hand it over to those
that are interested, might as well do it.
And I'd like to go to time for a moment
because it ties in with the concept of you cannot understand
memorialized information about, quote unquote,
the gods if you don't understand space, matter and time.
And how many times have you heard about time travel?
Right. All this stuff.
And when that, by the way,
when that first started hitting society,
Western society around turn of the 20th century,
that was because of people like J.J.
Thompson and Alexanderson and Nikola Tesla,
who were playing around with electric circuits and figuring out how to actually
stop the phasing delays because delay has to do with time.
And it was described as, wow, now we can control time.
Yes, on an electrical level.
But, you know, if you're just learning how to do this technology,
you can actually manifest other things as well.
But that's when the Jules Verne and all the other
fiction, which is always based on something going on in society,
you know, like when it's a fashion thing to talk about time travel,
it's fashionable, just like when Franklin started procuring lightning rods.
Right. You know, with experiment with the kite
and the key and people in France love the idea of a lightning rod.
And they were putting little lightning rods on their hats in the early eighteen
hundreds, you know, because it was fashionable.
Just like you hear about time travel now.
It's very fashionable.
And one thing about dealing with a society
that has a strong dummy load on it is that they're very susceptible to suggestion.
Meaning advertising and buy this, you know,
you see, it's a very commercial attribute.
But again, to go back to time with time travel, I'll make a statement.
You know, a helicopter is a time machine.
Well, how can it be so common?
And I thought time machines were uncommon.
Well, here's the example.
And it works no matter how you want to look at it.
Let's let's give the example that we're
in a big city and there's a parade that's going to last four hours.
OK, so that means that it takes four hours
from the front of the parade to the back of the parade to pass us.
And we're standing on the street.
And I say to you, Chuck, you know, or someone asks me,
I wonder what the last float will look like.
And, you know, everyone says, well, that's three and a half hours away.
OK, well, I say, OK, hold on a second.
So I have what they call a cell phone and I have an acquaintance up in a helicopter.
He's about a mile up.
And when I call him up and I asked him, can you see the helicopter?
And he said, I mean, can you see the parade person in the helicopter?
Right. And they said, yeah, I could look down.
I see the front of the parade and the back of parade all in one view.
And I ask him, what is the last float?
And he says, it's a green pig with wings.
I say, thanks a lot.
So I hang up and I tell you guys in three
and a half hours, you're going to see a green pig with wings.
Oh, I don't believe it. Oh, no, that's not.
I don't believe it. Maybe that's your opinion.
Whatever. Whatever. OK.
Three and a half hours.
What do you see? A green pig with wings.
Now.
All that happened here was getting
information from a high vantage point where they can actually see the entire
event from beginning to end, where if you're on the ground,
you have to actually wait for the time to transpire.
You see, that's all it is.
When you hear things about prophecies, right, that's all it is.
It is the event being seen from a high
vantage point, not in our material space.
And the funniest thing is, you know,
the lack of definition.
Some people say, well, yes, I understand the prophecies.
They don't look good, but we have to change them.
I'm like, well, if they can be changed, they're not prophecy.
Right.
Then it's just then it's just a suggestion that if you don't change it, this will
happen, and that is also an ancient text, like, for example, the story of Jonah.
Or who got swallowed by the big fish,
he was supposed to go and give a society of the Assyrians, let's say,
Nineveh, a message, and if he didn't, they'd be destroyed.
And he says, no, I don't want to go.
But no matter what happened, he was still sent.
He gave the message and they did it.
And you see, so it's very interesting how there is no definition.
There is no real handle on the reality of these elements, space, matter and time.
And it's very, very simple.
And you know how you gauge it very simply,
you know, walk to someone on the street and say, what day is it today?
And if they say anything between Monday, Friday or January through December
and you bring up, well, wait a second, this is a work schedule.
You know, it could be packaged in a way where you can give the information
in a minute and say, hey, you know, when you have a birthday every year,
it's a different day of the week. Well, who makes that stuff up?
You know, something like that.
And a lot of them go into cognitive dissonance.
If they can't get if they can't realize they're running on someone's private work
schedule that's made up every year based on nothing physical.
How are they going to go and start contemplating?
Let's say knowledge or information memorialized from the gods.
It's not going to happen.
This is true.
You know, one thing that occurs to me, though,
when you were using the example of the helicopter, quite honestly,
is that that is a change in space.
You're receiving information from a different perspective.
Yes. Created by.
But isn't that a little bit of a confusion there?
Because time and space are not the same thing.
You can know something that someone can't capture from a vantage point.
I mean, isn't that a bit confusing?
Not really here.
Let's define it very simply based on looking
at things that were written on more than 100 years ago.
Time is simply the recordation of events, just like it's just a form of communication.
And just like if you're on a construction
site and someone says, you know, cut that board 16 inches long.
Well, you are operating in the English measurement,
where if you're in Europe, it would be 40 centimeters or something.
Right.
Because you've agreed to use that measurement.
Right. Right now, everyone has agreed to use
the wind up toy known as the clock and the Pope's work schedule.
So it works to a certain point, but it works within the construct that you
all agree to, but it has nothing to do with nature.
Right. So if you see a tree, for example,
in the southwest of the U.S., there is not an indigenous tree.
It's called the China Berry tree.
And every year, exactly on the 23rd day of the seventh month,
the leaves start turning yellow and it drops the small nuts, you know,
that berries that it has every year, 10 years in a row.
But if you use the Pope's work schedule,
you could be office two weeks, five days, 10 days, three weeks every year.
It just shifts around because that work
schedule has absolutely nothing to do with anything in nature.
So now you're using a reference point that is disconnected from the entire
lateral environment around you.
How many times you ever heard people say we have to get back to nature?
Right. That's one of our problems.
Now, for example, if you look at the English
measurement system that was originally based on cubits and hands,
which is off of the anthropological body. Right.
You know, a hand was around six inches,
a cubit was around 18, which was the average length of a grown man's right.
OK, so even then, when the origin of these systems was sort
of based on something organic or biological, you see.
So so all it is now, basically, with time, space and matter,
is when you're discussing this consistently, that everyone agrees this is how
we're going to communicate.
The suggestion is that it should be based on something real.
Versus completely debased,
where it comes out of like some hidden place that no one knows.
Like you remember, let's say growing up when before the electronic conventions,
I remember growing up where the parents or adults said we have
to go to the hardware store and get a calendar because it's the end of the year.
So we know what day, you know, a month it's going to be next year.
They need that piece of paper right now.
They're just now they're using electronic conventions for it.
Right. Right.
Yeah. So it's the convention.
Is the convention that you're using based
in something in the natural world or is it debased and fiat?
So so let's stop for a second.
I think we mentioned this on the first episode.
Is the money based on anything or is it fiat?
It's fiat. Right.
Right. Is is the legal system based on anything or is it fiat?
It's fiat.
Right.
Are the religions based on anything or is it fiat?
It's fiat.
Right, because any religion on the planet right now,
any of their practices or tradition have absolutely nothing to do with anything
that's in the books that they profess to subscribe to.
So it's fiat. Right.
Right. Science. It's fiat.
How do I know?
Well, because this afternoon,
you know, they say that electricity is electrons going down the wire.
Right. Right.
So I had a low voltage system and I deliberately cut the wire and I was
waiting for all the electrons to spill out of the wire so I could sweep them up.
You see what I mean?
No, I understand.
I mean, it occurs to me that, you know,
even if you get a large room full of people and you all agree that the one wall
is not there, even if every single person in that room agrees, though,
and somebody tries to walk through it, they're still going to bash their face
into the wall, right? That's material in that space.
And that's time.
But here, if you want to be practical,
because all the ancient texts are very practical,
I can say that you see this space, the room, by the way, is a room,
a room if no one's in it. But anyway,
in this space, there's material called a wall.
And in time, meaning I know a guy who's got a backhoe with a wrecking bar on it.
In half an hour, he'll be here and that wall will be gone.
And guess what? That's a plan coming together, is it not?
No, this is true. Yeah.
But if we all sit around and intend for it, you know, it's not there.
We're all going to walk and fall down.
And that's exactly what's happening when people go to ancient texts
because, again, interpretation, there's only one interpretation,
but there are many versions, right? Like by the word interpretation,
meaning if you're an ambassador to the U.N., you go with an interpreter
and he can't be giving a version. He he has to be precise and accurate.
And if you replace that interpreter with another interpreter.
He would pretty much say the same exact thing.
This is true. And I'll tell you something else.
We're going to do a little something different tonight, by the way.
If you are listening to this live and your friend request,
Charles Dot Ocelli Space Ocelli on Skype and decide that you would like to call in
and join into the conversation, ask a question, make an observation,
whatever it is you wish, I will actually be able to take your calls
via Skype tonight.
So we're trying this.
Hopefully someone will answer and decide to participate or.
So we have the I think we'll have the phone lines open as well,
but let's try the Skype thing, because a lot of people have wanted to join in via Skype.
If not, I think we might be able to get the phone lines up at two one eight
three three nine eight five two five.
But like I said before, Charles Dot Ocelli spelled O.C.H.E.L.L.I.
Space Ocelli, that is me.
If you contact request me and then call in afterwards,
I will add you into the discussion. OK, so.
And this is at the Greeks request as well, just so everybody knows,
because a lot of times, you know, they actually ask me,
did the Greek really want to do that?
Meaning what's that calls or saying what I'm saying?
Well, saying what I say or doing what I do on the show, sometimes it's like,
oh, I'm surprised that he wanted to do a weekly show with you.
That was a question in the chat room earlier, actually, that you didn't get
to answer what made you decide to do a weekly show,
you know, as if I had nothing to say about it either.
So, well, let's just say it seemed the right thing to do at the time or times.
And I think it needs to be said because I
don't hear what we're discussing anywhere else or can find it.
And I think it needs to be said right now.
There's going to be a big change coming.
And I think we're giving people the trailer to the full feature that's on its way.
And there might be some personal responsibility
evoked, you know, in the back of one's
conscious to say, if you found out things that are validatable and objectifiable by
anyone and you're not hearing it, you've got to say something.
You've just got to say it.
Well, and that is the compulsion that drives me to do this show very much,
because I would like to get the unique information out there so that people have
a chance to understand what is about to unfold.
And meanwhile, we still have a lot more
to discuss, and we will get to it in the second hour.
I assure you,
we barely even touched upon the fact that there are many gods that have died.
And probably somebody wants to know what your proof is there.
We did start to discuss it, but then veered off into another area,
which is the same, I think it's the same area, because even with proof,
it doesn't matter. I mean, look at
look at what's going on here.
So.
Absolutely.
And we'll be right back with Ocelli and the Greek on American Freedom Radio.
Stick around.
Welcome to the American Institution, American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are three million
edible food plants on Earth and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC.
It's non-GMO and is 100 percent gluten free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle,
contains 53 percent protein and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces three brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder,
brain fuel for depression, bipolar disorders and stress.
Total Care anti-cancer agent that cleans
the liver and organs and increases memory, rejuvenate, invigorates and heals
the body, mind and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
American Freedom Radio is back.
We're trying to become commercial free,
apart from a few honorable advertisers that we would give ad space to,
even if they couldn't pay us.
In this quest to deliver quality radio with very few annoying ads,
we are now asking the listeners like you to open up and become partners
with American Freedom Radio.
We all know the economy is controlled
and a new system called the peer-to-peer economy is now within our grasp.
That means if you'd like this network
with its incredible hosts and credible information to be nothing
but the content you want to hear, then you must realize that you cannot
be a part of it if you're just sitting on the sidelines watching.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and pledge your support today.
Donate according to your means.
Some can only afford one dollar a month,
while others can afford one hundred dollars a month.
Regardless of the size of your contribution,
it all adds up to keeping the network owners and the radio hosts housed
and fed at the end of every month. Thank you.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit
and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change
the landscape of various pain-related health care costs,
epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's
finest 99.9 percent pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer and it saves you over one third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to American Freedom Radio dot com,
the network who perseveres in delivering
intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun,
honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable
discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service
to the community with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you
personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio
and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something
back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at American
Freedom Radio dot com or volunteer by emailing American Freedom Radio dot com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules, no rules, no taboo topics, taboo topics, no fear of no fear of doom.
We are our American Freedom Radio, American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
the only broadcast information the sonic entity known as Ocelli.
So the second hour of Ocelli in the Greek
coming out to you live by American Freedom Radio at American Freedom Radio dot com.
Here we are and we are going to try this
experiment of taking the Skype calls while on the air.
But we'll see what my Internet does.
And like I said before, the turn of the hour,
according to the wind up clock or the digital representation thereof,
we'll also take phone calls and you can friend request me on Skype.
If you're not already on my list,
Charles Ocelli spelled O-C-H-E-L-L-I, a space and then Ocelli again.
That's how you find it on your Skype directory.
And that's me.
And I will gladly add you in.
I think we'll actually probably have one call in about a minute and a half
and we'll be able to test it and see what happens when we do it.
Anyway,
we are discussing.
Well, a great many things, as per the usual on this show,
but the initial premise had to do with, well, gee, how do we understand what's going on?
Is there one God?
Of course, we've covered that before.
Is God dead? Are there dead gods?
Is there one God?
We've been through all of that.
But I bet there are some people out there
wondering on the particulars a little bit.
They're Greek like, well, which ones are we talking about?
And what is the proof that you have of these memorializations of
these events that are supposed to be the deaths of what we would call gods?
Well, the proof and well, the information for first of all,
any information, it doesn't matter what it is, should be validated.
Right. And then all we have is the record to go off of.
Right.
So like one can say, well, how do we know George Washington even existed?
Or how do we know who wrote the Constitution?
Well, if everything is memorialized
regarding those questions and it could be answered,
you still have a crossroad.
You might still have those that say, well, I don't believe it.
I don't think it's true.
Well, don't argue it. Just walk away.
Then the other fork in the road is that this is a good record versus a poor record.
And let's look at it and see if it can be
pieced together and find evidence and other pieces of information,
because ultimately we're not there, you see.
So in terms of discussion based on the validity of what information
and memorialization we have, we can piece it together as such.
And that's the best we can do right now.
And it also helps us explain
well, us and anyone who does this kind of work.
What is going on around us right now?
Hmm. Absolutely.
So I have actually joined a Skype caller to the show.
Jillian, how are you tonight?
I'm well, thanks, Chuck.
How are you and all of your friends?
Well, we have you've actually joined
into Ocelli in the Greek, which is a different show than most people are
accustomed to, or actually everyone is accustomed to, realistically.
And it's different than my own show generally.
But we are discussing some pretty interesting topics here.
Have you heard any of what's going on?
Only about half a half a very long sentence.
I heard about a little bit.
I think. Were you talking about gods?
Well, you said I think when I turned it, you said we've discussed the gods.
And yes, there are many sorts of gods and one God.
And is there one God and blah, blah.
And there we were. I was here.
Hmm. Absolutely.
Well, the fact is, we were discussing how
there are many gods which have been memorialized based on secular historians
which have nothing to do with religious beliefs or or faith, et cetera, et cetera.
And we're kind of wondering if you have any questions about that, because
well, this is where we're at.
I mean, a lot of people discuss how there's one God as opposed to multiples.
And how do you feel about that?
What do you think? And do you know what we're talking about?
Mm hmm.
Sure, sure.
I mean, I think when they're talking about one God, they're talking about the
underlying matrix of existence, you know, the the I don't know what a modern word
for that would be, but it's like.
They're, you know, their perception, you know, their raw energy.
And then on top of that, there's plenty of room for other gods because they're all
sort of like expressions of aspects of this enormous
energy. So they're a little bit of a more of a relative truth.
Hmm. What do you think about God?
Call it absolute. You're gone.
Well, hang on. Well, what do you think about that,
Greek, that the idea that there's one relative sort of power source and one
absolute power source would be, you know, expressions of that singularity?
That is that's the side effects of the dummy load.
What I mean by that is we like to make up that what we like to say that makes us feel
good and other people agree with us.
But when you say the space, the energy, the source, that is very different.
In other words, that has been delineated through the ages.
Yes, those things exist.
And there is a source for these things, but there's more specifics to it.
There you see.
So matrix, meaning the womb were essentially because we're still being
formed as a species, as a society, spiritually and so forth, materially as
well, you could say we're still sort of in a matrix or in a womb condition.
But the point that we're trying to get
across and impart is that there's a multitude of of information regarding
specifics to say that we're just this main source of energy.
It's like coming to Earth and yeah,
there's a river on Earth and there's a dog and there's a man and he was nice.
And now we're back here.
What are you calling the main source of energy?
I don't what I was thinking.
No, no, no.
What we're discussing is the is the non material aspect that controls
the material aspect as it's been memorialized through history.
No one is anymore.
Everyone has given up and looking at all of the various texts,
information that has been brought been brought forth to this day.
A lot of people call them religious texts or ancient history.
And you've heard of like revisionist history, right?
How they start making it up is changing the story.
We modern people or current society cannot go further back with any accuracy
more than 100 years or 150 years around the mid 19th century.
All knowledge of this was really a cut off from the people today.
And there was another major cut off around 500 B.C.,
which I call the big cosmic censorship.
But what you're saying is valid in terms of, yes, there is a major energy source.
Sure. It's called the life force.
You know, where do you get the energy to get
up from your chair and walk across the room?
None of these academic scientists can explain how that happens.
There's no way that the muscles and the bones are supporting you.
I mean, there's another form of levity, right?
It's called the life force or the ancient.
They used to call it the ether.
And they and when they first came up
with electricity, you know, it came out of nowhere, really.
And you also call it chi, do you?
Yes. The chi, the chi in Asia, let's say,
chi in Japan, prana in India, zoe in Greek, that's why we have zoology.
Now, the thing is, it's been, well, I shouldn't say proven,
but we have an ether, a field, a life field that manifests everything
that we see in the material energetic world.
But no one has ever been able to really quantify it or seriously qualify it.
And I'll go back to a saying that was said in the 19th century.
Just because I don't know how I digest
my food doesn't mean I'm not going to eat my supper.
Right.
You see, so we don't know much about this energy source.
But what we do know is that we have a collection of information that's been
preserved to this day from ancient times that no one is looking at.
And when we look at the groups, quote unquote, the religious groups,
you hear about them all the time.
You know, I'm so spiritual or the alternative, really,
you know, all these little groups, you hear people go, I'm spiritual.
Right. And they know nothing about the spiritual
realm that has been memorialized for thousands of years to this day.
They're just making stuff up.
Like, for example, you will not find in any ancient text
the concept of when you die, you are reincarnated as a dog or a cat
or a butterfly or someone else that is not in any ancient text.
But yet it prevails in the Tibetan society.
You know, the people walk away and you won't find that.
You want to know what's really funny, Greg?
I actually was a Tibetan Buddhist nun
and I actually studied quite a bit about this stuff.
It's good.
It's a good secrecity that you're quoting.
And that is what I meant when I when I was talking about the underlying
matrix in Tibetan Buddhism or in Sanskrit, it's called the Dharmakaya.
Dharma meaning truth and kaya meaning body.
Or they also call it the reality body.
And it's it's the underlying matrix of existence.
And it's the unmanifested.
And they say it's clear, light and formless that has the ability to perceive.
Well, I when I have to relate to Christians because I grew up
supposed Church of England
denomination was put upon me and I went to a Church of England school
and went to chapel every day for half an hour like you do when you go to a Church
of England school and I studied biblical studies as a year 12
you know, fascination.
And then I went off and studied Tibetan Buddhism.
So I call the Dharmakaya that you're speaking about the unmanifested.
I call that I think that's what Christians are getting at,
even though some of them don't know it would be the purest interpretation of God.
Right, but again, that is in contemporary times,
but if we actually look at the wealth of information in detail and specifics,
you know, what we're trying to discuss here is beyond the ritual, like,
for example, a common woman in the Western world,
let's say, we'll use common terms, drives a car.
She knows that if she opens the door,
sits in it and pushes on this pedal and turns the steering wheel,
she'll get the job done and safely.
And that's all she needs to know.
But she doesn't know typically, you know, exactly.
And but you do have to know a certain amount of mechanics.
What happens if the tire goes flat?
It's good to be self-sufficient, right?
So what we're discussing here is to say it is not difficult to be self-sufficient.
You know, some people are completely turned off about that.
They'll call for help where all they have to do is just do this.
And in a minute they're on their way again.
So what we're trying to impart to people is that these things were written
for everyone, it's a universal message and no one has been looking at the details.
They'll say, you know, enough, not enough.
Yeah. And it's and they're not that difficult
because they were written that that anyone could understand them.
And the reason I say that is because the gods do not work in futility
to say that we do not understand this message.
And it was written to not be understood.
How many times have you heard that in religious circles?
Right. Yeah.
That's all the time, all the time, especially.
That is indirectly calling the gods futile.
And I assure you, they are not futile.
Not even remotely. I know people who've seen them.
In fact, I've seen a couple of Buddhas and and an angel and things,
but there are other people who've seen, you know, like in the Tibetan Buddhist
iconography, they have Tara and
they have all these different colored deities.
Well, I have a friend who is a nice anecdotal story,
because often when you talk about these things, it's nice to have an anecdotal story.
Of course, people's next question would be what drugs were they on?
It usually is.
But I was considered oxygen, by the way, is considered a drug now.
So go ahead. Yes, sorry.
It is a drug, isn't it?
Sorry, go ahead.
This friend of mine, a Buddhist, I met him as a Buddhist
before this, before he was a Buddhist, so it's a long time ago.
But he was he's an honest guy.
He and a friend were in the forest.
A green Buddha, a green goddess, Tara from Ireland,
you know, the one that appeared, Ireland, I think it's Tara.
And in Tibetan Buddhism and in Sanskrit,
she's also called Tara, appeared in the tree and she was dancing and just dancing
in the tree. And oddly enough, my friend Kate,
they both saw it and they both discussed it.
And she was exquisite and very lively and full of energy.
And then she don't know what happened to her.
She must have disappeared eventually.
Anyway, one guy went off and became a Christian minister.
And my friend met a Tibetan Lama,
the same teacher as mine, and he became a Tibetan Buddhist and was very delighted,
you know, because Tara was in Tibetan Buddhism, too.
Yeah, these are elementals.
People will discover they can be identified just like if you were walking.
They called her she's a Buddha.
Yeah.
Those are there's a see, just like in society, you have social ranks,
you know, you go from the street sweeper to the doctor up to the, you know,
the mayor of the town to the to the king, right?
You have the various social ranks and positions of what they do in society.
The spiritual realm has that as well.
And when when you read that they had created the material realm,
which is not far fetched to see that in any ancient text, right?
You see that they are part of the creation deities, right?
They manifested this,
just like you were to construct something.
You have an architect, the chief contractor.
Can I interrupt you?
Tibetan Buddhism doesn't believe anyone created anything.
They think that it's mine.
Tibetan Buddhism, from my understanding of it,
says it's all mind created by us in a group cause.
Yeah, that would...
You go on. Yes.
But you have to realize who's us when there is very complex,
just like, for example, when you read the U.S. Constitution,
it says we the people and people have been applying it to themselves.
And it only applies to those who wrote the Constitution.
So there's a word trickery there.
And also, you have to realize that the common Buddhism that is taught today
and practiced by monks as such really did not exist as such before 500 B.C.
Tibetan Buddhism didn't exist until a thousand years ago.
Yeah, well, everything that it's built on.
You see, the reason why I'm saying this is what's interesting is around 500 B.C.
there was a very big cosmic censorship that came on this planet that rearranged
all of the spiritual beliefs of people, not the texts and customs.
And that was the main thrust into where we are today.
And the different evolutions of all these
beliefs really started around 500 B.C.
And yeah, so it does. Yeah, exactly.
So what I'm saying, this is contemporary again and it changes.
And if you really push anyone,
they rarely get any information that's more than 150 years old.
But but here's I appreciate you.
Thank you for your your the story you gave us as well,
because it shows that these things are discussed and seen and manifest
and considered by people, you know, it's not it's no longer just
for discussion, but people, they're life changing events and such.
But the knowledge of these things will
be known as we progress more into the future.
It's just the same as if we don't know the type of creatures that are on the bottom
of the ocean because we we cannot go into that environment.
And once you can go into the environment, you can come back with great detail.
And what I'd like to say is we don't have
to make things up because it's already been done for us thousands of years ago.
Right. And look, I'm going to I'm going to let
you go, Jillian, because I've got I got somebody else trying to get in.
And I do want to say, I do want to take one Skype caller at a time so we don't
degrade the signal too much. But if you do try and drop in, guys,
you can try a little bit ahead of you here.
Somebody else drop off because
what will happen is you'll hear it a little late.
There's a little delay.
So if you're on the Charles Ocelli Ocelli Skype list,
I can add you right into the call, but I will only do one at a time.
OK, guys. So I just want to let you know that.
But Jillian, really, I appreciate your input here.
And you got any final sort of thought about what we've discussed here?
Yeah, well, I just basically say that I think after you deal with the absolute
truth and after that, everything just goes into different levels of truth,
like relative and relative, relative and relative, relative, relative.
But I
that's all I have to say for now.
Jillian, I'll let you go.
Listen, thank you so much.
Appreciate it. It's a pleasure.
I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
Yeah. Bye.
So like I said, yeah, if you guys want to try now, that's OK.
But I'm only going to put one on at a time.
But, you know, Greg, this is interesting
because I think you were talking about the hierarchy here
and how that is seen.
Sometimes people see things of greatness and well, from their perspective,
if they've never seen anything greater than what they're witnessing,
obviously that's the greatest thing they've ever seen.
So if one witnessed something that was a lower form of a god,
you know, lower on the rungs of the hierarchy there, one might imagine that
that they've that they've seen the great deity just in that one stroke.
I mean, look, it's extremely amazing to see a bicycle and see someone travel
on a bicycle if you've never seen a car before comparatively.
Right. Absolutely.
And that's exactly the metaphor and that's exactly the proportion of it.
For the past two millennia,
any of the higher ranking deities have said we're hands off.
You guys are on your own to the lower ones.
And that's an interesting concept.
But, you know, and that will be proven out in time, of course.
Absolutely.
So, yeah, so hopefully if you guys want to try and join in, go right ahead.
If you're listening and you're on my Skype list, if not, go ahead and request me
and I'll put you in there.
Also, let me check the switchboard.
Well, we don't have anybody on the switchboard, but you can call in there, too,
if it's easier for you.
Of course, internationally,
the Skype would probably be better because it won't cost you anything.
But 218-339-8525,
we'll take some calls if anyone dares to step into this conversation.
All right.
Now, Chuck, you know, I said higher and lower.
That's for communication purposes only.
The other concept to sort of relay or impart is that in the spiritual realm,
it's not like man's kingdom, which is higher and lower.
The street sweeper being at the bottom
and the king being at the top, the highest or the top of the pyramid,
for example, structure.
But there is a pyramid structure, actually, in the spiritual.
And you see, it's very difficult to convey.
I want to say four things at the same time.
But in the spiritual realm, most of the examples that were being given,
it is a lateral kingdom.
You have the inner circles, you're in or out.
That's why when you look at the, for example,
the biblical accounts, Eve came from Adam's side, not from his bottom, right?
You are sitting on the left hand or the right hand, right?
In terms of space, there is a higher and lower, you know, for example.
But in the spiritual realm of rank, it's a lateral ranking system, you see.
That's why, for example, Solomon was the wisest of all men
because he asked for he was asked for knowledge or wisdom.
He could have asked for riches, right?
As according to the text, what did he ask for?
He said, I need wisdom so I can see how to come in and go out.
He didn't say how to go up and down or how to rise to be king or whatever.
It was in and out.
So that is the spiritual dialogue you even it's common.
You've heard people say that is my inner circle.
Right.
You know, so when you hear that lateral
positioning in rank, that is how the spiritual realm works.
It's very interesting to study that,
because in the material kingdom, a man manifests higher and lower.
well, right.
But, I mean, I was just going with that
orientation because I generally think of things as, you know, a
a not lateral, I think of them as a as a vertical vertical.
Right. That was the word I was searching for.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's that's acceptable in the society.
And that's how I see it.
And I use that as well to communicate
because that just like saying inches or metric or whatever, it's just a reference.
That's acceptable to give the the the position.
But, you know, as you go more into the information, let's say the data using
computer terms, you'll see it's lateral.
That's in other words, there's a contrast in what people believe, you see.
But when the when the spiritual realm interacts with the physical realm,
that now it takes a physical presence and it always appears to be from a higher
vertical position within the physical realm.
But that's kind of subject to interpretation, isn't it?
After all, something that is perceived as
coming from on high, let's just to borrow a phrase, right,
is not necessarily from a higher point, but it may manifest itself in that way.
Yeah, based on our physical limitations on the scale that we were made,
because, you know, when we look at how it's discussed, how everything was remade.
So to inhabit us,
you know, where the average man is given, you know, being two meters tall or six
feet, let's say, or, you know, and we have a certain height.
The reason we have this proportion or scale is so we experience peace.
You know, you hear that term go to peace,
like Salaam or Shalom and be peace, you know, or peace.
You know, that's very important for man to wish that upon other man.
Right.
And we have that scale that we have
anthropomorphic shape and height so we can be at peace with the environment.
See, because if we were as tall as an ant,
if a branch fell, it would feel like an earthquake, you know,
eight on the Richter scale, right?
It wouldn't be very peaceful to be that small on the earth.
And but if you were 300 feet tall,
the jet stream would be blowing your hair back at 100 miles per hour.
How can you get anything done?
You see, so we're giving this we're given
the scale of height in this environment so we can experience peace,
which is what's which is a common denominator of what's wished on people
throughout the ancient texts in the ancient world and modern world as well.
Right. Even in more modern vernacular, this is one of those things that you do.
You wish someone well or a peaceful journey or just, you know,
the hippie concept of peace and all that.
There was actually a reason for it.
And this is this is what it is.
It is one of those consistent
sentiments, let's just say.
And it's usually used to wish one not to be challenged
in the material world physically.
Right.
But in the in the spiritual realm, it it's of the mind.
There is no peace.
You see, that's different there as well, because if you look at what people are
saying and wondering and thinking and the frustration in society right now about
things, there is no peace of the mind or that's another thing.
Peace of mind. Right.
But which is spirit.
There is no peace in the spiritual realm of mankind right now.
Look at the the way the religions act, the politicians act, the sciences.
You know, it's all part of the mind or the spirit is the spiritual realm is not
at peace right now. So when we say peace, we usually mean it
in the material sense.
Right. Well, that is true.
Yeah. I mean, and most of your sentiments that
are uttered verbally are meant to be manifest physically.
That is generally the purpose by which people do attempt to communicate things.
Their their verbal communications are meant to manifest physically.
I think a lot of people forget about that.
Yeah, we're we're locked into the physical and also the the dummy load is put
on the physical as well around the turn of the 20th century with Einstein.
You know,
that whole relativism was pushed and thrusted on people, you know,
people, if you if they did some research on when evolution and relativism was
thrust into society through academia, there were riots in the streets.
There were protests, many contrary articles.
You know, I mean, this is hogwash.
Look at look at all their distorted measurements.
And, you know, if we came from apes, why are there still apes?
And, you know, there was a lot of protest.
And this is the the protest of society
against these concepts of relativism and evolution has not been carried forward.
And the true weight that it had during the time when these things were put
in society and people are not aware of it, they think that,
you know, current people think that, oh, yeah, relativism and evolution and this
material sense of twisted perception just just came in because it was the right
thing to do or we you know, we it's a better idea.
It was not accepted as such at the beginning of the 20th century.
There's a lot of friction against it,
kind of like now when there's a lot of people protesting against the public
policy or a law, they still thrust it into the society.
Then the people just learn to live with it, you know.
Right. Right.
Now, I see an odd question in the chat room.
I don't necessarily understand it.
Perhaps you will.
If the gods are plurality, are they equal in their relevance to use as a creation?
To use as a creation.
Yeah, they are all very, very relevant.
Just like in society, you've got, you know, mechanics, cooks, chefs,
you know, very every year.
Like, what do you want to do when you grow up?
Right. I want to be a musician or I want to be an architect.
I want to be a carpenter. I want to be a plumber.
They have a veritable plethora there.
That's why when we look at a lot of the original people,
they had
homage to the god of the river, the god of the sky, the god of the grasshopper,
the god of the snake, you know, there's a there's a film and a book,
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy in the film Towards the End.
And when they're rebuilding the earth,
you know, he's been given a tour by one of the people, I guess.
And he says, well, how are you involved in this construction?
He says, oh, I built Norway.
You see, it's going to be quite a surprise
when people figure out that these a lot of these primitive cultures were
as as advertised as being primitive, were highly evolved to understand
that there is an elemental or a spiritual side to all of the things that we see.
Well, how many times do you hear today?
Oh, the beer, the bees are disappearing.
All right. You hear that.
Right.
Where was the whales at one point? Right.
And I wonder why.
Well, it's the glyphosate they're using in this and that.
Well, and they can't really narrow it down.
It's because the deity behind the bees is pulling them out of this existence.
You know, like, for example,
you want to name or let's say go to the direction of a really mean deity
or an elemental or a really mean ass one would be the one behind cockroaches.
I was hoping you were going to bring it up.
Yeah, because they take eight hundred times
the radiation of a human or something like that.
You can't kill them. And they just prolific.
Right.
The deity behind, you know, very fast breeding.
And for example, down to the microbes, there are elements and deities behind that.
And that's why people have problems.
When you look at, for example, what is it called?
Pestilences where you're overrun by locusts, you know, things like that.
There's a deity behind that, you know.
Right. Actually, they and they corrected their
question a little bit because it first said to use as a creation.
But but what they corrected it to say was to us as creation.
So the odds are plurality.
Are they equal in their relevance to us as creation?
So, oh, well, we're according to the text, we're within their family,
but we don't have their power.
Our power is limited to the material world and very little of it in their world
in terms of what they can do.
If you go back to the let's say for the
Hebrew text, the text where the gods are the Elohim or the El,
the the what what that word means is to emanate an emanator.
So as if you were standing, let's say,
in a part an empty parking lot and you would say car and a car immediately
appears, you're an emanator, you're a god, you see.
And this is actually personified somehow in science fiction and in
fiction, you know, with these djinns and, you know,
they call them genies giving me three wishes, right?
And they just speak it.
So these things are, you know, in other words,
when you start looking at what's been memorialized
and what these words really mean and we get an interpretation,
we start to see that we we've been presented with all of this
through through fictional accounts and then also you'll notice is a lot
of the factual accounts were presented by fictional accounts also.
So we've learned to accept everything as being fiction right now.
Look at, you know,
the Warren Commission or the 9-11 Commission or the outcome of World War Two
or, you know, the people are fed fiction, in other words,
just to go along and be happy consumers, right?
And this time is ending, by the way, in relatively short period.
Not not this week, not next month, not next year.
But shortly thereafter, people are going to say we need
something with a little more meat or a little more basis behind it.
And they will find out more about the that's why we keep going back
and discussing on and off the gods, because in the vernacular,
regardless of what you believe in it or not, when you say the term God or gods,
it means something higher and more powerful.
I mean, and if you have any sanity, you would want to know about that.
It's all right.
I mean, you would want to know about the the most.
Look, depending on how you how you take it,
they would be much more destructive and much more productive than we are.
And they would have the will to affect all of us.
So you might want to be aware of these kind of things.
It's sort of like, well, I don't pay attention to the weather
until, you know, until the hurricane comes through and rips down my house.
Well,
yeah, it's a little late, a little late.
And you've got to understand that, you know,
you ever see how they board up their houses before a tornado or hurricane.
That's the worst thing to do.
You need to open all the windows and doors and just let it go right through.
If you if you tighten the house down like that,
it'll rip the roof off because of the vacuum.
You need to equalize it.
So it's just funny, you know, people that we discuss the weather
with and how weather with and how it really works versus what you're told
by the meteorologist is anyone, by the way, who's ever taken the advice
that you should open your windows or remove them and open your doors.
You'll be fine in a situation in a weather situation like that.
You see, I always thought that was only
during tornadoes you had to worry about that kind of thing.
Honestly, I didn't realize that hurricanes would be
another situation where it was a good idea to do so.
The hurricane is the ultimate manifestation of that energy over a large
area where the tornado is the ultimate manifestation of that energy in a small
area, more concentrated, same energy, the weather.
It's a biological phenomenon.
so, yeah, so it seems like the best advice to give someone would be just take
anything, you know, turn it upside down. Now it's right side up.
Right.
OK, well, that's that's interesting as well, but my my point here was that,
you know, you can't complain about the damage done of something you're unaware
of, I guess, but but, you know, people still do.
They do.
And that's the interesting thing about the time they're in right now.
First of all, they cannot discern the time.
Right. Just like the you know,
the hurricanes coming a day or two before and you might take some preparation.
But with the spiritual matters,
they cannot discern spiritual matters at all right now.
Humanity is locked out of that by choice.
They prefer to be willfully ignorant, you see.
And when it when it starts rearing its existence into this realm, it's it's
even then people will go along with it
and will and will still not be able to discern it for a short while.
They will.
But ultimately, you know, when you you mentioned destruction and power,
when you talk about war and destruction, mankind is only familiar
through history, photographs or folklore about the destruction and the horrors
of war, right? Everyone will agree.
Yeah, that's only when and that's pretty horrible.
And that's man doing war with man.
People have no concept of what happens
when the gods do war with each other or with man.
That is a level of horror and destruction that is that cannot even be imagined.
You see, and this is somewhat explained again
by these primitive agents and information that we have today.
Go figure.
Yeah, fascinating how some of the original
ideas seem to be a whole lot more accurate than the delusion that or the disillusionment
of those same ideas much, much later on,
you know, very much like a a grand sort of display of that old game
telephone where you would pass a piece of information between a bunch of people.
And by the time it gets to the end of the line, it's unrecognizable.
You know, well, the thing about this,
the high vantage point information that anyone can access, right,
is that what it what will it will allow one to be able to live a life more efficiently.
Right. Well, what that means is even with information,
how many I mean, according to some people in alternative media,
we should have had a destruction or some kind of calamity,
what they call by the Pope's work schedule September, right, this year.
Supposedly it didn't happen right.
And then last year it was the big thing
about the prepping. And according to another individual,
we all should have been in FEMA camps 10 years ago.
So and these things are being broadcast, the worry, the doom, this and that.
And a lot of people actually go out and buy cans and put them away and buy guns.
And yeah, and concerned about the cost.
And yeah. And so is that efficiency?
I mean, look at the what efficiency is there with the 1950s with duck and cover?
How many underground shelters were built
because the Soviet Union was supposed to nuke the United States of America?
Do you think if you knew that wasn't going to happen, you would have?
I mean, I don't know.
Back then in that money in those days, what did it cost to build a bomb shelter?
You see what what a waste right now.
Actually, some people will now seek those
types of houses because they make good wine cellars, you see.
Well, there's a usefulness for it, but it wasn't readily apparent at the time.
Right.
Here's here's another here's another odd
question that that came into the chat room, by the way, which, you know, still,
guys, I will take those Skype calls for the next little bit.
We do have about, hmm, 15 more minutes or so of live time left.
So if you want to join in, go ahead.
Charles Ocelli space Ocelli on Skype.
And one person is waiting to join into the conversation.
I don't know why.
But anyway, reading from the chat room,
the question in a couple of different forms is, do you believe in non duality?
And what is it?
Well, belief.
Well, here's the thing.
In the material world, there's a lot of duality right up and down.
Cold, hot, male, female, good, bad.
Yeah, that's one of the that's one of the things, you know, there is there is a
duality in this realm, but in the other realm, there is a duality
that's communicated to us as well.
But I believe there's even more beyond the duality.
There's always a third side to things like, you know,
people say there's the front and back of a coin, but there's a third side to a coin.
It's called the reeded edge and gold coins.
They put that serration marks called the reeded edge to see that the coin hasn't
lost any value because you didn't scrape any material off of it.
So sometimes it's the third side that gives
the value or shows if the value has been tampered with.
And let's say, for example, when you say
something getting really large towards infinity, it's really large.
But something getting infinitely small is physically small.
But the count or how small it is is also very large in both directions.
So we're sort of locked in that reality at this point.
But there is a third side and a fourth side.
And I think that will be examined a little closer.
Do I believe in it? No, I can only report
on what would be best to report on radio and discuss that anyone who has interest
at least will have an outline of something to discuss or study in their own personal
lives. Right, right.
Well, you know, I do find it fascinating that people often talk about the two sides
of the coin completely ignoring the depth of the coin, so to speak,
which is determined by the third side, which is determined by the third side.
And of course, regardless of the sort of
well, the surface.
Of the you know, the surface
measurement you can give to one side or the other, quite honestly, it is the the
thickness of the coin by which the things are usually
very much, very much measurable, you know, and that that is fascinating right there.
I mean, after all,
a coin the size of the old old American dollars,
you know, the peace dollars or Morgan dollars, something like that.
When it was made paper thin
in other cultures, you find something that's very, very much nearly worthless.
And of course, they're much more pliable and bendable, et cetera, et cetera.
So it's always good to remember that there are multitudes of sides to things.
But the one of the signs from a spiritual
perspective or of the mind of the of the age coming to an end,
because when the age comes to an end, you know, there's a lot of doom and gloom
is the destruction of duality.
Like right now, how many times have you heard?
There is no good or evil.
There is no male or female or there is the destruction of the duality
or the pairing or the balance is being taken out right now.
Politically, medically, scientifically and such.
So we have someone else.
We do. Seth, how are you doing?
Greetings. Thanks for bringing me into the conversation.
I suppose that at this point it is my
you can use me as an example of how intent is essentially
without merit or purpose because it was my intent to
listen to the program and to call in
significantly earlier than I did.
But I got my times mixed up and didn't realize that I was I was as late
to the conversation as I was, but it's good to hear both of you on air
and broadcasting and I wanted to say hello.
Hello, Seth. Thank you for coming.
Yeah, absolutely.
I intended to be here about an hour ago,
but the the difference in time zones has gotten me.
So, OK, yeah.
And what would you like to add or take away, as you would say?
Well, I would like to thank Chuck for
hosting the program and Greek as well for being here.
It's it's good to hear this type of conversation being broadcast.
So I guess that I just wanted to thank you both for that.
I added
that Chuck is a contact on Skype and I told him that I was waiting to call
into until I could catch up with the conversation.
And then I heard him say that the conversation is coming to an end here
in a few minutes. So I guess my apologies for that.
But it's OK.
It's good to be with on air and to hear
the the subject matter being discussed that's being discussed.
So thank you.
Well, you're welcome.
And I hope you if you represent just more than yourself, let's say we don't
I don't feel like it's an act of futility.
And I hope anyone that's listening is is perhaps rethinking not because they
should, but because they could, you know, what they believe in.
Absolutely.
And look, much appreciated that you even wanted to participate,
even if you missed it a little bit, of course, this will wind up being archived
and you'll be able to revisit it later.
But I found it interesting to try and add people to the discussion tonight.
Sorry that you missed out on some of the conversation.
But really, thank you very much, actually,
for for being interested and and giving it giving this conversation.
It's it's day in court, if you will.
It is. We're electronic court.
Yeah, yeah.
Certainly, certainly it's my pleasure.
And thanks for bringing me on.
I look forward to the shows in the future as well.
I'm me and the Greek or the Greek and I have spoken at length over the last few
years, and I know that it's it's worth listening to.
You're not going to hear it anywhere else.
So thanks again for broadcasting.
Yeah, I really enjoy words.
The language that we're using to communicate right now is English.
And over the last several years, I've become very frustrated with English
as a language because we borrow words from other languages.
And instead of borrowing them for purpose, we borrow them.
We pronounce it and we mean something different.
So we get words in our language like psychology
that have nothing to do with this study of spirit.
And, you know, that's just an example.
Another one that's a favorite is nice.
You know, the the actual that that word was an abbreviated form of the word
nation and actually meant silly or stupid when it was first being spoken aloud
and used as a sound for meaning.
And now
we use such words to mean something is pleasant or OK.
We use psychology for the
PSY.
The PSY prefix is the spirit and it's been disconnected.
And yeah, the the use of words is well,
you can easily say then if it doesn't matter, then it doesn't matter if you say
what you mean or mean what you say.
And in terms of everyone wishing themselves to be nice is I read somewhere
in a really old book that they will put the curses upon themselves.
So it's very interesting how you can
discern the times simply just by looking at how people use words.
Yeah, absolutely.
And it's not something that is
when it is addressed, when it's brought up, if I bring it up in conversation and I
point out, you know, the the history of words and what's being said,
the most common response that I get is, well, you know what I'm saying.
And yes, that's what I'm pointing out.
I'm pointing out that what we're saying has an effect.
And, you know, if the meanings of words,
regardless of time, is important and I believe that it is
to communicate in an accurate and worthwhile manner.
You know, if you're going to talk about
anything, the easiest way to learn about that is is through increasing one's
vocabulary and comprehension of the vocabulary.
So this is true.
And you know what I find fascinating really is that in alternative media, they
are quite quick to point out that history has been hijacked, that religion has been
hijacked, but they completely ignore the fact that our languages have also been
hijacked, you know, and all with purpose.
None of this by accident.
None of it without design.
There is an absolute reason why this has occurred.
And it is to make sure that knowledge is not readily available and that
that what you would call fit and proper Greek is it's also not readily and easily
accessible. It's a war.
It's really a war in wartime and any really good training of military academy.
The first thing you want to do if you have
to confront the enemy is make sure he cannot communicate amongst himself.
Absolutely.
The cosmic of war is to bring into confusion.
So, yeah, so this is clearly what's going on.
It also needs to be discerned and it is
discounted and there is no discernment.
And that's why how many times have you heard people say, I don't know what's going on.
I don't know how to fix the problems we have.
You know, and, you know, whenever I get into personal discussions with people
before they tell me, quote, unquote, their point of view of what they think is a
social problem or financial problem or whatever, I let them introduce the topic
and I always interrupt them and I say, you know, you're on planet Earth.
Right. And they say, well, what does that mean?
Yes, I do know that.
I said, well, then if you've been here for more than 15 minutes,
you've pretty much assessed the situation and what you're telling me is already
pretty clear how to fix it.
You just have to wait.
And they look and then they're totally befuddled, you know, so.
Well, you know, that does bring to mind
something I know I read as a child in a very old translation of some text
where it stated that there is no war without deception.
And deception is really the greatest weapon that that anyone can utilize against
their enemy. Now, I don't know where I read that.
I'm pulling that quote out of virtually nowhere.
But Sun Tzu, the art of war is mentioned.
It sounds like something from Sun Tzu, doesn't it?
If you were to paraphrase him.
But here's the thing. We're already in it.
We're born into this and we're here.
So if you're thrust into the battlefield, right, and you find yourself there,
you have to operate with a level of efficiency.
If you're inefficient, your boots will be wet.
Your feet will rot. You'll run out of food.
You'll be you want to be operating with efficiency.
And where is the outrage when you go
through the alternative media and people are chattering and actually more
than chattering, saying that we're going to have a big calamity this, quote unquote,
September or why are these people still allowed to speak?
You see, in a lawful society, if someone says something is going to happen
and it doesn't happen, you pull them out of their bed at night.
And it's not it's not pretty.
The people that have been going around for the past decade on the alternative media,
shouting out all of these dates and of destruction and calamity and it doesn't
happen, why are they still speaking? Why is that allowed?
Well, that tells me that no one really cares.
And if no one really cares, well, what the hell?
You better figure out how to be efficient
in a world where no one really cares.
Well, I certainly care.
This is why I pointed out and I call it out all the time.
I love pointing out the fact that the world did not end at the end of what they
call September, and we're still all here because the doomsday
prophets, one thing about them, as you look back in history,
is that they were all incorrect just about every single time
when they made these public pronouncements.
And I have often wondered why there is not some retribution
for the the effects that they have had on their listeners.
And that counts for, you know,
the guys on the street corner a couple of hundred years ago to the people that are
doing this in an electronic sense today.
We're almost out of time.
Seth, I do appreciate you as a listener,
and I'm very glad that you called in and and offered what you did.
Is there anything you'd like to say before I let you go?
No, man, just again, thanks for having the program and
given, you know, given voice to the topics that you are.
I appreciate it and I look forward to more.
All right. Well, we look forward to doing this more
for you because it needs to be done.
And thank you, Seth.
So, Greg, you know, to put a bow on this particular package.
And yes, I do that to irritate you just a little bit to put a bow on this
particular package just before we go.
What is it that you think needs to be said in closing here?
Oh, man, that there's more to come in time.
You know, people that know me from personal discussions are wondering why I'm
speaking and actually doing a show because I've pretty much said I've done
speaking and calling in for the next few years.
And I gave that a few months and I said, you know,
it's really even more frustrating to sit back and not hear anything.
The silence was deafening.
So I in closing again, I just want this is our fourth time coming together.
And I want to thank you personally as well.
And everyone at AFR
for making it happen, really, even though even for me personally, it's unexpected.
All I'd like to say in closing is let's just keep keep at it in little,
quote, unquote, baby steps.
Absolutely.
And that is what's going to happen here.
And we do appreciate the fact that we are able to do this on American Freedom Radio
and American Freedom Radio dot com.
And I can assure you of this much.
If our intent is to be manifest, there will be much more of this to come.
And a good purpose for speaking is not just
to necessarily hear your own self speak or doing a, quote, unquote, good show,
but it's to help whoever is listening as well,
which we hope that we've assisted you with something tonight.
And I do wish anyone listening to us and paying attention.
Peace for sure.
Thanks, Chuck. Thank you, Greg.
And thank you guys out there.
Have a good night.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio Freedom Freedom, American
Freedom Radio Radio,
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat,
improves digestion and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United
States and classified it as a Schedule one drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant
for over 80 years and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now, you know, hemp is not marijuana and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts and to help people understand
that hemp protein powder is the best kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53 percent protein, is gluten free,
anti-inflammatory, non-GMO and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367
and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you only at HempUSA.org.
What kind of person are you?
How do you see yourself?
Are you the kind of person that lets everyone else do all the work,
just hoping that you'll be able to get some of the crumbs that fall from the table?
Or are you the kind of person that rolls
up their sleeves and does the dirty jobs that no one else wants to do?
Are you hoping that all the activists giving their blood,
sweat and tears to serve humanity are going to solve all the world's problems?
Or are you just wondering, is there something simple I can do to contribute?
Yes. Yes, there is.
Help us.
Help us do what we do.
Partner up with American Freedom Radio today by gifting a regular amount
to support the network and your favorite hosts,
bringing you less commercials and more information.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and start donating today from between one dollar and one hundred dollars per month.
According to the kind of person you are.
Thank you very much for your support.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation involves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape.
Various pain related health care costs,
epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders and even soldier suicides.
Crystal pure CBD is made with the industry's finest ninety nine point nine
percent pure CBD crystals, no paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer
and it saves you over one third in cost.
Crystal pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to American Freedom Radio Dotcom,
the network who perseveres in delivering
intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun,
honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The host sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver
quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you
personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and
alternative media. Now it's time for you to give something
back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at American
Freedom Radio Dotcom or volunteer by emailing American Freedom Radio Dotcom.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules, no rules, no taboo topics, no taboo topics,
no fear of doom, no fear of doom.
We are, we are American Freedom Radio, American Freedom Radio.