The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand would be the
So we begin yet another broadcast of Ocelli and the Greek here on American Freedom Radio from the facilities of AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
It is, according to the Pope's work schedule, it is the 29th day of December.
Which would be, well, the 10th month according to it, the 29th day, but, well, Greek, what is your understanding through observation of the lawful day?
Well, it's obviously seven days since the last time we announced it.
Okay, it's around the 17th of the 11th month lawfully, meaning the tigers, the whales, the bees, the fish, the plants, the rivers, that's the clock they go on, if you want to call it a clock.
And when I say clock, I'm not talking about that thing, you know, the wind-up toy or the digital representation as you have coined.
So I would say that that is a very simple way to see if people are still paying attention.
I mean, it seems like people are discussing anything and everything under the sun except the most obvious and the most pertinent things.
And never really discussing the sun either, by the way. I tried to a little bit in the last show I did, but, you know, it's not being discussed, is it?
Well, the interesting thing about the sun is that's why you're not going to outer space, because if you do, you can't come back and tell anyone what you saw, because what you saw is going to be freakishly different than what you've been told.
And that's why people that do go into outer space or representation thereof, they are very much controlled on what they say publicly.
Because let's just throw this in. Light, you know, you can't see light. You only see light when it bounces off of something, like, you know, a flashlight, you know, dark at night.
You don't see the light. You only see it when it bounces off of something. I'm not talking about smoke or dust, but from a campfire either.
And that's still transverse light. In space, you have longitudinal light where it's instant.
So forget about the rubbish that if a supernova happened 100 million light years away, it takes 100 million light years to see it. It's absolutely instant, no matter how far it is.
The thing about this type of light is you could be in outer space and you cannot see the sun.
What you see as the sun on the planet is the disk or the radiation as it forms in the atmosphere.
That's why when it rises, you know, you ever see the sun at sundown or sunrise, it's this pink or orange or reddish color, then it goes bright white and yellow.
You know, it's how it's going through the atmosphere. But if you're in outer space, you could be staring right at the sun and you will see nothing but blackness.
You could still burn your eye out and you will see sunlight on your spacesuit and the planets, but you will not see the sun.
That's why you're not going to outer space. It just changes too much.
You know, the interesting thing there is I've tried to describe to you and others that I feel as though I'm living in a fluorescent light bulb because I can observe this myself,
but it's only based on the fact that I have a bit of a handicap when it comes to being overly sensitive to that which we call light, allegedly.
So it looks the way you describe it. So it's not a shocker to me, but to other people, it seems a little bit outside of the realm of possibility.
Right. Well, it's interesting. This show is not about other people. It's about people. There's lots of labels for people. So this is for people.
Now, what's interesting about that, by the way, I've got to say this again. I don't believe I'm doing this again on radio, but we are.
So let's make the best of it. Now, the best part of making the best of anything is talking about stuff that's really good and interesting.
There's also a balance between that and accommodating your audience. Now, we don't really know who's listening, but we do know that we have at least four listeners, at least.
So if we're going to accommodate anyone, might as well start there. Right.
But you know, you know what else, too, is I should take this moment to state that we do have open phone lines since it is about people.
They could participate in the discussion. Please do. So the deal is the number for those of you who wish to do so is 218-339-8525.
218-339-8525. And I will add you in, but there are a couple of rules, aren't there, Greg?
Well, let's just say before we state the rules, do we need to amend them or are they satisfactory to your personal liking?
I like them because I think they are simple and very plain, and I think they cover a lot of different possibilities without being extraneous.
So I do appreciate the simplicity of them.
Right. Well, when you live in a world or a universe that anything is possible, just having a small set of rules or just two, let's say, is not restrictive because just don't do these two things.
And there's an infinite amount of other things you can say or do. So these are the things.
The first is don't talk about yourself because, you know, in private or in public when you're around people, whether it's radio or in person, everyone seems interested, but they really don't care about you.
It's society. They say you've got to act interested. But people, when you're speaking on the radio about yourself, everyone is wondering when is this person going to shut up so I can get the mic and talk about myself.
So don't talk about yourself, number one. Number two, if you are under the influence of any kind of chemical, natural or otherwise, liquid, pill form, powder or whatever, don't call because you might think you sound all right, but everyone else can tell you are not.
So those are basically the two things. I don't know what might be a third or fourth, but I think those two make for good radio at this point.
There we go with a stuck mute button for a second, but it is, like I said, very plain, very simple, and I think fit and proper to make those two particular rules.
I don't like the word rules, though, I got to say. They're more like guidelines, aren't they? Because we can't necessarily predict what someone might do if they call in, and they don't necessarily observe the rules as rules, but they are suggested.
And of course, if you don't adhere to them, you are subject to dismissal at any time.
The red button.
There you go.
All right. Now, the other way, if you are on a phablet, tablet, computer as such, you can use Skype, superior audio quality.
And in order to come on with Skype, just go to the Skype search box and type in Ocelli and the Greek, and I'm standing by to accept your contact request.
So for Skype, it is Ocelli and the Greek.
And for spelling, you can check AFR's radio schedule.
That will give you the correct spelling.
It's spelled just like it sounds.
Yeah, that's for sure.
And, you know, of course, my name is O-C-H-E-L-L-I.
There you go.
I gave it to you anyway.
Even though the Greek tells you to go look, I'm just going to give it to you.
How about that?
And once again, I'll give you the regular standard phone line, you know, just before we continue with the discussion.
218-339-8525.
The Greek is in control of the Skype that we just gave you, but I have the phone lines in front of me.
So there you go.
218-339-8525.
And these are the two ways in which you, the listener, can participate.
Okay.
Done with all of that Greek.
Now, we did say this is about people, or this is not necessarily about – well, what were we saying now?
Excuse me.
I got a little lost.
No, that's fine.
Let's not – maybe it's lack of – low sugar, like they say, right?
And let's talk about that tonight.
The reason why is because of that being this.
People get hungry, and when you're hungry, you're looking for food.
And I'm going to just kind of bring it up right now as I'm making a cup of coffee.
On Uncommon Radio on AFR, I did another project here.
We did two episodes on how to prepare food, and we had really good response.
And, by the way, I want to thank everyone who has emailed Uncommon Radio.
And when we say four listeners, you know, it's in jest, and it's not really in earnest.
In earnest, we've gotten over, let's say, hundreds of emails, let's say, at this point on the Uncommon Radio,
and every one of them is thoughtful and they are listening.
And they're all asking questions that are baseful or lawful, you know, in other words,
not like I don't like what you're saying kind of thing, you know, or it doesn't matter kind of thing.
And, by the way, don't feel intimidated.
If you feel like calling in and telling us how you're enjoying an aimless life of baselessness, that's fine too,
so as long as you meet the first two rules.
But, you know, people get hungry, right?
You brought up the people.
This is just about talking at people until they call in.
Then we can speak with them, right?
That's true, yes.
And, you know, here's the thing, Chuck.
I guess you've been around an Internet radio on the receiving end, the giving end,
long enough to know that that form of media doesn't discuss food unless you have these alternative health kind of things,
you know, buy these drops or buy these pills or whatever, right?
Well, on occasion we do talk about the changes that people have made to food and is this correct or is this a problem?
Is it healthy?
Is it worthy of consumption, genetically modified organisms?
These types of discussion topics do come up.
And then, yes, quite often you are inundated with the product-based, hey, buy my crap to deal with what I just told you about is the problem, yeah.
Yeah, irrelevant of your geographical location or season.
It's still the medicine show.
Hey, if it doesn't make you feel better, put it in your car, you'll get better gas mileage kind of attitude, right?
So, yeah, the reason I'm bringing this up again is because it was a tremendous success on the feedback on actually doing a cooking show.
And from watching, let's say, if you've ever seen cable TV or public TV or whatever that's become quite famous in the past 30 years,
I'd say really 15 cooking shows.
And when I watch them, I always tell people,
you're never going to learn how to cook by watching these cooking shows because they miss the fundamentals.
And I said this over a decade and a half ago, and I'm correct,
because I discuss things about food with people who do watch cooking shows,
and beyond boiling water and maybe frying something into a cardboard consistency, they still don't know how to cook.
And we found out that actually giving some simple principles, even on radio,
I had gotten at least a slew of about two scores of e-mails on the successes.
And I think last week we had someone calling from what they call Ireland, that area,
that was really truly thankful about the suggestions that led to excellent rice and coffee and other things like that.
I don't know if you remember that.
That was brought to my attention as well.
So let's get into it real quick.
And, you know, typically the show kind of gets warmed up by the second hour because all the dummy load has to be cleared out in the first hour.
You know, kind of got to settle in and settle out.
But I think it's good to just jump right in.
And, I mean, who doesn't like to eat, you know, when you think about it?
Not only who doesn't like to eat, but if you consider that you are creating something which has more than one component to it,
the treatment of the components is obviously worthy of discussion.
You know, you store certain things in your refrigeration for a reason.
You, you know, say, oh, I don't know, keep certain things dry for a reason, all these kinds of things.
And, you know, those cooking shows you were talking about before never really talk about the treatment of such things.
I mean, they might tell you how to marinate something, but that has nothing to do with the treatment of the, well,
the different facets of what you're about to assemble, does it?
Right, or just even the subtleties of what is really going on, the basics of it, right?
And how people are, it seems like the more they do, in other words, people tend to damage the quality of the food more than help it along.
So we're going to discuss the subtleties that when you start to incorporate, you know, heat and chemistry,
basically are the two main things you have to have, not a deep understanding,
but a good sense of what is going on with heat and chemistry.
That's really what it's about.
And then there's the subtleties of it.
Now, we do have someone that just, let's see if I can bring him in.
He goes by the handle Regular Joe before we start, because really one of the reasons for getting together here is to make it a call-in kind of show,
more leaning towards that direction.
Because, you know, in two hours, if I start monologuing, I'm going to bury the audience.
So let's not, you know, let's keep it light and let's stay on topic if possible.
Right, sounds good.
And Regular Joe, if you bring him in, I know who we're talking about.
So this ought to be interesting, actually.
Okay, either way, I'm trying to bring him in.
So we'll see.
In the meantime, about food, call failed.
So we'll wait on that.
So when we discuss food, what's the simplest thing we could look at, right?
You notice that different geographical areas on the earth produce different produce.
When we talk about, let's say, vegetation, right, you know, you have in the Arctic, in the cold areas, you have almost zero vegetation.
And then as it gets warmer, more temperate to tropical, the vegetation seems to flourish.
You also have, as geography changes, different types of animal life, meaning fish and fowl as well, right?
Like you've heard of cold water fish and things like that.
And we're going to bring in, we have a Regular Joe on.
Regular Joe, go ahead.
How are you?
I'm good.
All right, come on in.
What you got?
What's on your mind?
Yeah, how you doing, Joe?
It's good to hear from you.
And I know that you listen to the show often.
So, you know, by all means, what is it you're bringing to the table tonight?
I don't know.
You guys, I did listen to some of the cooking shows that the Greek was speaking of and did try the potatoes.
Does work.
Stove top?
Okay.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
When you drain it.
Yeah, I did try that.
It did work very well.
It saves you a lot on your heating bill, right?
Or your utility bill.
So you could use a real small amount of heat to bake a lot of potatoes really quickly.
We might get into that.
Okay, excellent.
Actually, my wife makes them that way every time now, so.
Okay.
Does she know where you got the information?
Yes, she does.
Okay, very good.
I thought you'd keep it a secret, but anyway, go ahead.
No, she just doesn't participate as much as I do.
I've actually heard every episode of Ocelli and the Greek, so.
I'm sorry to hear that, man.
And the Uncommon Scenes as well.
I heard all of those as well, so.
So, yeah.
Still, the observational timekeeping.
I get close, but I seem to always be a day behind.
I do not know why I'm doing that.
That's okay.
That's okay, because it's not that it is, it appears to be.
No one can really say what day it is.
You can in a lawful society.
Those things are important.
If you're going to put pen to paper or a stylus to stone,
you're going to have to figure out that you want accurate information.
But at this point, what I tell people is if you gain a little bit of knowledge,
the position that you're in compared to those who don't know is not a small margin.
It's miles.
So those who know versus those who don't know,
it's not like they're standing next to each other anymore.
They're not even in the same continent anymore.
That's why I keep using the reference surface-dwelling earth inhabitant,
where what we talk about here is not for the people on this planet,
but if someone wants to visit and wants to know what it's like to be here,
because go talk to people about how to keep time and watch what happens.
Look at their eyes.
Look at their face.
I know exactly what you're talking about, because I've tried to.
And where I'm still novice, if I try to explain this to someone else,
it's poorly at best.
But still, the eyes glaze.
They look at me like, where are you from?
What are you talking about?
I've never heard anything like this.
It's correct, though.
It is a glaze in the eyes.
I do know exactly what you're talking about when you say that,
because I've seen it myself.
Go ahead.
I've kept notes.
I like to plant things.
My flowers and things that I plant every year,
I noted on the Pope's work schedule, per se,
what day they bloomed versus what day it was, as you call it, lawfully.
So next year at that time, if I keep my observations correct,
then that will be something that I can see for myself.
That's right, because the pretty little flowers that need bullshit to grow
do go on the lawful timekeeping.
And you can get all your bullshit from Internet radio or mainstream media,
by the way.
But actually, that's a different kind of bullshit.
Plants require a different kind of shit.
That is a lawful term, though.
You want to call it dung, you want to call it dung.
But anyway, yeah.
So I've noted the azaleas, the morning glories, the blackberries, the roses,
just to see by next year, you know, is this something I can observe myself?
Do I need confirmation on this, or is it confirmed?
Plants certainly don't read the Pope's work schedule.
So there you go.
What are they going to adhere to?
They're going to adhere to the conditions that are, well,
pre-programmed in their biology to produce.
I mean, it's that simple, right?
According to the celestial bodies, and believe it or not,
the earth is a celestial body if you're not on the earth.
If you're standing on the moon, the earth is celestial to you, right?
But the earth is celestial objectively.
So, yeah, it does go by all these other things.
The reason why I started pressing the issue of how important it is for those
that work in any kind of industry with some modicum of professionalism that
rely on natural events, it is important to know lawful timekeeping,
but no, they don't want to, typically you want to hear that, right?
I mean, how many professions rely on things that are based on nature,
you know, even mining, you know, farming, fishing, you know,
on and on and on, right?
Agriculture.
And zoologists, right?
Entomologists.
People work with insects.
You can go on and on, and it's still ignored.
It might be, I wouldn't say it's the root of the problem,
but it's definitely one of the branches of it, right?
Well, it sure does seem as though if you don't adhere to the conditions on the
planet, you're working against yourself.
So, you know, there you go.
Okay, Joe, you want to just sit back and mute out or anything else?
We're just going to keep going.
We're going to keep plowing on the traces we laid out about food.
How does that sound to you?
Yeah, that sounds good.
I can mute out.
Yeah, you can mute out and hang by.
If you want to make a comment, you can either text it,
and I'll bring you in again, or just go ahead and shout.
So we're going to keep going.
To add one other aspect, since we're discussing food tonight,
there is a question in the chat room related to it,
and that is about what is it lawfully that one should be feeding their dog?
Because obviously the dog is not supposed to eat.
Well, let's just say you feed dog food to a dog, right?
I know you've said that before.
Well, there's no such thing as a carnivore.
They're really omnivores.
The carnivore term that they each strictly meet is a fallacy.
You'll find lions eating grass.
You'll find, you know, whatever.
You cut open a shark, you'll see all kinds of things in there,
not because they're trolling the bottom as garbage eaters, right?
There really is no distinct carnivore as such.
Many in the fish kingdom tend to be, you know, like the big fish eats the smaller fish
and so on and so forth.
There are some exceptions with insects and things like that.
But how do you lawfully – see, law comes from your god, from your deity.
So if you are an average surface-dwelling earth inhabitant,
you probably have succumbed to the goddess religion,
which you're going to look at the guys, the devils with the white lab coats.
They call them scientists and nutritionists and doctors to tell you,
and they are always changing, right?
But this is a question that comes up often.
It comes from your god.
And if you're going to have to do some research, it's called homework.
We've had some people call up and ask questions,
and obviously they didn't do their homework.
Maybe we'll use that as a – like the gong, right?
If you ask a basic question like who is god, you haven't done your homework,
we'll just red button you because that is a whole subject, right?
That's like you were talking about cars and you're asking what a steering wheel is.
Well, we should have gotten past that if we're talking about cars.
You should be slightly familiar.
When I say your god, you're going to have to look at what's been memorialized about the gods,
and you'll find there's really only one that gives law, and it's interesting.
And then it's a matter of whether you believe in it or not is not relevant,
is whether you have a lawful mind.
Think about it, Chuck.
If you don't like tennis, why are you going to try to get tennis lessons, right?
How many people don't like golf and go and get golfing lessons?
They don't.
You just avoid the whole thing if you don't have a desire for it.
So the problem with that – it's not a problem,
but if you're going to evaluate the status of humanity right now,
they're just generally downright unlawful and vile.
But fortunately, humanity is at a level of vileness right now, repugnant,
another word for being disgusting, in a juvenile sense.
What we've talked about things to come, starting in the next decade or so,
humanity's vileness is going to become more mature.
What does that mean?
Incredible brutality and cruelty.
See, an adult can bestow more brutality and cruelty on their victim than a child can.
So right now, what you've seen through human history is nothing compared to what is coming.
In other words, the level of lies and deceit mixed in with, let's say,
a cover of lawfulness is what's coming.
And it's going to be very pleasant because you've got to understand the human mind
or the spirit that most people have again succumbed to.
But that really came out of another – that's a whole other subject.
But let's go back to the dog.
Before we go back to the dog, I think that part of the failure here is that you're attempting to access laws given by a god
when people are not adhering to the laws which are already presented to them via their biology,
via their existence already.
We're acting in contradiction.
Well, there really are no laws.
A law is an abstract.
You know, like I've seen devices before used in industry,
and no matter how much I pondered it or took it apart and put it back together,
I really didn't know what it was until I got what was called the manual for it.
And then I was like, oh, man, I got it, you know, real quick.
And you could review the manual and the device could be on another continent
and be more familiar with it sometimes than having the device in the same room without the manual.
So let's go to high level of law.
Now, when you're dealing with the public, by the way, there's a lot of sayings about how vile the public is,
and I don't need to go.
You can mention a few of them.
Everyone's heard something about how the public is.
We're not addressing the public at large.
We're addressing the few that are looking for what things are based on, right, and reality,
meaning material reality, mind reality, which is spiritual reality.
And when you put the mind and the spirit together, you get alchemy or the ability to control both, right?
So when you look at the high level of law, let's just go through it very quickly, and I'm going to paraphrase.
It states, for example, if you touch a flesh of a dead thing, meaning like an animal,
whether it's fish, fowl or a four-legged or whatever, right, an animal,
you're in an unclean state, and the word used is tamah, which is, it actually doesn't really mean unclean.
It means you're doing it backwards with bad water.
All right, because water is very important.
So let me ask you, Chuck, you know, okay, so you touch the flesh of a dead animal.
You're unclean until noon.
If you wash, there's a lot of ceremonial washing, then you become clean after that, right?
So if a piece of fabric or whatever touches it, it's unclean.
Let me ask you, Chuck, if you're going to have a chicken sandwich, are you touching flesh?
Yes, right?
Yeah, at some point you have to, yeah.
Yeah, right, right.
So now if you're preparing food for a dog, are you touching dead flesh usually?
Yes, unless you're going to feed it live animal.
Right, most cases, yeah, you're not feeding live animals to your dog, true.
Right, in most cases, yeah, and I've seen junkyards dogs do otherwise.
But so what I would suggest being around, let's say, dogs is feed them before noon and then wash, and you'll be fine.
But then you get, you know, into that, that's the law for that.
It's very simple.
Okay?
Okay.
And most people, you know, hate law, right?
So you bring that up, like, you know, people say, well, whose law?
Well, who gets to make the laws?
And I've actually in public discussions before said, well, who gets to make the laws?
I was like, you do.
You choose it.
You choose the law, but you can't go, if you're going to go without choosing, you're still making a choice, right?
If you choose, right, if you choose no law form or the abandonment of any law form, you've just chosen what?
Unlawfulness, un-debasedness, right?
I don't care as long as it makes me happy.
Like you ever go into the marketplace, you know, and the way you don't conditionally endorse it is if someone rings you up,
you just give them some notes and you tell them, I hope you get money for it someday, you know, every time.
And that's how, you know, this way you're not endorsing it as money.
And, you know, if you discuss the money system with anyone, they're like, I don't care.
As long as I go to the store and buy something with it, I don't care, right?
So that's a choice, right?
You've gotten into – so the funny thing is most people that live or pursue or let's say don't concern or inquire about lawfulness
are the ones that complain the most.
But anyway, so have we ever complained about anything together on the show?
I don't think so.
Not to my memory, you know, it's possible.
I think maybe being smart about it, which means to poke with a sharp object or commentary, objective commentary,
leaving heresy out, heresy meaning what we prefer.
The funny thing is I always listen to people saying, well, I agree with that or I don't agree with that.
So who cares, you know, what you agree with.
It doesn't mean that – but this is the society that we're in.
So let's just jump back.
Let's jump off the merry-go-round and go – merry-go-round being the typical topical nature, that almost rhymes, of what we discussed,
which has essentially boiled down to commentary because we can discuss any subject
and you will see harsh commentary against or for the current conventions,
whether they're traditional, industrial, lawful, scientific, political or whatever.
You will see very harsh commentary or in contrast and it's actually quite objective.
Like jumping back on the topic though because we might want to title this a food show.
Let's just jump back in.
As we stated before, you'll notice that being on the planet, geographically,
there's a variety of what is considered to be foodstuff changes.
Now what is fit to eat, by the way, comes from your God as well.
Did we ever go through the food rules real quick?
Do you want to do that just for people?
I think that would be a good idea because when you discuss this, you often say latitudinally – excuse me.
I flubbed that word a little bit.
Or geographically.
That it does change and that this is what you need to observe.
But quite honestly, I don't think you've really broken that down for people.
Well, there are two different things here.
There are two different ways to look at it.
The first way is what's lawful from the divine sense,
and the other way is what makes sense based on your ability to acquire food to eat
and still be in balance and harmony with the environment.
And by the way, if anyone wants to look up what yin and yang is, like yin spelled W-I-N,
I mean Y-I-N and yang being Y-A-N-G, yin and yang,
which is the Taoist sort of relationship of the energies of ethereal energies of food,
they have several charts, yin and yang foods,
and, you know, like yin is a property and yang is a property
and they're on opposite ends of the scale.
That's another way to discern.
But let's do the lawful part first, and then we'll get into the geographical part.
All right?
All right.
The lawful part is very simple.
If you jump into a high level of law form, that's what makes, for example,
the scriptural text first class.
You've heard me say that.
It's not because I have an adherence to any particular desire.
It's just that I found it to be first class.
If I suggest, Chuck, I'm going to give you an international airplane ticket and it's free
and you could sit first class business or coach,
why would you sit anywhere other than first class, right?
And by the way, really good first class tickets run around 20 grand now these days.
And you could take a shower too, but anyway.
All right.
So here's the discernment, very simple.
If it's got a four-legged, let's get into the law,
and this is going to rub a lot of people the wrong way, but, you know, we're not there.
You know, in other words, if it's rubbing you the wrong way or you don't like it,
well, you know, just turn it off.
And here we go.
They're very simple.
This is from the high law form for mankind.
Okay?
Let's go through the four-legged animals.
If an animal's got four legs, it should chew the cud and have a clove and hoof.
And it also gives you discernment in the text.
In other words, a pig's got a clove and hoof, right, but it doesn't chew the cud, does he?
So he's out.
Now a rabbit chews the cud, but he has a paw, so he's out, right, or she.
So, you know, basically four-legged animals would be your cow, bovine, it would be lamb, goat,
those types of animals, llama, by the way.
The reason why the Scripture gives you discernment is so if, let's say, we're traveling somewhere
and we're looking for dinner and we're feeling like meat and we see a furry creature or a not-so-furry creature,
with four legs, what's the discernment for is it fitting proper to eat?
Well, does it have a clove and hoof?
Let's see.
Okay, that's check.
And does it chew the cud?
Yeah, it does.
Well, guess what?
That's dinner, right?
Like a llama, for example.
Someone was giving away a llama.
I looked him up and I said, man, this sucker chews the cud and it's got a clove and hoof.
That's dinner.
You know what I mean?
Which, by the way, I'm being asked about chew the cud, exactly how you would define that simply.
You could look it up.
There's several ways.
Rumination.
You ever hear of the term meditation, to meditate on something?
Well, of course.
Yeah, but that's a thoughtful way of chewing the cud.
You take something and you ever download a program to the computer that's, you know,
hundreds of megabytes or whatever and you don't use it until tomorrow or later,
you bring it up and use it a little bit at a time?
That's like similar parallel.
You could look up what chewing the cud is and the technical aspects of it.
Now let's jump to the next thing.
If it comes out of water, right, whether it's the ocean, the lake, the stream, the river,
freshwater, saltwater, it should have fins and scales.
Simple enough.
Does a clam fit?
No, ain't got no fins, ain't got no scales.
Lobster?
Ain't got no fins, ain't got no scales.
Now look at this.
A catfish, it's got fins, but it doesn't have scales.
Now a shark, it's got fins, but it ain't got scales.
It's got skin, right?
All right, so now you know your discernment for fish, right?
And that's real, or things that come out of the water, not necessarily fish.
Now the next thing is fowl, birds.
It should have a crop, which is like a second stomach.
You ever keep birds, chickens, doves, whatever, you ever throw down a lot of seeds or food,
you ever notice that they just keep pecking away and eating, right?
And you ever notice as they're doing that, their chest keeps getting bigger and bigger and bigger?
Right, that would be the crop section.
So most birds do have that.
The ones that don't have it would be like a swan, an eagle, a vulture, or a crow.
You ever heard of eating crow, and eating those types of birds is not considered lawful.
You ever hear about eating crow, like a saying, it's like taking back your own words or something, right?
Well, sure, you eat crow when you're being forced to eat something,
or you're being forced to consume the results of something that you've done poorly or incorrectly,
or you've made a statement, you're said to be eating crow, yeah.
Right, yeah, so these things kind of come in.
Now, the other thing is with plants.
That's real simple.
It should have green leaves and produce some kind of a seed.
Now, last week someone brought up to my attention,
he didn't answer one of the callers when he says, are potatoes lawful?
Well, do potatoes produce, do they have green leaves and a seed?
Yes, they do.
They have a flower.
Actually, we were discussing how sometimes certain potatoes will produce something that looks like a berry.
So in other words, Chuck, do mushrooms qualify?
Do they have green leaves and produce seeds or flowers, blossoms?
Do mushrooms do that?
No, they don't, do they?
Have you heard of these superfoods called spirulina, algae, you know, superfood, you know,
and it's like, well, okay, does algae produce, does it have green leaves and produce a seed?
No, it doesn't.
It produces through mitosis.
You know, a piece breaks off and it keeps growing, right?
Well, the same thing with plankton then, right?
There you go.
Well, yeah, plankton would be, I believe, a fauna, not a flora.
Fauna would be animal, flora would be plant.
So those are the rules from the high level of law, which is not to be discussed publicly,
but we did it, no harm done, right?
Now let's jump back to the practical aspect of it.
This is the part that I bring up about being geographically correct with your environment
or being in balance.
Like, for example, if you're living in an area where it's cold every day,
day in, day out for a season, your body will be adjusting to that environment different
than if you were living in a place that was warm day in and day out.
Very simple, right?
Just by looking at the clothing you wear and the way you actually feel
and looking at the environment.
Just look at the environment, right, how it looks in the winter and how it is in the summer.
Stop taking it for granted.
What you will see is that the foods and the things that are edible that are in a warm climate,
when you consume them locally or from the same latitude, right, because let's say, Chuck,
you're somewhere, I don't know, middle of the east coast of the U.S., right?
So you just put your finger across the map of the world and you'll find that 99% of the time,
as long as you move left or right from where you are,
you will see that the temperature and the climate and the food that grows is generally the same.
Like, you know, in the northeast, you'll see apples, pears, and cherries, right?
And down in the south, you'll see more tropical foods, you know, like maybe orange citrus
and maybe bananas and things, right?
And you'll see this across the planet.
So the reason I suggest eating cross-latitude is this way you have variety, okay?
So when you are in a hot climate and you eat the food from the surrounding environment
or cross-latitude as such, it will adjust your body to be in harmony with it.
Now, if you are in a cold climate, it will do the same.
Let's say, for example, you're in a cold climate, or it's a cold season like winter,
and you eat bananas.
Where do bananas grow in a warm climate, right?
That banana, when you consume it, will change your body chemistry to being in the tropics
and how are you going to fare in the wintertime?
Not very well.
That's why they tell these devils with white coats tell you vitamin C is good for colds,
and there's vitamin C in oranges.
And by the way, no one knows what's in food because the way they assay it or test it,
they juice out of the orange and they dehydrate it and they burn it
and combine it with chemicals to tell you there's vitamin C.
Now, you ever heard of measuring actually changing something, right?
You have to change it.
No one knows what's in an orange.
No one knows what's in a banana because in order to describe it scientifically,
you have to kill it, dry it, burn it, right?
So is it still the same?
No way.
No, it's been transformed by the use of heat.
Everything gets transformed when you heat it a bit.
Or you kill it.
Yeah, or it gets destroyed if you heat it too much.
Yeah, like if you're eating a banana, it's still alive,
but if you take it to a laboratory to tell you what's in it, they'll have to kill it, right?
Like they can produce all the, let's say, chemical constituents in a banana or a carrot,
but they can't put that in the ground and it will grow.
But you can take a carrot out of your fridge box right now and put it in the ground,
and guess what?
In three weeks, you'll see it growing, right?
You'll see even less than that.
You'll see evidence of growth.
Yeah, they're anti-life.
So that is a simple way we've discussed going back to the orange juice.
They tell the children you need vitamin C, and they're knee-deep in the snow in the northeast,
and they're all going out and buying orange juice because the citrus season is in the winter.
And do the children get better or do they get loaded up with mucus and all that, right?
They don't get better, do they?
No.
Yeah.
So I've had, I think I've mentioned nine out of ten people that I've recommended this to say it works.
The one out of ten that it didn't work went as such.
I said, well, what do you mean it didn't work?
And they replied, well, it just didn't work.
I said, well, what did you do or didn't do so I get some feedback?
They said, well, I didn't do any of it.
It just didn't sound right.
Okay.
So I have to include them as, you know, the one that didn't work because they didn't even bother trying it.
But anyone who's ever bothered living this way.
Now, by the way, Chuck, you've heard, okay, let's just say it this way.
This isn't really good for commerce, is it?
How much is invested in transport ships?
Right now, Chuck, you can go to what they call a local grocery store or supermarket,
and you'll probably find foods from tropical places right now wherever you are, let's say, in the western world, right?
Oh, complete displacement in the vegetation.
I mean, you get stuff from China, in some cases, being delivered to small-town America.
In other cases, you have stuff from Mexico showing up in New York City, et cetera.
So, yeah.
Well, China may not be bad because it's cross-latitude.
Like Sichuan or north of Guangzhou, you might be able to get cross-latitude.
But you're really fumbling into the tropical zone, let's say, in the cold northeast.
And this is not going to be good for, you know, you're adapting to the cold weather.
Now, I've heard people say, you know, I'm a schoolteacher, and I caught the cold from the children.
But you ever notice that the little girl who lives in a traditional Chinese family didn't catch the cold,
or the other fellow who eats traditionally, the child didn't catch the cold, but everyone else did?
The reason why they think that you actually caught the common cold from someone is because if you go at the supermarket,
you'll see the schoolteacher pushing a cart, buying bananas in December, what they call December,
and most of the parents from all the other children buying similar foods.
And also you have what's called the pagan holidays around this time.
And they're full of sugary, you know, sweets.
Aren't there a lot of sweets and exotic foods being brought during what they call the holiday season?
Do you think they sweeten it with apple juice, or do you think they're sweetening it with all forms of whatever?
Chocolate.
And where does sugar come from, too?
That's another thing, right?
Yeah.
And the corn syrups that they're using are grass tars.
So the thing is, again, we've also mentioned if bacteria is the cause for causing the cold or these flu symptoms,
that means we can all throw out our refrigerators because it seems that they're getting more active when it gets colder.
The reason we have refrigeration is to put these little bugs into dormancy, so the food, you know.
So anyway, if there are logic that…
Well, you know, along this line, real quick, by the way,
before you get into the thing about the little bugs that get into you and allegedly give you, you know, your diseases,
how about coffee, though?
Because coffee is one of those things that is not…
Yeah, it's tropical.
So what about coffee?
Well, here's the thing.
You gauge how well you're adapting to the environment,
and then you gauge at what level of extremes you're going to sequester the range of what you're eating.
Meaning if it's wintertime where you're at and you like drinking coffee all year round and you're okay,
you know, you're not eating bananas and a lot of tropical foods and sugars,
and you're okay, you know, you could do more coffee or keep doing the coffee.
But let's say you go out and you're cold and you're uncomfortable.
You should cut the coffee back.
There are coffee substitutes that were developed during the 40s, what they call World War II.
Tropical shipping lanes were shut off, so the people in Europe, they love their coffee.
Germans, Swiss, Norwegian, I mean, you know, they love coffee there,
and actually they prepare coffee.
The Italians, right, they all love coffee.
So they couldn't get coffee as easily as they used to because of the war,
so they came up with various coffee substitutes.
Jano was one of them.
Cafix is another.
They're basically roasted nuts and chicory that are ground together.
So that is another good coffee substitute.
You won't get the buzz from the caffeine,
but that will give you a headache for a day or two if you really do a lot of coffee, right?
So there's the thing about coffee.
The thing is about showing discernment, you know.
That's why, again, you know, any first-class information allows, let's just say it this way.
You're showing people how to fish instead of giving them fish, right?
That's more first-class, let's say, right?
Well, that's the best way, yeah, absolutely.
So discern based on where it grows and where you're at,
and that's basically the aspect of, you know, the discernment of food.
The subject matter was pretty much going to go into the fine subtleties that can be conveyed through,
sonically conveyed about not screwing up food.
Like, for example, you brought up coffee,
and people ask me about this type of coffee or that type of coffee,
you know, more like a connoisseur or a coffee snob, let's say, right?
And before I get into it too much about the subtleties of preparing like a perfect cup of coffee,
I ask them, how are you going to make it?
The minute they say they've got a coffee maker, you know, the ones you plug in, you know, and all that,
like you said, you're going to ruin good coffee with that.
You can't – that is not for good coffee.
Actually, if you actually look at the history of that, when the electric coffee –
I guess there's name brands, you know, a coffee machine, you know, that you see, right?
You pour the water in, you put the grinds in, push the button, walk away, right?
Right, right.
Okay, when that was developed and became widespread, they had to reformulate coffees.
That's why when you go down what they call the shops, they say this is really good for coffee machines.
You ever know – you know, they used to say that.
Because if you have really good coffee, you're ruining it and that thing because the water is too hot
and it just – the dwell time is too long.
So you have a lot of name brand coffees that were actually marketed as being very good in coffee machines, right?
You remember growing up in, let's say, this is not really being shown so much as it was, let's say, 25, 30, 40 years ago.
Buy this coffee because it works well in a machine.
So you're going to ruin coffee.
You know, we're going to talk about the subtleties of things like that.
So you're not going to make a cup of coffee in a coffee machine, period.
Yeah, and with exposure to some barista training,
I do understand that there is a difference in the way that you expose it to heat and things like that.
The dwell time, the grinding process is actually rather important as well.
You know, all of these things play a role in what it is you create.
And then there's this crap they call instant coffee, which is absolutely awful.
Well, you know, if you've got to live, you know, when I was traveling and doing work with mines and things like that,
living out of a van for a couple of months, you know, instant coffee saved my life, literally.
Okay.
I'm not going to say I haven't drank it, and I'm not going to say I haven't utilized it.
I'm just going to say I don't appreciate it as much.
Right.
There you go.
So let's get into the subtleties.
The discernment aspect is there.
The thing is, you know, one thing that is not discussed in how to discern anymore is quality.
If you ever look at people, again, in these grocery stores or supermarkets,
they have a list of things to buy.
It seems like if they're going to pick up a piece of fruit or vegetable or a package,
they look the other way while they're loading it into the cart,
where traditionally you would inspect the vegetable or the fruit.
You know, you smell it by the stem.
You look for its texture, its color, its fragrance.
I notice that people have abandoned that as much as they used to do it these days, right?
So you're going to have to learn how to discern quality,
and the quality of that is, of course, then based on eating locally.
If you want to adapt to the environment or the season that you're in,
there's a very simple way to look at it.
Now, one thing we can jump to in terms of seasonal eating, when you, for example,
dehydrate, pickle, or cook something, you're changing it.
That is a very basic form of transmutation or alchemy.
Alchemy meaning like there's a, you know, like, for example, in America on the East Coast,
you know, you get a pickle with your hamburger.
No one says, give me cucumber with the hamburger.
They say, give me a pickle, and a pickle's got a very distinct flavor.
There's different types of pickles as such, but you know what that is.
That is basically a brined cucumber of a certain type, right?
And, you know, when you eat a pickle, it's a pickle, man.
It's not a cucumber.
Well, yes, it is.
Like when you eat a banana chip, which are quite tasty, that is no longer a banana.
It's changed.
Even its chemical constituencies have changed to a degree.
They've been, you know, readjusted, let's say.
So, for example, traditionally, what you grew in the summer, you pickled for eating in the winter,
whether it was beans and veg and things like that.
So when you have something that is pickled, it is more permissible, let's say,
in your adaptive capability to eat, as long as it's not too extreme.
That's why I mentioned to people, look up what yin and yang is, Y-I-N and Y-A-N-G.
There's a couple of charts.
Now, the macrobiotics are really into this stuff.
I call them macroneurotics.
But, you know, you want to cherry-pick the best information.
But you also want to discern there might be some really good information in some really crappy settings.
There's a lot of stuff on the Internet that's just really, really bad,
and they might have a little kernel in there.
But you don't want to go sifting through somebody's poop to get a piece of undigested corn, now do you?
But anyway, so you've got to use your discernment on that.
So the thing here now to get into the subtleties, I mean, there's the concept you brought up, coffee.
We can rely on some input, if you like.
I don't think it would be prudent for time to go over all the things that we did over almost four hours
on Uncommon Radio, which is on AFR archives.
We talked about rice.
I think one of the callers, Regular Joe, gave us the praises on the stovetop baked, you know,
and all these other things that were shortcuts that actually increased the quality.
I think what do you think, Chuck?
Should we do a quick review on those things, or should we just direct everyone to the archive?
I think we should direct everyone to the archive if it already exists.
If they really want the information, they can go get it.
And we should blaze new trails here is what I think should happen, is my opinion.
No, let's do that.
The addendum, let's say, to what we've discussed previous would be as such.
When you're purchasing food or growing food or acquiring food for quality, for its quality,
or you want to learn more about what is quality food is something that we can discuss.
We can get into also the nature of water and how to prepare water and other things like that.
Now, one thing I didn't get into, which we could start getting more into, is what is quality?
How do you define that, right?
Well, obviously it is a characteristic or a trait when you're looking either at a grouping of things
or an individual of things.
Like, for example, Chuck, if you were, let's say, commercially ready to purchase a few tons of apples,
do you just glaze over the truck as it backs over,
or do you start pulling a few apple representative samples out and looking at them very closely individually?
Representative samples, especially random sampling, is usually the smartest thing
because you're not necessarily going to have the time and resources available to inspect every single piece.
So it would be wise to, at the very least, take a representative sample.
Exactly.
So this is what you do.
So if you have an interest, for example, and if you go back to the archives,
you'll learn about very simple ways to be more efficient and produce good meals.
We didn't get into the quality aspect.
So let's say you're out shopping.
Most people, I think we even mentioned in the last show, are living in this society,
which is not geared towards self-manifesting food production.
In other words, most people, when they think of getting food, they have to go to the market these days, right?
Well, right.
Now, listen, I don't want that point to be cut off.
We are living in a point in time in human history where you are quite disconnected from your own food production.
But I think that is something that should be covered at the top of the next hour
because, well, you hear the music.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotic.
Yes, I like.
Very much.
Radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions, running my companies, and I hated feeling groggy and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret.
The powers that be want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride.
Our brains are under siege and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve, a revolutionary breakthrough in a category of cognitive enhancers called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself at DNAEvolveSample.com.
That's DNAEvolveSample.com.
Supplies are limited, so go to DNAEvolveSample.com right now.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces three brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates, and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
Yo, what's up? Check this out.
The voice of the revolution.
American Freedom Radio.
What about show business?
Show business, completely dishonest, corrupt, and full of shit, but in a nice way.
Plenty of expensive drugs and perverted sex.
If you're gonna be full of shit, might as well enjoy your work.
Then you have the media.
Not just the news media, let's include them all.
The media are almost literally exploding with bullshit.
Because they're located right at the crossroads of all the other bullshit.
The media are made up of equal parts advertising, politics, business, public relations, and show business.
These people are sitting right at bullshit junction.
There's enough bullshit in the media for Texas to open a branch office.
And you still have enough left over to start two law firms and a Christian bookstore.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Providers for free education?
Well, that's obviously a factor, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America...
All the information they provide is free?
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, man?
Exploiting commonplace corruption?
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice?
Bringing light to important information nobody else does?
Well, they never censor, hang up, or cut off their guests?
Well, that's no fun, is it?
Well, they created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative, and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shows and scum?
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from,
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable people without a voice,
bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream, and alternative media shows and scum?
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are.
American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents.
Second hour begins of Ocelli and the Greek here on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
where I will just take this moment to say that you could and should, if you're being provided information, consider making a donation.
Of course, if you go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com, there is a big old donate banner there,
and I advise you click on it and use it because, well, you are receiving information from this network that is not heard elsewhere,
and you definitely get a different style of things here that you don't get anywhere else.
I mean, personally, as a broadcaster on my own show separate from this one, there are no restrictions that I'm held to.
I am absolutely an independent purveyor of information, and this show is an example of, well, things that are not being said elsewhere.
So there you go.
Let's keep that in mind as we move forward.
Now I've done that for the day, and you guys entered a bunch of things in text.
Do you mind if I get to a couple of things really quick before we get back to discussion?
It's about what they're thinking at some level, too, so go for it.
Roll on.
Okay.
Well, first off, there is the – and I'll group these things all together.
Preparing water for man, animals, and the soil, there should be a difference, it seems.
Yes, there is.
There would probably be conventional ways in which this is universal.
There's sort of the best conditions for water.
You and I did a private show about that particularly, which is at my website.
But I don't know if you want to address that quickly.
Yeah, we could.
Let's go down through all of them and then just remind me so we don't – I need adult supervision.
So go for it.
No problem.
In this case, I am playing the role of an adult on radio, although I may not be one in real life.
Back to it, there is the question about alcohol and tobacco
and whether these things are lawful slash fit and proper depending on the questioner.
That question was asked by more than one person.
My favorite question here, which is really – I figured this should have explained itself,
but is cannabis lawful, fit and proper?
To me, it appears to be fit and proper as a food,
and it appears to be fit and proper for consumption and all things, in fact.
So I don't know. Maybe I'm incorrect.
So there's the three things I wanted to bring up, and who knows what else will come next.
By the way, we haven't gotten a regular phone caller yet on the listener line at 218-339-8525.
218-339-8525, we have gotten one Skype caller,
which if you search on Skype for the contact Ocelli and the Greek
and ask for contact with that Skype handle, you can be added to the conversation.
The Greek is in control of that.
I am in control of the phone lines.
So there you go. There's your opportunity to chime in.
Ask your question directly.
We'll make a comment providing you adhere to it.
Chuck, your audio is fading like you're going down a tunnel.
Maybe AFR will check that on their end.
I just wanted to pre-explain.
Okay. All right.
Well, we were getting into the – let's just answer the questions real quick.
I think one of them was the lawfulness of things.
We mentioned the discernment of what is lawful earlier based on a high level of law,
which is pretty much unknown by most people,
but we mentioned in any way you could seek the archive from the first hour for that.
And all of those things do meet being lawful,
meaning the sources of all those things you mentioned,
like for example, alcohol doesn't grow on trees, does it?
But the source of it, what is lawful, right, generally speaking, right?
And the cannabis and all these other things.
And the first thing people think of is mind or mood or physical altering properties of those things,
whether it's the cannabis, tobacco, coffee, caffeine or whatever.
That's the first thing that comes to mind in terms of a grouping, right?
But wait a minute. Here's the problem with that.
Doesn't everything we consume actually have the capability of altering mind or mood?
Even if it is in a very minor sense.
Or major, yeah. And we're going to get into that when we discuss the quality of things.
But let's just revisit that, and I'll show you some experiments that anyone can do to prove that,
what you just said, from subtle to extreme.
Okay.
If you read the allegory and the metaphor and the explanation of high level law,
you can pretty much do anything as long as you don't lose what's called self-control
and knowledge of what is right or wrong.
Like, for example, if you overconsume alcohol, you might eventually lose your grip
and control over what is right and wrong.
Like, for example, you might just pee on yourself, right, or something.
And you can go on and on.
The same with cannabis and tobacco and other things as well.
You can actually smoke yourself into oblivion, even with just tobacco.
Actually, nicotine, before a lot of the newer synthetic chemicals, was a major ingredient in insecticide, right?
Yeah, wonderful pesticide, in fact, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I think one, I think a milligram is enough to kill you if it's injected subdermally.
Or a tenth of a milligram or something.
So all of these things, there are certain, let's say, quote, unquote, religious circles that say no coffee,
no alcohol, or this or that or whatever.
And that is just basically keeping people in that state.
You know, you just want to get over it.
Like, in other words, you are not your behavior.
If you were, quote, unquote, alcoholic or addicted to any other substance,
because there are physical dependencies where the body no longer compensates and requires a substance, right?
Like, you've heard of people withdrawing from any substance, and it's usually uncomfortable, right?
Usually you survive it as well.
So that's because the body is no longer compensating and is relying on that chemical to produce a certain function in the body,
being a biological machine, right?
And that's all the withdrawal is.
But you are not your behavior, for example.
That's why I've spoken privately, a lot of people ask me about Alcohol Anonymous,
and I've researched that and it is a horrible, horrible institution.
Most of its victims state that it's helped them a lot, but they don't realize the trap that they're in, right?
And the trap is that they are now defining you by your behavior.
In other words, they take that behavior and make it empirical versus ephemeral.
Empirical meaning something that does not change versus ephemeral, which is something that can change.
And that is actually one part of the pranking that is considered traditional.
I don't want to get into that because there's many organizations that are supposedly supposed to help people with quote-unquote addictions,
and what I've discovered is that they are doing nothing more than creating a subclass in society of people
that really needed to be propped up and helped to go through that,
and what they're doing is they're pinning it on them as being a function of their actual self.
You say alcoholism is a disease, or I was an addict to this, and I will be one for the rest of my life.
I mean, that is not true, right?
In other words, if you run a red light, you are not defined as a red light runner, are you?
You just happen to do it.
Even if you did it for five years in a row every day, that is not who you are.
That is a behavior, right?
And so that is a thing when you ask, for example, certain religious things,
when you ask people who are born-again Christians being saved, ask them, saved from what?
And they can't answer you.
They don't know.
Now, here's an odd thing, though, because when people perform a certain task in life,
which is supposed to be their vocation, a lot of times they are then described as that vocation,
and their actions do become a label.
Yes, it's a label, but it can change.
You are not that.
You happen to be highly skilled in that.
Like years ago, someone says, hey, man, you know how to roll a Philly or a Dutch?
I'm like, what are you talking about?
It's basically where you buy a cigar, tear it open, and fill it with marijuana.
And I didn't know what the hell they were talking about, and they showed me.
I was like, holy crap, that's a lot of skill to do that.
I don't roll very well myself.
They could be doing that all their lives.
If they are considered to be defined as that's what they are,
would that be considered a high level or a low level of existence?
Don't answer that.
Leave it for the listener to consider that question.
You know what I mean?
So there's many aspects to it.
So basically if you're losing knowledge of what you should do or shouldn't do,
now is it possible to go into an unlawful baseless state?
Absolutely, right?
And that's where that behavioral aspect goes into.
But the discernment of that now, the questions, you know,
let's say we're leaning towards the mind-altering stuff, right,
which is also physically altering.
You know, a lot of these substances, if you do a lot of it, you actually,
you know, you could lose your teeth, your hair, you get bad skin,
things like that, too.
So it's not just mind-altering.
You know, we didn't bring up magic mushrooms.
You've heard of that before, right, and peyote and things.
Well, is that lawful?
Well, let's see.
Does it have the criteria for plant-based consumables?
No, it doesn't, right?
It's not green.
It doesn't have a seed.
It doesn't produce anything like that.
See, so that's another thing.
I just brought that in because that is something that there is a,
quote-unquote, market or sector of society that does talk about that
and use that as well, right?
So where the poppy plant, for example,
where things are produced, morphines and opioids and opiates, for example,
that is lawful, right, because it meets the criteria.
They make a flower.
They have green leaves.
It produces a seed.
Where the mushroom would not fit the discerning criteria.
You can have whatever you want.
We're just mentioning the basics of it.
So that's where the quality aspect comes in.
Now, we were discussing about doing a representative batch sampling, right?
So when you're going to the market, whether you consider yourself to be
vegetarian, whether to be a carnivore, those are the two, you know,
meat lover and vegetarian, those are the two extremes, right?
Let's leave the breatharians out and all that.
And then there's a mix in between, right?
There's pescatarians, people who the only animal they would eat would be fish.
And then there's ovolactic.
They don't eat meat, but they eat dairy products and eggs, right?
There's all these varieties in there of that.
Now, how do you understand the quality and how do you discern the quality before
you get into preparation is by getting a sample of it.
For example, when you're buying at the market, ask them if the source is
consistent, whether you're going to be buying meat from them or fish or any eggs
or whatever, is your source consistent?
In other words, is that, let's say there's a particular brand on the product,
let's say eggs or whatever, you know, you can ask, you know, are they consistent?
You know, with the Internet you can go and look up the company,
see how consistent they are.
Is there complaints about consistency?
Is there complaints about cleanliness?
Because that stuff is very easy to access.
Now, where years ago you had to do, let's say, a FOIA request from the FDA
or something, right?
So you look for consistency.
Another thing to see for consistency is if you don't get information on that,
you're going to have to get a sample.
Years ago when I used to go shopping at places like Balducci's or Dina and
DeLuca and all that, when you bought olive oil, for example, as a courtesy,
they had one open and a bowl with some of the olive oil
and pieces of bread around it.
So before you, you know, made a purchase, you know, right?
Sample.
You've seen that done very often.
Oh, yeah.
Well, even going to a deli counter, you used to be able to say, you know,
let me see, let me try the cheese or try the meat or whatever too.
Yeah, and they do accommodate you still.
Very often when a lot of things are vacuum packed and sealed,
it's kind of hard to do that.
So there's your answer.
If you can, for quality, Chuck, I think you closed the first hour.
It would be simple that the chances of you knowing
or meeting the person who grew the food you're going to eat are slim to none
these days, right?
If you don't know who, right.
So now you're going to have to go to the next level.
Even to the next level with these super-duper superstores,
the chances of you even knowing the people who are selling it to you are slim to
none.
The clerks and the matters are always changing, right?
Right.
So it's this anonymous, would you say lack of character,
lack of human interaction with the way people acquire food.
So how do you start discerning?
So let's say you're shopping without giving a name at one of these super-duper
stores, whatever.
That's what I think they call them these days, right?
Let's say you go to, let's pick meat, for example.
When an animal is slaughtered and it knows it's going to die,
the adrenaline in the body starts to go up very high.
Now, the quality of adrenaline does not go away from the meat,
even at a high temperature.
I think adrenaline, in order to start destabilizing the molecule,
is way above the boiling point of water,
which is 212 or so Fahrenheit or 100 degrees Celsius centigrade,
where even a super well-done piece of meat is about 180.
So there's no way you're going to be able to cook the adrenaline out of meat,
right?
So in other words, when the animal, you've heard of like halal,
as in Muslim means permissible and haram is unpermissible.
The way of slaughtering animals, quote-unquote humanely, right,
is where the animal is in a relaxed state and doesn't pour this adrenaline.
One of the symptoms, I'm just kind of cherry-picking the quality categories here.
One of the ways to know if you had meat that was, let's say,
tainted with a lot of adrenaline is if you have a meal and that night you get
night sweats or you feel very, let's say, anxious,
or you might get a slight headache but it's not really a headache,
or you might feel muscles or tendons contracting.
Those are all symptoms of adrenal, let's say, influx into the digestive system.
There are many others, but that is a simple way.
Let's say I've had many people, you know, I said, how was the steak there?
And they're like, it was great.
And then I stopped them there.
I said, well, how'd you sleep that night?
They're like, it's funny you ask.
You know, I kind of got up three times to go to the bathroom and I had a night sweat.
I'm like, oh, great.
Now I know.
The steak there isn't that great.
It's full of adrenaline, right?
And that is a very simple way to discern certain things.
Many of these markets that do sell meats, they tend to have a consistent supplier.
So if you go somewhere, you get yourself a piece of meat, whether it's fowl or not,
meaning bird or whatever, beef or anything else like that, just do a small sample,
cook it up, see how you feel.
Give yourself maybe 24 hours and see if you felt good, right?
That is a very simple way when you're dealing with the flesh of an animal.
I see that there is also, just to address since we're on the topic of animals,
what comes out of the water, let's say.
Someone addressed Fukushima and the water and all that.
Now, that is a subject that we have addressed in the past.
I think there's an old man that goes around the Internet.
He's quite popular, not to mention his name.
I think a year ago or two, he was saying,
we're all going to die from Fukushima and we're all still here.
The nature of things radioactive, by the way, is still unknown to most people.
Even nuclear physicists, when they work in the industry,
they have to be privately taught on what is really going on.
I would invite anyone to consider a video called Nuclear Scare Scam by Galen Windsor.
You're not going to like it, but it's the truth.
The reason why you're told these nuclear things are so dangerous is because to protect the inventory.
If people knew really how, I wouldn't say harmless,
but not as harmful as radioactive material is as they've been told,
the industry that has radioactive material would have to install a very elaborate security apparatus
because people would break into nuclear power plants and grab the rods with their hands and walk out with them.
So if you tell people they're highly toxic and dangerous, everyone stays away.
So it's basically the reverse psychology of preventing the installation of an incredible security apparatus.
I mean, refined plutonium could be 100,000 a gram, right?
So you've all been scammed.
Watch Windsor Galen.
I'm not necessarily endorsing him, but if you speak to people,
that's why whenever there is any nuclear event other than the ones that you're not supposed to know about,
they never have anyone from the industry discussing it publicly.
It's always someone from academia or a critic, right?
And we just said that even if you go to academia, you don't know what's going on until you get into industry.
So the worst you're going to get from a nuclear disaster like that is a bad case of the measles.
Now, what people don't understand is nuclear power plants and nuclear events as such that are used in industry,
it's not necessarily the nuclear material itself,
but all the other materials surrounding the nuclear material that is used, for example, to control the reaction.
Like you've heard of cooling water and things like that.
I don't want to get into this too deeply, but there are things like, for example,
there's a substance called pyrocool, and it is a water that – it's an additive you put in water,
and it's considered a UV suppressor, ultraviolet suppressor, and that is very toxic.
When you look at the refinement of nuclear material, we were talking about some really nasty acids.
I don't want to get into the specifics.
And when those are dumped into the environment or exposed to the environment are extremely toxic.
So overall, the industry itself, not just the material itself,
but all the other materials that surround that industry are extremely toxic.
Yes, you see.
So it is a bad thing all around.
But no, you're not going to die from Fukushima, and it's not affecting as much as you're being told,
because that makes for really good – what do they call – what's that term, porn?
Fear porn.
Fear porn, yeah.
People like that.
So I'm not going to get into this, because this is very –
there are certain subjects I don't get into in public, which is like 9-11,
what nuclear material really is, certain aspects or whatever,
because the wave that the public is minding of information regarding that subject is so contrary to the reality of it
that you can't – you have no – you don't even have a chance to even have a rational discussion on it.
Because people are in – whenever you bring up things like 9-11 or nuclear industry and other topics,
the moon landing, people are very heavily emotionally invested in them,
and you cannot – just like the old – what is it – private investigator movies in the 30s, black and white,
when the woman comes in to hire a private investigator, she's crying.
He can't get anything out of her until she gets emotionally level, right?
It's like just the facts, ma'am.
Remember that?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, why don't you just relax?
So right now, there's too many subjects that are too emotionally based.
So just eat some chocolate, drink some wine, relax, and then maybe in the future, it will be discussed, the emotional side.
So okay, let's go back to the quality.
What do you think?
Well, yeah, I do want to go back to the quality,
but I also want to remind you that we needed to discuss water a bit more, number one,
and number two, a couple of other interesting thoughts have come into my sphere here.
One of them is a question about have you ever attended AA or any recovery group yourself?
That's one thing.
Yes, I have with some people.
I was very curious.
I did some research on that in the 80s.
Okay.
That's one question answered easily.
Another one is that if you're not defined by your actions,
then what is the point of adhering to lawful actions if they're not going to define you?
The lawful actions affect the environment very heavily.
So the reason you live lawfully is because of your responsibility to others around you and the environment.
I think we've discussed this back when we did the initial Ocelli and the Greek roundabout
where the reason why you're having so many natural disasters and toxic water
and bad situation on this planet is not because you're actually polluting the planet.
It's because of the way you're behaving to each other.
See?
The planet reacts to it.
You know, this might sound kind of redundant because everyone else kind of says it,
but they can't give any details, is do you know that the Earth has a spirit?
It has a mind also?
Oh, yeah, we do.
Can you tell me about it?
No, they can't.
The specifics of it is the things like the Earth, the sun, I know this sounds kind of hooky-dokey, whatever,
the moon, all the celestial bodies around the Earth, they have a spiritual quality to them
that is also dependent, their behavior is dependent on man's behavior to each other.
So if you're not defined by your own behavior, the reason why you do things that are lawful would be,
I think we gave the analogy, like if you're in the military on a surface ship,
you probably won't be reprimanded carrying a loaded sidearm.
But if you're in a submarine, you probably will be highly reprimanded for carrying a loaded sidearm
because if it goes off, you're jeopardizing the entire ship.
You see?
It's very different.
So on this ship, for example, there's a high level of law that states that if you do these things,
you will have peace, prosperity, the Earth will give you abundance, you'll have good water, good weather.
Right?
So that's why when you read, for example, in certain ancient writs, certain things are punishable by death,
like deliberately murdering someone or other things.
It has nothing to do with what your morality judgment call on that is.
It is to satisfy the Earth.
And there are substitutions.
Now, this is a complex concept, but it's a very simple concept when you grasp that there is a necessity for law form.
Right?
Absolutely.
That makes perfect sense.
But we did kind of skip over the water for animals, soil, and people.
Let's go for that.
Yeah, let's skip that one.
Well, for example, let's go for plants.
For example, you ever notice no matter how much you water a lawn through, let's say, municipal water or well water,
it doesn't green up as well as if you get a rainfall for 15 minutes, right?
Right.
The reason for that is the quality of the water.
The Victor Shawberger, I would send someone or anyone to start looking at his mindset regarding water.
He brings up something called immature water, which is a water that is ready to take on other qualities,
but it doesn't have – it's not very vital.
Plants enjoy that very much because the other thing you have to remember,
and this goes back to the episode we called the container.
If you rinse off – have a plant, any plant, monocot preferably, like grass.
Take it out of the ground or an onion.
Rinse it off really well.
Get a spray bottle and spray the roots with it.
Does the water get absorbed immediately into the root,
or does the water kind of pill up and bead on the root like a freshly waxed car?
The answer is the second.
Have you ever done that, right?
Yeah.
No, absolutely.
A lot of times what you'll have is it will seem to just sit on the surface of the plant.
And it beats up like a freshly waxed car almost.
So that's called hydrophobic.
It means it doesn't want the water to go near it.
So when you're actually watering plants, you're not watering the plants.
You're watering the soil.
There's a big difference in concept there.
When you have an extreme situation like a plant cutting or removing the plant and putting it in water,
yes, it will live longer in the water than not in the water,
but typically when it's in its natural state, you're watering the soil.
So that is a completely different concept now, right?
That's why the problem with irrigation is not necessarily getting the water to the plant,
but it's actually the erosion that's caused by irrigation, damaging of the soil.
Victor Schauberger talks about that also.
There's a system of watering that he discusses.
Now, with animals, animals tend to be a little more forgiving because they don't really complain about dirty water
as much as people would if you offered them to drink, right?
Whether it's a communication thing because we're not really speaking,
they're not really directly communicating with us,
or whether because every time even though there's a dirty bowl of water, the dog will drink it,
who is he to complain to, right?
When was the last time you gave a dog a bone and he told you it didn't taste good, right?
It doesn't happen usually, right?
I mean, they might act a certain way.
Now, you got to realize that the effects of the animal are very different.
There's a field that runs through everything, okay?
A very simple description is Wi-Fi or radio.
You don't see it, but certain devices pick it up.
You ever notice how the majority of humanity, their spinal column is vertical?
You have these bones that carry nerve tissue through the center and other things that are stacked vertically.
You ever notice most animals, is their spine running vertical according to the earth, perpendicular,
or is it parallel to the earth's surface or horizontal?
You ever notice that?
Parallel or horizontal, right.
Right. You know the concept of an antenna.
Years ago, if you move an antenna one way, you get good reception, and bad reception in another direction.
The reason why we have, you know, people can get on all fours, but animals tend to be there
because that is where they have the best reception for the fields and the ether that is going through the planet.
This is a little bit maybe, would you say esoteric, occult maybe, knowledge?
Let's just give it anyway, right?
People are vertical.
Apes can go both ways, but we didn't evolve from apes.
I assure you that.
You'll find that out later.
If you want to believe that, that's fine.
So these things also are part of what you tune yourself to and what you find acceptable.
For example, the highest quality water, even for plants to a certain degree, would be spring water type quality, right?
That is where the water is manifest in its highest quality, meaning for temperature and quality of conveying energy, let's just say.
It would make sense if the earth itself is governing the temperature, then it would be best for that area if the water came from there.
Wouldn't it be best to keep the water local, too?
Yes, it is, versus transport.
For example, if you're going to produce an elaborate device, meaning an elaborate device that produces exceptional quality water,
you should be able to use any water source to produce excellent water quality on the business end, right?
And this was sort of presented to certain people, and they said, you know that, for example, in Japan,
there are cargo ships that show up every day to unload bottled water from France.
And with the device that you have here, for example, your water is far superior.
They can take water from anywhere and have exceptional quality water.
So that's the idea with the principle with Victor Schauberger.
But now there's two types of water.
Let's get to the plants, animals, and food right away.
We have about a half hour left, and you know how long winded we can get or the Greek can get regarding water.
So let's keep it real.
I was going to say, not necessarily me, but yeah, go ahead.
Well, let's just say, yeah.
The thing is, all information has to accommodate the audience.
So since the question was asked, let's just cut to the chase and give it based on the discernment.
This is how you basically would want to look for fish, right, versus being given fish.
Now, water is in two basic states, you know, that you deal with after it's rained or somehow you're dealing with it.
You could even deal with water as it's falling from the sky, but typically you will find water in two basic states.
The basic states that it's in is one, that it's moving, you know, a river, a tap from your house, of the house,
or, you know, some delivery system where there's movement.
And the other state is where it's stationary in a container.
So those are the two different states, okay?
So we'll go with the stationary one first.
If you look in the natural world, whenever water or something that's predominantly water,
like organs in the body or other things like that, plants and things like that,
you'll notice that when there is a given amount of fluid, it's always in an ovoid shape, ovoid meaning egg-like,
meaning it appears to be round or spherical, but one end is a little pointier than the other.
And the reason why that is is because the ovoid or the egg shape creates an instability,
a geometric instability, which allows for dynamic movement, although it be slow in many cases,
to occur within the fluid.
And because of the dynamicism, you have a consistent temperature.
In other words, you don't have a hot side and a cold side, and also pathogens don't want to grow,
and it also prevents gases from forming.
Now, why wouldn't, for example, a sphere be or an ellipse?
Because when you have a sphere, the distance of the outside of the sphere to the center is equal in all directions, right?
So if you were to put fluid into that, and even if there was slight motion,
it would immediately become static because the distance to the center is the same.
Now, if you have an elliptical shape that is 3D, let's say, well, the two ends are pointy now, right?
Now, not all the outside is the same distance from the center, but because it's symmetrical,
there will be movement, and then the symmetry sets in, and because the opposite sides are equal,
it will find staticness again.
So now let's visit the ovoid shape.
The center of the egg is almost like a triangle, not quite.
It's actually constructed from a pentagram, by the way, and it's outside of the pentagram.
You use a triangle, a circle, and a pentagram to construct, let's say, a chicken egg geometry, right?
Right.
You will find, because one end of the egg is a little pointier, less oblong than the other opposite end, right?
Because that's the first thing you see.
If you see a spherical shape and you say, well, or a round shape, you say, that's egg-shaped,
typically it denotes one end is a little sharper of an angle than the opposite end, right?
Typically, in any object, it's egg-shaped.
So you would say in that case, then, when you look at the mass, center of mass of the egg,
and the two opposite sides, if there's any movement, that movement will continue,
because as each opposing end tries to find the center, when it reaches the other end,
because it's geometrically different, it will be deflected and reflected differently towards the center,
and this goes on perpetually.
Very simple, right?
So this is why you're looking for an egg shape.
Now, an egg shape doesn't have to look like a chicken egg.
It could be what's called an amphora.
Have you ever seen the ancient vessels known as amphoras that the ancients had?
You couldn't stand them up.
They had a point at the bottom.
Have you ever seen those, Chuck?
You could look up an amphora.
And the reason why they had that is many people will say, well,
that's because they didn't have refrigeration.
That is not true.
They were focusing on the quality of the liquid.
Now, I think we've brought up J.J. Thompson.
You see, this is like describing chess pieces.
There's no simple way.
But we brought up J.J. Thompson because he mentioned in a lot of his studies,
or one of his main studies that I've considered to be his main study,
is that momentum and weight is not in mass.
These are actually lines of force that attach to things,
and the quality of the material attracts a certain quality of line of force.
That's why a piece of lead is heavier than a piece of paper,
not because of the actual mass itself, right?
So when you look at the movement of fluids in an ovoid shape,
you constantly have these lines of force attaching to things that are moving,
and that would say is the primary reason why you want the egg shape,
because now you have this energetic system that binds itself to the fluid.
I know this might sound, yes,
it would be a little sublime perhaps on the esoteric or occult,
but we're not going to say who is.
So let's just give it that way.
Now, if you want to consider what you see going around, like, for example,
right now if you go to the stores or the shops or what,
you have containers with flat bottoms, they're box-shaped.
They even have wine in a box, right, with a plastic liner.
So why do they do that?
Because it's strictly for commerce,
because you can pack cube-shaped or rectangular-shaped containers more densely
than round things, right?
So that's the sole reason.
That's why if it is easily and commonly observed,
not known, that eating tropical food in a cold climate is harmful,
why are they offering it to you?
Because it's commercial.
That is the law of commerce.
In other words, there's a lot of people that are trying to go into law forms,
these quote-unquote patriots and such,
and they're looking at things like constitutions and other laws,
but what they fail to realize is that commerce is king.
You cannot disturb the flow of commerce, right?
So now religions and law forms and other things and governments have taken on
that credo that commerce is king, and that's why you're in the state that you're in.
So to go back to the water, for example, the ovoid shape is best.
Now, if you cannot obtain an ovoid shape, avoid a flat bottom.
How's that?
Avoid a 90-degree angle.
There's lots of containers.
For example, a wine bottle laying on its side, stored on its side,
will give you a better quality wine than one that is standing vertical.
Now, the main reason they tell you that is is because the cork is wet
and it doesn't shrink, it keeps the cork more stable.
Yes, that is true as well, but you could do that with other containers as well.
Now, what is the other most important thing with water is that its quality is affected by heat and light.
If water is subject to heat and light, its quality decreases,
meaning its life-carrying capacity decreases.
What does that mean?
It means that let's say you water plants with water that is kept cool and in the dark,
the plant will react more favorably and be of higher quality than water that is kept in the light and is warm.
This is an experiment that anyone can do.
Now, there's something that Schauberger called an anomaly point.
For example, that is a point where you have a condition where it is best for that thing.
For example, in Fahrenheit, Chuck, we call it 98.6.
For the human body, that is an anomaly point.
If I said, Chuck, the temperature of the body is 104, how do you think I'd feel?
Not very good.
Well, I would imagine, yeah, it's too warm for…
A fever.
Yeah, it would be a fever, right.
Right, and let's say I was 86.
That's hypothermia, let's say, right?
So water would be 39 degrees Fahrenheit or 4 degrees Celsius, 4.2 or 39.4, but 39 and 4.
So what does that give you is it gives you a very easy way to assess raising the quality of water via refrigeration.
Why do I say that?
And it's so simple to do because most refrigerators are typically set between 39 and 40 degrees, like it or not.
That just happens to be one of the interesting things that is available to most cultures that have a plug-in fridge or otherwise, right?
Right.
Okay, so basically keeping water in the fridge, which is also what?
Dark, right?
A lot of people wonder, is the light in the fridge on even when you close the door, right?
Okay, so it's not, right?
Come on now, wait a minute.
I know.
Who do you think is listening to this that would wonder, does the light stay on when I –
I didn't say there was a funny thing.
I think it might have even been a Seinfeld or something like that.
The guy kept opening and closing the door, wondering if it's on or not.
So here's the two-fold maxim for water.
Avoid the flat bottom and or put it in the fridge overnight, and you will notice that the quality has risen.
Now, it doesn't mean drinking it cold either.
Like someone says, well, yeah, the cold liquid will always taste better than when it's at room temperature.
Yes, that is true.
It's more refreshing and more invigorating.
But you will also notice that you can do a side-by-side quality test where one glass of water,
a container of water was not subject to the dark and the fridge overnight, and the other one was.
Let the other one, the one that was overnight in the dark and in the fridge, put it on the counter.
Let it come up to temperature and taste the two.
You will see there's a discernible quality in how refreshing it is,
even though it's the same temperature as the one that wasn't treated that way and it's more invigorating.
What I mean by refreshment and invigoration, refreshment comes immediately.
Invigoration is how you feel, let's say, 5, 10, 15 minutes later, right?
And literally the consistency of the thing is different depending on the temperature.
I mean it's just that simple.
That's how I would explain it.
So the consistency of the water being changed by the temperature
means that it's introduced into the body in a slightly different form, right?
Right, but the side-by-side quality tests were both at the same temperature.
You will notice the one that was stored properly overnight does taste a little better regardless.
Typically, drinking water should be, let's say, maybe between 45 and 50 degrees,
so it's not too cold, you know, or 6 degrees or 7 degrees Celsius, let's say.
And this gives you the high quality that you might be looking for.
But in terms of animals, why not give the animals the highest quality water you can?
For example, if you have a watering storage tank or something, put a shade cover over it.
Have you seen, gone through the countryside, Chuck,
and seen water tanks and they're just exposed to the sun, even though they have a cover on them, right?
They should be doubly insulated from the light, just a shade cover or an awning type deal, right,
to keep it out of the light.
If not, because those are typically single-layered containers, right?
And what I mean by covering it from the light, meaning not just a double wall or something,
but actually a layer of air that can circulate around it, right, keep it out of the sun.
Another thing you could do for the animals is keep the water moving, right,
if you can, always by adding or taking some away.
I've had several discussions in private about certain ancient alchemic techniques about treating water
and very simple, you know, how you imbue a charge of positive or negative to water.
And one guy started doing this and he got back to me and he says,
the horse had an old horse and I did what you said regarding the water and it grew a new set of teeth.
You know, because, you know, as they get older, their teeth break off and stuff and they chew on whatever.
Right.
And someone else said they were doing that with plants and they didn't have the success with it.
So, you know, there's a little bit of subjectiveness to it.
And that's very simple.
Something that has a positive charge, especially with water, tends to be, let's say,
stinky, warm and more pathogenic breeding.
Something that water that when it has a negative charge to it,
it tends to be cooler, cleaner and not pathogenic breeding.
Very simple, right?
So let's say you have a given body of water.
When you remove, let's say, a ladle, let's say you've got a barrel of water, Chuck,
and you stick a cup in there or a pail and you remove some water from it,
the water that you pulled out of the bucket has a positive charge,
but the water now that is in the pail has taken on a negative charge,
where before it was more neutral.
And that will also neutralize over time, you see.
So one of the alchemic things was producing certain solutions,
was you would have a given container of water.
You pour out a top third, you wait, and then you pour out another third of it
and you just use the last third that's left, and that is the most negatively charged.
Interesting.
Very simple to do, right?
You can do this at home as well.
Pour yourself a glass of water, pour off a quarter or a third, wait a few minutes,
pour off another quarter or a third, and then just drink the last bit,
and you'll notice how charging and refreshing that little last bit is.
Now this will drive a physicist or a scientist insane, you know.
I mean if they look at that, they'll say,
you can't prove that scientifically with their instruments, right?
But that is one way of imbuing the charge into water.
And this is, again, we've mentioned several times
we were having a little bit of an esoteric conversation.
Why not, right?
Why not throw in some ancient stuff and, you know, why not, right?
If we're not going to do it, who is?
Exactly.
You know, and the other odd question here right along this topic is,
does the temperature of 39 correlate to the degree of the curve
used in the storing container?
No.
The degree of the curve, meaning the egg shape,
let's say the ovoid or non-rectangular, no.
Yeah, well, it didn't make any sense to me, but I figured I should ask the question.
No, no, sure, sure.
Another thing that was asked about the ovoid shape here is,
is that why a light bulb sort of has an egg shape as well for the same kind of reasons?
That's a good question.
I don't know, but I think that what we consider the light bulb's shape
is a convention that was started back in the days from when you blew glass.
Have you ever seen glass blowing?
You always get a tapered end that they break off or cut off?
No, I think that's exactly where it came from as well, but I'm not sure.
So I figured I would just throw it in.
You know, and really I'd like to encourage you guys more often to ask these questions yourselves
as opposed to going into chat.
In fact, I think that this will be the last time that I enter the chat questions into the show.
I'd rather that you guys do it yourselves if you want to ask a question or add in a comment.
What do you think, Greg?
Should I?
Yeah, well, this is the last time since the other last time.
We encourage people to call in.
This was initially, I guess, reassembled or reloaded, as Ocelli in the Greek, as a call-in show.
We haven't stressed that, but the crew over at AFR did, and we've never really stressed that,
but we prefer to pretty much get together and do it more of a call-in type theme,
and not to say that no one has called in, but we prefer more of you do.
Absolutely.
So anyway, when you do these things with a positive and negative charge,
you've got to wonder also if this has something to do with the way you handle, well, produce, right?
Isn't there a proper way, despite the convention of commerce?
Yes.
Yes, there is a proper way.
Since we're on the topic of refrigeration, meaning that container that is sealed, you know,
and cools things down because it's cool inside, you know, if you work in the restaurant business
and you put meat on the top shelf of, let's say, a walk-in box and the veg on the bottom,
you get fined by the health authorities, right?
The meat needs to go on the bottom and the veg needs to go on top, you know.
So if, let's say, a meat container would leak, you wouldn't get it on the lettuce, right?
But if you look at most crispers or storage prefabricated from the factory in the refrigerator,
do you notice they have the vegetable crispers on the very bottom?
Yes, they do.
Yeah, so let's say someone goes and buys something that they're going to cook as a roast or a big slab of meat,
where are they going to put it?
Above that, aren't they, 99% of the time?
Almost always, yeah.
So why is it that the health authorities fine you if you do that commercially,
but at home they're promoting that you do that?
Do you think there's something wrong here?
Well, you know, there definitely is,
and I always thought it might be because drippings from meat products are, well,
a little more difficult to deal with when contaminating the vegetables.
But what is the –
Well, ultimately, you want two fridges, one for animal product, one for vegetable product, right?
Well, that would be the smart thing, and, you know, there are people that do separate things like that.
And it's cheaper, actually.
You can get these little college fridges, you know, they're about waist high.
For two of those, it still costs less than a decent quality full-size fridge.
So just plug in two fridges.
You don't have any meat.
You could turn it off.
Think about it for a moment, all right?
And the dairy would be the same.
Dairy would be in between.
I wouldn't store the dairy with the meat, and I wouldn't store it, you know, with the veg.
So maybe a third fridge is in order, right?
I doubt it.
You see?
So one thing to do here is consider that.
The convention is unlawful.
Let's say – I wouldn't say unlawful, but it doesn't seem fit and proper from good common sense, does it,
in most people's homes, the way that it's set up.
So was that part of a question or just a comment that we decided to create here regarding meat?
I had the comment about the meat, actually, and what I was thinking about the dripping.
That's what I said.
Oh, it's blood usually or some kind of plasma fluid or something, and it would be considered not clean,
and I would consider anything that it fell on that's not meat to be contaminated once that happens.
Well, right, and what I was saying is the reason why the health authorities would tell you to put it on the bottom
is that this way it would end up on the floor as opposed to on your food.
It won't contaminate, right.
Okay, so the quality aspect here, we covered a little bit in terms of sampling of your food
and then the treatment of water.
By the way, we have gotten quite a bit of inquiry, let's say on the Uncommon Sense email,
regarding many thanks and regarding the commentary on water.
This is just a commentary on a commentary.
There are so many – if you go online regarding water, again, the medicine show,
this water, that water, whatever, how many people really consider themselves water experts
which is just saying you could pretty much do it yourself if you keep it in an ovoid
or as close to ovoid shape as possible in the dark and cool, none.
They all want to sell you something or device.
So, again, commerce is king because they've infused it with extra oxygen
or they've infused it with or they've gotten it from some great source,
so therefore you need to buy their package.
I've seen – you wouldn't believe how many links and things that I've sent for review.
People, stop asking the Greek for approval.
Stop asking for approval.
You will figure it out eventually or actually what we do like to discuss is how to discern
because when you have discernment, you don't need to ask for approval.
You might ask for approval in terms of discussion to improve that discernment
but not just write out what do you think of this, is it good or bad without any input on your own.
So learn to discern and yes, it is the road less traveled in many, many ways
but if you find yourself on this rock amongst the rest of the surface-dwelling earth inhabitants
and they're all pretty much the same by the way.
They all look different and they sound different
but they are very monotonous, monotone earth inhabitants.
The ones that are paying attention I find have either been taken out or keep to themselves
and they're not really discussing things and how to be objective and how to discern.
So again, do you think there's anything else in chat or call in or Chuck
that you would want to cover a little bit more on the quality and on water?
Otherwise, we can just continue.
Well, we're coming close to the end of this time period.
So I would think that we might want to get in the final jabs if you will
and conclude the entire thought process before the music starts to play.
Okay.
In terms of quality, let's refer back to the Uncommon Radio that's archived at AFR.
If you go to past shows, you'll find The Perfect Rice I believe is a title and more on cooking.
Again, since we're discussing quality, what you will find there,
the techniques that are discussed regarding I think it was regular Joe that called in.
He was very grateful about the potato preparation.
Many people have commented on other preparations that have been discussed.
Those were specific preparations that were discussed on that archive show of many different things.
And it was not just, you know, hey, what do you think, you know, how about just making this?
No, it was actually the fine points that make it better.
And when you make something better, you're increasing its quality.
So again, I would urge anyone to go back and look at the archives if they're still available.
I don't even know if they're available.
Like I reckon that they are.
I think they still are, number one.
Number two, you know what, there was one thing I did miss in the flurry before that I wanted to throw at you real quick.
And I know the answer to this, but I'll throw it to you anyway.
You know, especially because I'm partially Sicilian, they go, hey, wait a minute, what about garlic?
Yeah, garlic is interesting.
All those, the onions, there's a family, you know, in there.
It's a very potent, very high, you know, the chemists will tell you it's very high in sulfur and such.
There's certain in traditions, Hindu traditions, I believe,
or others that say stay away from that, it keeps you spiritually low.
And they have a substitute called HIN, H-I-N, instead of that.
It's very potent.
And one thing to determine is we never really discussed how do you determine if something is edible from a survivalist point of view.
And let's get into that maybe for, it'll only take a minute or two.
And that will actually give you a little more light on garlic.
Let's say you're left somewhere.
You know what?
Hold on.
Let's hang on to that because we actually have somebody on the line, if you don't mind.
Go for it.
I'd like to add him in.
Because we only have a few minutes left, I'm adding the 510 area code into the discussion.
Damn.
Hello.
They're on the air.
Did you want to add into the discussion here?
Going once, going twice.
Bad connection.
All right.
Well, I'll put you back on hold because we weren't getting a clear sound from you.
So go ahead with the onions and the garlic and such.
That would be, when you have an idea of how to determine what's edible, let's say when you're outside of the norm
and you're in an extreme situation, that's where the survivalist attitude comes in, right?
It's no longer normal.
If you find yourself around vegetation, you're not sure if it's edible or not.
Really, really simple.
And this is not the only way, but it is a way that's easy to explain.
If you find a piece of vegetation, break off a leaf or what you plan on eating
and rub it on your wrist or the inside part of your elbow or your underarm.
Those are the very tender, very receptive aspects of your outer skin, right, on the limb.
And you wait 15 minutes.
And if there's no reaction, then rub a little bit on your lower lip and slightly on the upper lip, above and below.
Why?
Because the upper lip and the lower lip represent the small and large intestine, right?
Wait about 15 minutes.
If there's no reaction, then go ahead and touch it on the inside of your upper lip
and the inside of your lower lip.
Wait about 15 minutes.
You're 45 minutes into it now.
No reaction.
You can just take a bite of it and spit it out.
And then you might have to wait about an hour once you bite into it and spit it out.
If there's still no reaction, now you're almost an hour or two hours into it now,
then you go ahead, take a small bite and swallow it and wait again about a half an hour to an hour.
And if there's no reaction, it probably is edible to eat enough for you to survive.
Now let's go back to the garlic.
Take a piece of garlic, fresh garlic, and go ahead and rub it on your wrist or the inside of your elbow.
And how does that feel, right?
So, anyway, we'll continue again, and that's it for now.
Absolutely.
The Ocelli and the Greek sonic entity has ended for this particular time period.
We will see you again next week.
Take care.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American Freedom Radio.
Radio.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions, running my companies, and I hated feeling groggy and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret the powers that be want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride, our brains are under siege, and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve, a revolutionary breakthrough in a category of cognitive enhancers called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself at DNAEvolveSample.com.
That's DNAEvolveSample.com.
Supplies are limited, so go to DNAEvolveSample.com right now.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion, and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years, and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein, is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367,
and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
The world is like a ride at an amusement park.
And when you choose to go on it, you think it's real, because that's how powerful our minds are.
And the ride goes up and down and round and round.
It has thrills and chills, and it's very brightly colored, and it's very loud.
And it's fun for a while.
Some people have been on the ride for a long time, and they begin to question,
is this real, or is this just a ride?
And other people have remembered, and they come back to us, and they say,
hey, don't worry, don't be afraid, ever, because this is just a ride.
And we kill those people.
The eyes of fear want you to put bigger locks on your door, buy guns, close yourself off.
The eyes of love instead see all of us as one.
Here's what we can do to change the world right now to a better ride.
Take all that money we spend on weapons and defense each year,
and instead spend it feeding, clothing, and educating the poor of the world,
which it would many times over, not one human being excluded,
and we can explore space together, both inner and outer, forever in peace.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is AmericanFreedomRadio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow,
friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver
quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio at ymail.com.
Vaccines, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.