The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand, the Sonic
Well, good evening, I guess, according to the wind up toy. It is just after 10 p.m.
here on the East Coast of what was formerly known as America.
But anyway, what is the date today? I wonder, because, well, I haven't been doing my observation correctly.
And I got to say, I don't like looking at this thing they call a calendar.
Although I have to conduct business that way with some people, because that's all they understand.
What is the lawful day of the week?
Yeah, good. I'm glad you said day and not date, because dates are things that hang on trees or things on the Pope's work schedule.
More years ago, people went on dates. Right. I think they do now.
So I don't know what they're calling it now.
But yeah, it's if you want to use a system that is lawful, meaning don't be so arrogant to think that the birds, the bees, the whales, the rivers and the planets go on the Pope's ridiculous work schedule.
If you're not that arrogant and you want to find out how to really keep time, you would probably be observing roughly.
It's the 11th month and about the 10th day till noon.
Well, there you have it. And of course, this is Ocelli in the Greek, which is broadcast on American Freedom Radio.
And we do remind you that American Freedom Radio stays on the air because people like you, the listener, participate in that funding.
OK, so I do want to tell you that there is a link at American Freedom Radio dot com to donate, although it is sort of an exchange because you are receiving information at this point in time that you're not going to hear elsewhere.
So if you think about it, you are sort of, well, putting a bit of value in the tip jar for the value you're receiving.
Anyway, I'll leave that announcement alone and also remind people that we take calls on this show at two, one, eight, three, three, nine, eight, five, two, five.
Once again, two, one, eight, three, three, nine, eight, five, two, five.
If you're able to operate a phone and you're not intoxicated, we do encourage you to call.
The two rules are basically don't talk about yourself because no one cares, even though they say they do.
And the second rule is if you're somehow under the influence, no, you don't sound fine.
Guess what? If you're under the influence, you sound like you're under the influence.
So those are basically the two rules, I'd say, or guidelines.
Well, yeah, guidelines sounds good.
And tonight we're going to discuss the hardcore history of Christianity.
Now, that may sound like quite a tall order.
Right.
What do you think?
Very difficult to do because you can't create a vacuum or even explain anything without giving the other side, the left-hand, right-hand rule kind of thing.
But I had a thought today, and I kind of reminded myself, we're going to be on radio tonight.
Maybe if I could retain some of that thought and give the analogy.
Like, for example, you just brought up, you know, donating the AFR, you know, because there's information and such.
Right. And whatever.
OK, that's a good thing, let's say.
But then there's a there's a concept here where I call it the mindset.
Right. And that's that's portrayed really well in Hollywood and in cartoons.
You know, when they show you a professor has a stereotype, a doctor has a stereotype.
There's these stereotypes that are shown throughout society and art and even law enforcement.
Right. And in society.
Yeah. The stereotype is the representation of the mindset.
And it's a mindset.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, you've got the hip hop stereotype, you know, I mean, how many stereotypes are there?
Thousands. Right.
And ultimately, they're just people.
It's their appearance and their mindset that grants them that stereotype.
OK, now a midget is a midget and a giant is a giant.
They can't change that. Right.
And but but the stereotype is a mindset.
So there's a mindset that people get used to because when you're comfortable, you let things hang, you let things flow, be yourself.
You know, you've heard that. Right.
But we've also discussed in the past that it's all external input.
Your thoughts are not your own. You just take it for granted.
You know, like if you're an adult and you had to learn how to walk, it would be a chore.
But after a while, you don't think of it because it's like riding a bike.
You know, it comes naturally.
Thinking is something that is external.
And pretty much everything is external.
We're constantly receiving and broadcasting.
So so the concept of be yourself, you know, without going into some weird psychological analogy, you know, how can you be when it's all external?
It's what you grab onto, what you tune into. Right.
What you resonate with, what people say. Right.
Or what you're dissonant with, which is the opposite of resonance.
So this is an analogy I want to bring up.
And this is actually true. But take it how you like.
This is from working in various technical fields.
And this could be, let's say, working with aviation, working with automotive and also working with industrial design and things like that.
So that's the setting of this quick little story that also goes back to what we're doing.
You and I on Ocelli and the Greek Reloaded.
Right.
So the story goes like this.
There's a shop and they're considered the best in their field, aviation, automotive, whatever.
And not only are they considered the best in their field, but they truly are.
And why? What makes someone the best?
Because what they're putting out is better than good.
Okay.
Because if you're putting out stuff that's not good, you'll be out of business.
So you have to be to be the best.
Not only do you have to be good, but you have to be way better than good.
Right.
And known as it's called the high end.
Or, you know, in industry.
So this particular shop, for example, had needed some extra hires, you know, needed to bring on some more people to accommodate the workload.
So we reached out and got a mechanic, let's say, and got him from another type of shop.
But that shop was not known to do the best of the best of the best work.
They did very good work.
Okay.
So when this person came on for one day a week, you know, they seemed like they would fit.
Well, for the first half of the day, actually, they came on for two days.
For the first half of the day or the first day, it took them that long just to get acclimated to the way things were done in the shop that was really good.
They had to kind of, you know, because they were still used to working five days at the other shop that was just, you know.
All right.
Okay.
So what happened then, it's like the second.
So the second half of their time there, they picked up on the vibe and they were and they fit in quite well.
But then, you know, because they were a part timer, they left and then they came back next week.
And we noticed, you know, when this person came back, it took them like six hours to get back into the way of doing things really, really well.
Right.
Like.
Okay.
So what the interesting part of this, you know, and after a while, this person no longer could could could really hang.
So they left.
But what the interesting part is going back to the other shop where they were, they were so thankful because they were like, this guy was never really such a great mechanic.
But he worked with you guys for a couple of days or a day and he comes over here and he's the best mechanic in the shop.
But with us, you know, let's say he sucked.
I mean, he took him half the time to get acclimated.
Right.
You know, you get the drift.
So because we did things on a different level.
So so this is the point, like we talk about whatever, when you listen to information, quote unquote, on on media, which which you have television, you have Internet, you have stuff in print.
Heaven forbid.
Is there still stuff in print?
I wonder, you know.
Yeah, I think about that often.
You know, the the only factor missing from this discussion, just I want to briefly interrupt, is that when this guy started out, he came in with something.
That was already imparted to him.
And I think that if he had not been born with, say, two hands, the skill set might have been different.
If he had not been born with good eyesight, the skill set might have been different.
Certain things are factors based on the hardware as well.
Right.
Oh, yeah. Well, the hard.
Well, it's all about hardware.
But, you know, what good is it if it does if it if the program and the input to make it move doesn't work well?
And maybe is it just because you've got a Formula One race car in the driveway doesn't mean you can put it on the track and do well.
Most people. Actually, this is a fact.
Ninety nine point nine, nine, nine, nine percent of the population think they're good drivers.
Couldn't you can't even put a Formula race car in gear.
Nonetheless, drive it. It's a it's a it's a very specific skill.
Right. No, I have everything.
So so the point I want to just go with it with the radio is the stuff this is cut to the chase.
This is this is about this is this is an objectivity.
The stuff that is discussed here on Ocelli and the Greek reloaded and the manner of which is discussed is very different from where it's discussed anywhere at all.
Period. It's very unique in that sense.
Now, you have the illusion that, you know, maybe, you know, this we don't really specialize in anything.
Right. We don't you don't come to Ocelli and the Greek reloaded to hear about one topic because it's basically a commentary on human society.
For those that are not from here, let's say, because, you know, who are you going to tell this to here?
Right. Because it gets very critical. The thing is.
So you're all over the Internet. You're taking media all over the place.
You come to Ocelli and the Greek and it'll take you the first hour just to dump all the dummy load stuff that you hear everywhere else.
And maybe in the second hour, you're going to get the mindset.
And then by the second hour, you go to another show and you're like, what the hell are they talking about?
Because now you've seen how to be objective and clear.
And then you and then you fall back into it.
Then you come back next week and you're all dummy loaded again.
And so basically the point here is, Chuck, the first hour is just getting warmed up, like getting the mindset correct.
And almost every show that we do or whenever typically there are two hours like a mechanic acclimating himself to the shop on the first day or half day.
Right. Right. And then. Yeah, it's right.
So I've noticed this. I mean, this this happens.
It's a natural thing. And I've done this.
I've come up with this assumption from actually listening to some of the comments prior and after the show, the recordings.
And actually, I went back and did a little bit of listening to some archive stuff, which I never really do.
So I just want to say the two hours is not enough.
Now, when you bring up the concept, let's go.
Let's cut to the chase and talk about we're going to talk about the hardcore history of Christianity.
Well, that's that's eight hour preface on a 20 hour lecture.
I mean, it's not going to happen. It's not going to happen anywhere.
Right. And if you say, well, Greek, they do that university.
Are you joking? Are you joking?
By the way, not to we got to kick them in the shins a little bit.
The university people, if anyone has been listening to Chuck and myself here,
Ocelli and the Greek Reloader or the old ones and you do me a favor right now on YouTube,
they have MIT and Harvard University lectures put up on YouTube and they're full length.
Right. Go listen to that crap with some discernment.
They're not saying anything. Right.
There's a lot of time.
There's a whole lot of time spent where I'm saying to myself and I've sat and listened to some of these things.
I don't get the point of why I'm sitting here listening to this.
It's because people are being pranked and they love the prank.
So maybe we should jump into the subject matter.
Give another little bit of a preface, an analogy to it.
We're going to discuss the. Let's see.
How do you remember the mindset, man? That's really difficult.
Right. Isn't it, Chuck? You see the mindset.
How do we have to accommodate the mindset? Right.
So how do you accommodate the mindset of this is a private conversation done in public?
I just said before the show started, you and I. Right.
We're having a private conversation in public.
How else would you put it? Right.
So if you're feeling voyeuristic, here's your chance to get off anyway.
OK, so the thing here is this.
The mindset is very simple.
Forget about anything that has to do with what you think is faith, religion, God, all this other stuff,
because anything and everything you think about that is based on the culture administering what it what what is in place to you.
Most people, in other words, have not done the research and don't care to look more into what they think they believe in,
whether it's religion, dogma, faith or any any opinion.
Most people function like when you bring up the concept of Christianity, Islam, Hinduism, Hinduism, Buddhism.
They know a small amount of stuff.
It's all false, by the way, that they get any religion in any culture that they've gotten from the culture.
And the only reason they admit to being such is because it's kind of like they have a laundry list of things.
They need to be a citizen in this society. And one of them is religion. Check one.
OK, I got that checked. Yes. OK, fine. That's enough.
I don't need to know anymore. Right. And this is the way people function in most things, even jobs, what they call their career.
Right. They have a very narrow slice and they perform in that.
Why? Because they get what they think is compensation. So they have what? Food, clothing and shelter.
So we discuss a little bit beyond food, clothing and shelter here. So going back to the Christian element,
this is not religious. Why? Because we brought up the university.
Most of university professors, by the way, even as a generalization, are self-professed atheists. Right.
Typically, most of the most part in academia, most people are considered themselves or self-professed atheists. Right.
Right. OK, so. But by the way, by the way, in their own records or academic paradigm,
the past 2000 years historically is called what? It's called the Christian era.
So this is not it's beyond. Yes, it's considered a religion, quote unquote, but it's beyond that.
It needs to be looked at only because it's been memorialized as a historic milestone by these atheists.
Isn't that isn't that a freaking ironic contradiction? Right.
But yeah, but we've also said before the majority of the people on this planet, no matter how religious you think you are,
if you haven't looked into the nature of these things, you're probably pagan or atheist anyway.
I mean, you could line up one hundred thousand Christians and I'll show you how they're all either atheist or pagan.
The same with the Islam, the same with the Hindus. Why? Pagan meaning that they're not.
OK, we've got to find another word for that, meaning that they're just going along to get along or atheist,
meaning that there's no God there or gods. Right. Right.
Like if someone if someone says you believe you believe in God and you say yes.
And that's the end of the conversation. That is about as erroneous as you can get,
because nowhere is it memorialized as God other than the King James or in modern English and things that came out of King James,
let's say, or the Latin. It's always plural. And then the other thing is, which one?
And it never, ever, ever, ever gets there. And it can't because the society is under what?
Cosmic censorship. You're censored. So this is a subject that is talk about no taboo topics. Right.
Well, yeah. And oddly enough, I have a couple of questions that were posed to me in in well on social media that that people wanted to ask.
And I think you're about to get to the subject that that they asked about it.
If not, I will interject them on behalf of the listener, though, as you go forward.
Because they do want to know about, you know, your reference to the scriptures because you're about to hit on that topic.
Somewhat lightly, because we can talk about the scriptures, but it's going to be so far into what people have heard, even on the fringe.
It's even more foreign than that. So but go ahead. Well, I want to interject that that portion of the question,
because two questions were posted to me by somebody. I'll identify him as Michael.
I'm not going to give the entire name. But the thing is that Michael had said exactly this.
When he says the scriptures have not been translated from the Greek or Hebrew, I've heard him say that.
I've heard him say that to use the interlinear. You know, first of all, he's asking about that.
And then he says, what is an interlinear and where can I get one? Doesn't that mean it has been translated into English?
No, that would be a parallel. An interlinear is like a Rosetta Stone.
You have three parallel languages on the Rosetta Stone that are visible. You would have two parallel languages.
You would have an interlinear would be would actually list the text as it's been preserved to this date.
Right. And then underneath it or next to it, it would have the language of your choosing.
Right. So in an English Hebrew interlinear, you can have.
Right. Would be what's or English Greek or you can have a Hebrew Spanish interlinear where you have the text in its original language and then in Spanish underneath or Japanese or Chinese.
So it would be that's a good question because the detail there is thus you have the original language of preservation and then the language that you use below it word for word.
Right, right. And the problem with that is when the when the language of preservation goes from left to right.
You're going to be reading underneath each corresponding word in your language that you prefer from left to right, even though you might be used to reading.
I'm sorry. Right to left. Did I say left to right? If the initial play of the let's say, for example, the what's considered the Old Testament.
We'll talk about how there is no such thing as Old and New Testament. It's one piece.
But for example, Hebrew runs right to left. So you're going to be reading if you have an English Hebrew interlinear, you're going to be reading right to left, which is unusual just from the get go.
Right. And it's word for word. But I suggest people go there and that's just like step face.
I haven't discussed this might be the first time I've I think I've brought it up before, Chuck, is that once you get to the interlinear and you do it with discernment, guess what you're going to find out?
Those sons of bitches aren't giving you the right information either. Oops. Did I just say that?
How do we. Yeah. What is the most obvious reason that you can discern that even interlinears are they're better than that thing called King James or NIV?
All the Bibles, regardless if they're in Chinese, Japanese, New International Version, Dewey Reams, Young's literal translation, they're all based on King James.
All of them. How do you know if the first verse is in the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth? That's King James.
It doesn't matter what they tell you, what version it is or what language. That's all King James.
It just shows you how this is like a monopoly on this. Right. Big time.
But going back to the interlinear, how do you know that they're not even giving you what you should be getting?
Or let's say you think you might have it now because you're at the interlinear.
What's your first glaring sign that when you get to an interlinear, which is supposed to give you word for word that they're not giving it to you?
Well, let's say you're I'm not really suggesting here, even though I would to go and actually learn the original language eventually.
But, Chuck, if you've ever seen an interlinear, you'll have the Hebrew and then running right below it is the English word for word. Right.
And, you know, that seems pretty reasonable. But what how can you discern that they're not giving it to you either?
I'll tell you, even if you haven't looked at it, typically an interlinear,
you would see the language of preservation Hebrew or Greek and then each corresponding English word below it.
And then all of a sudden you see, let's say, word in Hebrew and right below it.
Do you see a corresponding word or do you see dash, dash, dash?
You see dash, dash, dash. And they're not even bothering to give you what that word means.
They just omit it. But it's there. Yeah, right.
So it'll be there in Hebrew, but they don't give you the English. It just give you a series of hyphens.
It's like just keep just forget about this one and just keep going. Wait a second.
Now, let me ask you a question, though, because here's here's the thing that confused me, because I can't read Hebrew, but I can read Latin.
And sometimes with Latin, I can take one word in Latin and it winds up breaking into three English words.
Is is this not sure dashes or what? No, no, no. OK.
Well, I didn't know that. So you could do that also. But they do that also.
Sometimes they'll give a Hebrew word and there'll be three words underneath it.
Yes. Like a conjugate or other things, too. Exactly.
But it's simply it's just blatant omittance of the of the text.
So so I really haven't had much people still for the past decade have been what is an internal leader?
How do I go there? But very few people, actually none, maybe two in 10 years after speaking to hundreds, have come back and said, hey, man, you can't trust that.
I said, I know, but I'm not going to go out and bury everyone with every.
You see, this is see people when they come to get information, whether it's university or alternative media or whatever,
they come with a tic-tac-toe or checkers mindset.
You know, this is all this is not only like reality is not only forget about tic-tac-toe and checkers.
It's it's more like chess, but like 3D chess or, you know, working on three boards at the same time.
Right. You know, very complicated. But it doesn't mean it can't be done.
You see, so and then this is just not this.
This these types of conversations do not mix well with what sort of typical surface dwelling earth inhabitants are heavily involved in,
not just involved in, but heavily involved in.
I mean, it's very easy to say that humanity has to make 500 steps just to get to zero there in the minus column in big time.
So so these discussions are maybe a loose, futile commentary on what's going on, you know.
But but to get into the hardcore aspect of Christianity, you know,
you notice how we just spent the past few minutes discussing the scriptures,
obviously, because you have a listener apparently that is listening, asking these questions. Right.
So we're doing it out of courtesy. But please, I'm going to take a half a second pause.
Right there. If if you think that anything in Christianity or any other religion, anything,
not one thing has anything to do with the scriptures, you're delusional.
Now, that sounds like a very almost angry kind of like, you know, kick them in the shins kind of statement.
It's not because in order to have a rational discussion, if one percent of Christianity was biblical, you'd have to grant it.
If point zero two percent of it was biblical, you would have to grant it to be rational, no matter how you have to grant it.
If it was 50 percent or 10 percent or what, you know, you have to find one thing.
But it's zero. And that is really a tall statement.
It doesn't even shock people because they know.
Well, and that's the interesting thing here.
The follow on question from Michael, by the way, I think speaks directly to the point you just made.
And I'm just going to read it verbatim. So take it for what it's worth.
And remember, you know, I don't read too well on air.
So much surrounds fear, fear of punishment or going to hell when you die.
This was always ingrained in our minds as being brought up in a Christian or a Catholic environment.
Then he says there is no heaven or hell and that we sleep when we die.
I'm having a hard time grasping that because I thought the evil and the cruel things that mankind does to life on this planet had repercussions.
Yes, it does. But it doesn't on a tic-tac-toe checkers level.
You know, look, in Chinatown, they got a chicken that will beat you at checkers.
I'm serious. It's a look. You stand behind the glass.
You put a bucket in and the chicker plays checkers with you and it wins almost every time.
There's been more than one chicken that does that, in fact.
Yeah. Yeah. OK, there you go. So, I mean, we're not chickens.
You know, I mean, playing checkers is one thing. Playing checkers with chickens is another.
And discussing what culture has put on humanity is just outright criminal.
Now, here's the thing about that. When I say there's no heaven or hell in the context that you're told, absolutely true.
There is a heavenly realm. And what they call heaven, meaning it's the sky, there are three heavens that are explained in the ancient texts.
Right. Now, hell is simply the word when you read it in Latin, when you read it in English or any other language.
It's the word that actually in the original text means the grave. Right.
It's not this infernal place. Right. And what they're confusing you with the biblical,
they interchange that word like spirit and soul, which are distinctly very different.
They interchange the word grave, which with the the other term,
which is Sheol or Gehenna, which is a place where you capture spirits.
Have you you know, you can capture a genie in the bottle.
They show you in the cartoons and he can't come out until you open the cork.
You know that thing, you know, I guess even though they're all powerful, supposedly genies, they can grant you things.
But once you put the cork on the bottle, they're stuck. Is that true?
Is that how the myth goes on that, by the way? Something like that.
Yeah, they can't get out unless you open it. Right.
That concept is a biblical concept where there is a place where spirits are contained.
And I've gotten into detail, actually, on one of the previous episode a while back on what it is.
And it's just, you know, it's OK. At least, you know, it could be referenced.
How do you keep spirits? But anyway, people are not like when you're very simply when you die.
It's like being asleep without dreaming.
That's why you'll have one of these guys with a black dress and a white collar at a funeral.
Reading is always with the Lord, always with heaven, always a bad guys in hell.
But meanwhile, what does it say written in stone? Does it say that he's in hell or he's in heaven?
What does it say on the tombstones? Usually rest in peace.
So how the hell are you going to be burning in hell or plucking a harp in heaven if you are resting in peace?
So guess what? It's written in stone. You know, it's interesting.
Like, you know, you think twice before you write something in stone. Right.
So you better be correct. You better be correct. It is correct. It's rest in peace.
So you're resting in peace. So we'll get into that.
This gets into a little more of the functional part.
But the whole big thing here about this is, you know how we mentioned Internet radio and information and all this.
I like to use what happened. You know, we can discuss what really happened there that anyone can look up if they do it with discernment.
Or what's the hardcore history of Christianity? That's a fork in the road right now.
Which one do you want to take? Anyone in chat or Chuck, what do you think?
Should we just discuss Christianity like we said what it is, why people do where it came from?
Or should we discuss like a little bit of the reality of what really happened?
And it's like, oh, man, how dare how can the Greek know no one else says, well, you could know if you weren't so lazy.
Oh, did I just say that? But people are very comfortable, you know, so we can go either way.
Well, I think we should stick with the hardcore history of Christianity for the time being.
And I'll tell you why I'm looking in chat, because obviously some of the things you've said are causing a bit of a reaction.
And I'll read for you part of what is being said.
Excuse me, the NIV and the KJV, excuse me, are not all the same.
One is a literal translation and the other is a summary which uses more opinion of the writer.
The literal translation, excuse me, adheres to what the Greek and Hebrew actually say while making it so that the English speaking people can read it is what the person wrote in the chat.
Oh, yeah, well, we've been discussing that for a long time. That just isn't so.
You can do you can you can you can just move on, because if you look at an interlinear, you will find what that person just wrote just isn't so.
You know, if we if we go with that belief, then, you know, red is green and black is white.
And, you know, just because, you know, there's a picture at university of an elephant says this is a banana.
Well, you know, the book says that's literal. So I guess an elephant now is a banana.
No, it doesn't. Sorry. Next, let's keep moving on the hardcore history of Christianity.
Not to dismiss this person, but obviously there's a lot of there's no homework being done here.
And this is exactly what we're talking about. The consensus. Right.
The NIV has been marketed and the King James has been marketed as such. Right.
And give you an example, the ignorance that surrounds the subject.
You know, if you mentioned any biblical character, even the later ones, they typically were finished with their lives by the first century A.D. or 100 A.D.
They were mostly all gone. Right. And the King James initiated around.
Well, it was really put out in public around 1611. So fifteen hundred and eleven years later.
OK. Going to a Bible study once and I was so excited.
You know, when you're young, dumb and full of you know what rhymes with that, you you you go and you want to share these things.
And I found out that, no, these people don't want to hear anything.
They got there a little. You could actually you could pull their Bibles from their Bible study and replace it with voodoo dolls and headless chickens.
They would be the same. But anyway, I know it's a little harsh, but it's true, folks.
One person saying, well, that's not accurate, doesn't say that at all.
And the old lady stands up and she wants to beat me up and she says, you can't say that the King James Bible is the only true word of God.
It was good enough for the Apostle Paul is good enough for me.
And you just got to shake your head because the Apostle Paul died fifteen hundred years before it was written.
So, I mean, this is the mindset. Wow.
I mean, we talk about I mean, you can't there's nothing to work with there.
Actually, there is what you do. You work out, you work on getting shoes you can run with and make sure the car battery is good.
You know what I mean? That's why I tell people if you're going to buy shoes, make sure you can run in them.
Right. The lady says, what do you think of those shoes? Well, I don't know what I think of them. Can you run in them?
If you can run in the shoes, they're good.
And then when you get to the car, make sure the car starts and get the hell out of there.
So I can't work with that. You see. So, OK, I just had to throw that.
That's an extreme. I know that's one extreme, but it goes from there all the way to the mild conversation.
Right. It's just right. But the hardcore Christianity, let's let's get into it with what people can associate with,
because what people can associate with always makes it more tangible. Right.
If you start to discuss, for example, a society where everyone grew their own food now in a society where the majority of the people have industrial food production,
where they get it wrapped in plastic from the store, you know, you really can't discuss that culture.
I mean, you could say to a person that's used to getting industrial food that's wrapped in plastic, growing your own food.
Yeah, they'll say, yeah, I get that.
But but they don't get what it's like if everyone grew their own food, how different the culture would be.
So you can't just it doesn't cross over very well. You see my point.
So if we start discussing how it started, we need to give points that people can attach to.
And the easiest thing to do is by looking at historically the evolution.
Now, do you want to go really far back? Let's go back to the first evidence.
Remember, we said what people are used to seeing because there's no knowledge base on this.
Right. Why do I say there's no knowledge base?
Well, yeah. And as you said, as as society has evolved or at least festered, changed, whatever,
you know, you can't imagine such a such a widespread sort of influence like what would the culture be like if all we did was grow our food?
That's something that's detached from this reality to a degree.
Now, that's not to say that there aren't some people that do.
But it's not just growing food, Chuck, is all the other stuff that goes along with it, that this culture cannot understand because.
Because, for instance, let's just say I grew a lot of food myself.
This would change the way that I interact with people because I'd probably have extra if I got good at it.
I would probably learn to exchange that with others so that it wouldn't rot.
Or I'd learn how to package it and keep it or can it or preserve it somehow.
Not necessarily in a negative way, etc.
And this would change the way that I do commerce and therefore the trajectory of my entire life if I were able to do this.
Right. And the way you observe the weather would be different.
Right. Well, I would have to observe the weather differently if I were to participate in agriculture as a constant.
And the way you viewed water and all these things.
Yeah. Well, right. Because water would take on an entirely different meaning in my life.
It wouldn't simply be that which I require to sustain myself and to wash in, etc.
It would become something else.
So this would literally not just change a single perspective.
But if this was done on a large scale, this would change a lot of the things that are happening now into something else.
It would be a different mindset.
Not just about growing food, but about everything that you did.
Well, right. But I'm just laying it out for people.
I hear you. That's the same analogy as do you know what a horse and carriage is or do you know what a sailing ship with cloth sails is?
Yes. Yeah. But when you start discussing the society that use that as their primary paradigm, the way people thought was very different.
So that doesn't transfer over well. That's why when people try to read things from another time period, they don't get it.
What does this mean? Or it's misunderstood or they have to read into it what they know.
Right. Right. Exactly. Because, look, if I tell you that a fidgety thought is something that I use on a daily basis.
Now, I just made up that word. But you would say, well, I don't know what that is.
You have no relatable point for it. It could be something similar to a spoon.
But, you know, if I tell you that I use that on a daily basis, now that's one thing.
If it's a spoon, it's yet another thing. If it's a weapon, let's say that that gives you a completely different characteristic.
So if you don't understand the terms and you don't understand the reference points, how can you actually get down to getting into the mindset after all?
Right. You know, I was doing I did some radio yesterday and a person wanted me to discuss history for two hours.
And I said, you know, it's really hard because the mindset doesn't cross over.
So the best you can do is give some facts and don't give facts that are elusive and maybe distinctive or just that period,
but give facts about how things were that we still have today.
But back then and one of the things that I discuss that they found to be profound was the library.
If you go into a library now and you start reading out loud, what do they do?
They come over and say, you know, read silently or get out. Now, if you went to an ancient library, what would it would be like?
You would walk into the door and you would get the reading material either from an attendant or whatever,
and you would walk over to a booth and you would sit down and you would read it out loud in a little booth.
And if you were with if it was a long piece of work, you would bring several people with you and you would pass it around.
And so that was like the birth of the conference room, for example. Right.
So now when you walk into a library, it's like the morgue.
But back then in ancient times, you would walk into the library and depending on its size or some of them had 100,
if not thousands of booths of various sizes.
Could you imagine people or, you know,
reading organized material because it would be thousands or hundreds of people speaking all at the same time.
And they're not completely soundproof.
So could you imagine, Chuck, you could actually lean against,
put your hand on the wall of the building or your feet on the floor and feel the vibration.
Right. And it wouldn't really sound like a crowd speaking.
It's a little different because this is not conversational.
This is actually a steady rhythmic reading.
This has not been experienced by anyone in modern times at all.
Yeah, the closest thing I can think to relate it to is when I was a musician
and I would rent a place in a practice building and there were, you know,
10 other bands or groups of musicians.
And if you walked in the hallway, you were confronted by the sounds from 10 different rooms.
OK, but it wasn't just sound.
There was this organized rhythm that each one had where they meshed or didn't.
Yeah, exactly. Exactly. And to varying degrees.
I mean, some guys were highly professional and precision.
Others were, you know, writing material or tuning or whatever.
And you were dealing with all levels at seemingly at once, you know.
And the thing was, why? Why did they read out loud in the libraries like that?
Because guess what, folks? No one read silently.
Everything that was read, it was understood that you read out loud.
And once I was walked in on someone watching an old black and white film
and the scene was a captain in his quarters and he was reading a letter out loud.
And I told the person that is historically accurate for that time period.
They're not just doing it for theatrical purposes for the audience.
That is very accurate. Even if you were alone, you read out loud.
That was just how it was done. Just like now, if you put headphones on, you know,
you expect, you know, to have something coming out of them.
You know, there's they're not just earplugs anymore. Right.
Because years ago, if you saw someone putting something over their ears,
it was because they were cold or to stop the noise.
Now it's to make noise. Right.
Except for, you know, people with a jackhammer or a construction site or something. Right.
So earplugs are still in use, but generally speaking in society,
if you see somebody putting something over their ears,
you're thinking that they are trying to listen to something.
Yeah. It's the opposite of what they were, let's say, 100 years ago or 50 years ago.
Yeah. So these things flip like that. And it's a big deal.
But, you know, if, for example, if you took a picture of people,
let's say, walking through Times Square or an urban environment now and sent it back a thousand years,
why is everyone wearing earplugs? No, they're not.
You see, there's music coming through. Oh, I don't get it.
Well, you have to explain that to me. Right. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, it doesn't. So these a lot of the things that you see are very strange.
But let's start at the very beginning.
You know, if you go and we're going to discuss this from a non-academic,
non-pedantic viewpoint, but just give people the direction on how to perhaps run and go.
And I'm not going to give too many references.
I'll give descriptions that you could find. And I'm looking at one reference that I pulled up.
I'm not even going to read what it is, but you can go to any quote unquote Christian country right now.
And part of the accoutrement or decoration or ornament is usually a chain with a crucifix or a cross being worn.
Right. I mean, you see it pretty much everywhere.
You even see rappers on stage wearing big crucifixes now.
It's become a fashion thing since the 80s, perhaps. Right.
And I would say the 1970s or so, the the larger pronounced cross came into vogue, so to speak.
I mean, everybody from, you know, the guys in Black Sabbath to the hippies to to Madonna, for God's sake,
have prominently worn these things. And like you said, rappers and it's a it's a commonplace piece of jewelry now.
Yes. Well, where would you say you've seen it first?
Well, the first place I recall seeing it was in a church around around a clergyman's neck, honestly.
But OK, very, very good. That's that's one way to that's one way to say it. Exactly.
And then it but then you saw it, you noticed it was around pretty much, you know, if you once you were made aware of it, you started,
you know, you could notice that it was prominent or sometimes people wear it under their shirt and it was a symbol of their faith.
And if you ask them what it's a symbol of, they would proclaim, well, it's a faith in my savior or this, that or the other.
OK, so it sounds very unique. And right away, people think it's biblical.
But if you have a search engine, you can do a very simple search and put in an Assyrian A.S.S.Y.R.I.A.N.
That's Syrian, but a Syrian king wearing a cross. And if you want to get real specific, put in Stele, which is S-T-E-L-E,
which just means a stone image. And what you will see. Have we brought up the Assyrians before, Chuck?
Well, you and I have. Yeah, we've discussed it. We seem to be the only ones doing it, too.
But anyway. Which is not to be confused with Syria, by the way. This is Assyria.
Assyria with a double S with an A in the beginning and a Y after the R.
If you go look at that in the museums, they have kings wearing crucifixes very much in the style of the way the Christians do.
And this was dated around 900 B.C. So if you ask him why he's wearing a cross and a crucifix.
Now, if a king wears one, you know, there was thousands of other people wearing them as well.
And this had denoted rank. And in this case, it did not denote rank. It denoted a certain faith.
Now, what's interesting about that is if we start looking at the various chronological time points of Christianity,
supposedly being based on something like they say Anno Domini that started what?
2016 or so years ago from a certain character.
Why is the same iconography or imagery being used almost a thousand years prior to that?
Because it's not new. Right.
Because it obviously doesn't relate to the specific method of execution utilized to martyr this figure.
Right. And we've said it before. And, you know, it's interesting.
I've had conversations with people, short ones and long ones, how there was no crucifixion.
He was executed, but there was no crucifixion. And they get it.
And then a day or two later, they forget it, the specifics.
And all you have to do is read the biblical text, which no one does.
But anyway, so if you look at the first thing they put in front of you is that, you know, meaning the cross,
just like other religions have their own symbols, like Buddha, Buddhism has a little fat man.
And Islam has the crescent and the star, which is not a crescent, by the way.
And I don't know why people call it a crescent. But because I guess it looks like that.
You know, if you ever look at, by the way, the symbol of Islam and they call it the star and the crescent.
Right. If you ever look closely, that's not a crescent. It has the crescent shape, but it is not a crescent.
So what is it? You know, it's very simple. Once someone tells you, then you see it.
Like, have you ever seen those photographs sometimes where it's an old woman and a young lady at the same time?
Depends on how you look at it or if you're being shown what to look for. Right.
Oh, right. Yeah. It's a matter of perspective. Yeah. Right.
And if you objectify it, there's no way a crescent doesn't have that geometry.
So what is it? Actually, should we just say what it is? What do you think?
Go ahead. It's an eclipse. It's one. It's one. It's the moon moving in front of the sun.
Anyway, that was that was the only other possibility I ever had in my mind for what it could represent.
You know, because that's what makes sense. Yeah. So, well, if you look at it, it's not a crescent.
Yeah. A crescent would be a sphere that's lit from the side and it forms like a moon crescent.
Right. Or something. So. But it has a general crescent geometric shape.
Actually, what it what it is, something else. So let's continue.
So now we're finding evidence of the iconography and the symbology goes back almost 900 years prior.
And if you want, Chuck, I could bring it up and if someone wants to drop a link in chat or I could drop a link for you,
you could see the image. It's a king. Should I do that for you, by the way, even though we're live?
Well, if you want to drop it in the chat at American Freedom Radio dot com, there's a chat room which is live.
Also, we we also have a caller on the line, Greek. Should I introduce them into the conversation?
Yeah. Why not? OK. Well. Let's see.
Three, five, three area code. You are on the air. Hey, guys.
Mary met this week. I'm calling from Europe. All right.
How are you guys doing? You guys from New Jersey? Something like that.
You know what? Yes. Something like that. You guys are certainly a proverbial needle in the haystack amongst all the B.S.
It's out there. You know, I've been a longtime listener to you, Greek.
Initially, I struggled with your reports. Yeah.
But I've come to appreciate the quality of the information that you bring forth.
And also, I like your rules, guys. I think it's I think they're wonderful.
I think, you know, don't talk about yourself is fantastic.
You know, when callers call into you over the years, listen to you.
It's kind of like the equivalent of someone with their nails on the chalkboard when they start talking about antidote or personal information.
Or, you know, I guess it's just personal information for themselves and pleasure themselves.
But, you know, I'm such a fan of you. And there's so many questions I'd love to ask you.
You tend to roll out these. I'm sorry. I'm just crashing your conversation right here.
I just woke up. No, you're not. You are the conversation. Go ahead.
Yeah, please do continue. I mean, you're the key to this conversation the way I see it.
So go ahead. Sounds like he may be dropped off. Is he still showing?
Yeah, he's still showing. Well, if we could bring him back in or just we'll speak until he starts.
Just if you hear us call her, you just speak right over us. But we can't hear you.
I'm going to put you back on hold for a second and see if that corrects the problem.
You know, it is interesting. Of course, he got to say a few things there.
We did not cut you off, by the way. Let me see if bringing him.
Let me see if bringing you back on helps. And we don't want to necessarily hear from him because he's complimenting us.
Yeah, you got something. Come on. But anyway, go ahead. Yeah. Hi.
Oh, yeah. OK. Well, yeah. So. Oh, gosh. I'm out in the middle of Ireland on the country.
So, yeah, you say. Yeah. You say things and something and they're generally just left hanging there.
And I just feel like reaching through the radio and just like, oh, my God, what?
For example, many years ago, I used to be a prankster.
And I Greek, I guess you kind of helped me along with that. I was a descriptive, prescriptive person.
If you know what I mean. And I'd love for you to go into ways that we can help people heal themselves.
Ways to heal pain. That's just one. Yeah. Can I can I just roll out a few things and I'll get off.
No, no, please don't keep rolling. Yeah, please do. Please go. OK. OK. Yes. OK.
OK. The other thing was, like, how do we separate ourselves from other service dwelling inhabitants?
As you say, apart from putting on a hat. Do it with your mind first. It doesn't have to be physical.
OK. You ever hear of people being having long distance relationships? How do they do that?
They have the same mindset. So the distance doesn't matter.
You can be standing next to someone or live in a society that you don't agree with.
And air quotes, let's say, where you find to be unlawful.
It doesn't mean you have to think like them and do what they do whenever you get a chance not to.
It's called insulation. Yeah. But yeah, that's the remedy for that. It's very simple.
OK. Yeah. You say when this worldwide scheme begins in the Middle East, in the coming years,
you state that inhabitants are going to lose their religion.
And what's going on here in Europe is kind of nutty right now.
And, you know, and you can look at religions. I think all religions are kind of nuts, but some are nuttier by degree.
And you look at some of some of these folks that are from cradle to grave are pretty much brainwashed.
Can they be rehabilitated? That's the question.
No, let me just put it this way. Mankind passed the rehabilitation stage over 2000 years ago.
And, you know, some some of the some of the inmates in the prison are often, you know, different types of criminals.
Don't forget. It doesn't mean that they're really all that different.
So the degrees to which you see the the different religions being out of line are kind of irrelevant when it comes down to it,
because it's all criminal and it's all against against the reality which has presented itself to us.
If we choose to embrace it, that's the way I see it.
You know, I don't know. Well, let's just. Well, that's fine. It's OK, Chuck.
Let's just go back to the basics. Right. The basics is why are the religions bad?
All of them, because they're all debased, meaning it's like the money is debased.
Right. That's why there's so many problems with money.
So if all the if all the religions were not fiat and they actually did anything that was in the text that they alleged to subscribe to,
like let's say Islam did anything in the Koran, Christians did anything in the biblical text,
the same with the Jews and the Buddhists did anything with their writings.
And so did the Hindus. It would all be fine because they're all in agreement.
They all talk about being lawful and they give you hints and guidelines of what's lawful and what's not.
You wouldn't. In other words, right and wrong is not negotiable.
And people then to become become more self anarchistic, let's say,
which means you don't need a leader because you know the right thing.
Anarchy means the A means without an Arcos means head.
And that just means that in an anarchistic society, you don't need a leader or someone to tell you what to do.
You are fully educated about it. And there's always very little crime in those types of societies
because you think two or three times before you do anything in the opposite.
The type of government systems that have been going on on this planet for thousands of years is people don't think that way.
They just do whatever they want as long as they can get what get away with it. Don't get caught.
They don't have any moral consciousness.
If the people went and rebased their religions, those religions would not exist as they are today.
So that's why I say they're unrehabilitated.
But there is going to come a point where they will seem rehabilitated in the future.
And that's part of what's coming in the next decade.
But don't fall for it.
You can enjoy it.
I would love for you to kind of tease that out.
Yeah, I'd love to tease it.
Because the thing that scares the shit out of me is I have a large family, lots of children, not kids.
And I sit at them, like for example tonight, looking at them sleeping and thinking about their future.
What is the future for us?
I've said this before and I could give specifics.
You've got about a decade and a half left before most of the kill shots are administered to the society, right?
And on the planet by the gods, right?
So why don't you hang on and we'll continue that thought.
Yeah, absolutely.
Stay tuned to Ocelli and the Greek.
We'll be right back here on American Freedom Radio.
And Mr. Caller, who we did not identify, please stick with us as well.
I think it's going to get deeper in the second hour.
Greek, what do you think so far?
Oh, sure.
Let's keep going.
All right.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions, running my companies, and I hated feeling groggy and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret the powers that be want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride, our brains are under siege and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve, a revolutionary breakthrough in a category of cognitive enhancers called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself at DNAEvolveSample.com.
That's DNAEvolveSample.com.
Supplies are limited, so go to DNAEvolveSample.com right now.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you Hemp Protein Powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp Protein Powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein, and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates, and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
Yo, what's up? Check this out.
The voice of the revolution.
American Freedom Radio.
What about show business?
Show business, completely dishonest, corrupt, and full of shit, but in a nice way.
Plenty of expensive drugs and perverted sex.
If you're gonna be full of shit, might as well enjoy your work.
Then you have the media.
Not just the news media, let's include them all.
The media are almost literally exploding with bullshit.
Because they're located right at the crossroads of all the other bullshit.
The media are made up of equal parts advertising, politics, business, public relations, and show business.
These people are sitting right at bullshit junction.
There's enough bullshit in the media for Texas to open a branch office.
And you still have enough left over to start two law firms and a Christian bookstore.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us with free education?
Well, that's obviously effective, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America...
All the information they provide is free?
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, man?
Exploiting commonplace corruption?
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice?
Bringing light to important information nobody else does?
They never censor, hang up, or cut off their guests?
Well, that's no fun, is it?
They created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative, and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shows and scum?
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from,
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable people without a voice,
bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream, and alternative media shows and scum?
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents...
So the second hour of Ocelli and the Greek begins on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
We are going through some interesting information tonight, Greek, the hardcore history of Christianity.
We've only just scratched the surface after having given a bit of a primer on it, I think, and it's actually very interesting.
We also had a caller from Ireland who has, looks like to me, rejoined on the phone lines if we want to bring him back in.
And a couple of comments from chat and elsewhere have also come in during the break.
So where would you like to start?
Your choice is yours. Go for it.
Let's go with the caller because he's waiting.
Absolutely. I think that would be the proper thing to do.
Okay. So our friend from Ireland is back on the line, I believe. How are you doing?
I'm a little bit more awake now.
I actually have an audience, so if a few people here, if that's okay, if another question pops in, is that okay with you guys?
Oh, sure. Yeah, we've got an audience here, I think.
Okay.
It seems that way.
You have many fans.
I guess the overriding consensus right here is one of the most important questions is how do we choose our deity?
Yeah, that's a hard one. That's like a catch-22, isn't it?
That's kind of like when you go to a club, a nightclub, you want to get in.
They have the ropes and the bouncer, right?
And you want to go in and the bouncer says, well, you can't come in.
And you're like, why? Because you need a pass.
And you ask him, well, where do I get a pass?
Well, from inside.
Well, how am I going to get a pass from inside if you don't let me in?
So what's the deal, right?
That's the spiritual side.
The secular side or the way that people function is do a little bit of research on that subject.
Let's say you don't know how to cook a leg of lamb.
How do we cook a leg of lamb?
Well, we get a recipe, right?
We try it out, see if it works, right?
And ask someone who does.
You see, it's very simple.
It's very technical.
In other words, this kind of information is technically accessible.
And that's why sometimes I sound like I'm harping because a lot of people say, you know, I do believe in God.
And I'm like, well, you've got a problem there because you're not  it's a plural.
And which one?
And they can't go further.
Why? Because they haven't done their homework.
See, but an interesting thing here is that he has sought  seeking out the recipe for a leg of lamb.
Come to somebody who it sounds like has understood who their deity is, which would be you, and ask you.
How is it that you cook that recipe?
So I actually think this was very, very appropriate.
It's very simple.
You have to have a  before you even go to that, why do you want to get information from a god, basically?
It's how to do things, right?
Even cook a leg of lamb, right, let's say.
So it has to do with law.
When you hear the term law, most people think a tax law, traffic law, dealing with an attorney or a cop or a lawsuit.
That's not what it's about.
Law is  are the rules or guidelines that you use to  how you keep time, what you wear, what you eat, how you do business,
how you do a contract, how you raise a family, how you tie your shoelaces.
All these are laws.
You've heard of like laws of physics, all this other stuff, right?
So if you're going to go on the concept of law, you're going to have to understand that there's something in there called claims.
So I mean how difficult is it to let's say if you go to a government building to recognize the clerk from the manager of the government building,
let's say to a congressman, to the president, because as you start looking at those positions,
they also come with different descriptions.
So the higher up you go, the description changes and there's a little more involved.
What you will do is if you go back and look at the ancient texts, you will see that they all have claims of a hierarchy,
and beyond that, you will see that some have very little information and some have more information,
and then it boils down to very simply this.
If I said I was going to give you an international plane ticket and it's free, where do you want to sit?
Coach, business or first class?
It costs the same, which is nothing.
Where do you want to sit?
Well, most people would choose first class,
and what's called the biblical text is first class in all information based on the claims that the deity makes,
the amount of law that's in there, and also the amount of prophecy of things to come and history.
So that's pretty easy right there, but the problem is if you pick up something in English,
it gets very, very difficult because it ain't so.
Now, this is not a personal thing.
This is just the way the information is laid out.
Now, if you want to go with other information that is based on different things,
you might want to look at other, quote, unquote, writs about gods, right, because it's about getting to the writ first, right?
Comprehend the writ.
That's right.
And, right, so the thing is, you know, some of these things are long, but, you know, there's always excuses.
Like, for example, if something is 1,000 pages long, if you just read three pages a day in one year, you'll go through it pretty easily, right?
Get familiar with it.
You know, just like a computer, you could spend five minutes downloading a program that's 1,000 pages long.
It doesn't mean you need to use it right away, but get it downloaded.
So most people don't even have a basic download of what's going on about history.
Forget about what's called the holy writs of the world or the gods.
They don't have any dedication or time to anything that's come before them in a holistic point of view.
You know, they just want to read something that someone wrote about it.
So that's the plain and simple thing, and I've done this rationally.
It has nothing to do with what I personally believe in.
I could tell you simply, personally, I like good stuff, man.
If I have a choice between eating at a five-star restaurant or a fast food place, I'll probably pick the five-star restaurant every time, right?
But a lot of people wouldn't.
Hi, Greg.
Hi.
I'd like to ask a question, if it's okay.
So where is a good place to start to get this information?
I know you're a Greek.
You know, you understand the Greek language.
But as, you know, starting as an English speaker to access this, is there some reference?
Yeah, yeah.
There's a very simple way to do it.
And I actually had half a dozen discussions about this this week privately on what they call Skype.
If you want to learn about anything, let's say put all this subject matter aside.
Let's say you're going to go work somewhere or even something even more trivial like play a game, a board game, or at a casino with blackjack or whatever.
You have to know the rules of the game, right?
Or when you get a certain occupation, these are the rules, right?
Whether it's informal, unwritten etiquette, all the way to very formal and very stringent rules.
Whenever you want to learn anything about anything, learn what the laws of that thing are.
Like, for example, we don't know what bears really are, but we know enough about them that we can say loosely we know what bears are.
I mean, the only ones, the only beings that know what bears are are the bears, right?
When you think about it.
And the gods, obviously, who made them.
So what are the rules of this?
So what the conversations that boil down to this week, which are very similar to these questions, was if you're going to approach the biblical text, just read the law about it.
First, there's the book of Leviticus and Deuteronomy and Numbers have basically the laws, right?
And just get familiar with the laws where if you were to be quizzed on something like what's the law of contract on this, you can loosely answer it.
And you'll notice that there are only about a very small of them apply to you because most of them are technical.
But get familiar with the laws or the rules first.
People try to jump in around and think it's a religious document, and they don't understand the rules or the laws.
I mean, does that, you know, even you've heard the term the laws of physics, right?
Right.
Well, you know, if you're going to work in engineering or science or whatever, they teach you these laws or rules about thermodynamics and motion, momentum, weight and all these other things before you become functional.
Even though they're academically sound, but practically not, you will find the same in the biblical text.
You will say that, well, this doesn't really apply to the society that I'm in.
It doesn't matter.
The question is, are you familiar with the rules or the laws first before you engage the rest?
And that is the most sane approach.
When you talk about the book of Leviticus, are you talking from the King James Bible?
Is that the  or is that
No.
Yeah.
Well, in Hebrew it would be the Sefir Vayikra, right?
And they translated that or Vayikra into Leviticus because of the Levitical group that was  it was supposed to mind it, let's say.
Now, when I say  regardless of King James, any Bible you pick up, even if it's in Japanese, is based on that.
NIV, any of them are the King James, essentially.
And the way you identify that it is a King James is the first verse, which says,
In the beginning God created the heavens and the earth.
Wherever you read that, that came out of that time period, which is based on what King James did.
Now, here's the thing.
It is good to be familiar.
You can read it in the King James as well because if you're not familiar with the King James, which is colloquial,
you will not be able to engage other people, you see.
How can you have a conversation in it?
So you have to be familiar with that to some degree because that's what society does, even though it's incorrect.
It's incorrect and there's over 30,000 errors in it, which is very poor.
I mean if there were five errors, it would be considered fair.
A hundred errors would be not worth reading.
But there's over 30,000, so what are you going to do?
I mean you have no choice at this point if you're going to communicate with your surface-dwelling earth inhabitants.
But you will find when you start picking up the errors, you will see there's a pattern of mistakes,
even though the mistakes that they did in the King James are not random.
Eventually you will find the pattern, and even though you're not familiar with the direct translation of,
let's say, a particular chapter or book, you will see how it's wrong because you know the law.
See, when you  there's a lot of  if you read the King James,
just most of the stuff that they state in there is just downright unlawful if you read the law.
So you know it's got to be a mistake.
Could you give an example of that?
Oh, sure.
Like an example of that would be when King David was to go and number
he says King David went and numbered the people.
You're not supposed to number the people.
You're supposed to count them.
And the scripture says go and number the people.
And then later on King David gets in trouble for numbering the people because it doesn't say number the people.
It says count the people, do a census.
But later on he gets in trouble for it.
So it doesn't make sense.
So in other words, it's unlawful to number the people, but it's lawful to count them.
In other words, counting the people would be a head count, Chuck, like a census, how many people live here.
But numbering the people is issuing them a serial number.
Does that sound like something you might have heard of before?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah.
And that's been confused.
That's a simple example.
The other one is the New Testament is wrought with errors, completely unlawful in many aspects.
Then we get into nitpicking on words.
Like this is why I always bring up there is no crucifixion.
It's very simple.
Now there's a million websites and books written on that.
Oh, yeah, the Christ walked off the cross.
He lived in India.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
If there's any biblical discussion at all about any topic, the first thing the person speaking on it should say is even though the text has not been translated even to this day,
since we're on the subject matter, let's discuss it and let's be loose about it because what you've read is not accurate.
And this discussion is not being brought up at all.
And it needs to be done that the information is erroneous that's out there.
So that is a simple approach that needs to be taken.
So, yeah, I see our friend in Ireland has passed the phone to someone else.
And, you know, I'm not sure what other questions there might be or if there's someone else that wants the phone passed to them.
Oh, yes, we do.
I kind of shift gears here.
We have a child here to ask the question about even the germ theory, actually, the germ theory, fantastic stuff there.
It's how the Greeks debased and debunked all that.
But even locally and across latitudes, the child asks, what about potatoes here?
Since they don't come from here, but they're grown here.
Is that is that lawful?
Is that is that healthy?
Well, OK, bouncing back to how the human body works, it's really simple.
If it's cold outside, you should eat.
You shouldn't eat food that's grown in the tropics because the food grown in the tropics will change your body chemistry to being in the tropics.
And you're going to feel cold.
So a potato is indigenous to you and they do grow their cross laterally, I believe.
So it would be fine.
Also, keep in mind that when you cook and preserve dry or pickle foods, it changes them.
You've heard of the term transmutation, right?
And usually when you hear that, it's like turning lead into gold or something.
Right. But really what it means is to change one thing into another.
When you cook, pickle or preserve food, you're changing it now into something else.
It's the most basic form of transmutation.
So that needs to be considered as well.
But a potato, I would say, would be where you are fine.
OK.
The 19-year-old, since you're on the transmutation, he has a question about the digestive system.
When you talked about the interstitial pressure of the digestive lining in the gut, that's phenomenal.
I've never heard that before.
It just makes perfect sense.
As you can kind of guess, we were in our past life doctors.
No past life.
Wonderful.
Go ahead.
OK.
I get it.
But yeah, that we're not a filter bag.
But the thing is this.
He said, well, we juice every morning.
And he had beetroot juice and he peed red.
So is that a matter of like rain?
Is it signaling like Dr. Fitzalbert Poff, that kind of thing?
Is that what that is?
The body?
Yeah.
It's done through induction.
Just like a coil in electricity can move the field from one coil to the next, the body moves material like that.
It produces it.
Now, the reason why he peed red is because the body recognized the beet as something it could produce and it produced it.
And then it got to the bladder, right?
Actually, the bladder produced it that way.
The bladder is very  one day we'll get into the specific organs.
But what's interesting is if you ate something like plastic that the body didn't recognize,
you wouldn't see any sign of it in the blood or the bladder or anything.
It would just pass as a lump, right, where you could eat other things that are lumps that the body recognizes,
like salt and dried foods, and the body recognizes it, right?
Like margarine, for example, is something that the body does not recognize.
It just passes through the body.
Most foods are plastic.
Yeah.
I have another question for another child about water.
And what  if water is not H2O, what the hell is it?
And what is  how do you produce good quality water?
Well, water is  think of it as an element, just like your periodic table of elements,
which has  and they say elements are elemental or they're imperial.
They're not ephemeral.
Ephemeral means they don't change.
The illusion that water is a compound, it's an illusion of a basic transmutation
or disassociation or emergence of electrodes and air in water.
In other words, they initially started using electricity to break water into hydrogen and oxygen,
and they came up with the assumption in 1811 over three days of experimenting that,
oh, water must be hydrogen and oxygen.
And it's not because they were never able to take the entire volume down to hydrogen and oxygen.
It's a basic element.
And this is discussed in the ancient texts, by the way.
Water is very, very important.
And it's one of these things that have been brushed under the rug for good reason
because if you understand  I've always said publicly that once mankind had deep comprehension of water,
he will be able to master the physical universe.
I'll say that again.
If mankind had a deep comprehension of water, he would be able to master all physical reality.
What does that make him?
A god, pretty much, and it's not time yet.
And those that are able to master that do godlike things, for example.
The water you make  the advice you gave us, we always do like a cursory thing where we take two plants
and we do one with tap water and one with your water that's kept cool, dark, and round bottom.
And the plants, of course, grow better.
And so you can imagine what that does to the body.
It's just phenomenal.
Oh, by the way, your rice, the coffee, what else?
Everything is  we made your rice today.
It was phenomenal.
Oh, the recipe works?
It's very simple.
The perfect rice.
And it's probably the best rice, right?
It's phenomenal.
This is from the Uncommon Sense on AFR we did about a year ago or so.
We did two episodes, I think, on how to do some very basic cooking.
And one of them was called The Perfect Rice and how you can always make the perfect rice.
Thank you.
Well, excellent.
Do you guys have anything else you want to get into?
Just a quick mention.
When people master water or understand water, they can do amazing things.
And you refer to some people being able to do that.
Who are those people?
Most of  I'll put it this way.
Most of them that were able to do it are dead.
And those that can do it aren't talking about how to do it right now exactly.
How's that?
You're talking like Wilhelm Reich.
I would say Victor Schauberger was one of them.
Schauberger, yeah.
Yeah, Victor Schauberger would be the  there's several others that are unheard of.
I could even bring up names.
It wouldn't matter.
They've passed.
And there's a few people left, yep.
But if you do come up with something like that, it doesn't mean you can't use it.
Just don't talk about it.
Okay.
Well, listen, we thank you so much.
You guys are probably the only contemporaries alive that we're interested in speaking with.
And we appreciate all your information, and we will certainly contribute to your show.
Thank you very much.
Well, thanks very much.
Well, I do appreciate all the questions there, that's for sure.
I like it when we can get into a discussion.
And with that in mind, we actually have somebody on the Skype, Greg, if you wouldn't mind going to that person.
And that is somebody that I'm extremely familiar with.
It's Daniel Lewis-Crumpton, who is the author of Then Came the Flood, has been on AFR many a time on my show, et cetera, et cetera.
I remember.
And is also the man behind DownloadedContent.com right now, which is an interesting story, to say the least, if you haven't heard of it before.
But Daniel has joined us, and I have no idea what he wants to discuss.
But where are you at, Daniel?
How are you doing?
I interrupt this regularly scheduled broadcast to bring your listeners a public service announcement, Chuck.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Hey, man.
Just got home from a 12-step, and I heard you on the radio.
I guess you were doing some overtime, but I got two good pieces of news for you and your audience.
And as a fellow agent of chaos, I know that you'll be happy to know that DC has finally revealed that there are actually three jokers in the DC universe, not one.
Okay.
Second good piece of news for everybody out there listening.
I am the executive producer of the Ocelli Effect documentary Nutshell, which is in production right now.
And it is 85% complete, 85% complete.
And so we're shooting for January.
So the reason I wanted to bust up in here and interrupt you real quick is to let everybody know that it will be coming out in January.
I guess it's up to Chuck when he chooses launch.
However, we were fronted a great amount of resources to get this documentary off the ground and seeing as how it's Christmas.
And we'd like to finish wrapping this documentary.
If everybody who's listening could go to ocelli.com, there's a donate button.
Help Chuck pay this off because he got it on time.
So I know everybody wants to see it.
Chuck hasn't really even seen it.
I've been working very intensely on it.
So it's exciting.
The footage that I was cutting up last night and watching it go on the test monitors, I think Chuck's going to love it.
I know his listeners are going to love it.
But we still got to pay the bills on it to get it out there.
So we're kind of doing it in faith.
So I had to jump in and tell you that as soon as I got in today, man, because I'm super excited about it.
Well, look, I appreciate that, Daniel.
But kind of interesting that we're doing this on this show because I didn't know that's what you wanted to do.
I was kind of hoping you were going to add into the conversation, although I do appreciate all that you just said.
And I'm sure you have some thoughts related to what's being discussed tonight, don't you?
What's that? What are we talking about?
Thanks, Daniel. That's great.
And the thing is if you're going to do any kind of funding, I'll just give some  this is a private conversation in public.
I found that people like to donate, and they should.
But I like to suggest that putting a figure on it, like back in the days when they used to do drives,
they had something that looked like a thermometer.
They wanted to raise $100K.
And then as the donations came in, how much percentage is done?
Because people like things to be close-ended.
So whatever you want to raise, I mean add a little bit, pat it a little bit,
and show how much you've gotten roughly in percentage.
And that kind of motivates people to get it done.
I just want to throw that in.
Is this the Greek?
Yeah.
Hey, Greek. How are you doing?
Merry Christmas.
It's Christmas, guys.
So put whatever you think Chuck is worth on it.
It's the spirit of Christmas.
I personally know that he put a lot of stuff into this, a lot of energy, time, passion.
There's a lot of people who believe in him who actually help.
Patricia is one of them.
Barry Prince is one of them.
A lot of other people who don't want to be named, don't want to take credit for it,
have funded the launch of this documentary.
But honestly, if Chuck has ever done anything for you guys that made you think,
made you laugh, gave you hope, anything like that, whatever is on your heart.
If you're in the chat, if you're listening to this on the rebroadcast,
I mean I know I personally put some resources into it.
Greek, I'm sure you have or will before the end of the night so it can get launched.
So really, honestly, it's the Christmas spirit.
Well, also if Chuck pissed you off, send him money.
I mean not just because you feel like  how about this?
Why all that?
How about if you don't like Chuck, send him money?
How's that?
That will work.
You'll get there quicker.
Thanks, Daniel.
Well, we're going to get back into what we're hammering.
I don't like Chuck and I'll send him money.
There you go.
Look, if everybody that hates me
You set too many limitations.
If everybody that hates me sends $10 right now, I'll go away because I'll
No, no, no.
You got to keep coming back because they'll hate you some more and send you more.
You see, don't put limits on yourselves, man.
You want the people that don't like you to send you the money.
You see, I mean look at how that works, man.
I mean it's limitless.
Just keep going for it.
Thanks, Daniel.
We're going to jump right back into what we were doing, man.
What are we doing?
I got a minute.
Thanks.
So we were on the next  let's jump back.
We appreciate the call from Ireland.
I mean not because he said good stuff.
I mean it's just that he's listening like you said, Chuck.
So that means there are three other people out there.
But we just finished talking about like we were going to give a history.
We've got about a half hour left of what people call the Christian era and what
symbology has been put in front of them because sometimes when people get a
little bit more of an understanding of the history of the thing, they kind of
understand more about the thing, right?
So what we brought up, I dropped in chat, is an image of  you can reference it.
It's an ancient Assyrian king wearing pretty much the iconography or the
symbology that you see in modern Catholic or Christian nations and even
personified in culture as fashion now, Chuck, right?
It's being used as a fashionable statement which is quite accurate, right?
Well, that's the interesting part here is that we do see the sign of the cross
being one of these things that is part of the iconography, if you will, of what's
supposed to be Christianity.
It's at least supposed to be suggestive of it and what the story is, is that again,
it's because this is the method of execution that was allegedly used for the
character  oh, I'm saying  but that's why I said allegedly used for the
character that we have now come to call Jesus Christ.
Now let me just interrupt for a moment.
A lot of people also like to do comparative with what's called the Egyptian Ankh.
Now you notice we didn't go there.
Why?
Because if you look at the Egyptian Ankh, it was something that was  it was a
divining tool that was held in the hand.
Just like divining rods, you know, people used to find water in the ground and
things like that, right?
The Ankh was used as a divining tool to find power spots in the ground, let's say,
or other things like that.
We're not talking  we're talking  in other words, the image you dropped in
chat of this ancient Assyrian king from about 900 B.C. is about as specific and
as according to what you get today, right?
It's not an Ankh.
It's just clear as day that it's what you see in any, quote, unquote,
Christian culture right now.
So I just wanted to throw that in also.
Now, by the way, since we brought up  I was going to bring up how the
crucifixion and all that, how there is none.
How do we know that?
Well, the biblical text doesn't state it.
And you know what?
Historical text doesn't state it, right?
Now, where do you go in the biblical text to find out very simply there was no
crucifixion?
And we've gone over this, Chuck, before.
I think on the fourth episode a couple of years ago with you.
And it's very simple.
Even if you've seen the movies, when the Christ is brought to Pontius Pilate,
what does Pontius Pilate do?
He does a public handwashing, right, with a bowl of water, right?
You've heard of that.
Even if you've never read the biblical text, they show that in the films.
But after that, everything falls apart.
Now, symbolically, doing a public handwashing, what does that mean?
Well, he states what that means, that anything that happens from now on,
I cannot be held liable for, right?
But where did he get that notion to do the wash basin with the public
handwashing?
That is part of what?
Biblical law also.
Most people don't know that because they don't read the law, right?
That was done for the elders.
Why?
I'll throw it in there.
Because the elders had to do that to show that they had no part of something.
And you can get into the details more on your own time.
So right there, when Pontius Pilate takes the water out to do a handwashing,
it means that he is fully competent of the law of Moses, right?
Today, culturally, people would state that they wash their hands of a situation.
Yes.
This is common vernacular.
Even though it's not adherent to a law form,
if you ask people why they're doing it, they don't know why.
But back then, for example, in order to be educated,
see he was a prefect governor of Judea, and if you spoke to Pontius Pilate,
guess what?
He represented Caesar.
It was pretty much just as good as speaking to Caesar.
If you're a Roman citizen, you had a right to go and have court at Caesar's
court, but this is not the issue.
In other words,
Pontius Pilate was very highly educated of that part of the world.
Now, just to continue,
what is the next thing in the biblical text that Pontius Pilate states regarding
this man that is brought to him?
If you go read in the text, I'm going to paraphrase here.
He says,
I see no guilt in this man and I'm returning him back to you to use your law.
And he's addressing the Judean authorities.
In another part of the text, if you harmonize it,
he says through another account, another book in the New Testament,
he says, you have a law.
Use your law.
Who is he addressing?
Those who brought him, who brought him to him was the Judean authorities.
Let me ask you, what kind of method of execution do the Judean authorities use?
Do they use Roman law?
Do they use the law of Moses?
It would be the latter, wouldn't it?
Well, I would think it would have to be the law of Moses.
Right.
And under the law of Moses,
it's very clear that capital punishment is death by stoning.
Right?
Well, that's what I thought it was.
Yeah.
Well, you don't have to.
But there's a hierarchy of crimes.
And if it's a very high crime, you're to be hanging from a tree
or actually fastened to a tree is the Hebrew term when that event is happening.
Now, what is the highest crime in Mosaic law?
I'll answer it.
Blasphemy.
And what was the Christ accused of?
So now when we go to the rest of the context, we know it's an almond tree
because there's over 30 hints to what kind of a tree it was.
I mean, unless you're really dense and you can't take a hint,
there's over 30 references to the almond tree and something very important happening.
Right?
Now, here's the other point.
The people passed for all these hours doing what?
They passed from 3rd to the 9th.
So anyway, you can get into it.
And by the way, it's not even over yet.
You know what happens if something is hanging from a tree in the biblical law?
It's considered accursed.
And anything accursed is to be what?
Burned.
That's why even in the movies, you know, they took his body and they put it in a tomb.
And do you remember that tomb had to be guarded by Roman soldiers?
Why?
Because it says in the text the Judean authorities wanted to come and get it and do what with it?
Anyway, that's why if anyone shows you an artifact from that time, it can't be.
Now, that's the biblical text.
It's very easy.
Anyone can read this.
If you can read English, even in the King James, it comes through.
Now, if you look up what the term crucifix means, it's a botanical term,
meaning it has to do with a flowering tree or a blossom.
Go look it up.
That's what a crucifix means.
So it's been changed.
Now, that's the biblical side of it.
That's the execution.
You know, this is supposed to be a season of when he was born, right?
But anyway, that's a very simple  did you  did I  was that pretty simple enough series of events
that I laid out here on there is no crucifixion, how you can space that out pretty easily?
Well, the other problem for me is that according to Roman history the way I understand it,
even if the Romans had been the executioners,
they would not have utilized crucifixion on a crossbar the way it's described.
This was not done at this point in history.
No.
They cut your head off or they flayed you publicly.
But even then, you want to get into just a little more detail.
We don't have a lot of time, but we have enough time to go over the cursory things that we're going to give.
It's very simple.
The reason the Romans were involved is why?
Because Judea was under Roman occupation.
Let's just flip that around for the mindset.
Remember we discussed the mindset earlier on, right?
Let's say the U.S. was taken over by Russia, let's say, okay?
And they're occupied now by Russia in an overt military fashion.
What does that mean?
Now when you walk around the streets you see a Russian soldier with a machine gun on the corner.
Does that sound about right for an occupation?
Sounds about right, yeah.
Okay.
Now let's say in America you have a tradition called the Fourth of July.
Now how are you going to do that under occupation?
Well, you have to go to the occupiers, the Russians, and say, hey, listen, guys.
We do this thing called the Fourth of July.
And the Russians will say, okay, you can do your fireworks and your parades, but we're going to manage it.
We're going to put out the yellow caution barrier tape.
We're going to control the crowds.
We're going to be  you see?
Right.
No, no.
I understand that.
However, with an understanding of Roman occupation, again, with my understanding of Roman history,
sometimes they did allow local authorities to still handle certain things.
Yes.
Which makes perfect sense here that they would allow if the Judaic authorities.
Judean, yeah.
Judean, excuse me, authorities were still present and holding a post under Roman rule.
They would still have a situation where Pilate, even though he might have had the authority to make the decision,
would have still turned him back over to the local authorities.
Perhaps, but now we're getting into a point of what we think,
and the purpose here is to just maybe guide the listener through a simple way that they can find the fundamental.
Well, I'm just saying that that makes it plausible, that's all.
Sure, but yeah, but you know what else is plausible?
Oswald shot Kennedy, right?
But anyway, so how about you hear about a bunch of Arabs with box cutters?
Anyway, so the thing here is this.
You'll see a lot of people say there's no historical reference.
There is no historical reference of the Christian Jesus, but there is a historical reference of the biblical one.
How do we find that?
Unfortunately, to my dismay, it is no longer online.
They've really changed it, and what am I talking about?
I'm talking about letters of Pontius Pilate to Claudius Tiberius Caesar.
You were able to get  now they have  it's been infiltrated.
It says the true translation of Pontius Pilate's letters to Claudius Tiberius Caesar,
and whenever you see the true  you know what that means.
It's not.
It's redacted.
They're missing.
You can go to a university and find them.
Now, why is that a real historical record?
Because the Romans were really much into  very much into record keeping.
They're actually  the Roman and Greek style of record keeping is still the model today, by the way, okay?
So if you go and investigate  not to get into too much, but let's just spend another two minutes, okay?
If you go and investigate the historical side, Pontius Pilate was writing frequently to Claudius Tiberius Caesar.
Why?
Because when he had taken his post in Judea, he was undermanned and understaffed to the point where he told his higher ranking officers,
do not wear Roman garb.
Go in disguise because we are so few in number that if the people find  you see, we can't protect you, you see.
So he was waiting for backup, and the backup came in the form of Syrian mercenaries.
But during that time, he kept writing letters like basically, where's my help?
You know, I need troops here.
You know, I have to go in disguise, you know, public, right?
So he kept  to make a short story long or a long story short here, he says in one of the letters that he ran into someone
that was told was speaking against authority, and he went and listened to this man named Joshua.
And it turned out that he wasn't speaking against Roman authority.
He was speaking out against the religious authority at the time, right, the Sadducees and Pharisees.
And what's interesting is he couldn't really pinpoint him if he was a philosopher, a teacher, a wise man.
He was too young, so forth.
And he took a liking to what he was saying.
He found it to be more profound than any of the philosophies that he's ever heard or read anywhere.
And then just to really shorten this without getting more into it, he says that at one point,
this man Joshua was brought to him by the authorities for trial, judgment, and execution,
but he couldn't really control the matter because the angry mob took him away to be stoned.
This is the historical record.
Now, if you think you're Christian and there's a crucifixion, you read that, you're going to say,
oh, that has nothing to do with what I believe, right?
Do you get it?
It wouldn't given what you've been told, yeah.
Yes, the historical record, the secular record, and the biblical record are in 100% agreement.
But the Christian record, they'll tell you there is no historical, there is nothing.
Don't read the Bible, you see.
So what's going on here?
What's going on is Oswald shot Kennedy, there was a bunch of hijackers with box cutters,
and Japan attacked Pearl Harbor, and on and on and on and on.
It just  when is it going to end?
Well, I'm showing you here where it started, right?
Perhaps.
Can I say something?
You just did.
Go for it.
Go ahead now.
I think you raise a lot of good points, and I think that a lot of the points that you're raising,
a lot of people who do consider themselves Christian do miss.
They miss the forest for the trees, and I also am a minister, but what I tend to do is
was there a historical figure?
Was there not a historical figure?
Was it a tree?
Was it a post?
Was it a cross?
I just look at  I'm a layman, and I read it, and the Bible itself says that itself is an allegory for our learning,
for our teaching.
It's an allegory.
It's a story, and if there was a historical Yeshua or Jesus or however you want to pronounce his name here on this earth,
the things that he did  there's not enough books on the earth to contain what he did.
But knowing that it's an allegory, the entire story, just like Buddha or Krishna or any other sun deity,
the layman in me wants to bring it down to the kiss rule, which is keep it simple, stupid,
and for me, the entirety of the Bible really boils down to be good to other people.
Be good to other people.
Okay, but that's fine for you, and there's 6,999,999,000 that has it for me.
We're trying to give the objective point on what it's based on.
For example, old coins, they put the reeded edge, the little ridges on the outside,
because before they did that, people would scrape away a little bit of gold every time it got past,
and then its value was worth nothing.
We're trying to put a reeded edge on the information where if you saw a gold coin
and that little serrated edge was gone, it means it's not the full value.
So we're trying to show  whenever we give information,
we try to put a reeded edge on it to show that it hasn't been tampered with, right?
And that's just being objective.
There's a lot of aspects, and have you ever heard of the fox and the grapes?
Well, Greg, I think that we all can agree that it's been tampered with,
but none of the tampering is going to contradict be good to other people, I don't think.
No, it doesn't, but good and evil are kind of different too.
If you just robbed a bank and you're running down the street,
and everyone says, get them, and the cops knock you down,
are the cops good to you or are they bad to you?
They're pretty bad.
It depends, right?
You see my point?
So you've got to  again, it's the general good and general evil.
Right now you live in a society where pretty much everything that people consider good is downright evil,
and pretty much what people consider as evil is good.
So how do you manage that?
You can't.
The only thing you can do is set yourself apart.
Let's just carry on on the conversation.
I don't mean to step on you, but we only have about 20 minutes left.
Chuck, I want to go to the next point here,
which is one of the salient points on maybe considering what happened.
I don't need to bring up what happened with the Kennedy assassination or 9-11
or other events in history to say that the official story is pretty much there to serve the officials, right?
Then the rest of it is just enough so people can go on with their lives
and feel like they've got a satisfactory reasoning for why it happened,
but we know it's not true, right?
That's pretty much it.
What happened in the first century, people communicated very rapidly through commerce.
You see, if you were doing commerce with fresh fruits and vegetables,
it didn't matter if you were pulling it by horse or by ship,
you had to get it to where you were going fast, right?
So just like the post, they put it on commercial planes and commercial ships
because they get there quickly and the post gets there quickly, right?
So information of some very fantastic things that were happening in the area of Judea
were getting around the world, but no one really got the specifics
because in order to know the specifics, too, you needed to know the law, right?
Like we just stated, right?
You can't sit at a blackjack and not know how to play it.
How are you going to do it?
Or chess, how can you not know anything?
This is how people are trying to manage things, right?
So no one really knew.
So whenever you heard something fantastic, you had to say,
well, it had to do something with the gods.
And you already had a god, you know, a geographical one.
You know how like the Norse and the Celtics had their gods
and the North Africa and the Greeks had their others
and the Persians had their others, right?
They each had their geographical.
So whenever they heard something phenomenal like that,
they had to associate it with something simply that they were already associating with.
So you see, just like, for example, if you look at the research on the JFK assassination
or research on 9-11, there's tons of it, right?
But how much of it is really accurate?
You know, you might have a few little accurate points there,
but on the whole, they all fall apart very quickly, right?
But they're there to satisfy for some reason.
So what happened, there was a lot of events that had to be explained.
Now, if we look very closely, now we can jump into, we have a few minutes left,
who financed modern Christianity back then,
or we could talk about the two major groups that became the iconography of the financier.
So should we go with the two major groups?
We've discussed the financier of this project, and his name was Simon Magus.
He is of Samaritan extraction.
Have you ever heard of the term the Good Samaritan?
You ever heard of that?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, right, because whenever there was criticism of what he was doing,
he's good, man, leave him alone.
You know, the Good Samaritan.
Now, why are the Samaritans important?
Because they were generally a pagan culture, but they also integrated the biblical law.
So they were pretty much doing a little bit of everything.
So they were slightly more knowledgeable than most people
in what's known as biblical law than the other cultures,
because they had previously integrated.
That's why when the Christ meets the Samaritan woman, he says,
well, you have all of these husbands, but one of them you're not married to, meaning, you know.
So what's interesting, he was a magician, meaning ledger domain and doing magic tricks, right?
But he was also extremely wealthy.
So he was a David Copperfield or Houdini illusionist with the budget of Bill Gates.
You can do a lot with that, right?
Because it's very impressive to be around someone who can do these kinds of magic tricks,
and it's even more impressive to see how he was able to finance anything he set his mind to do, right?
So he was the one that grabbed, and actually that's why when you look before Constantine,
you had a tremendous amount of works that were just like the 9-11 commission report, right?
That was commissioned to be written.
There was one, wasn't there the, was it called the Warren Commission or something?
The Warren Commission was the first investigation of the Kennedy assassination.
Right. So what commission did Simon Magus do?
Have you ever heard of Gnosticism?
Well, yeah, I have, but it seems...
Well, Holmes is simplifying it here, is that what it is?
Yeah, it seems that way.
Okay, let's keep going.
Okay, this is a really good basis to look at it, right?
Now, anything that I'm telling you, you can bet.
Anyone can bet, and you will see that is the predominant figure behind that, right?
Why would I, there were others, but why was he the most predominant?
Because he was the most influential because of his character and his ability,
and also he was the most influential because of his financial purse.
Okay?
Now, what's interesting here real quick, and I know we're running low on time,
but I know that Daniel, who's back on the line,
part of his description for himself is Gnostic,
and I know that he directly objects to this idea about Simon Magus,
and I'd kind of like to let him ask you about that.
Sure, but how about we, let me just get these two other points in,
if you can remember that, we'll do that.
Because that's a personal objection, you know,
what if he was Muslim and he objected to it?
Let's stick to the subject, right?
The other two things I wanted to bring up that people need,
that they do things without explaining,
how's the audio, by the way, am I coming through okay?
You're coming through just fine to me, yeah.
All right, because I just had someone that was monitoring
and saying that I'm very far away.
Okay, so the other point, there's two things that were grabbed onto,
two things that were grabbed onto that are still culturally alive today,
in terms of iconography and the way that this religion,
which is actually a major world culture, functions.
One of them would be the ancient god of Serapis,
who was a god that kind of bridged Greek and Egyptian culture together,
and most of the iconography, and the halos,
and all these things that you see, and the church architecture,
came from the cults of Serapis, okay?
The other one, Aesclepius, or Aesclepius,
I guess how would you spell that, let me look that up,
A-S-C perhaps, Aesclepius, A-S-C-L-E-P-I-U-S,
Aesclepius would be brief,
he was the god of healing, the Greek god of healing,
and the god of good health.
And the groups that surrounded him also took interest
in what was going on in the first century in Judea,
and many of their behaviors from these two groups,
Serapis and Aesclepius, are the majority of the iconography,
the visuals that you get, the gestures,
and the language that you see in modern Christianity today.
Let's give a couple of examples for that, real quick,
and then I'll yield and we'll see what Daniel has to say.
I'm doing this for the audience, by the way.
Let's go backwards.
Aesclepius, because he was the god of healing and such,
have you ever heard of people say, God bless you?
Yeah, of course, all the time.
In conversation?
Sneeze, cough, whatever, yeah.
Or even in a conversation.
In general term, yeah, God bless you,
like as a parting thing to feel good,
or as a recognition of something which is good, etc.
Sure, that came from the cult of Aesclepius.
That was one of the main things they did.
Also, have you ever heard of, there were two festivals,
one in the spring and one in the winter,
that were for Aesclepius, right?
And also Serapis.
Now, with Serapis, have you ever heard of,
let me just put it this way,
with the cult of Serapis and Aesclepius,
the lords, or the people who ran industry,
during the winter festival,
they would give a financial bonus,
or gifts to their, let's say presents,
to their workers, just before the festival.
Have you ever heard of what's called a Christmas bonus?
Yes.
That's where that comes from.
And that's been going on with Serapis and Aesclepius
for a very, very long time.
Have you ever seen the iconography of a certain bearded figure
with his arm and his hand up and his fingers up?
It looks like a scout salute, usually two fingers up or so.
Right?
That is the sign of the cult of Aesclepius.
And you can still see statues of it today.
And this is just a direct thing,
because if you actually read, again,
in what the biblical text is supposed to be,
their foundation,
there is nowhere in there where it says,
God bless you, even in that loose thing.
It doesn't command that.
It's not even done culturally.
This is very foreign to what the basis of it is supposed to be.
So where did it come from?
So these are the various aspects of it.
We haven't discussed what's called Christmas.
And the irony of that, Chuck,
is it's already been very easily established
that whatever day you're going to observe,
whether it's a holiday or even an anniversary
or any other personal thing,
how are you going to do it accurately
if you're using the Pope's work schedule?
Because right now, it's over ten days off.
So in other words,
people think it's going to be Christmas in a few days.
It was actually a week ago last year.
Rawfully, meaning the birds, the sun.
So in other words, the birds, the bees, the whales, the lions, the tigers.
So what's wrong with these people?
They think they're doing...
Why are there observations all over the place like that?
Don't they know what day it is?
So when anyone wants to do any observation,
like years ago,
you're going to have to go to the hardware store
or now it's done with the digital convention.
So if you're complaining about anything,
don't forget you've agreed to it.
Anyway, with that said,
I think throwing in the cult of Asclepius
and the cult of Serapis,
we don't have to discuss it.
Just getting it out there
so people can look it up on their own
and the behavior and the culture
and how it's carried forward to this day.
That's why when we say it's 0% biblical,
we just give more information
so people can look
and see how all-encompassing
the Simon Magus, the Asclepius, and the Serapis
is at the foundation
of what people call Christianity is.
So with that said, I yield.
Go ahead, Daniel.
I wanted to get to the fact
of what we were talking about.
I'll forgive you for stepping on the derogatory,
but I guess what I would have to say,
because I don't have time,
as short as 2 Corinthians says,
is who have also made us ministers of the New Testament,
not of the letter,
but of the spirit.
For the letter killeth,
but the spirit giveth life.
And that's kind of one of my key verses
in that we can search the scriptures
and search the scriptures
for all types of technicalities,
loopholes, contradictions,
and infractions against history,
but it's the spirit
of what the book is talking about.
And like I said,
when I first got on tonight,
I just got back from a 12-step program
that happened to be hosted by a church.
I met with a lot of men
at a rescue mission
who were homeless,
who were destitute,
decided to give it up on
because they're ignorant,
they're stupid,
and there's no hope for them.
Some of them are going to see
their kids for Christmas
and their parents.
And I saw a bunch of people
who called themselves Christians
with no idea how to read Greek,
no idea how to read Hebrew,
have no depth whatsoever
in any of this subject matter,
grab them,
love them,
tell them everything's going to be okay,
lift them up from the muck and the mire,
and be as Christ-like
as that book possibly demands
and asks us to be,
with complete ignorance
of head knowledge,
but with a heart knowledge
that Christ computed to us
first of Christ,
whatever you believe it is.
Okay, hold on right there.
I get your sentiment,
but whatever you believe it is.
Hold on, hold on.
Whatever you believe it is.
When you said whatever,
we don't go,
well, hold on.
When you said
whatever you believe it is,
now we could be talking
about Mickey Mouse.
I just want to say,
oh, okay.
Hey, it's Mickey Mouse.
It's Mickey Mouse.
It allows you to feed the hungry
and clothe those without clothes
and shelter those without shelters.
If Mickey Mouse
inspired you to do that,
then believe in Mickey Mouse.
That's me, man.
Well, that's what we're talking about.
Not everybody wants Mickey Mouse.
Thank you again for the comment.
And also remember
that when they were
sacrificing children
in ancient Canaan,
they also had places
to help people and like that.
So anyway,
thanks very much, everyone.
Thanks, Chuck.
Absolutely, guys.
The work of Jesus Ocelli in the Greek
is done for this particular time period,
but we shall return next week
according to the Pope's work schedule
on Thursday.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck
because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly
like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions,
running my companies,
and I hated feeling groggy
and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret.
The powers that be
want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride,
our brains are under siege
and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon
to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve,
a revolutionary breakthrough
in a category of cognitive enhancers
called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve
and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again
and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself
at DNAEvolveSample.com
That's DNAEvolveSample.com
Supplies are limited,
so go to DNAEvolveSample.com
right now.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle,
burns fat,
improves digestion,
and feeds the entire body
the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the US government
banned the hemp plant
from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule 1 drug
to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused
about this plant for over 80 years
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana
and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties
of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world
to know these basic facts
and to help people understand
that hemp protein powder
is the best-kept health secret
you need to know about.
Remember,
hemp protein powder
contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free,
anti-inflammatory,
non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367
888-910-4367
and see what our powder,
seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org
The world is like a ride
at an amusement park
and when you choose to go on it,
you think it's real
because that's how powerful
our minds are.
And the ride goes up and down
and round and round.
It has thrills and chills
and it's very brightly colored
and it's very loud.
And it's fun for a while.
Some people have been on the ride
for a long time
and they begin to question,
is this real or is this just a ride?
And other people have remembered
and they come back to us
and they say,
hey, don't worry,
don't be afraid ever
because this is just a ride
and we kill those people.
The eyes of fear
want you to put bigger locks
on your door,
buy guns,
close yourself off.
The eyes of love
instead see all of us as one.
Here's what we can do
to change the world right now
to a better ride.
Take all that money
we spend on weapons
and defense each year
and instead spend it
feeding, clothing,
and educating the poor
of the world,
which it would many times over.
Not one human being excluded
and we can explore space together.
Both inner and outer.
Forever.