The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand was this.
Good evening, American Freedom Radio listeners, this is Ocelli in the Greek, as that interesting introduction told you.
So, it is midnight, allegedly, on the East Coast, and 9pm on the West Coast, and God knows what time it is wherever you are, however you're listening to this.
We don't exactly know how to keep time anymore, do we? The little wind-up toy, well, hey, I'm starting to sound like somebody else.
Well, you know, look, it might be the 15th day of the 8th month till noon, and by the Pope's work schedule, it's 10-10-2015.
Except where I'm standing, it's 10-11-2015.
Okay, the wind-up toy changes, yeah, but it goes from noon to noon.
Well, we'll see, we'll see how things progress, and I mean that with a pun.
Yeah, things will be different.
So maybe we're a little bit ahead of the curve discussing these things now, but at least they're being said, and I think that's why we're doing this.
That's what is important, certainly.
And, of course, just for those keeping score at home, this is episode two.
Alrighty.
Now, last week I did promise that we would get into the concept of the container.
Okay, that's what I'm thinking of calling this show.
The concept of the container.
What are you talking about, Chuck? Are you high? No.
The concept of the container. Which container are we talking about?
Well, let's begin with the human body.
There's a lot of misunderstandings about the concept of the container out there.
A lot of misinformation, I would say.
A lot of, well, what do we call that?
That would be the, oh, what do you call that exactly?
Misdirection from the technicians?
Well, there's that, plus there's also the cosmic, what do you say?
Oh, I call it cosmic censorship.
Cosmic censorship. I don't know why the word censorship was alluded to.
Yeah, humans are censored big time, and it will be lifted, but we should discuss these things before anyway.
These are things that are hopefully going to reveal some of the censorship.
Correct, and that's the thing.
You know, we did this kind of in an impromptu fashion yesterday,
but sort of reloaded a lot of the information from previous broadcasts,
and oddly enough, those that did hear it and told me about it,
you know, gave me that thing they call feedback.
Seemed to believe that none of that had ever been said before.
I find that interesting.
Hmm, some of it, all of it, or all of it?
I couldn't get them to identify it.
See, that's the fun part, too, is they couldn't quantify it.
You know, when they say, oh, that show was good, I say, well, what part of it?
The entire thing might not have been.
And they say, no, the whole thing was, but they don't really mean the whole thing was.
They mean that the part that they understood or grasped at that moment
felt good to them for some reason, you know.
Yeah, they call it resonate.
You know, it resonates, you know, it's in tune.
What if the information is dissonant, the opposite of resonance?
You know, that's one thing that the objectivity doesn't care.
The truth must be told.
And I don't even like using that word truth anymore.
It's been dragged through the streets and kicked like a tin can.
Nothing's sacred anymore.
But let's just say things that don't require special research or special equipment
or someone else to tell you how to think.
Right, you can actually embrace these things without being forced to embrace them, too.
You know, the psychological and emotional domination that goes on
through that cosmic censorship we're talking about.
Well, anyway, back to the subject at hand.
The human body, Greek.
You know, you said something to me, and I'll start here.
I know it's going to sound like I'm not starting from the beginning,
but trust me, this is the beginning in my mind.
Blood pressure.
Now, this is one of the most cited statistics, or I shouldn't say statistics, no.
Vital statistics, I guess.
Yeah, or diagnoses, yeah.
Diagnoses, right.
I don't know what it is.
I'm having this slippage between my brain and my mouth today.
And more so since the clock struck 12 here on the East Coast, I guess.
I don't know why that is.
But either way, we'll repair it in progress as we continue the broadcast.
Okay.
So blood pressure, though, is one of these things where people really hang their status regarding their health.
They hang it upon this stat or this statistic known as blood pressure.
What is blood pressure, Greg?
Well, historically, it was started by having the concept of understanding how the system works,
you know, the cardiovascular system.
And the men doing the research had good intentions and were trying to draft a body of work that, you know, other people can reference, right?
And, you know, just like there's a game called helicopter or airplane.
You tell someone a story or whatever, you know, and it changes from person to person.
Oh, telephone.
Helicopter or airplane, that's the financial system.
Yeah, telephone or something.
Yeah, so the story changes.
And this concept of pressure now has gotten to the point where it's not understood and it's been, let's say, the level of inaccuracy has created a lot of grief,
but much to the pleasure and relief of most that believe in such a thing, if you know what I mean.
Right.
And the concept, though, is supposed to be that the amount of pressure in the vessel causes conditions to be exacerbated, right?
I mean, that's.
Well, yeah.
Well, here here's the thing.
There's something, you know, is that healthy?
People say, you know, no.
Is it healthful?
Right.
Is it conducive to health or is it damaging?
I think part of the purpose of saying these things is to give a clear perspective.
You know, so if we're going to go down different roads, it all leads to the same thing is, you know, everyone wants to be they don't want to be in pain.
They want to be, quote unquote, healthy.
They want to be fit. Right.
So how do these things tie in?
I don't know if that might be the purpose of the discussion.
I think maybe the purpose of the discussion I would like to see go where we just look at these things as an example that those that are willing to do the work, which means cognitively, think about other things that they're hearing in a very plain, almost childlike curiosity, not a childlike way where you're uneducated and moronic and immature,
but in a mature way that has the attributes of the curiosity of a child and the openness of a child with full maturity.
So let's go back to the blood pressure, if we would.
I'll give you a quick example about it.
Two examples.
I was once getting some toilet paper in a store known as a drugstore, and there was a man yelling and screaming at the pharmacist behind the counter that if he didn't get his blood pressure medication in time, he was going to die.
And I just had to walk over there and instigate some kind of reality check on both sides.
And the first thing I did was I pointed at the blood pressure machine.
It's like you'd use it yourself.
You put in 75 cents, and you sit down, and there's a cuff that inflates around the arm and stops the flow of blood.
With that machine, I kind of got the pharmacist's attention, and I said, hey, where do I get one of these?
And he says, what do you mean?
And I said, I want this particular machine.
I'd like to get one.
And he says, well, it's not ours.
We just rent it.
And he says, why do you want one?
And I said, well, because I'm starting a museum on medical fakery and quackery, and it's going to be one of the centerpieces.
So he looked at me really strange.
And then the customer, yelling and screaming about why isn't there any blood medication on time for him, said, who told you you're going to die?
And that kind of took him out of his little thing.
So the people are walking around in a trance.
And perhaps what we're going to say is going to stir up a few things where it's like sitting on a thumbtack gently.
What's interesting is before we get into the blood pressure, which is still about the blood pressure, since you opened it, let's roll with it.
You ever notice when you put your feet and hands in water, they get soggy?
And you ever look at your skin?
Does it crinkle up, or does it expand and inflate?
Well, eventually you wind up with that pruning effect, yeah.
Exactly.
It shrivels up.
Now, another example of that would be, let's say you're packing something in a bag, a seal-tight, air-tight bag, and you draw a vacuum on it.
Well, when you draw a vacuum on it, does it inflate, or does it shrivel up, right?
Right.
So very simply, you could see that there's a contractive force, a predominance or a preponderance of a contractive force in the body.
You know, as people get older and their skin grows and the musculature doesn't, do they naturally inflate, or do they get wrinkles as they get older?
You see, when you take a soft vessel or a soft container and you pull a vacuum on it, which is negative pressure or less than atmospheric pressure, it tends to shrivel up.
That's your first sign that your body is under a slight vacuum condition.
And this would be partially because of the atmospheric concern, what we used to describe as barometric pressure, right?
Where you have, in a general sense, like 15 pounds per square inch, you could measure it that way, this kind of thing.
All things are under this very same condition, so therefore it's not exactly relevant.
But what happens is the body sort of has its own...
Yeah, because that condition you just mentioned, sorry, the barometric pressure, that's a scalar function, meaning it's everywhere in the room, outside, in the building next door.
Yeah, we don't notice it because it's scalar in function, meaning it's everywhere, it's the same within reason.
But the body, what I meant by that, it's under a slight vacuum, and once we get momentum into this, all biological things have a slight vacuum, right?
Now, what maintains this vacuum? There's a lot of good work written on that.
I'd like to send people towards the direction of Victor Schauberger.
He was a German naturalist in the 30s.
A lot has been attributed to him and a lot of disinformation as well.
But there's a lot of simple things that people can understand.
Like, for example, if your body is under a slight vacuum and I inflate a cuff around your arm to block the flow of those fluids under a slight vacuum and tell you that you have a positive pressure, there's something wrong there.
Right, because observably, let's just say you put liquid into a Ziploc bag, which is in a vacuum-type condition, you end up not with a change in pressure, but just a shifting of the liquid.
Well, you could have a slightly negative pressure in there, meaning when you pop the bag open, you hear the vacuum seal is broken, but you could still move the liquid around under a vacuum.
Yeah, but that's what I'm saying. You're not actually opening the container and therefore changing the pressure, right?
No, no, you're not. Well, containers are opened all the time. They're called knife wounds, stab wounds, surgeries, yeah.
Right?
Right.
Yeah, and in essence, the body is under a slight vacuum condition.
So what they're doing is they're blocking the flow, which is under a vacuum, and creating a proportion, meaning what is the pressure, let's say, in the vessel in between beats, right?
If you want to get more on the technical end, which I don't, so let's stay on the practical layman's terms.
That is one of the main misunderstandings, and there is an entire industry built around it, and it's not the automotive industry.
Yeah, so they're quite wealthy. You have to understand that during the changeover of the industrial age, most of the men that were known as medical quacks, or sadists, or just generally very cruel and sick individuals, were made leaders and heads of the current industry we're alluding to, right?
So you've got to see that when we're trying to speak objectively, we also have to discuss certain objective history from the other side as well.
The essence, again, about blood pressure is very simple.
The body is under a slight vacuum condition.
So if there is any movement, it is under a vacuum.
So this concept of pressure is misunderstood by the populace.
What's happened is, again, let's just say it this way.
Under the concept of cattle management, you do what you're told, right?
So if you're told such a thing exists, it must, because how do you know?
Because you were told so, right?
And therefore it exists, and therefore because you were told so, yeah.
And under cattle management, that's good enough, right?
But hopefully we're not addressing cattle. We want to address men and women.
And from that respect, you can ask these types of questions to any of the technicians, and they have no answers regarding it.
They always kick the can around or pass the buck.
So one can also see when you break the barrier known as the skin, it takes several seconds, if not sometimes up to a minute,
depending on how deep you go, for any fluids to be expelled.
If there was any kind of a pressure, anyone who's worked around a garden hose,
even under a low pressure will notice that any immediate puncture or anything
will cause a massive expellation, whether it's air or liquid or what have you.
Whatever is within the pressurized vessel, yeah.
Yeah, exactly. So there's further research that should be done.
I could also direct people. There's a Frank Chester, wonderful man.
As in Chester draws it, C-H-E-S-T-E-R.
He has something called the Chesterhedron, and he's done work on the geometry of the heart.
Because going into one's own research on air might make it sound like something that I believe defeats the purpose of our show,
which is to speak plainly and speak to everyone so they can walk away feeling that they've gotten something they can use.
If anyone wants to go in any various depths in the matter, they can look into Victor Schauberger or Frank Chester.
Or they could research biological vacuum.
All biological things are under a slight vacuum condition.
You see, in order for things to grow, all living things have an inward motion towards them, right?
Even from a nutrition, you go out and you take in heat to warm up.
You take in cold to cool down.
You think of living things, what does it need?
You say they're taking in, right?
What does the baby need to eat?
Taking in.
Most of the time, when you interact with something living, you're thinking or concerned about what you're going to give it.
Yes, babies expel.
People expel.
Animals expel.
Plants are a very good example because you're always thinking, does the plant need more light?
Does it need more water?
There's an inward motion, a feeding motion, where when things are alive and when things die and they go into chemical decomposition,
it all goes into outward motion, which is positive pressure.
When you see a rotten piece of fruit, it swells and expels liquids and odors and things, just like a cadaver would.
So all living things are inward, and when they die, they become outward projecting.
So this concept of a biological vacuum is something that has been negated with complete apathy across the board in society.
And when I mean this, I like to discuss things also that are going to be original in thought or in concept to the alternative as well.
The reason why I'm saying this is a lot of alternative, quote-unquote, medicine doctors and practitioners still rely on this concept of pressure,
which is inaccurate, to say the least.
Right, because you have these presumptions that are just established as the canon of knowledge regarding the human body.
It's still based on the same misunderstanding, whether they call it alternative medicine or it's called allopathic medicine or whatever it is you want to call it.
The truth is that they're all based on these assumptions that just don't really have any basis in a lot of cases.
Well, it's because of the training and what's available.
Again, 100% external input.
If you can capture, you see, if you understand that the society at large on the planet is censored and you can realize that and act upon it,
the first thing you would do is take control of all information, right?
Because you know they're censored and anything that they get is extremely limited anyway.
So now if you control the 1% that people can perceive or less than that, now you're pretty much ruler of the world, right?
Well, that's the thing. To rule the information is to rule the world.
I always thought it was quite profound to say that the victors write the histories.
Well, kind of true considering the fact that most times those that are confronted by, say, large militaries or individuals that seek to assert a genocide or whatever,
they usually are the only ones left standing, so who else could possibly write the histories?
Well, sometimes the victor wants to show the posture that he's the loser.
Oh, I'm not saying that they're always going to write it for the most preferable viewpoint for themselves.
In fact, it might be a whole lot more advantageous to them to create a history where they are the victim.
Or the victim, yeah, and the losers, yeah.
Yeah, so they can actually get whatever's left on the table.
Right.
And they wouldn't have to fight for it anymore, now it'll be just given to them through sympathy.
Exactly, right.
Or pride of the other. I mean, I have a conversation whenever I meet, this is a little off topic, with anyone in the military,
I said, what do you think the Americans are going to do when they found out they lost World War II to the Japanese?
And they're like, huh, what, what? And they walk away.
Which is a fact, they did, but it's been publicized in reverse.
But that's another, and I would like to bring an expert on who's done research on that, maybe in the future,
but it's not very difficult to prove.
Who knows, maybe episode three could actually be warfare and the reality of the victor and the spoils.
Oh yeah, well actually, I mean, the Americans have lost every war they've ever been in,
unless they're going into destroying the civilian population.
But either way, that's another concept.
Right, we'll get to that at some point in time.
You know, and I think to myself, when it comes to, because you mentioned the blood pressure medication
that this guy was looking for when you were at the pharmacy.
And the dependence on medications and the way that they seem to have quite the role
when it comes to dictating to the cattle what is going to happen as well.
You know, in some cases people end up with medications that seem to cause other complications
which require another medication, et cetera, et cetera.
Again, the foundation being porous to begin with means that there are a lot of holes for one to fall into.
Well, they're so far removed from reality that the only thing left for them is religion.
Have you ever heard, you know, like if you want to turn an atheist into a religious person,
throw them into a foxhole or something in the war, you know?
Oh yeah, that there are no atheists in foxholes.
Yeah, yeah, that's right. Yeah, exactly.
So what happens is because the information and the, it's multi-generation,
multi-generation and the reality has been removed from the people's perception
that they're in 100% religious mode, but belief right now,
not necessarily in the belief that the actual chemicals that they're taking are doing anything for them positive,
but the belief that the people that are directing them in that direction are also, you know,
trying to do something to help them, they believe that as well.
Well, either they have authority through their greater education
or they have authority just by virtue of their authority.
That's what seems to be the assumption, right?
Many of the older people, when you bring up the concept that the doctors are incompetent,
they'll say, well, there's no way they can be, you know?
So it's 100% by belief at this point.
But the point here with the pressure is when people realize that all biological systems are under a slight vacuum condition
and it is an inward pressure, not an outward,
and any fluids or anything that moves in the body is under a negative pressure, not a positive pressure,
that will lead to, for the next society, a technical field known as quote-unquote medicine that actually works
and will be in the hands of the people in a very common way, not in a specialized way.
Shifting the alleged scientific paradigm to something that's actually functional
as opposed to the quackery that exists now.
Yeah, you'll be able to have things in your home or on the public street that, you know,
would pretty much regenerate the body.
You know, we can get into that and discuss a little bit further into the internals of the body
and I'll bring up a reference that Gene Roddenberry used in his Star Trek series with the food replicator,
which is going to be very interesting.
There are many things that have been shown to us.
You know, I remember years ago being asked if I wanted to sign a donor card.
It was one of these, you know, the species that prevail in the government offices.
You know, you do certain paperwork and they robotically present you with an offer.
And, you know, a donor, what's a donor card?
You know, in case, you know, you, whatever, you know.
Oh, right. Give up your organs so that somebody else might survive.
It's a benevolent thing to do and you won't be needing them anyway, so why don't you just do this?
Yeah, it's a science, right?
So I looked at the lady behind the counter and I said,
Oh, no, no, when this body dies, I'm going to donate it to science fiction, right?
And she kind of looked at me like, okay.
So it sounds just like a joke only, but.
Yeah, I mean, here's the interesting part.
As time went on and we started doing, we, you know, whoever else was doing research in this direction,
found out that it's, it is science fiction.
It's a religion.
Again, like Oliver Heaviside said, it's scientism and it's very scienticulous.
But nonetheless, when we understand that we do have a slight vacuum condition in our body,
that leads into a whole study and field of research and understanding, you know,
what is good for you or what is good to do changes dramatically,
because right now we're completely apathetic to that condition.
You know, we just don't know anything.
We just think the only thing we know about pressure, about the body, is that we have a blood pressure.
It's never been discussed, at least in recent times, that we are under a slight vacuum condition.
So this is something that people will, you know, hear through us and hear through others, hopefully in the future,
and will be, let's just say for the little time that humanity has left, lead to better research and better practices.
Well, a lot of things are going to improve as we approach the zero hour, so to speak.
Oh, yeah. They have to.
Yeah.
Because you go out with a bang.
Everything always fizzles out.
You ever notice when a balloon is, all the air is let out of it, it goes around the room slowly,
and as all the air is almost out, it just kind of really quickly accelerates.
You know, it's the formula F equals P over V.
Yeah, so the blood pressure concept is something to have fun with.
People should research it, and we'll see what comes up with it in the future.
But at this point, if everyone has a machine, I'd still be interested,
because I think starting a museum of medical fakery and quackery is going to be interesting and a lot of fun.
You know, you might be shut down pretty quickly, but I think it's still something that's worth starting.
Yeah, if you absolutely call out the pharmaceutical industry and the medical complex itself,
you know, those people that we love to point to at the AMA and the CDC and everything else,
and if you basically blow the whistle on the whole game and tell them that their entire foundation is fictitious,
well, yeah, that's the kind of thing that usually is not appreciated.
Well, we would have a right to do it in commerce, you see.
You would use the commerce clause, and we would have to, you know, what do they call it, redact,
you know, with a big fat black magic marker, you know, make sure we're not stepping on any toes.
And, yeah, we're not going to point the fingers at anyone specifically.
It's just, you know, having fun.
You know, what's wrong with having fun?
But anyway, yeah, it's just something to entertain.
But, yeah, we were calling it the container.
So now that we've suggested or imparted the concept that you're under a vacuum, you know,
what happens when you, let's say, have a difference in pressure, whether it's positive, like a car tire, you know,
or negative, which would be like an air conditioning system or a vacuum cleaner or something,
what happens when you get a hole in something that has a different pressure than the atmosphere, right?
You have leaking, right?
Right, it attempts to get equilibrium with the other pressure that's being applied, right?
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So if the body has a slightly different pressure being on the minus than the atmosphere, then guess what?
Your whole body is sealed inside and out.
Isn't that interesting?
Well, now, see, most people would say to you, though, that there are various orifices in the body,
so therefore there's openings.
Tunnels, like the main one would be from the mouth all the way down to the back end, the base of your spine,
there's an opening, right?
That's a straight tunnel right through with complicated turns and things inside and various places to stop and rest.
And then you have the openings of the ears, which is a cul-de-sac, basically, and the lung is like a cul-de-sac.
You go in, there's another area, and you turn around and come back out.
So when you look at the concept of this slightly minus pressure, the skin can't be porous, the intestines can't be porous,
the stomach can't be porous, and the lungs can't be porous.
Isn't that interesting?
Well, that's also rather odd, considering that people are concerned with the pores in their skin constantly.
Yeah, there are pores in there which are, again, small cul-de-sacs.
If anyone could research the schematics and the drawings and the renderings that are available,
and you will see that the pore of the skin is a small ovoid-shaped cavity in various conditions, of course,
and follicles that go down to a certain level into the body, and they stop.
There's a dead end there, right?
So more like potholes than pores.
Yeah, okay, with some people's complexion, maybe, yeah.
But I would say that these are geometric forms that are sealed.
The interstitial spaces, here's a big word, interstitial spaces between the cells are so tight that they're pretty much airtight,
which is very interesting.
So when you eat something and it passes, how many times a year it passes through the body?
A dog swallows a hairbrush, oh, he'll pass it, right, or something, right?
A big dog, let's say, when you eat something, oh, maybe I'll pass it, right?
Or you bring it back up, right?
It's not that it goes into the body.
It's even in our common language.
We know that it passes through, right?
Very often I've had discussions with technicians, and they say, you know, buy this super supplement, you know, because it gets absorbed.
And I'm like, excuse me?
What do you mean it gets absorbed?
How does it get absorbed?
And the scienticulousness comes out where they, in metaphor, pretty much describe your body as a filter bag or a sponge, right?
And I'm like, well, okay.
And then when you start, you know, get your chance to speak and you bring up anything regarding a biological vacuum,
the only thing they could say is I have 30 years' experience.
I have 30 years' experience.
I have 20 years' experience.
I went to this school.
It's like, yeah, okay, sure.
But we're talking about this right now.
They can't handle it, right?
Because they're protecting, you know, their aspect of management that they've received.
Right.
So when we consider, let's say, for example, something simple, if we go on the outside of the body,
when you look at on a hot day you're working and you sweat, right, you know, that's something real.
You can imagine.
I mean, you don't have to imagine.
You can see it.
But what we do imagine when people are asked, when I say people, not just everyday people.
I'm talking about the people, you know, that are supposed to guard and hold, you know,
are the entitled people that know everything in the industry.
When you ask them how this sweat comes through, again,
they just try to describe your body as being some kind of filter bag or something, and it just isn't so.
You know, if anyone has taken any time at all and lives in an area where there's a heavy rainstorm,
when you see the clouds come overhead and it's fixing on raining, right,
get yourself under a porch or somewhere or a window that's really clean and watch what's going on.
You know, if you've got the time.
And can anyone honestly say that those hundreds of thousands, if not millions of tons of water,
are being carried by those clouds and dumped on you in the form of rain?
There's no water in those clouds.
So the water, what's going on is forming underneath the cloud.
It's a requirement, right?
Even though it has rained with no clouds, I've seen that as well.
But this is another form of the natural world that is a biological function,
very much how the body produces liquids and diminishes them as well.
So what's interesting is what is happening, let's say,
when you sweat on the outside of your body is very similar in an energetic perspective
the way you would see rain forming underneath a rain cloud.
And, you know, pilots know that you go through a cloud and, you know,
you're not going to hit a block of wall, a wall of water.
There is no water in the cloud at all.
And not to be mistaken with fog, which is mist which descends and goes into the valleys.
And now it sounds like we're being a little cryptic maybe on the description
because it is really fantastic when you find out how these things are formed.
And speaking of the fantastic, I'll share another person who has very good reference material.
He did most of his writing in the 50s and 60s.
And his name is Louis Kervran, K-E-R-V-R-A-N.
And he was interested in a lot of the ways that how the body worked.
And this is to tie in with our, you know, the biological vacuum.
He wondered, you know, how a chicken when it lays an egg produces a, you know,
very high calcium, 99% calcium shell.
There's no way that these chickens are eating that much calcium.
So he did an experiment and he sequestered the diet of the chickens
where they had no calcium in their diet at all.
And they still produced a very robust, you know, calcium-fortified egg
when they had a rich diet in magnesium and other things like that.
So he started getting into the discussion of the body is actually transmuting these elements.
And, of course, when he gained popularity,
he wanted to go the standard route and convince academia.
And they made fun of him.
They invited him to speak, but they cancelled it.
And when he showed up, they gave him a book on biology 101
and told him to go home and read it, which, you know, of course,
was just a way like, you know, we don't want your stuff here.
He had also done some very interesting experiments on potassium
and things like that in the Moroccan desert
where he had proven that potassium is created in the body from sodium.
He had workers in the oil fields from the French military
working all day in the desert, sweating profusely, taking samples of their sweat.
They had high levels of potassium when given sodium, high-quality sodium.
So there goes another thing, you know.
I mean, the body is actually producing these things under a vacuum condition.
Now, what I find fascinating are two points so far that I take away from this.
One is that one often describes participation in a religion as practicing that religion, right?
You also practice medicine, first of all.
Secondly, you made a reference briefly to the replicator in Star Trek.
Now, to kind of break that down for people,
this is where the replicator is supposed to reorganize something into an approximation of a substance.
Right, and it does it indiscriminately.
Yeah, based on what you want to eat.
What's interesting is when, you know, as the food passes through the body,
anyone can do some research on the layers that are in the stomach,
all the way from the mouth to the anus, all of that, all of the cells are completely sealed.
There are voids in there.
There are things that look fibrous or things that look elongated.
There is no filtration.
There is nothing that passes through the intestine.
The food is actually de-energized and the body recreates inside of its vacuum what it requires
based on what it can remove from, you know, how biocompatible it is,
which I want to lead into the concept of calories and how that's a misnomer with food.
You know, when they apply calories to food, that's like saying how long is that distance?
Well, it's nine pounds.
Well, that's the wrong scale for that distance, right?
So the calories have absolutely nothing to do with food.
So that leads into that discussion as well.
I'm kind of being a little standoffish on coming out and discussing a lot of this stuff,
even though we said we're going to discuss the body because it just sounds too fantastic.
But if anyone is interested in this matter, they could research the level of cells
and the level of tissue that surround what they call the intestines that are allegedly absorbing,
like a filter or a sponge, what you're eating.
And you'll see that the spaces and the things that these things are made of,
you know, anyone who's made sausage or cooked sausage knows that the skin of the sausage,
which is the animal intestine, is not porous.
Now, it begins to become porous when it's dead and it's decomposing.
So it's a very interesting.
These things, even though we said we're going to discuss the body,
I like to tiptoe or dance between the raindrops, so to speak,
because we're not going against anything or anyone,
because nothing can exist at this point on such a large magnitude
without the 100 percent or the majority support of the people, you see.
So speaking against any institution or industry is actually speaking against the will of the people, you see.
So the thing here, this is not about will or whistleblowing or even educating.
It's about giving a narrative, a dialogue and an exposure and imparting of information
that just is not being discussed, that just needs to be said for the sake of saying it
and doing it responsibly.
You know, the other interesting thought that I had is that when you were talking about observing the rain
and the millions of drops falling, when they fall upon the human body,
it's not as though the sponge becomes engorged because it's not a sponge.
No, you're not porous. You're completely sealed.
You have a tunnel that goes through the body. It's from the mouth to the anus.
That's the only opening in the body.
Everything else is just as sealed as sealed can be.
Watertight, airtight, you know.
And this is, again, the reason why we're saying this, there might be some young people
that might want to pursue quote-unquote medicine or health or that industry.
If they hear what we're saying and they see that it is something self-evident,
they might be in a position to create a field of study or within any other institution
and have these things looked at objectively.
See, when I was a child, I found it strange, the concept of biology,
because they would explain to me that about food intake anyway,
you took food into your body, your stomach broke it down,
and then your blood cells would carry around the broken down components
to different parts of your body.
And this whole thing became so cartoonish to me
because, okay, the blood cells are now carrying around little bundles of food,
in my mind, you know, as a child,
and these bundles of food go where?
To other cells where what? They sit down and have a picnic?
I mean, it didn't make any sense to me.
No, yeah, it's absurd.
Well, that means that you were in introductory state prison when you learned that.
I mean, that's the joke for the public education system.
Oh, absolutely, yes.
Yeah, that's introduction to state prison, yes.
And when I say state, I mean it could be local, federal, county, international, doesn't matter.
Oh, right.
Yeah, it's just a need-to-know basis.
And here's the thing, from years and years and years of going around
and discussing this with the captains of that industry, they don't know.
And they don't care to know, which, you know, it's very interesting.
So there's a complete stalemate right now in that main quote-unquote mainstream of any development.
See, what they're focused on is 2,000 to 5,000 years of battlefield medicine, you know,
where most of the medicine is based on when you were damaged, harmed, injured on a battlefield
that you'd be patched up, put back together.
So it's fairly effective for traumatic events.
You know, in other words, you can stop bleeding with this.
You can prevent premature, well, heart failure, this kind of thing with these techniques.
But realistically, when it comes to encouraging health in the human organism, they're kind of clueless.
Yeah, and it's by decision.
They've consciously made that effort to stay there.
Because things are just seemingly, you know, even when something is not working,
it works enough that you just keep it going, you know, instead of fixing it.
You know, they just keep driving this thing.
But what they're also doing is applying this battlefield medicine to people that have succumbed from, you know, degraded health.
Like if someone gets a heart attack or what they call a stroke or what they call a heart attack
or all of these things, they apply that battlefield medicine.
Okay, he's not breathing, so let's stuff a tube down his throat, you know.
It's very simple, you know, things.
All these treatments are, again, based on battlefield medicine.
But again, this is, to shy away from that particular industry,
discussing the human body in an objective way might be, you know, more beneficial.
I think there's enough bashing of the medical system right now,
not that we should give them a break, but I don't think they're worth bashing
because it's pretty self-evident what's going on.
It's a religion, and just like you brought up the concept of a practice,
you know, a lot of people joke around and they say,
well, they're practicing, they don't know how to do it.
I say, no, it has nothing to do with whether they know exactly what they're doing.
It's a religion, just like you said.
They're practicing.
In other words, they're doing something regularly.
What that something is is up to them and their followers.
Well, I'll tell you another concept, and where a lot of things are mistranslated,
okay, would be in the interaction between,
now we've only really talked about the human body
and how it reacts to other stimulus such as food, such as drugs,
such as the blood pressure cuff, water, air.
Okay, well, when human bodies interact with one another,
there's a lot of odd concepts there too, isn't there?
Oh, completely.
You know, here's an interesting point.
Let's go back a little bit to some allegedly great men like Volta and Galvani.
You know, Volta is the giveaway, right, the Volt electricity,
and Galvani, galvanic reaction, you know.
These were medical men.
These were naturalists,
and they were relied on giving the world information, that solid information,
even to Ben Franklin, believe it or not, up until the early 19th century.
All electricity was considered to be part of a function of biological organisms.
It wasn't until Faraday, later on, who experimented with bottles and wood
and pieces of metal that he discovered electromagnetism, let's say,
in our modern age and started associating it with metal.
And back in those days, it was known that metal was known as an electrical obstructor.
So what does this have to do?
The early research on electricity as we know it today,
and that goes from, you know, plugging a socket into a wall,
into a cell or a battery, to radio, micro,
and all the other frequencies and things that people consider are generated that way.
Initially, this whole entire field of electricity was considered
to be solely part of biological living things.
It wasn't until recently, really, less than 150 years or less than 200 years,
was it attributed to what we call conductors, metal conductors now.
So when you say, when we understand the attributes of what we call,
let's say, electricity in our narrow way, which is still misunderstood,
if the body is electric and we look at what can be garnered from electricity
all the way to radio, let's say, and transmission,
it's amazing what can happen when two bodies are in proximity of each other
or touching each other.
Or let's say they are distant from each other across the globe.
Can you communicate across the globe with electricity?
Of course you can.
So yes, there's a tremendous field and a tremendous discussion
that can be brought, you know, again, with the human body.
And there is a voltage, a quote-unquote voltage.
I say quote-unquote voltage because the term volt is very misunderstood.
It has to do with magnetics more than what people think.
There is a voltage in the body.
It's in millivolts, and some people say it's around 25 or 15 millivolts
that requires a healthy, you know, man or a woman, adult.
But this is a type of electricity that is longitudinal, not a transverse.
It's a type of electricity that Tesla used.
And again, to tie it in, all Tesla did is harness the electrostatic component
and this biological electricity.
So again, to spin off into the electrical side of things,
because it was known historically that biological creatures
and biological things were the carriers of electricity,
it puts a new scope on, you know, people being, you know,
in their interrelating physically, mentally, and all that.
There are energy fields there that, you know, that's a massive discussion
of how that happens.
Well, right, and some people just think that that's sort of a new-agey concept
and that's about it.
Also, from a biological standpoint, usually the only time I hear
the concept of electrical responses or what you're describing here
is usually just in the brain.
But meanwhile, if the brain and the rest of the body are interconnected, right,
you have a lot of, well, there's neurological events that people describe
and they sort of describe it as an electrical concept.
But that's a bit off, isn't it?
No, within the loose terms of the field of electricity,
it's sort of correct because they're looking in that direction.
I mean, for those that are technical and know what a coil is
and know what a capacitor is, you know, if you look at the cell wall
and you look at, you know, how it stores things, right, and it's a container,
and if you look at what they call DNA being a spiral form,
that would be one was the capacitor, one is the coil,
and that's a basic tank circuit, and that's how you store energy
or synthesize energy or create harmonics in electronics
using a very simple capacitor and a very simple coil,
and that's basically how the electrical system in the body is hooked up.
Or let's just say that electrical systems that are being built technically
are mimicking biological systems, and there hasn't been a cross-pollination,
you know, of the two fields because simply the people working in electricity today
don't know what they're doing, and the people working in biology
don't know what they're doing, so it's the blind leading the blind, let's say,
or the deaf leading the deaf, or the mute leading the mute.
Or it's the three monkeys, see no evil, hear no evil, speak no evil at this point
because it seems like only in certain alternative circles
is there a lot to do about these things.
Right, so Helen Keller and her long-lost twin basically trying to navigate.
Yeah, this is true, and I'll tell you it's an odd concept for me
because, again, when we talk about the interaction from one to the other,
if you have two electrical systems that are in close proximity to one another,
it's easy to see reactions. You have one affecting the other, things like that,
and meanwhile, if the biology functions that way, the same principle might apply, wouldn't it?
Oh, yeah. Look at electricity. Let's say simple or complex waveforms,
you have a concept of feedback, interference, right?
They can compound each other, and it's usable energy, not usable energy,
parasitic energy. We use electrical, quote-unquote, terms in society.
You know, I feel charged, right? Or I feel drained.
Absolutely true. And sometimes you get a charge out of a lot of things,
and things do get electric in an exciting atmosphere, right?
So stick around. Ocelli and the Greeks' first hour are done,
but there is much more to come on American Freedom Radio.
Welcome to American Institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth,
and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein,
and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand-new detox formulations of micro plant powders.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
American Freedom Radio is back.
We're trying to become commercial-free, apart from a few honorable advertisers
that we would give ad space to, even if they couldn't pay us.
In this quest to deliver quality radio with very few annoying ads,
we are now asking the listeners like you to open up and become partners with American Freedom Radio.
We all know the economy is controlled,
and a new system called the peer-to-peer economy is now within our grasp.
That means if you'd like this network, with its incredible hosts and credible information,
to be nothing but the content you want to hear,
then you must realize that you cannot be a part of it if you're just sitting on the sidelines watching.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and pledge your support today.
Donate according to your means.
Some can only afford $1 a month, while others can afford $100 a month.
Regardless of the size of your contribution,
it all adds up to keeping the network owners and the radio hosts
housed and fed at the end of every month.
Thank you.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit,
and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape
various pain-related health care costs, epilepsy and autism,
rising mental disorders, and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer, and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
the only broadcast information the sonic entity known has.
Quite an epic sound at the beginning of the second hour.
Well, it was the same thing at the beginning of the first hour, wasn't it?
Greg, are you with me?
Yeah, I'm here. It still sounds good.
Okay. Well, hey, you know, for a second there, things got too quiet.
Oh, okay. Silence, yeah.
It's the silence between the notes that makes the music sometimes.
Absolutely. As a matter of fact, that's the best part of a lot of people's songs.
Anyway, getting back to it, though,
we were discussing at the end of the first hour the electrical reaction that goes on,
and I call it the electrical reaction, and I'm not properly stating this, am I?
It's the electrical action, really.
Yeah, for lack of a better term.
There's someone who coined the word electricity,
but this is a field that is misunderstood and just plainly not understood anymore.
It's technically accessible, right?
I mean, you have wall sockets, and you have what they call batteries, which are really cells,
and there's radio, and there's transmissions, and there's  right?
It's technically accessible, but they don't really know what they're doing.
When we discuss it on a biological side, that's more of the quote-unquote electricity that Tesla was using,
Alexanderson was using, Galvani was observing, Volta was observing,
Faraday was playing with to a certain degree.
But just to keep it simple and accessible in people's minds,
there is a measurable voltage in the body.
There is the concept of using it in our language.
There is a concept of even  there's electrotherapy that was a very important advancement in the early 20th century
with Reif and other people all the way to Hilda Clark.
And then there was a woman called Ruth Drown, like Brown with a D, Drown, D-R-O-W-N,
and she was using more of the ethereal or the
and using that word ether is a bad word sometimes around Einsteinians,
but yes, the ethereal or biological fields that Tesla was using as well.
And anyone could look up Ruth Drown.
There's sparse stuff on her.
She was quickly sent to the grave when  same with Tesla wasn't quickly sent to the grave,
but after Tesla had his height early on, he spent the next 40 years feeding pigeons.
So yes, this is not a field that is respectful to those who want to advance it,
let's just say, on this planet at this time.
But the electrical aspect, as people know, there's popular or very unpopular furniture
that's even been named after the electric, as in chair, and electrocution,
so that these are, again, things that, yes, the body is subject to it,
and the body, again, historically, from the people that originated our modern concept of it,
had considered and wrote profusely that it was
electricity was something that was reserved for biological entities, let's say,
or biological beings in the material sense.
So yes, it's very interesting.
And then also there's a study from Egyptology and other things that there are gods behind what's called electricity,
which is a whole other subject we'll get into more when we might want to discuss the spiritual realm,
and not what we believe in or what we want to believe in or make stuff up,
but what has been memorialized over thousands of years.
I guess the topic tonight is more about the human body and what can be observed by the observer,
and hopefully, unless the machines are listening, which they are,
anyone that is, quote-unquote, human, or men and women are listening,
they can relate to without any specialized training or specialized equipment.
Right. And you know what also occurs to me is that hidden in the language, once again,
is another interesting point.
You know how they say that people are attracted to one another,
or that someone has a magnetic personality, or there is the concept of magnetism in one's persona, right?
If they have an attractive personality, and again, attraction.
Gee, all of these things sound very much related to magnetism.
And the energetic, what people call energy, or really what people, it's the energy.
It's interesting how people talk about energy, and they want free energy, right?
They don't want free energy.
They really should be asking for free power, because the energy is all around us.
It's when they want to turn it into power so it does work.
This is a type of, quote-unquote, energy that covers the entire span of what we can discuss regarding that field.
But discussing that field without the history behind it and clarification of the terms, again, may not help the audience.
But yes, it is very much so, and sometimes people are just called electric, right?
That's true.
Find them to be electric or something.
And again, these are terms, because remember, electricity, still the way we use it as power, is fairly recent.
You know, the way it's just gone everywhere, and the type of electricity we're using is very recent,
where the biological type has been sort of swept under the rug.
And yes, there is an electrical component.
How that's done in the body is the same way it's done anywhere else.
Not to divert into electricity, but in a short way, if you go on a construction site and it's remote, off the grid,
and you see someone on the back of their pickup truck, and they've got their power tools plugged into it,
you ask them what that is, they call that an electrical generator, don't they?
Right.
Or a power station.
That doesn't generate any more electricity than a water pump generates water.
Let's go out and buy a water pump.
Just open the box, pull out the cord, leave it in the box, and plug it in.
Do you expect water to start shooting out of it?
Well, no, because it's not literally generating water.
It's more of a conductor, in a way.
Well, what it does is, say, the water pump, you connect one end, the suction side, to the static or the low pressure,
and then based on the pump's design, will increase that pressure or volume according to the specific design of the pump.
The same with the electrical generator.
You have right now what they're using is a coil and a magnet, and they're rotating a magnet in a coil,
and what it's doing is, based on the design of the magnet and the coil,
it will give a specific volume and pressure of this fluid that's static or scalar in the environment.
It's the same thing.
Just like you can condense moisture out of the air, energy can be condensed very slowly.
Biological beings do it all the time, plants, animals, people.
Or you can have a water pump or an electrical generator, which is nothing but a magnetic pump, based on its specification,
because you could have a pump that does what they call a generator, just do specific types of voltages,
like 110 or AC or 480 AC like they have on airplanes and ships or 12-volt DC, so just like a water pump,
how many gallons per minute or what pressure.
So this concept of energy is around us constantly because things are always moving, but we don't notice them, right?
And that's what we're in touch with, and that's the scalar concept, meaning it's just we don't see it changing, so it must not be there.
Again, Einstein did a great job to harm, or relativists, which actually relativism existed way before Einstein,
but the relativists had done a good job of harming man's perception of that
and reduced everything to a material world and bending space and things like that.
So the electrical side of the human body is, again, an open field, but without giving advice but giving advice,
be very careful because if people are looking to do electric therapy, which is becoming prevalent,
you must understand that it's not understood by current society.
As it was, let's say, 150 years ago, you would have been much safer on the regard of electricity.
But something else about, as we were speaking on the topic of the human body,
and we discussed food passing through the system, right, and how the body replicates what it needs from it.
You ever go into a shop or look at a package of food, and it's mandatory now that they do nutrition information on packaged food, right?
You have this term called calories on there, and people are concerned about calories
because they think it has something about gaining weight that is not a...
Let's just give the history.
Well, it was odd because you had mentioned in the first hour, I think,
that calories compared to food is pretty much like saying how much time has gone by, and you say three miles.
It's the wrong yardstick, so to speak.
It's completely, yeah.
It is because it is too narrow of a materialistic observation.
The definition of a calorie, loosely paraphrasing here,
is the amount of thermal energy to raise one cubic centimeter or one gram of water one degree Celsius.
That's all it is.
The way that this was developed is if you want to find out how many calories, let's say, is in a banana,
they take a banana and they burn it until it gives off no more heat, completely burned up,
and that's how many calories are in a banana.
So when you eat a banana and it passes through your body, it's still burnable.
There's still material there that energy could be extracted.
You see, so the concept of calories has nothing to do with the issue of biocompatibility.
So unless you know someone who poops charcoal briquettes, calories are irrelevant.
Now, a cubic centimeter, I think, of chlorinated plastic's got 2,000 calories.
Let's speak in English.
If you swallow a bottle cap, plastic bottle cap, and being around young children,
eventually they get curious and swallow things like that,
you can go through their stool and you will pick out a bottle cap.
And that bottle cap could have 400 or 500 calories, according to the definition of a calorie.
I wonder how many calories a penny has because children often swallow pennies.
That would be, believe it or not, if you can get that material to combust,
you could probably run your car for a couple of miles on it, give you an idea.
If you could get the metal to go into that state, it would be in the millions if not billions of calories.
So this whole thing, there's no discussion on if it's biocompatible.
It's kind of like if you stuck your hand in a DVD player.
You're not expecting to see any movie, are you, because the input is not compatible.
It's just completely incompatible.
It is so materialistic that it has gone to the point of being ridiculous.
There's no consideration of how the body works.
But here's the point.
There's 7 billion, according to the World Bank, because they keep the stats on their property,
7 billion, 100 million or so humans on the planet.
It could be more than that, a hell of a lot more or less, depending on if they're cooking the books, right?
Because this is financial, these numbers we get.
There could be someone out there that is pooping charcoal.
And if you do poop charcoal, you would actually add validity to the caloric intake value of food.
So you could call in or let us know if you are pooping charcoal,
and we will retract that statement of calories being a misnomer when it comes to food.
Oh, absolutely.
No, absolutely, and I'll tell you what, I'm more than happy to get someone to contact me on Facebook
if you can stick your hand in a DVD player and get it to project a movie onto your TV screen
because I want to talk to you.
You've got to be an interesting dude.
That's right.
There's a lot of possibilities.
I'm not going to shun that.
But for most people that I've ever met or have met or most likely will meet,
they don't poop charcoal and they can't play movies off their hands.
Right.
But just saying, if you can, we would love to hear from you.
That's for sure.
Here's the point also.
But making it mandatory that you list calories on food labels legally
because there might be someone who poops charcoal briquettes is kind of a waste of time also.
So anyway.
Well, that would also be like having to list the amount that it would take to have it fall on your head and kill you.
So if it comes to so many cubic inches of this particular product that could be lethal
if dropped from a building on you, that's about how relevant that would be, I guess.
A brick falling off of a building hitting you on the head is biocompatible in a negative way.
And there's a lot of things people are concerned about what the medical, quote-unquote,
technicians are doing in a negative way.
But let's just maybe go more on the positive path.
Like, for example, have you ever heard of something called the common cold
that they get during the winter and it's caused by bacteria or the flu?
You ever heard of that concept?
Wash your hands and it's all in the winter.
Well, hasn't that rendered all refrigeration of food unnecessary?
Because I thought we had refrigerators so we can refrigerate food to keep the bacteria down in a low count
so the food doesn't decompose, right?
Isn't cold or low temperature retard the growth of these little critters?
They're supposedly making us sick.
Supposed to slow it down at least, right?
Right. So shouldn't people then be getting the cold or the flu in the summertime then?
When all these critters... you ever walk in the city in the summertime and it's a garbage day?
Kind of hold your nose, you know?
But in the winter it's not so bad, right?
Because the critters are kind of like dormant.
So if these critters are dormant, how can they be the culprit?
Hmm.
Very interesting.
Now, of course, in defense, I've heard, oh, well, it shows up under a microscope.
Well, there's a lot of things that show up under a microscope they don't want to talk about or don't know anyway.
Let's just stick with the basics.
If we are in tune with the environment, which you really have no choice,
whether you're inside or outside in the winter and it's cold,
if you're outside, you know you're going to need to insulate your body.
And if you're inside, you better have some heat on, otherwise you'll be complaining.
So you're going to be in tune with the environment, whether you're indoors all the time or outside, right?
And the same with the summer.
If you're outside in the summer, you want to keep cool.
And if you're just inside and you're the type of person that doesn't go outside at all,
you're going to demand that the building is cold.
So then you know it's cooled down and you know that it's summer.
So you're in tune with the seasons.
Now, could it be that when you eat a certain type of food that grows during a certain type of season,
it changes your body chemistry to that season?
Like, here's a simple concept.
Let's say you eat a banana.
Where do bananas grow in the cold or warm climate?
It would be a warm climate.
Okay.
So what would happen if you tried to grow a banana in a cold climate?
It wouldn't grow, right?
Okay.
So there's something going on there with the banana energetically as well,
as you discussed various forms of energy, that requires this warm climate.
And it is a constituent of this warm growth.
In other words, anything that relates to warmth, chemically, materialistically as well, is related in the banana.
Now, if you eat a banana and it's cold out and it starts to change your body chemistry to living somewhere where it's warm,
your body is going to wonder what the hell is going on.
And I would say it really doesn't change your body chemistry.
What it does is it encourages your body to produce things, to reproduce the aspect of the banana, which is tropical,
which is in contrast to the cold weather.
So in keeping it in certain simple terms, people that live in colder climates tend to have thicker blood, right?
You've heard that?
Than people in warmer climates, you have a thinner blood.
So eating foods out of season will change or eating foods in season will keep your body in sync.
So eating cross latitude, you'll see that people don't get in places where people do not import and export foods that are outside of their latitude.
They don't have the problem of the common cold or the flu.
Now, we're not talking about engineered flus, which are biochemical aspects, you know, and used in wartime and, you know, whatever.
We're talking about the unmolested biosphere, as it were.
And here's the interesting part about that, is that's very true.
When you find indigenous people who don't have commerce that spans a very great distance, you'll often find that they don't have a great deal of illness.
You know, like, legendarily, it was always said that, you know, what they call Native Americans now, what I called Indians when I was a kid,
those individuals, legendarily, were not ill very often at all because they subsisted on very, very local things.
Even when they hunted, gathered, whatever it was that they consumed, they subsisted, for the most part, on things that were extremely local and without refrigeration or storage or whatever else.
The majority of the time, they were also consuming, I guess would be a proper term, consuming things that were in season, for the most part, as well.
Correct. So you'll see a schoolteacher say, I caught the cold from the children.
But on the weekend, you see the families of the children and the schoolteacher with a shopping cart loading, you know, sugary snacks, which are, you know, grown from the tropics in the winter.
They have their quote-unquote holidays, right, in the winter, and they celebrate with all these exotic foods.
They eat bananas because they're told that it's good, you get potassium from it, right, where Louis Courant says, no, the body produces potassium.
All right, so they're eating the same type of diet, right, in there.
They have this concept, a strange concept, that it's caused by bacteria because it's found in a decomposing blood sample in a laboratory.
And when the blood is removed from the body, it goes into decomposition unless it's put into preservation mode.
And it's preserved either with chemicals or temperature. It's still dead, just like a pickled cucumber is not a cucumber.
Pickled herring is not live herring.
So, again, the fault here is that people are accepting all of their information coming from basically the study of cadavers and dead things.
Now, the purpose of us discussing the intake is not necessarily on what people should or could or not eat.
That actually is a discussion of law in itself.
The discussion would be perhaps giving an example of the antithesis.
If you lived in the tropics and you had, let's say, arctic char or tuna or something that was a cold water fish,
you may not necessarily come down with a cold, a quick expellation, expelling, you know, we'll talk about what mucus is in a moment,
but you might get a rash, you might feel an allergy.
You definitely will not be able to keep yourself cool because now this arctic food will start changing your body to living in the arctic.
You know, it seems that altogether what can be taken from the majority of what we've discussed tonight,
I would say, is that the more that you are in equilibrium with your immediate environment,
the greater the promotion of what they call health or comfort is.
It seems to be that's the logic.
Am I missing something?
Yeah.
No, no, that is the logic, and you're not missing anything at all in the environment.
You're going to be in the environment regardless, no matter how artificial you think it is.
You see, that's the thing that people think when you make a statement like that.
I've had a lot of people come back and say, well, I can't live like that.
You know, I live in an apartment or something.
It doesn't matter where you're living within the environment.
There are things that you cannot escape like the change of season and your latitude, right?
Right.
And also if you notice, again, with the food concept and illness, if you put your hand around the earth
and you go around the globe, you'll see that countries that are on particular latitude have similar diets, right?
Like the tropics across the whole globe will have a very similar type of cuisine, let's say.
And as you go north and south, it changes not invariably, but they're very similar.
That's why it would be very simple to eat seasonally within your environment
and have variety by just looking opposite the globe.
Are they experiencing the same season, meaning across latitude?
So you can have a tremendous amount of variety.
So essentially it would be to avoid, in the wintertime, avoid all tropical food.
And that would be, consider, you know, coffee and sugar to be an extreme aspect of that.
But yes, if you're having a hard time adjusting to the season and you think it's bacteria,
the most rational and objective suggestion would be that you're not eating according to the season that you're living in.
And this is not only true for people, it's also true for animals as well or any living being.
You know, plants kind of give it up.
A lot of the plants during the season change, like during winter, they just shut down, don't they, the trees?
Right, right.
No, but that's a matter of hibernation, which there are some animals that do that as well.
You know, and people are affected by the season also.
Well, they're affected by everything, as we've explained before, completely subject to 100% external input.
So obviously the environment would play a role in this too, because that's external input from yourself.
So there you go, once again.
Well, from an information perspective, yeah, it's all external or experiential.
But you've got to, you know, be very leery of, you know, how many times have you heard people,
you know, or witnessed this.
Well, you know, if you go to a Ledger Domain magic show, you know,
there's many people that have witnessed a woman being sawed in half and put back together on stage.
And they'll write a legal affidavit, they swore under the penalty of perjury,
they saw a woman being sawed in half and put back together.
But we know that that's a trick.
Or you could watch a mass murder on a movie screen, you could literally say you were a witness to a murder.
But it's not, it's a form of, it's showmanship.
And unfortunately, the level of showmanship that has been going around on this planet has, I think, led people so far astray.
I mean, actually to the benefit of some, because remember, if you're dealing with a censored population,
those who seem to grab onto the 1% of information that can be imparted to the people and take control of that,
then they take control of all the information.
Because the people are only getting less than 1%, it's very easy to control.
Yeah, well, if you control, you know, in other words, if someone were to redact 99 out of 100 words on a page,
and you're the only one who knows what that one word says, well, you now have control of all the words,
because all the rest are redacted anyway.
So back to the colds.
You know, they tell the children up in the Northeast or in the snowing part of the country that vitamin C is good for your cold.
Vitamin C is good for you right now.
If anyone wants to study the father of vitamins, it's Rudolf Hoschka.
He did a lot of experiments, and he wanted to figure out what vitality, what gave food its vitality, and thus the term vitamin.
Vitamin, yeah.
And if he were alive today, he would really be angry in the way that vitamins are being discussed,
because they're not what people think they are.
But they tell the children, drink plenty of orange juice, you know, up in the country in the high part of the latitude, let's say,
where it's snowing outside.
You know, oranges never grow there anyway.
We kill an orange in a laboratory, and it decomposes into acid, and we now say that it's vitamin C, and it stops cold.
So the poor children are drinking orange juice of snow outside, and do you think they're going to get any better?
Well, from what we've discussed tonight, there's no way.
There's no way, and they don't, so they run and get the suppressants.
So what they get is, I'm getting the sniffles, right?
You've heard that, you know, the mucus.
Listen, I can attest to this whole process, because I lived in the northeastern part of the United States most of my life,
and, yeah, this is precisely what everybody says.
And for some reason, vitamin C is almost its own sect in the religion of health.
It is, yeah.
There are people that seem to think that vitamin C will cure every single ailment,
and it's a constant thing that you must consume at all times.
I mean, it really does remind me of some of the more bizarre sort of religious revivals that I've seen,
when I think about the mentality behind it.
Well, the thing is, look, at this point in the state that humanity's in,
if it works for them and they believe that it works for them, there's a lot of power in that.
But we're here not to knock that, I guess, even though I'd like to.
It's another adventure.
No, I just find it humorous that, you know, just eat your vitamin C.
Everything is curable with vitamin C.
There are literally people that behave and speak this way.
Anything that ails you, vitamin C, vitamin C.
And don't worry, there's no negative to taking it all,
and the worst thing that will happen is, you know, you'll urinate a bit more.
There's no such thing as vitamin C.
It's an acid that they've been sequestered and packaged and taken, and it's called vitamin C, and it's good.
Now, it can be, and we can discuss the alkaline acid aspect,
but I want to go back to the sniffles real quick, you know, the mucus it's called, right?
You know, the mucus, you know?
When you see the body developing a mucus, it's trying to plug the orifices.
To increase vacuum.
Like, for example, when a woman is carrying a child at the bottom of the uterus,
you know, what keeps everything, all the fluids and what keeps it all sealed up?
There's a mucus plug there.
Yeah, I was going to say it's commonly referred to as a mucus plug, yeah.
So when you see someone developing mucus, what they call congestion,
the body is losing vacuum.
So one must eventually discover this biological vacuum needs to be maintained.
It's very, very simple.
But, see, now how does that relate to the overwhelming development of mucus during a cold?
The body develops it.
Well, here's one thing.
Let's say you're taking your oranges, vitamin C, right?
And you're living up in the north or very south where it's cold.
The body sees it as being something compatible, right?
It's not like the plastic bottle cap, which is not compatible.
It sees a form of vegetation. It's sort of compatible.
But it's getting really bad mixed messages.
It's able to reproduce aspects of it.
But if it does it, it also has to figure out how to counteract it
because the blood is going to thin out, let's say in simple terms,
and adjust the body to a warm temperature or to a warm season
where the body already knows it's in a cold season.
So you're basically doing a love-hate relationship with your body there.
One aspect is, yes, we will recreate it, but when we recreate this,
we also have to protect the body by using a mucus layer,
which is also a layer of protection.
And now when you have this stagnation,
and there's something called live blood testing,
which is fought against by the establishment,
which is you've got to keep the tissue alive when it's removed from whatever you're studying.
There's a man up in Canada, I don't recall his name.
He was doing a study on this, and he was looking at blood samples,
and he would see live blood samples now,
which most people have never seen in the medical profession.
And he would see a small flash of light, and a blood cell would appear.
And then he would see a small flash of light, and a fungus would appear.
Another flash of light, and a bacteria would appear.
And he's like, this is really strange.
There's a clear sample, and then these random things appearing,
precluded by a flash of light, this is really strange.
Sounds rather science fiction-y, really.
Doesn't it? Yeah.
I think his life was threatened, if not,
they did take his life, whoever they is, and his daughters as well, back in the 80s.
Or he might have recovered or something.
And this study has been swept, this live blood testing.
There's a few things on what they call the inner web.
It's interesting, the internet's a web, it's like a spider weaves a web.
The concept of the body wanting to maintain a vacuum,
and expressing it in a material sense that people can relate to,
is the concept of the understanding of the human body.
It's not all material, it's not all just about vacuum,
it's not all about energy, it's soliloquy, the dance of the balancing act.
Like you've heard people saying, being in balance.
I think the points that we've explained tonight are a very, very simple form of balance.
And to be objective, as if, let's say we were on a starship and brought to another planet.
What would you do then?
Their doctors couldn't help you, but you'd have to immediately see that you were now in that environment.
So how would you adapt?
It's the same thing here.
Guess what, every day you wake up, just imagine you were just dropped here.
What do you really see? What is really around you?
What is really going on?
What would be the objective way?
Look, if we were brought to Earth here for the first time,
we would study the natural environment and find in places like the rainforest
that the most brightly colored small animals are the most toxic as well, right?
What's interesting, when you go into a place where people buy their food,
the most brightly colored packages are the children's food,
which also happen to be the most toxic.
Yeah, well...
Isn't that an interesting parallel?
That is a rather fascinating parallel.
And even the food itself, most loudly colored foods that are produced,
you know, processed foods and things like that.
Have you ever noticed the most vividly colored stuff is also the least healthy?
Yeah, like in nature, if something is just extremely brightly colored,
it says, well, all the other surrounding creatures stay away from that
because it's very toxic.
But the humans, let's say, for lack of a better term at this point,
or men and women, they mimic that as nutrition for their offspring.
How twisted is that?
Well, one of these days we are going to have to cover
exactly how humanity handles their children
because I am appalled at the very least.
But, yeah, that's a whole other subject.
Well, the archives may be on the Ocelli effect.
We did discuss what cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common.
I've been saying that for about a decade now.
That's the simplest thing.
Yeah, and, you know, there are thousands of archaeological sites
going on every day throughout the world.
And you ever notice how little reporting is being done on it?
Mm-hmm.
One of the reasons is because they're finding things that they don't want to discuss,
like maybe small pots that are in the shape of a small child,
cooking pots, and little children's bones that have been bleached white
because they were boiled with scraping marks on them.
And guess why they're scraping?
You want to get every little bit of meat off of there.
This was very prevalent in the ancient societies,
and that's why people that work in archaeology know
that they change the crews every two weeks or a month.
And this is why.
And here's the really interesting part of that.
A lot of people figure that this is only relegated to certain cultures.
Oh, no, it's across the board.
And you're still doing it now with your birthday cakes and your dolls,
which is evidence that a child has been eaten,
and your, quote-unquote, religious institutions,
the way their buildings are shaped and their procedures and their rituals
are all based on human sacrifice.
Yeah, it's not good, folks.
But anyway, that is not a judgment call.
That is just an observation because, yeah.
It just seems to be counterproductive, too.
I mean, take a step back and invest not a little bit even in the emotional.
It seems to me rather counterproductive to slaughter your own offspring.
Yeah, and that's the basis, believe it or not, of human culture right now,
that if you were to come to this planet and spend a few minutes here and leave
and say, oh, yeah, the records show we were here 5,000 years ago
and they were obsessed with eating children,
and they still are, the concept of it.
That's the subject.
Well, fortunately, it's late night for most people.
And, yeah, they will find this out.
And believe it or not, when this becomes mainstream knowledge,
the people will take it lying down like it's no big deal.
But it will become mainstream in the future.
Well, yeah, I do believe you there.
And I think it's thankfully I don't live with the images in my mind at all times about these things.
But this revelation came to me some time ago that there was a great cruelty
that we visit upon the best part of ourselves, and it's justified so often
because, you know, through the youth comes the strength, you know.
And the younger they are, the more potent they are.
And all of these things have been encouraged.
And they're not just in these odd symbols,
but they're also resonant things that continue to persist in the culture as well.
And the evidence is everywhere.
Yeah.
In cosmic history books, let's just say hypothetically,
this planet is known as the dominant, quote-unquote, species being humans,
and they're known as being the ones that eat their children.
That's what you're known for cosmically.
Even though you think you've developed all these technological things,
and you're so wonderful and whatever, that's what you're known for cosmically at this point.
And it's not a, yeah, everything else has been washed away.
There's a myriad of accomplishments that mankind might want to pat himself on the back.
But sorry, folks, the inhabitants of this planet, mankind is known as those that do that.
So, yeah, yeah.
It's going to be quite a day for those that find it sickening to see that it will stop,
at least in the culture, because it's shown in the culture as well.
It's interesting, when you study the history of the eating of children
and the destruction and sacrificing of children,
and the more you study this about the culture,
you will see it in just about every culture, in their artwork, in their religions,
in their traditions, in their holidays, in their customs.
And they don't know it.
Now, it doesn't matter if they know it or not.
They're doing it.
And there are others that do know that from a cosmic perspective,
and they're not happy about it.
Even in the simplest, strangest ways,
the things that people believe are affectionate on this planet
actually harken back to that cannibalistic tendency.
I don't know how many times you've observed a mother playing with a baby,
and they talk about eating them in a playful way.
Have you ever heard the term having your cake and eating it too?
That's about having your child and eating it too.
Yeah.
That's what the cake represents and the birthday candles.
Oh, yeah, but I mean literally a mother will communicate to its child,
I'm going to eat your feet, this kind of thing.
Oh, yeah, yeah, exactly.
In an excuse way.
Oh, yeah, I see what you're saying.
It's passive.
Obviously, they're usually not saying that they're literally going to eat the child.
But if you're not there and you have a transcript of it, it looks pretty macabre, right?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Right, exactly.
That's the perfect way to put it is if you just have a transcript of this planet,
this is the kind of thing that you're treated to.
And even when it comes to things like sexuality
and given acceptable practices of affection, like I said,
the act of kissing even is supposed to harken back to the cannibalistic resonance in our beings.
I read a whole, I can't recall the text,
but I tell you it was one of the weirdest things I ever sat and read
and had to consider because it was like, well, yeah, where would this concept come from?
Well, the scariest part of the cannibalistic is that, you're ready for this?
People who have a taste for pork have a taste for human flesh.
In ancient history, if you heard that men were turned to pigs, for example, in Ulysses, in the Odyssey,
that is a metaphor for they were eaten
because if human flesh were prepared like a pork loin, a pork eater would eat that
and say that was the best pork loin I ever had.
So there's a very interesting part, and this has nothing to do with any religious connotation
because, again, the religions have nothing to do with the text that they supposedly subscribe to.
But from a biblical point of view, from a lawful stance of what man should eat,
there are very clear descriptions on how to identify what's edible or not.
And there is the example of the pig and the rabbit, for example, of things not to eat and why.
But people haven't studied these ancient texts, so they walk away saying, well, it just says don't eat pork.
And they don't understand the rest of the story, let's say.
It's pretty scary.
We're not discussing what one eats or not, but beware of pork eaters.
And I know that's actually gotten quite a few people in trouble publicly by saying that because pork is big business.
But I assure you that there's a film, Soylent Green.
Soylent Green is people, remember?
Pork is people, people.
So if you've got a taste for pork, you're pretty easy to fool.
If it got that dark, and it could be that dark now, we just don't know it.
Because from doing research, I found out that reality is not 10 or 100 or 1,000 times,
but more than 10,000 or a million times worse than what people think of what is really going on.
Even with the darkest reaches of the Internet and the deepest, darkest, most far-fetched conspiracy theories
are still pale in comparison to what reality is.
So anyway, that's the end of the subject.
Absolutely.
And much like taking it back to the original subject, once again, the inverse is true as well.
The amount of misunderstanding, as much as people believe that we are in an age of modern science
and modern understanding regarding ourselves,
the truth is that we don't even understand the droplets of water around us well enough to utilize them properly.
And we are far more complex than a drop of water.
But then again, so is a drop of water far more complex than people believe a drop of water is.
And we may not be, because here, if water is H2O, how many times have you heard that, water H2O?
Well, if water is H2O, and you're saying hydrogen and oxygen, right?
That comes from the periodic table of elements.
And if the periodic table of elements is accurate, then why does a bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air?
It shouldn't, because hydrogen being one and oxygen being 16, H2O should weigh 18.
But the molecular atomic weight, let's say if you get all the molecules of air, it's 28, 29.
It's almost double.
And it's funny, when you speak to these academics or quackademics, they'll tell you,
well, one's a gas, one's a liquid, ha, ha, ha.
I said, we're not talking about the phase.
It's irrelevant, just the actual molecule, regardless of what phase.
And water, by the way, doesn't have a gas phase.
If it did, condensation would be impossible.
So they can't answer that.
So, yeah, water can't be H2O and say that the periodic table is accurate.
So there's more to it.
And the other thing about water is, you know, that classic raindrop shape, you know?
Well, you can drop any other liquid known to man from the sky, and it will not form that raindrop shape.
Only water forms that.
You could drop paint, oil, ink, any other liquid you can imagine.
And unless it's mostly water, it will not form that shape.
Interesting.
So shape, again, has a lot to do with it, you know, the shape of things.
And oddly enough, we're always told that we're also 80% water anyway.
Actually, more than that.
It depends.
Yeah.
The water is a massive discussion in itself.
But, yeah, hopefully we've covered several things.
The vacuum, the seasonal effect on the body and the intake,
and the function of just the basics, that you are completely sealed, you know?
And, again, anything that comes out, unless it's through the main tunnel,
all the other things that come out of your body are essentially produced by the body and ejected.
Right.
Yeah.
That's why there's such a complex understanding of urine therapy.
One can almost say that the antivenom is produced in the urine immediately.
There's been a lot of strong evidence, suggestions have been made to people that have worked,
where if those who have been, let's say, quote-unquote poisoned by a venom from an insect or an animal,
a rapid drinking a little bit of the urine, just a very tiny amount, has an antivenomous effect.
It's like rephasing the body.
Very interesting concepts on these.
Even though I've had very good report on this several times,
and we cannot say that it's advisable for sure, but what is one to advise?
I don't think one can advise at all.
One can just report what they've seen.
Right.
And it depends on what people do with it as to whether it becomes advice or not.
Yeah.
And at this point, humanity is in a state where things are,
the level of apathy is so high that we need a new word for it, right?
It's gone beyond the apathy meter.
And then there's the level of frustration and distraction.
And you can hear it amongst any part of the population, whether it's in every sector of the population,
and also the mainstream and alternative media.
There's a tremendous frustration and tension that still prevails,
which will for the next couple of years, folks.
And so, you know, get used to it.
But, you know, they will survive it until they go to the next phase,
which I think almost with every show it's a good little thing to give a hint on what's coming.
And it does tie in a little bit with what they call, you know,
most people fixate themselves on this thing called, you know,
you've heard of that show called The News, right?
And what the alternative media likes to parrot, everything that the mainstream puts out.
I'm still waiting for the alternative media to actually come up with topics that are more original
and actually do some good investigative reporting,
which since there's nothing new under the sun,
you can report on things you've discovered about an ancient society,
and gosh, it should sound like the news.
But keep watching the Middle East.
It's not what you think, and everyone's going to be fine, at least for the next decade.
But this level of frustration that I'm still hearing in people's voices
and in their themes and in their narrative is just a sign of the times for the next few years.
Well, most things are, you know, symptomatic of the zeitgeist, I like to think.
You know, you are always a victim of the time you're in,
and that's not necessarily, once again, what is written down on the Pope's work schedule.
That is not necessarily what is being projected to you via the wind-up toy, which is the clock.
But the sign of the time as in the atmosphere, this particular moment,
which has yet to arrive, has already passed, and is currently happening, right?
Yeah, and there is absolutely no wisdom in being absorbed in the signs of the times
without fully understanding them.
There you go.
There's a lot of knowledge, and you can think about and discuss it,
but if you're absorbed into what's going on without understanding it,
there's no wisdom, I assure you, in that at all whatsoever.
And, of course, we like to bring up the concept of time,
and, yeah, there's no wisdom in writing October as 10,
when it really states it's 8, and so on and so forth.
So, yeah, so you know who you are out there.
Yeah.
Right.
Pretty much everyone.
Right, and it's no longer a Saturn day on the East Coast here, but it is.
The Sun's day, now, the Lord, yeah.
Yes, that's what it is.
Even though it's quite dark outside, I assure you, the new day did begin,
according to that thing they call a calendar.
Okay.
But, you know, the natural world, including your body, doesn't go by that.
That's the truth, and this is where we're at.
We're actually at a point where we're in contrast,
and we're fighting against the environment.
We're fighting against ourselves constantly,
everything seemingly counterproductive because no one is taking the time
to plainly examine these things and give the reports,
which is what we're attempting to do here.
Yeah.
I would say they've become so apathetic that the repercussions of that apathy
is what they're fighting.
I would tend to agree with you, absolutely.
And, you know, I don't know what you want to cover next time, but I don't know.
I'm thinking about, you know, we often have brought up the concept of
no one does follow what is in their alleged text, right?
I don't know, the contradiction in language?
What do you think?
Yeah, all that ties in because the alleged text could be the U.S. Constitution.
Oh, yes.
Or the Russian Constitution or any religion.
You know, they're all religions, by the way.
You know, if you look at how the deification thing works, yeah, it's funny,
especially in the alternative circles, how they've deified the quote-unquote
founding fathers and deified.
They even try to, you know, how we discussed that the gods are alive.
How many times have you heard the Constitution is a living, breathing document?
Are you crazy?
Are you kidding?
Are you nuts?
Oh, no, no, no, I'm sorry.
This is planet Earth.
This is normal.
That's right.
So we will continue this journey next week at the very same time, allegedly.
Thank you, Greek.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion, and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years, and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein, is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO, and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367, and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org
What kind of person are you? How do you see yourself?
Are you the kind of person that lets everyone else do all the work,
just hoping that you'll be able to get some of the crumbs that fall from the table?
Or are you the kind of person that rolls up their sleeves and does the dirty jobs that no one else wants to do?
Are you hoping that all the activists giving their blood, sweat, and tears to serve humanity
are going to solve all the world's problems?
Or are you just wondering, is there something simple I can do to contribute?
Yes. Yes, there is.
Help us. Help us do what we do.
Partner up with American Freedom Radio today by gifting a regular amount to support the network
and your favorite hosts, bringing you less commercials and more information.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and start donating today from between $1 and $100 per month
according to the kind of person you are.
Thank you very much for your support.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit, and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape
of various pain-related healthcare costs, epilepsy and autism,
rising mental disorders, and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer, and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.