American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The Sonic Entity Bill has been shown as the Greek.
American Freedom Radio
Tell the truth. Don't be bullshitting people.
There's enough bullshit as it is. In fact, there's just enough.
Did you know that?
There's just enough bullshit to hold things together in this country.
Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation.
Where would we be without our safe, familiar American bullshit?
Land of the free. Home of the brave. The American dream.
All men are equal. Justice is blind. The press is free. Your vote counts.
Business is honest. The good guys win.
The police are on your side.
God is watching you. Your standard of living will never decline.
And everything is going to be just fine.
The official national bullshit story.
I call it the American Okey Doke.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
The network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
the only broadcast information for sonic entities.
And the second hour begins.
Yes, we are live and being heard fairly loud in some places.
It is Ocelli in the Greek on American Freedom Radio
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Also being heard on Ocelli.com
I just checked it out to make sure the stream is intact.
Be there.
Anyway, we were discussing
the spirit and the soul
and what the difference is
and why this should be easily observable
thus far.
We also touched on the animal kingdom, Darwinism
all that kind of stuff in the first hour.
If you missed it, maybe you should make sure you get the archive when you get a chance.
Anyway,
How are we doing there, Greek?
Is that cricket still with you?
Not really, but that would be an insect, I guess.
Let's lump the insects with the animals
because they can't extend and touch themselves.
They have limbs to do so.
You notice as we go from plants to animals
plants usually extend outward.
They don't reach around and scratch themselves or grow into themselves.
Animals have been made
to be much more animated
and mankind even more so.
But the emphasis
on the animal topic
has to be built
on a foundation of defining the soul and the spirit
and the flesh.
You notice we didn't define the flesh very much
but we did discuss it in detail
on an episode called The Container, I believe.
Right, that was the very first time that we did this
as Ocelli in the Greek as the separate show.
The Container, right.
The second episode, yeah.
I think it would be episode 2 if you were to look it up somehow
or just in chronological order.
Right, and chronologically I guess we're on episode 12 at this point.
Yeah, and what's interesting is
these bodies including the plants were under a slight vacuum condition.
In other words, the pressure inside
of a plant or a human body or an animal
or a fish or anything alive is slightly less
than the ambient.
Slight vacuum condition, it's what
you might want to dub as a biological vacuum.
But nonetheless it is a vacuum meaning
slightly under negative pressure, right.
So we're kind of, you could say vacuum sealed.
Right, because we're not porous.
You don't absorb anything in your body materialistically.
Things pass through and over your body.
We've discussed this.
We might want to revisit how the body works
and just to throw in how the body works
and you notice we spend most of the time discussing the difference
between soul and spirit because that seems to elude
every man, woman and child you'll ever meet.
And even those that consider themselves spiritual cannot define it.
They think they can define it, but just listen to their definition.
And you'll notice that they don't know.
But the body,
let's bring up something really quick.
I was looking at an article from the DOH
Department of Health or something talking about the cold season
and how to prevent getting sick.
Now wait a second, aren't these scientists
and these quote unquote educated ones
telling you that the source of cold
or flu or these types of things that are seasonal
are caused by bacteria and viruses and things,
these little critters?
Well I've always found that odd because I thought that the purpose of a refrigerator,
now pardon me for being foolish,
but I always thought that the purpose for refrigerating things
was so that bacteria
could not grow on the food
so your food wouldn't go bad as they say.
Or go dormant.
They would go dormant in the cold let's say.
Right, but they wouldn't thrive.
How about that? There's a good way to put it.
They wouldn't thrive if they were in a colder atmosphere
which is what your refrigerator and your freezer
do to your food so that it is preserved.
So it's in the state.
So the medical, scientific, university and academic
and knowledgeable people definition
of this mild form of dis-ease,
colds and flus during the season,
the reasons that they're giving us for causing these colds
rendered all need for refrigeration useless, hasn't it?
So we don't need our refrigerators anymore
according to these guys.
As long as it's summertime or something, right?
You don't need them. Wait a minute,
in the summertime doesn't your food spoil quicker?
Yeah, exactly. So if you look at the academic and university
and the well-learned medical men,
oh yeah, the ones with degrees and licenses
and the big tall towers, if you listen to them,
yeah, the cause of disease,
we should all be getting the common cold
in the summertime.
Because that would be when the bacteria
would thrive in the warmth,
not necessarily the heat because in the heat
obviously when something is extremely hot
it's supposed to kill the bacteria
I've always been told.
Walk down a neighborhood in the winter with all the garbage cans out,
it's not too bad, but in the summer you really don't want to be there.
So the whole idea here,
the reason we're maybe harping on this point,
see how ridiculous humanity is.
I mean, I don't know why people,
the majority of the people don't pull these academics, doctors,
researchers, scientists, not some of them, all of them,
pull them out of their bedroom while they're sleeping and hit them on the head
with a wet newspaper.
And say, what are you guys saying? Stop it. Stop it now.
Time out for you. You know how they do to little children?
You've got to stop what you're saying. It's ridiculous.
And no one is calling them on it.
So just like four-year-olds or five-year-olds, if you don't call them on their behavior,
guess what they do? They keep doing it.
They continue, yes.
They pull out the poop and they do finger painting with poop all over the walls
and if you don't tell them to stop, they're going to grow up doing that.
So anyway,
back to the body.
The reason why you get a cold when it gets cold,
just like they say in this article from the Department of Health,
it's pretty recent.
Anyone could research it, I guess.
You catch a chill, you get cold. Well, guess what?
In cold weather, you need a thicker blood or a different constitution
or constituency in the body.
So if you're eating tropical foods,
sugars, chocolates,
bananas.
Oh, but you've got to eat bananas all the time because they're high in potassium. Ridiculous.
Your body will adjust to the tropics.
See, like for example, people that normally catch a cold
in the winter when they catch a chill, let's say.
I bet if you brought someone,
let's say people who are known as Eskimos down.
When you're out in a heavy parka, they're out in a T-shirt.
And they're not catching a cold, but you are
because their diet is different.
So the reason you're getting colds is because,
don't they call it some kind of silly holiday?
And I still haven't, just like the soul and the spirit,
no one can define to me what this is a holiday for.
And of course, many people will say it's a holiday
for the birth of whatever.
And I'm like, yeah, really? Where'd you get that information?
It doesn't exist.
So anyway, I mean, it does exist and it was September 11th.
We're going to have to throw that in again, according to the Pope's work schedule.
So at this time now,
during this holiday time, guess what people are eating?
Do you think they're eating foods that might have ingredients
that might have been grown in the tropics,
like sugars and chocolates and fruits and things like that?
Is it possible?
Most definitely.
Yeah, it seems that way, doesn't it?
So where does sugarcane grow?
And guess what? They're up in the cold areas,
eating these celebratory foods and guess what?
Yeah, bacteria, not.
Now what these morons do is, because remember,
we've discussed and you've brought it up many times,
they worship death, right?
So the way you study something is by killing it or blowing it up.
Like CERN, the way you study the matter and particles
is by smashing them together, right?
So we found this new animal called a goat, Chuck,
and the way we're going to learn and study this goat
is we're going to blow it up or kill it.
That's how we're going to study it, right?
So this is ridiculous.
Let's study the dead goat because that will tell us a lot about
how it behaves and everything.
So what they do, these morons, as they are, they should be called that,
and it's not a derogatory term, it's a very accurate term.
Look up and see what it means.
They take some cells from a living man or woman or child or animal
and they put it in a very clinical setting in preservatives
and they view it under a microscope.
Now those cells in that condition resemble anything in the condition
that they would be in when they're in the living being?
No.
So other things start to emerge like bacteria and things,
and they say, look, this is the cause of this.
This is so absurd, it's ridiculous.
And you have 7 billion people on the planet generally
that are not calling these morons out,
and it's not like one or two or three scientific idiots.
We're talking about millions of scientific morons on the planet right now.
Millions.
So like I said, don't expect, earlier in the past hour we said,
don't expect any rational thought or rational observation
or rational objective discussion on any subject from now on,
as long as you see things like colds being caused by bacteria.
Wash your hands.
Oh, boy.
Once every winter there is at least one of these barrages of information
that tell you this.
It is repeated over and over again.
I do remember when I was a kid even.
Yeah, they didn't have a child, right?
They didn't have the same type of, you know,
we obviously didn't have the Internet,
but these same types of articles would be printed in the newspapers,
and they would tell you to make sure you had,
well, there was a different set of junk that you were supposed to have,
but a lot of it contained sugars and things,
you know, cough drops and stuff like that,
which are all loaded with sugar and facsimiles thereof,
which, what is that going to do, like you said?
Where does sugarcane grow?
Well, you know,
Yeah, but check this out.
If you ask them to define what the spirit or the soul is,
do you think they could have? Probably not.
You get the most wishy-washy thing, and guess what?
If you don't know the definition of a spirit or the soul or the body,
you're deceived, and guess what?
If headquarters is deceived, only deception can come out of headquarters.
So if you're deceived about how your own headquarters works,
guess what is going to come out of headquarters? Deception.
And you're going to resonate with deception,
and anything that is not deception is going to be dissonant.
Isn't that interesting?
So that's why we brought up the animals,
and it's like, man, the poor animals, you know?
But the animals, again, they have their own purpose.
They process things, you see.
And we said that mankind shares the same soul with the animals.
Yes, meaning there is such a thing as animal resuscitation.
Just like, I think we might have given the analogy, Chuck,
if you were not breathing and I administered CPR,
or let's say resuscitation to you,
I put my soul into your body,
and then when you started breathing on your own,
now you became a living soul again with your own soul resuming, you see.
It's an action.
You can also, there is animal CPR,
where animals can be revived.
A dog can drown,
and you can administer a resuscitary procedure to a dog.
So you share the same soul.
That's all it is.
And the spirit is the mind.
You do not have the mind of an animal.
The mind or the spirit of an animal and a man is very different.
And just to hearken back to these primitive savages
that memorialize many texts for us,
from time immemorial until now,
it was written somewhere that the spirit of the animal
after death returns to the earth
as if the earth is a container
for the animal spirits,
for the minds of the animals.
Isn't that interesting to meditate on that?
And that's the only information that I've uncovered from ancient texts.
And if you want to figure out which ancient text it is,
just anybody do a search.
The spirit of the animal returns to the earth and hit enter
and see what you come up with. You might be surprised.
It's quite interesting.
So now here's the concept of, you heard of Mother Earth, right?
Or the earth, you know, the Gaia,
which is the Greek term for earth,
which actually in mythology was a titan.
No, Gaia was a titan.
Let's just say according to the text.
It houses the significance of the earth,
and I've got to throw this in there,
you know, soil is brown, pancakes are brown,
so pancakes are flat,
so the earth must be flat, right?
Anyway, so anyway,
the point here is that the significance,
you notice how the significant things are not being discussed,
but you know, because pancakes are flat, the earth has to be flat.
Anyway,
so it's a very interesting concept to meditate on,
and the concept of meditation is to think about something
and ruminate on it, which is like chewing the cut,
let's say, metaphorically.
Again, we talked about how people extend deception.
Ask anyone who is quote-unquote spiritual and says that they meditate off
and what defined meditation.
You're going to hear the most roundabout,
mushy, wishy-washy, opinionated junk you've ever imagined.
I'm serious.
No, you're right, but you know what this leads me to is yet another question,
which is,
is this anyone's fault?
Because after all, we said,
and you're right, it was the second episode, The Container,
but in the first episode that we did here,
we talked about how mankind is 100%
subject to external input.
Yes.
Is he not?
Can you prove that he's not?
It's kind of difficult to prove that you're not.
Well, I can't, and I'm not disputing that, but here's my question.
If we are subject to that external input,
then it must be external input
that is at the bottom of all of this.
Yes.
Cosmic censorship.
You know what it is, Chuck?
It's because of the way that maybe I might be ranting about it a little bit
that it sounds like it's their fault, but it really isn't.
But the interesting thing about it
is one of the last things to discover is the obvious.
When the censorship is lifted,
people will actually see what's five inches, five feet
in front of them.
Now they can't.
Did I ever give the metaphor that if you, let's say,
go into higher learning for, let's say, design, like architecture,
if you have a really good professor and you're in a very
high-end type of school,
mid-semester they get up usually
and they say, everyone in the class gets a B.
And the people that wanted an A are like,
damn, why? And the people getting a C are like, happy.
It's like, why does everyone get a B?
Because they basically tell you that when you go out into the world,
no matter what you design is going to be ignored because nobody looks more than
five feet in front of them anyway.
It's like, wow, now that's a really good education.
So anyway,
there's a cosmic censorship that's going on
and it's sort of frustrating when you start
looking at
how wonderful things really are, but also
how wonderful they really are with
all the confusion.
Still, most people have adequate
access to food, clothing, and shelter in what they call, let's say,
the industrialized nations, right?
Like we said earlier, we all haven't
died from Fukushima.
I don't know anyone who's in a FEMA camp.
No, we didn't get Ebola.
We didn't get locked into FEMA camps.
We haven't been inundated
by the invasion that allegedly
was spilling over our southern border that has completely
dominated all of the southern states.
Let's see, what else? Planet X.
Planet X, Nibiru, whatever.
These things did not eat us alive.
Gee, what was the other thing?
I can't remember it now, but remember the program,
the intelligence, military operation.
What did they call that?
Jade Helm.
Jade Helm, that's it.
Jade Helm was supposed to sweep us all away.
With all the threats and confusion and stupidity
that's put on mankind, the ability to still
be somewhat comfortable and, let's say,
rehabilitate from a hard day or
whatever is still possible for most people.
Especially if you're listening to this, you probably have
an internet, and if you have an internet, most likely, hopefully,
you have something to eat and a place to sleep.
What I mean by that is, it's just amazing
how, what's even more amazing,
even though there is so much deception in the world,
about basic stuff, we're not talking about deception like
Illuminati somewhere or some
black ops or secret space program,
you know, rubbish like that, you hear that all the time.
They're deceiving everyone in media control.
I mean, what kind of controlled media
blame do you have to put to notice that
you need a refrigerator to
slow down bacterial growth, but yet you believe
that colds are caused by bacteria. I mean,
where's the Illuminati in that? I mean, I don't understand.
We're talking about simple, simple stuff here.
The deceptions that we discuss are not
some far distant bunch of weak-chinned
guys underground planning
and plotting conspiracies. We're talking about
simple, simple things that
any individual, you know, that can walk across the room
and his breathing can rationalize, you see.
And this is the wonderful part to see how
so much of what is obvious just goes unnoticed.
You know, and that's why we were bringing up the animals
again. How can we discuss
this middle kingdom?
You know, let's call the animals in the middle, you know, plants first, animals then
mankind. Let's call it the middle kingdom
without really getting a handle on even
you know, what these definitions are because
you know, an animal has a spirit, an animal
has a soul, an animal has a body.
So discussing the animals and how they're slightly different
is how many people out there really got a handle on what
the definition of the spirit and the soul and the body is?
You know, again, we covered, you know, ask anyone
who thinks they're spiritual. They could be found all over the
place. They have websites that they're promoting books and
come listen to my radio show or ask them to find spirit.
You will hear again the most wishy-washy opinionated
garbage you've ever imagined. All of them.
So
on this respect and then the body, you've got
people talking about calories and vaccines
and catching a cold from bacteria. So how
can we discuss the animal kingdom
when most people still don't even have a handle on
what the spirit, the soul and the body and how any of that
works? You see, so
part of it is the
cosmic censorship, but the other part is these things are so obvious
that, you know, coming on the show here and just renting and just
spilling it out as it is,
has its own value.
Because if
these things are sort of like nailed down
in place where they're understood, there's going to be a massive
change. How many times have you heard there's a change coming, right?
How? That's like
saying, you know, I'm going to solve this quadratic equation
by chewing gum. That's all I hear. You know, there's people awakening
and there's a change coming.
Explain to me how and you're going to hear the most
idiotic, opinionated, irrational, undefined
crap you've ever imagined.
Right? Well, see, now I talk about a change coming
a lot and I've got to tell you that
I don't define it. I believe that
it is something as yet unrecorded
or unrelatable to what
I know as has been observed in the past.
That's about
as far as I can go. I don't make any claims to tell you
that I know the nature of the change
or anything like that. I just have this feeling
that we are approaching that time where
change is going to come. Now,
again, I don't claim to know as much
as you do about this, let's just say,
or as you report about this.
I don't know it because I haven't experienced
that no one has within the realm that we can reach,
but I can give a good report on things
that work. For example, if you're going to go in your car,
you know, you're going to
pretty much go every time, let's say, and you want to go
somewhere, you know, if you do certain things, it takes you there and occasionally
it breaks down. But most of the time, it's
super reliable, you know, 999 out of
1000. Now, if we look at a lot of the ancient information,
of course, they're ignorant savages. Anyway,
the ancient texts, they all seem to be in
accord with each other. Now, we're not talking religion now
at all. So, you know,
the main religions or
the mainstay paganism that's on the planet
right now, let's just say it that way.
We're looking at, they all have a very similar
narrative and there's great accuracy and
great detail. And reporting on that, like, for example,
we report on the coming Middle East Union,
right? Even if you don't have
access to understanding, let's say, things to come
and reading it, you can see that it's very
plausible. And we're not here to push things or
convince anyone of what's plausible. We're here to give a report
that's not being given.
But even taking a step back in the way that I've examined these
things, which is far different from the
way that you're reporting them, I would say
that it makes the most sense
from what I can observe,
that we're going to see
something like a unification. There is always
this process that occurs. Of course,
everyone has always stated that
when you see this type of disturbance in the Middle East,
I don't know if you remember this from childhood, but
even back then, before they had codified
any of these ideals like the
war on terror, before the post 9-11 reality
took hold, long before any of that was imagined,
when terrorism was something
that seemed completely unreal
and happened over there and all that stuff,
people always spoke about this in very subdued tones
that there would be a massive change
that would occur in the Middle East
where things would be reorganized in such a way
that it would change the world we know.
And that was
coming from the most ignorant possible perspective you could
imagine, but it doesn't mean it was wrong.
Oh no, it's actually quite correct.
But when you combine that with reckoning time
so you could juxtapose and orientate information
like with registration marks
when you line things up and you have
places, now you have a reference line.
The information that can be imparted on the future
is quite rich.
And by the way, the quote-unquote
you hear about psychics and remote viewers and all that stuff,
all that stuff has been shut down. And if anyone is still talking about being
a psychic or a remote viewer,
you're full of, you know what, that stuff doesn't work anymore.
20 years ago, maybe,
but that's one of the signs of things being shut down
by the way, cosmically.
So these things now, when we discuss the future,
it has to do with vantage point. It has nothing to do with
the crap that's been dummy loading
mankind for such a long time, but actually it would have been less of a dummy
load before time ended. So if that doesn't sound
confusing, but what we
like to get together and do here is impart things
to fill in the gap,
which is huge, because you can actually go out and see
what's being discussed in public right now on the internet,
let's say, or mainstream, and you can all lump it up
into one big lump. It's very narrow.
There's no depth and no width to it.
There's millions of subjects, let's say, but
they're paper thin and they're all very narrow.
So the gap that we're trying to fill is massive,
but with just two hours and just a little bit of information,
just to harken back to the animals,
I think belaboring
the point of comprehension of the soul and the spirit
and the body is primary to
any comprehension of anything that is alive and existing.
Like you mentioned earlier, everything breathes.
Even rocks breathe.
Trees breathe.
So the interesting thing
here is just to maybe
get to the end of it. I think you and I had a
discussion about the future of animals in private,
and I brought up that it was written that
the animals will start turning against mankind.
Now, I used to speak publicly on some round tables
several years ago in other places, and I kept
telling people, watch. These things are very subtle, these changes.
Watch what they call the news,
and you will start to see increasing reports on animal
attacks on mankind.
And if you actually look at the occurrence of animal
attacks, and I'm not just talking about dogs and sharks and things like that.
I'm talking about the entire animal kingdom.
Even the frequency of pests like mosquitoes and things like that
is going to be on the rise.
A very gradual rise that will peak within, let's say,
15 years or so.
So I think that was the crux of the discussion that you and I wanted to bring up
the animal subject.
And just to throw in, that's the spoiler.
The spoiler tidbit.
So if anyone wants to do a little bit of make it a hobby to research it,
look at the increased animal attacks in the quote-unquote news
as time progresses.
And it's going to be so gradual that it won't be alarming,
but if you know that it's coming,
it'll be a good confirmation.
Well, right.
I mean, in everything from the parasitic to the obvious
bears and things like this,
the more sensational it seems to be
increasing.
Yeah, like someone walking a country road or a suburban road normally
very safe and a pack of coyotes
or wolves or dogs come out of nowhere and chew them to pieces
and never happened before in that area.
Things like that.
Just very unusual.
When animals attack type video, people will go crazy with it, I'm sure.
Or maybe they'll retreat and not do it.
Who knows?
But the animal kingdom, see, the earth is tired of mankind
and so are the animals.
As we said earlier, the earth spirit houses the animal spirit.
You see?
So it's very interesting.
And why is the earth tired?
People think, well, it's because we're polluting and throwing plastic bags in the ocean.
It's nothing to do with that.
The earth can get rid of that, no problem.
Or nuclear detonations and things like that is not the problem with the earth.
The problem is there are agreements that were put in place
according to these ancient ignorant savages
known as those that came before us.
If you access their texts,
the earth had a facelift in order to inhabit mankind
and there were laws that mankind needs to stick to to behave.
It's our behavior to each other
that keeps the earth content.
Not whether we throw plastic bags in the landfill or the ocean
or build nuclear power plants or whatever, whatever.
Isn't that interesting?
And when this is discovered in the future, boy, is it going to be a sore time.
Because all these things that people are calling rights and to do things
are going to say, man, was that a stupid idea?
Anyway.
So, yeah.
That's the crux of the spoiler
about discussing the animals.
But the interesting thing is
you could look at the plants, just to harken back to the beginning.
The plants would be like a mainstay food source for both man and animal.
The animals are predominantly the processors.
Even though they're very few in number
compared to the number of plants.
And man is the steward.
Man would be the steward of all of this.
So we've walked away from our stewardship position
and that's how we could relate
to the animal relation between man and animals
is we're not practicing proper husbandry
at least in the industrial world.
So that would be the crux of the discussion.
But it would behoove anyone in the audience
we'd like to continue this concept of life
when we discuss the animals.
It's discussing the concept of life.
You've got to comprehend what the soul and the spirit is
and go back and look at ancient texts
relating to the existence of these things.
And the spoiler would be
be on alert for animal attacks on the increase and on the rise
as we go into the future.
Not next week or next month but yes possibly
but as the years progress.
And what's interesting is when you and I get together Chuck
we don't discuss what happened last week or this week.
We try to keep the subject broad
going forward in time as well
because the mindset now is just too narrow.
People used to look up for many things.
Now they just look down.
So maybe if we can get people to look across the room
that's a start.
That would be wonderful. Of course they look down
never at the earth below their feet
but generally they look down at their devices
or they look down at their floor
or their feet
but not very often do they look down at the earth.
Things are intercepting it.
But again the level of confusion
as we mentioned in the first hour
there are so many loose ends
that have been left for centuries.
Most people don't like to go back more than 100 years
because they have a reversion to that.
And just to throw in a little tidbit
if you study writings of the ancient Romans and the ancient Greeks
which are the same basically or the Babylonians
or any ancient society in their contemporary writings
of their day
you'll notice that when they started calling themselves modern
was typically when that civilization fell
if you can call it a civilization.
So isn't this considered a modern society or modern civilization?
Oh boy.
Yeah, it seems as though that generally heralds the demise.
Yes, and it's interesting how that works
the repeat of that through ignorance
or the usage of the term is very coincidental
coinciding with meaning
the whole concept of anything discussed
of the loose ends going back
any further than what's considered modern
is usually not wanting to be discussed
but if we go back just less than that
let's say 100 years or so
people are still using a private credit system
and they call their money bills
and they never ask who's going to pay those bills.
So that has to be tied up first
that has to be addressed
these issues
why is it when you get a quote unquote utility bill
from gas, electric power, water
they give you a check to pay for it
and it says attach with your payment
that is the payment
why aren't people figuring that out?
You can't move forward unless these things are taken care of
most of the western world
or any country that has a central bank
has been bankruptcy and receivership
why isn't anyone addressing that?
little children ask
mommy, daddy, where do babies come from?
but adults never ask where credit comes from
and don't say from thin air
it's not from thin air
anyone who tells you it comes from thin air is a moron
and that's a word not as a put down
look up what the term means
my favorite is taxpayer dollars
this guy is so far gone
there's no help at that point
these things need to be tied up first
why are there calories on food?
what the hell does that have to do with the human body?
nothing
they're still telling you that bacteria are causing colds
unless these things are tied up
come to a conclusion
which will probably never happen
as long as you have academics around
because by definition they're not supposed to do that
tie things up and come to a conclusion
as long as you've got academics
you're not going to have a rational in depth discussion
on any matter
public at large
isn't that the truth?
when you come around to it
if you don't understand
and I say this all the time
if you don't understand the language
how do you expect to speak about anything?
if you don't understand the world
how do you expect to interpret for someone else
what it is you're allegedly seeing
this is always a troublesome thing
I'll tell you something
I found this pretty funny
somebody said this in the chat room
clever handle again
nature always looks happier
where people treat each other lawfully
the first thing that occurs to me
when I see that statement
is where is it that people are treating each other
in a lawful manner
well it's again different levels
I would say the entire society on the surface
of the planet that we can observe
has pretty much gone to an unlawful state
but there's different grades within there
if you go into a really cheap greasy fast food place
you could still make the best choice
that you can there
don't get the triple cheeseburger bacon thing
get maybe a dessert and a coffee
and something else
you can get a better
I'm not saying what you should and shouldn't get
but you can always make the best decision
in the worst situation as well
I guess that would be lawfully
but what's interesting again
the lawfulness comes from your deity
and most people still
discuss this thing called God
and I'm like I don't know what you're talking about
when you say God you have to tell me which one
it's like the word army
do you expect to see just one there
well I just believe in army the source
everything is God
when you hear someone discussing God
substitute it with the word army
and you'll hear the most ridiculous crap
undefined opinionated junk you've ever imagined
they cannot do it
on one end I'm ranting about it
but on the other end it's like cosmic censorship
when is it going to end I'm tired of it
it's all around it's very difficult to communicate
but the concept of lawfulness
let me just throw this in and it's a dig
I had a discussion with someone about 6 or 8 months ago
and kind of brought up how most of the religions of the world
if not all of them are satanic meaning based on the adversary
not satanism as it's called perhaps
but they are adversarial
going against what they're supposed to be doing
it's like driving down the road the wrong way
you're going to crash eventually
so that's why a lot of wars are based on religious
zealotism or whatever
but we had a discussion with someone a few months ago
and he says you know that's really interesting you said that Greek
because there are a few towns
incorporated towns
and in their
doctrine or their documents they state
no houses of worship of any kind
this is like a religious free zone
no churches, no synagogues, no mosques, no temples of any kind
allowed and statistically
those places have no crime
yeah I recall this discussion
I don't know if it was you recounting it to me
or if I was there for that
with somebody and I said well
my immediate reaction was it makes perfect sense
we're talking about the mainstream
the major religions whatever they might be
they grow by the day
because they're all whatever
so at this point the lawfulness would be
things that bring peace, proper
interaction with the environment
what that means is if you got a job in a pet food store
they'll tell you it's five bucks an hour and all you can steal
and by the way when you feed the animals you give the fish food to the fish
the dog food to the dog and the bird food to the birds
but you know no one's around and you feel like
doing whatever you want so you give the bird food to the dog
and the fish food to the
the animals will eat it but it's not proper to do that
so the whole thing here
is these laws come from your deity
most people say well I don't believe in that
be on your way
and that's exactly what's going on
that's why you hear about a lot of especially alternative media
people are referred to as sheeple or cattle or whatever
why are they treating us so bad?
why are they spraying the skies?
why are they putting poison in the water?
why are they putting poison to try to inject us with vaccines?
well duh
you know
but anyway
you see I'm kind of leaving that open
everyone's like why why why why why
it's like oh boy
it's very simple
it's too simple, it's too obvious
and the time isn't yet, in the future it will be
but here's the thing
we want to discuss animals or anything else
but when these changes start coming
major changes and they're major if you know they're coming
but most people are just going to be like no big deal
the majority of the people on the planet
these things will happen and change
society as we know it now
will not resemble very much in less than 15 years
anything that they see right now
but everything will still be in place
and it's going to be all headquartered out of the Middle East area
what you call the Middle East
some people like to give you a hard time on defining it
but that general area
here's an interesting simple rational thing
you've heard of the concept of full circle
what goes around comes around
in all aspects of mankind's history
anything and everything has ever been memorialized
even the modern academic crap
they tell you civilization started there
and also the quote unquote gods
emanated from that area
the great battles
of the gods by the way
this is why it's been in the forefront of people's attention
on that
and what hopefully will happen around that time
as this new axial period
which is going to be very short
axial meaning a time period that changes everything that comes after it
like you've heard post 9-11 world or such
but the big axial period was around 500 BC
that we're still influenced by
but there's going to be one very similar to that
really big one coming in the mid 2020s
that's going to influence mankind big time
and by then
there will be more comprehension on what we try to broach
on what the animals are
and their place and the plants and our place here
meaning our place, meaning mankind
but before that time comes there will be more interest
and I think you and I have discussed
even just take something biblical
I've been saying for over 10 years now
watch there's going to be an increase in all things biblical
books, movies, remakes of movies, discussion
references
it's all going to be inaccurate and incorrect
but there is going to be an interest in that direction
you see
just like for example the interest right now with quote unquote terrorism
how much of it is accurate?
pretty much none of it
well I've got to tell you something else
there's also the pseudo-biblical scenarios
that are being replayed and also ramped up
it is not lost on me that
the concept of the Star Wars movies being resurrected
at about this time
makes perfect sense as well
well the Star Wars is good guy versus the bad guy
but what's interesting about the biblical text
you see in Star Wars most of the damage is done by the bad guys
on a planetary level
Death Star blows up the planet
but when you take a step back
you actually see that each side is doing all sorts of damage
I mean there was plenty of people that were killed
on the Death Star and etc
but in the biblical narrative
the adversary
let's oversimplify it
the bad guys take out people one by one
like attorneys, doctors, government, police
all these are religious
they just pick them out one by one
but let's just oversimplify it again
the good guys they come in and take out the whole lot very quickly
and they also let you know why they're doing it
and when they're doing it
I see that as a contrast to the Star Wars but nonetheless
I was made aware recently that they revived another
piece of junk called the Star Wars
and when I say it's like that
I really liked the first one, it was so impressive
but everything that comes after that
the CG or computer graphics don't look good enough
to even watch it for free
but anyway, movie opinions
I think I'll leave that for someone else
I just consider it that there is
this concept of spirituality
that runs through that series
that if you take it as an allegorical
exposition
it becomes nearly part
of the same type of narrative
but modernized, oversimplified
and placed into a different concept for modern audiences
again there's that word modern
it sounds appropriate
very appropriate by the way
there you go
you are seeing a resurgence in the biblical
although it is more like the pseudo-biblical
it's not even close but the mindset
most people think those things are accurate
or from the bible and they are not
I mean they are, the story is, but I have yet to see a book
or a movie that is even slightly biblically accurate
even slightly
or any of the ancient stuff
but I think in the past 50 years
there has been a revival of ancient mythological
ancient mythology, let's say in art form
even on the screen
right, I mean the genre of movies that came out
again with the movies, sorry
but when you are looking at stuff like 300
and Alexander being remade
yeah, Clash of the Titans
all of this stuff is being revived
as part of the same sort of storyline
and none of it is accurate
if you study what happened
but it doesn't matter
well, yeah, there you go again, it doesn't matter
because after all, like I said, it's the pseudo-relation
to the initial story once again
and there you are
yeah, and it's the setup
what it is, is people's minds are being set up
for something coming in the future
that their mind is already prepped
just like remember films in the 80s
where the Muslims were starting to be portrayed as terrorists
before there was any major memorialized event
and then when the event happened
it was very easy within 10 seconds to indict a Muslim character
because it was already in the minds
like true lies or back to the future
people from that part of the world are bad
well, right now there's a revival of things ancient
to some degree, even the storyline in Star Wars
because there's going to be a revival in actuality
in the next decade, what people call the next decade
regarding these matters
and that's why you and I get together to say these things
because guess what, before we were doing what we're doing now
these things aren't being said
or discussed, and I think they're critical
because they're going to happen
right, and at the very least it needs to be said
whether it is being heard or not
is yet another question
but the truth is that it is best to
if you are aware of things like this
it is best to speak
and do so at the appropriate time
and this appears to be the appropriate time for what we're doing
so we're almost out of time here
and I do want to ask the listener to go to
ocellianthegreek.com as well
not only that, but of course American Freedom Radio
we're very happy to be able to do it here on this platform
and I'm sure you're not going to disagree with me
on either one of those statements, Greg
oh no, well it's just a matter of giving good report
let's just keep the reports going
and if any help at all is appreciated
any credits thrown towards the station
or Chuck, is very much appreciated
and necessary
well right, because after all
nothing is being done without
some effort having been exerted
and I read somewhere that
that labor was, this is one of those things
I always thought was lawful
that you were supposed to compensate someone for labor always
I don't know, if you benefit from it
you're supposed to compensate them or something like that
I don't know where I heard that before
well when you hire someone
lawfully they should get their daily wages
and you don't wait the whole week, you get it every day
kind of thing, it's the day labor thing
it's actually lawful, have you ever seen those?
when the job is done by day by day
you get compensated, that's the ancient way
but we're modern now
oh no, we're not
we're trying not to be, although we're using what they call modern devices
but how do you want to wrap this one up
because I have a title in mind for this entire episode now
and it is the soul, the body
excuse me, the spirit, the soul, the body
and the ignorant savages of the ancients
or it could be
the soul, the spirit and the animal
maybe it would be, either way
I guess they like to interchange savage and animals
in common vernacular quite often
how many times have you heard people commit heinous acts
and they call them animals
there's a popular presidential candidate that's trying to do something like that
here we go again with the dummy load
oh, see I go star wars
and you make references to the candidates
wow, strange way to
the interesting thing
if you want to know who's going to be the next leader of any western nation
it's the one who's going to be the worst for the country
and that's just the trend, it's a worldwide trend
oh right, the one that is going to continue
the downward spiral
of the western nations, that's your winner
and there you go
and really the name doesn't matter
because it's all been changed to protect the guilty
because after all, no one is dealing with things on a mass scale
in a lawful sense
whether it's any western nation
study the character of the candidate
and the one that is the least competent
and willing to do the most evil
is the one who's going to be your next leader
it doesn't matter if it's the US or England or France or any one of the western countries
that is going to be one of the worldwide trends that you will see from now
here on out
and you can take that one to where you think you want to take it
yeah, because after all
taking it to the bank
well they're all closed anyway
there hasn't been a bank that's been open in about 82 years or so
and people still haven't noticed
and hopefully you've noticed the information that's been imparted here tonight
on Ocelli and the Greek
we thank you for tuning in to listen to us
and not being part of the dummy load out there
because we are the only two hours that you will get
no dummy loads attached
thank you very much, Greek
thanks, Chuck
and get prescribed psychotropic drugs
and commit suicide too
and try to become the biggest game in town
when you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected
I get unpaid taxes and if I can't find the money
the IRS are going to take my tops
I got a mandatory flu vaccine and now I'm autistic
I reported a vaccine reaction and the doctor told me to forget about it
what have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully
there's only one way to get the government off our backs
and that's to support American Freedom Radio
so what are you going to do?
you're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and give them some legal tender they can't refuse
nutritious food is real body armor
it builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion
and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs
did you know the US government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a schedule 1 drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant
people have been confused about this plant for over 80 years
and many still don't know what hemp is
so now you know hemp is not marijuana
and marijuana is not hemp
they are different varieties of the same species
hempusa.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder
is the best kept health secret you need to know about
remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein
is gluten free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO
and is loaded with nutrients
call 888-910-4367
888-910-4367
and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you
only at hempusa.org
what is the big deal about swearing to God
in the first place?
why does swearing to God mean you're going to tell the truth?
wouldn't affect me
if they said to me, you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth to help you God
I'd say, yeah!
I'll tell you about as much truth as the people who wrote that bible, how do you like that?
swearing to God is kid stuff
swearing to God doesn't mean anything, swearing on the bible doesn't mean anything
you know why? because bible or no bible
God or no God, if it suits their purposes
people are going to lie in court
the police do it all the time
all the time
yes they do, it's part of their job
to protect, to serve and to commit perjury
whenever it supports the state's case
swearing on the bible is just one more way of controlling people
and keeping them in line
and it's one more thing that holds us back as a species
it provides an example to follow
friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches
the hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty
the founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media
now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America
be as generous with us as we've been with you
click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com
vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included
we all know that they're not telling us the truth
so stand up for your rights, demand the real medicine
and your right to use it and grow it
this is Rick Simpson and you're listening to American Freedom Radio
no rules, no rules
no taboo topics
no fear of doom
we are American Freedom Radio