The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand would be the
Well, well, here we are on episode number two of the reloaded version of Ocelli and the Greek.
American Freedom Radio and AmericanFreedomRadio.com, that is where the signal you are listening to is originating from.
At any rate, how are you doing tonight, Greg?
Hey, Chuck and everybody, doing all right.
I guess people are going to, we got what, four or five people in the audience and two white guys on American Freedom Radio, or presumably white guys,
going to talk to everybody and see how we could fill up two hours or we could make it really useful.
Either way, it's really up to the audience and the way we're going to find out is if they call in, right?
Well, that is the other thing here, right?
We can either be productive or not, and well, there's many ways to spend two hours, isn't there, Greg?
Yeah, I don't believe I got suckered into doing radio again.
That's not being suckered, but let's just say, hey, why don't we give the date real quick, talk about suckers, man.
It's the third day, yeah, it's the third day of the 11th month, man.
The third day of the 11th month now doesn't seem to line up with that thing we call a calendar, though.
But you know what? That calendar doesn't line up with itself either.
That's not a problem.
No, it's not a problem. It's a prank. Since when is a prank a problem? Look, it's the –
What isn't a prank then, Greg?
There you go. Well, here's the thing. None of it is a prank if you're in it. If you're out of it, you see the pranking.
You see, if you're the one that's going to sit down on the chair that the thumbtack is on, you don't see the prank until it's too late, right?
I'm always going to do that.
So, yeah. And there's a – yeah, go ahead.
Well, here's the thing. Let's introduce before we get into meandering into God knows where because I obviously don't.
And which God are we talking about and what day is it again?
Look, if you want to participate in this conversation, there's a couple of rules, isn't there?
And you want to give the people those rules and I'll give them the number?
Yeah, basically – more lengthy was the last chapter, last episode.
Basically, don't talk about yourself. Nobody cares.
And if you're high stoned or drunk, don't call in because guess what?
If you're high stoned and drunk and you call in, you sound high stoned or drunk.
So that's pretty much it.
That's the short of it.
And you're going to hear – by the way, do we need to give a warning label that anything that pretty much the Greek says doesn't reflect the views shared by anyone else?
Not to be – anyway.
See, I wouldn't say that because some of your views are the same as mine.
So I may be just as culpable here as you are.
Okay, that will work for me.
Not all of them, mind you.
I don't agree with you on everything unlike what some people have criticized me for recently.
I got to say when the first episode came out of this reloaded version, it was like, hey, you don't disagree with him at all.
Well, not when he makes sense.
Yeah, but hold on.
Yeah, but Chuck, what is agreement and disagreement?
If you go to a restaurant and they serve you dog poo for dinner and you agree that it's food, you're still eating dog poo.
Agreement and disagreement is irrelevant.
What's relevant is the report accurate.
Is it good?
Is it trustworthy?
Is it validatable?
Is it a good report?
And that's really what's lacking.
I mean, come on, look.
I don't even listen to internet radio anymore because it's all dummy load.
So I'm like, wow, you know what I mean by dummy load.
I mean even if you don't know what it's defined as, it even kind of – it's one of those things that is self-defining, dummy and load.
So the thing is when is the reality going to start?
In other words, the reality of what?
The reality of conveyance of good reporting and real communication.
Well, soon.
Is it happening right now?
A little bit.
You're getting a glimpse.
It's kind of like going down the highway in a fog.
You only got five-foot visibility, but you know the road is pretty clear for 100 miles, right?
So anyway.
No, I understand.
It's just that when I said agreement, I meant I guess I should speak a little more plainly.
I should say that when it appears to my ears that you have reported something accurately, why would I argue about it and why would I contradict it?
Now, that's not to say that every single thing you ever say because, well, it's not a cult here and I do think for myself, at least I believe I do, that there won't be disagreements.
That's going to happen, that there won't be conflicts in your report and what I observe.
That does happen.
But it just didn't the last time at all, really, outside of, well, maybe some minor things, and who knows?
It might have been my misunderstanding, but either way.
Yeah, so that's the rearview mirror approach.
How about looking forward?
How about another loose rule, right?
Not a rule, but a guideline.
How's that?
Like paint between the lines, color between the lines kind of thing, so it looks neat.
You can do what you want.
But if you hear two people discussing something and they both say they are discussing the truth of the matter but their stories are different, guess what?
Either they're both wrong or one is correct because both of them cannot be correct if their story is different or their report is different, right?
And that's what the truth is about.
But what has happened on this cultural situation, traditional, because when you talk about religion, science, law, all these things, they're baseless.
They're based on what the culture has accepted, right?
Like Oswald shot Kennedy, Osama bin Laden was 9-11, this and that.
These religions are based on this because of that.
None of it is based on anything that's tangible.
It's all smoke and mirrors, everything.
Speaking of tangible communication, I did not give out the phone number just yet, so let me do that real quick.
218-339-8525.
That's 218-339-8525.
And if you are on the AFR Skype list, I guess we're going to allow some Skype callers to join in as well.
Message American Freedom Radio if you're already on the list.
And they'll see what they can do about adding you into the call as well.
But you are subject to early termination just so you know.
Go ahead.
Well, anyway, yeah, where do you go?
You know, here's the thing.
Did we ever discuss it?
I don't think you and I ever discussed or actually brought this concept up.
Let's just bring it this way.
The purpose of the Internet.
And this is not just the way we look at it, right?
The big purpose, because if you look at how it's functioning, you know, it's whatever it is, you know.
It's what do they call it, the World Wide Web, the World Wide Web and Internet and whatever.
The main purpose, and this is prophetically, when you look at what's going on with the Internet,
it's just as vile and disgusting as every other form of media.
What I mean by that, it's not what you choose.
It's what is initially shown to you on most homepages or browsers.
You know, they all have homepages.
What do you get on a homepage browser?
All this garbage, right?
Why?
Because that's what most people are interested in.
That's what most people have been interested in for thousands of years.
So its purpose is not unique, right?
But it is unique in the sense that it's connecting everyone on the entire planet where they can have video
and audio almost in real time.
What I mean by almost in real time, meaning within the same hour, someone can upload something to YouTube,
let's say, or one of these other video type resources that are easily accessible and go viral in an hour, right?
That's the purpose of the Internet.
It's audio and video.
Forget about the information exchange.
We just discussed how nothing is based on anything.
And prophetically, there is a requirement in the future that everyone on the planet is able to get firsthand information
through communicating audio and video certain events that are happening on the planet.
And that is the sole purpose of the Internet on a cosmic level.
On another level, it's just a tool like everything else, like the telephone and telegraph and television and radio and whatever, right?
Well, now that's interesting.
Where would you derive that information from?
That it's on a cosmic level.
Hang on.
Let me finish the question.
That on a cosmic level, that this is something that needed to come to pass.
Correct.
If you look in what's called the biblical or scriptural text,
there is going to come a time where the entire world will see certain things happening.
And it literally means that.
Now, you have to understand, many people, when they read something, even if it's Shakespeare,
anything that's literal means it's written.
Oral means it's not written, right?
And within the literal mechanism, meaning it's black ink on white paper or whatever,
there are mechanisms in grammar that switch between metaphor and literal, right?
You can see that, whether you're reading fiction or fact or anything.
The author usually directs the mind of the reader to whether they should take something literally
or as a metaphor for clarification.
If you look at the requirement that certain events are to be witnessed in audio and video form,
meaning they have to see and hear what's going on by the entire planet, how can that be done?
That cannot be done unless you do it through some form of communication.
Well, quite literally, let's just say.
We might have people listening to us right now in Australia.
What other mechanism could provide that on a mass scale so that there could be a massive amount of witnesses,
let's say, to an event?
And video and visual, too.
We could actually have a live feed that someone could tap in live right now,
even though we're not doing that.
It's just sonic, right?
You see how everything is gearing towards the video and the visual, just like the silly phones?
Right.
Okay.
Smartphones, sorry.
I'm waiting for the day when people are smart and phones are stupid.
Yeah, me, too.
But the fact is that we could be doing this via live streaming video right now
and communicate nearly instantaneously with millions of people,
although, like you said, we've probably got a dozen listening or something.
But the thing is we could easily communicate
and therefore demonstrate things in a visual sense to people on a massive scale.
That is now part of the capabilities based on the technology, right?
And it's being done, but it's all dummy load.
I mean, dummy load in the engineering sense is you put something on to drain the energy away
before you put it into its real use.
Or a dummy load would be someone in the gym who said they ran five miles or eight kilometers,
but they did it on a treadmill.
That treadmill is a dummy load.
You didn't go anywhere, but you dumped out the equivalent energy of that, right?
Okay.
You see?
Right.
Think about it for a moment.
Not only that, but look, if you're choosing to test a facility for anything
and you want to make sure that it's running, you're not going to, let's just say, for instance,
you wanted to broadcast a moon landing, okay, we're not going to get into an argument about that.
But the thing is if you wanted to broadcast a moon landing
and you wanted a lot of people to see it,
I'm very sure that the first time you decided to flip on a camera would not be the day you landed on the moon.
You would test this, make sure that it was reliable,
make sure that eventualities could be covered in case things went wrong, et cetera, et cetera, right?
But, you know, when you said the thing that my mind went to is we're not going to get an argument about that,
that's a mild form of pranking I see that's being used a lot, not that you're pranking me on this,
but that has to do with opinion.
But if we could talk about the moon landing on what anybody can see and leave your opinion out of it, right?
Now, what has happened now these days, because a lot of people have opinions of it, right?
Some people say we went to the moon no matter what, and they say we, you know, like they went, right?
And I don't want to look at the evidence,
and someone else will really almost take certain evidence and exaggerate it to the point
and try to read into it instead of reading out, you know?
So you got the two extremes.
But in any situation, if you view it objectively with a rational, you know, mind,
using the senses and try to filter out the stuff that deceives the senses,
because the senses are easy to deceive, you know, there's people that make a living doing that, you know?
So magicians, right, ledger domain.
So the thing is when there will come a time where people will communicate where their opinions won't matter
and they'll be giving good reports, you know, and look at, for example,
all of your things that you think people think are the backbone of their society are opinion-based, right?
Supreme Court, the legal society, the medical society, right?
All these things, the religious stuff, right?
It's all opinion-based.
So your backbone is based on pretty much, I don't know, smoke and mirrors.
Isn't opinion like smoke and mirror?
If you're better at manipulating the smoke and the mirror, your opinion will be seen more clearly, right,
as smoke and mirrors probably.
I don't know.
It appears that way.
Yeah.
The thing is I'm waiting for a society also that will go away from the opinion.
See, what the individual has as an opinion is irrelevant.
Give me an example.
Back in the days when I started studying full-time these things, not in any formal way but personally,
people always wanted to have a debate or argue a matter, right?
And, you know, being young and immature in these things, I engaged them.
But being able to walk and chew gum, you know, do two things at the same time,
while I was partaking in the debate or the argument, I was trying to remove myself in the third person
and actually kind of like rise above the situation and see what's really going on without really being in the middle of it, right?
Which is kind of hard to do.
So I did that a few times and I realized these idiots are putting on a show.
They'll say anything just to end up winning the argument or debate amongst the other viewers
or the participants or the bystanders, right?
So I started noticing what a waste of time to argue and debate.
So when they insist that you have to defend your statement through debate, what I usually did to get out of it,
and it showed, this proved how asinine arguing and debating is, that I would say,
if you're challenging the views that I've presented or the report to a debate,
would the purpose of debating myself be to actually be to win the debate, right?
And they're like, of course.
I want to debate you and win the debate.
So I said, well, if that's the purpose is just winning, I grant you the win now.
Why bother?
And that would just infuriate them.
They're like, no, you have to debate.
You can't just grant me the win.
Well, I'm granting you the win.
You win the debate without the debate.
And you see right there they get so upset because what does it mean?
It's just an irrational – it seems rational.
Debating and arguing seems rational because you're trying to use rationale during the event.
But just like any sports game, there has to be a draw or a winner and a loser, right?
Well, it does seem that way when two seemingly different factions compete,
whether they be made up of one player or multiple players, again, just based on my observation here.
But with the faculties that we have, think about it this way just for a minute.
If we were in a rational universe, wouldn't presenting, let's say, the truth of the matter
or something objective to a sentient being be enough?
Why does it have to be argued or debated?
Think about that for a moment.
In a rational universe, isn't projecting objectivity
or just a very basic objective report on something to a sentient being enough?
Why should there be arguing?
Think about that.
Well, no, I agree with you there.
That's why I like mathematics because mathematics is just rational communication.
You go to a store. I want eggs.
Okay, everybody says clap your hands.
This guy came in for eggs.
What does that get done?
Nothing.
Well, I want a dozen eggs.
Great.
Now I know what you're talking about, right?
More, more rational.
Yes, but if you make a claim – excuse me.
Hi.
Well, yes, I was just going to say Jillian has logged into the conversation
because, as I said before, you could join in if you're on the Skype list.
So open to all comers.
Here we go.
And also 218-339-8525 if you want to call in.
Jillian, you had something you wanted to add?
Yes, I wanted to add.
You're saying on the one hand that logic and reasoning used in a verbal form,
which one would call debate, is a waste of time.
And I'm saying if you make a claim and I actually would like to help you
or sort of unpack that claim a little bit, then that's the purpose of the argument.
That's the purpose of saying, hang on a minute, let's examine this claim.
Yes, yes, I agree.
Claims are a bitch, as they say, right?
Miners make claims.
Claims are where you draw a line in the sand, where you make a demand of something,
where you insist or you take ownership of something
and now you have to defend it, right?
Yes, more or less.
I try to avoid making claims.
I like giving good reporting.
Look, I think you're great.
The reason I did want to – the thing I did want to dispute is something I often find
with very highly intelligent people, and that is they say all religions are bad
and I don't think they've used their intelligence to see what the essence of religion is
and how it can actually take some people into closer to a good heart
and closer to understanding their own spirituality,
so long as they can throw the dogma out.
It's the old saying, don't throw out the baby with the bathwater.
Right, but religion is a subject that deals with the spirituality, which is the mind,
and then ultimately reaches out to the gods, and that is a matter that is not trivial, right?
Yes.
It has been trivialized, just like having – I've seen religion go from a pranking level
where a child says you have to do this religion, even though we know it's bullshit,
because we did it, right?
How could you put that on a child?
And the other thing is it goes from that level to peeling gum off your shoe
to it doesn't matter, it's all culture and tradition,
and I suggest that the concept of the spirit, which is the mind, the PSY prefix,
or the Ruach or Rook in Arabic or Hebrew, and you could look at other languages,
it is the mind, that is not trivial, and the gods are not trivial,
and they don't act in futility, but that is a very interesting subject to get into,
but the aspect of arguing is something that is also, if you look, it's beholden in many,
let's use this term, ancient writs of the world, not to argue or debate.
If you actually study any of them, whether it's the Aboriginal people of any place
that have records all the way to any culture,
the argument and debate is viewed as showmanship and to be avoided.
It's just a sport.
I already argue there, I already argue there,
because in the Tibetan Buddhist monasteries an enormous amount of time goes into debate,
and there's a lot of reason for this debate.
It's tradition.
Yeah, it's not just tradition, but it's actually so that you can use the intellect
to work upon misconceptions one has in the intellect, right?
So in other words, I hold a misconception, I present it to you,
you argue with it and debate it, and then you make some points,
and, you know, I try to be as egoless or am as egoless as possible,
and then I go, oh, he's right, that is a misconception that I'm holding.
I'm glad we had this conversation, right?
So that is the purpose of the higher school debates,
like they will be debating these different schools of Tibetan sort of theory of mind,
and those debates can blast apart lots of concepts that we just hold too rigidly
because we haven't examined them before.
Sure.
Well, once you start getting into a narrowed-down group where you have,
quote-unquote, like minds, right, when you subscribe to a religion,
you have more like-minded, and the subject gets narrower and narrower and more precise,
like sharpening a knife, right?
Right?
Okay, like iron sharpens iron, right?
That's good.
But two dull pieces of iron hitting each other for three hours, you know,
is not, you know, conducive to any benefit.
But if you look at, again, what I mean about the religions aren't good,
which I've said in the past, is that they're not adhering to any rules or guidelines,
and they change to the point where they become...
Hang on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's already an extraordinary claim saying they're not adhering to any guidelines.
So can you be more specific at which particular aspects in religions are not adhering?
Yes, yes.
They change through tradition and culture, as the culture changes.
Like, for example, since you brought up Buddhism, from what I've studied,
I haven't found it to be something of personal interest, but what I've looked at it,
it was originally assembled, and what is memorialized about it, right, that anyone can access,
meaning the initial references about it, was essentially what I would say,
how to live a life of integrity, basically.
In other words, walk your talk and talk your walk, right?
I don't agree or disagree so far.
Keep going, yep.
Yeah, like you know the story of the Buddha when the woman came to him with the child
that was eating too many sweets for the Buddha to advise the child,
and the Buddha said, come back in a month.
And the woman comes back in a month, and the Buddha then talks to the Buddha's office,
speaks to the child, and she says, well, why did you tell me to come back in a month?
Why couldn't you speak to him then?
He says, well, because when you first came to me, I was traveling myself,
and I was eating many sweets myself.
That's right.
Right?
So you see?
So there are things that are unspoken.
The child, even though you don't have to tell the child, look, I'm eating sweets too,
but there are finer points in everything that don't have to be spoken
that can be intuitively picked up on.
So you have to have integrity, right?
Yeah.
I said that I give that example for the audience because that shows a very high level of integrity, right?
You see?
So there's many aspects to it.
But essentially, what I mean by how it changes is we have references that we,
let me loosely use the term agree on because they're good references, right?
Like if you're on a construction site, you use tape measures and things like that so you can communicate.
But if you keep changing the tape measure mid-project,
and the project here would be the human project, right,
you get a little bit of confusion and things don't seem to fit anymore.
Right?
So what you're basically saying is that you have to agree upon a certain premise
before you can move from there.
Well, if it's a reference point, yes, it has to be agreed on.
If it's not a reference point, then it's not that important.
For the purposes of communication, right?
I mean it's not about the reference point as a solid fixed place in the universe necessarily.
It's more so that there's common ground to communicate on, right?
Yeah.
That's what covenants are for.
I'll give you an example.
The covenants were the different cultures of the world were memorialized
so people can make a statement and the person receiving the statement would know a lot about that individual
without having to spend a lot of time with them.
I'll give you a loose example.
If I say, for example, I am an Orthodox Jew or an Orthodox Muslim, right,
and you know right away just by hearing that that you will never come to the house
that I would prepare a supper for you and I would ever serve any pork, right,
because you're familiar in those covenants they don't eat pork, for example, right?
And then you're familiar with other things they would do like the days of their worship, let's say,
or a certain tradition just by them stating what covenant they live by.
That tells you a lot about a person, right?
You meet someone, but then it can be kind of loose.
You can have two people sitting at a bar, let's say, two men,
and one says, what do you do for a living?
And he says, I'm a painter.
And the other man says, well, you know, I'm a painter also.
Well, now, just with those few words, it sounds like they're doing the same thing.
Yes, they're working with brushes and paint,
but one is a house painter and the other one is a fine arts painter.
Yeah, I really agree.
It's so hard to have a conversation with anybody when you don't understand each other's language,
like, for example, the meaning of the word God.
It means that's easy.
That's a Teutonic word that means the sun in the sky.
Hang on a minute.
Hang on a minute, because that's exactly what I'm saying.
You know, like, what does God mean?
And you go, oh, that's easy.
You know, it's not what God means to me.
I'll tell you who I think, and I don't like giving a personal opinion, but I will mildly hear.
What we refer to as a lot of the native cultures or Aboriginal cultures,
they call them the great spirit, right?
Have you heard of that term?
Yes.
Many ancient cultures, older, you know, what we call Aboriginal or Indian,
meaning, you know, yeah, those savages that all the white people killed off, allegedly, right?
I'm saying that.
Those landholders.
Yeah, they used to call it the great spirit.
And if you pretty much narrow it down, that's what that would be.
And by the way, I'm going to just throw this out here, because I've asked this question,
not directly to the Pope himself, but some pretty very high up people in the Catholic or Christendom.
Chuck and I will be able to answer it for you.
Yeah, and also people, Tibetans, actually, from Tibet, which Hindu gurus, rabbis, imams,
and no one can answer, and it's so easy a child can see it once they have clear understanding.
What makes the great spirit the great spirit?
Or another way in the Western context would be the Almighty God, right, or the Almighty.
What makes the greatest spirit the great spirit, or the Almighty the Almighty?
Very simple.
And this is memorialized in most, if not all, the ancient texts.
So is that a question?
Yeah, no one seems to be able to answer it.
It's one of the simplest things, and it's a foundation point.
Okay, so do you want Chuck and I to try and answer that, or people in chat to try and answer that?
Yeah, let's let it hang.
It's very simple.
And it's not an opinion.
Well, my answer is that all things, and I do stress the word all things, are subject to the great spirit.
Okay.
That's pretty good.
Can you get more specific?
Yeah, well, in other words, the great spirit is subject to nothing.
That's the concept.
What specifically delineates them as the other spirits?
There are other spirits as well that are similar, but they are subject to one thing that he is not, that makes him the Almighty, or the greatest.
Hang on a minute.
You just called it a him instead of an it.
Well, the position is an it, and when you say him, it's not necessarily out of an anthropomorphic figure like we would discuss the need for genitalia, right?
Like when you say mankind, for example, when you say mankind, you also mean women, right?
Yeah, but once you call it Pater, once you call it above, then you take it away from below.
And if you're saying that the great spirit permeates all things…
No, I'm not saying that.
Well, I'm saying it does.
I said it.
Yeah, I said it.
It doesn't permeate all things, no.
Why not?
It's conscious of it.
But here's the point.
Wait, because we can't have that.
We haven't defined the premise.
We've already got a problem, because we haven't defined the premise of what God is, that it's all of a sudden become a he, or what the great spirit is.
No, it didn't all of a sudden become a he.
Hold on, hold on, dear.
When did it all of a sudden become a he?
That's been memorialized for thousands of years.
If we want to just piss on everything that's come before us, that's fine, too.
If you want to do that.
I don't like to do that.
Just wait a minute.
Let's go back a step.
I use the word source.
Let me just give this, because it's just an interesting thing.
This topic will be brushed under the rug.
It's just typical.
You're not going to brush this topic under the rug, because this is exactly what I want to unpack with you.
Let me just interject something.
What makes the almighty, the almighty, the great spirit, the great spirit in all cultures, you will find this if you seek it, the definition of it, and this is more indirectly, and some places more directly, is that the great spirit is not subject to death.
What does that mean?
Exactly.
Well, yeah, once we tell you, of course, it sounds right, but it's not in the forethought of anyone's mind.
Now, what that leads to is that the other gods, other gods are subject to death.
Well, wait a second, Greg.
That doesn't make any sense.
Well, if you actually study what has been memorialized before us, you will see that, Chuck, you might back me up on this, not back me up, but this thought.
You've heard of other gods being killed, right?
And anyone can study that.
Absolutely.
That's part of, that's always been part of the deal.
Their society, you know, the thing is, that's why I thought it was fair to say that the source, okay, I don't want to anthropomorphize the source in any which way, but the source is not subject to anything, and all things are subject to the source.
That's why I said, can you get more specific?
You're pretty right on on that, but the specific aspect is not subject to death.
Now, that brings in the subject.
You'll notice that all the ancient texts regarding what's called holy writs are about three things, about life, about death, and then law, which is how to live.
All ancient writs are based on that if you study it.
Not what religions tell you, the feel-good thing or finding your spirituality, all that stuff is hogwash.
That is the dummy load.
That is the cultural aspect.
That is the aspect that has been put on humanity on the great axial period around 2,500 years ago.
And yes, Buddhism started around then.
Hinduism started around then.
Christianity started around then.
Judaism, as it's known today, started around then.
And most of the Islamic pagan traditions started around then.
Well, you know, what the problem here is, though, is that we're not actually – we've actually – you've tried to marry the great spirit with God and, therefore, call the great spirit he.
Now, this isn't a feminist comment.
If you called it she, right, I'd be having exactly the same argument because we haven't agreed on the premise of the argument yet to be able to go any further.
It doesn't matter if we agree.
Yes, it does matter because you're making a whole lot of summations based upon – let me finish.
Yes, go ahead.
You have to be careful not to make a whole lot of summations based upon our agreeing or my agreeing with your premise, which is the nature of the great spirit.
Right, but I've never claimed that.
I'm simply reporting, if you listen clearly to what I've said, is that anyone can look at this.
The problem is that it is not fun, right?
It doesn't bring people joy to get mature and serious about any matter because you've been told so much what you believe in and the separation of thought, meaning why don't you speak?
I want your opinion, then his opinion and her opinion and whatever, and at the end of the day, nothing gets done, right?
But those that know how to assemble thoughts and don't concern themselves with agreement and debate get the things done in this society.
You ever notice that?
Yes, but I feel railroaded, right?
I feel as though you're saying, let's forget about this.
Oh, you don't agree on that?
Great.
Let's brush that aside and I'll just keep on telling you that this is correct and therefore this isn't a conversation.
No, no, I'm not saying it's correct.
I'm saying it's a good report.
If you see it as being – this is the thing.
In order for something to be correct and incorrect, it should be plain.
Now, if it's not plain, what people like to do is read into it.
They like to find the things that are maybe incorrect about it and just focus on that and not the general gist of it.
We can get more specific if you like.
I want to because what we're doing is we're creating confusion when we –
Get me out of that, Wee.
I'm on the sideline.
Maybe you and Chuck have at it.
I'm saying that we create confusion when we make an assumption as to what the great spirit is and that it's the same thing as God and it's called he.
We create confusion when we talk about the ultimate spiritual nature of our minds in such a murky way.
Well, what I can observe is that there's no reason to apply the he or she or any of those titles.
But I'm curious about why it is that there is a problem marrying the great spirit with this word God.
What is the issue with that, Jillian?
I have no problem, no particular problem with that if we recognize them as being the one thing.
But then once we call it he, all of a sudden it's gone.
What the heck are we talking about?
Because my idea of God and the great spirit have nothing to do with he.
But that's your idea.
All right.
You're allowed to make things up about things that are fine.
But the subject matter has been around for a long time and it's standing unexamined.
Well, this is why we're examining it.
And not only that, it's a change of experience.
It's an ongoing understanding.
So my understanding of God that I have now compared to my understanding of God when I was four are completely different concepts.
That's fine.
But we have seven billion people that way.
And one of the prerequisites is not to give too much of our personal stuff.
Oh, whose prerequisite is that?
Well, it's where we started off.
The guidelines for the show.
The guidelines for call-ins are two things.
If you're high stoned or drunk, don't call in because you may not think you sound that way,
but it's very obvious to those that are not that you do.
And the other thing is if you call in, don't talk too much about your personal stuff because everyone will.
I'll tell you why.
Hold on.
Because everyone wants to agree, but what they're really doing is they're sitting back and saying,
when is this person going to shut up so I can say what I want to say?
No one is listening.
What I've noticed being on humanity for more than half a century is that people don't do what they say
and they don't say what they do and they don't mean what they say and they don't say what they mean.
When you have people spilling their guts out, whether it's television, Internet, radio, in a book,
or let's say not in a book, the audience seems captive and it's polite to agree with the person
and give them the time, but no one cares.
This is humanity.
I agree.
And I've seen it all the time.
Exactly, and I know what you're referring to.
But the fact that I'm saying my opinion about religion at the age of four is different to my opinion about religion
isn't referring to myself.
I'm just using myself as an example.
But I could say the same about you, which I will do in the future if you prefer.
So do you have the same opinion of God?
What did you define God as?
I try to leave that out.
The last opinions I remember, these are the three major opinions I've had in life.
This is personal, but I'll share it, Chuck.
You might like this.
First it was I wanted a red fire truck.
I got the red fire truck.
Then I wanted those Rock'em Sock'em robot toys.
Remember that?
I do, yeah.
Yeah, and then after that I kind of like gave up on it because I noticed opinions were for you know what.
And right now the thing that I'm really looking for is a flying saucer to get off the stinking rock.
All right, next.
Well, you know, we're also being asked, by the way, just to interject here because first of all,
Gillian, leave the he thing out of it because I think that was –
If I just get a straight answer to that, then we could cut into what he means when he says God.
I don't care.
It's not the he thing.
Well, no.
Well, okay, look.
We can speak another language.
It seems that colloquially people in the Western world like to – when you say God,
you're going into that subject matter, right?
Just like when you say propeller or hull or something, you're talking about ships now.
It is a very inaccurate term.
English is a very inaccurate language.
If you want, we can speak Greek and you'll find that it's more precise.
Or we can speak Spanish.
It's an easy language to learn.
Basically there I said we could maybe learn some Spanish.
It's a little more accurate.
We can go on.
You can go through different languages.
I prefer over English for the very reason that English is such a piss poor version of communication.
I'll give you a quick example.
Any complete dictionary will show you 500,000 words in English.
It's all great to me.
Right?
But, you know, Shakespeare used about 20,000 of those words.
Your average college professor has about 1,000 in his vocabulary.
And your common oaf on the street typically uses between 150 words a day only.
So that should be inspirational, not desperational.
Why, Chuck?
Because if your common oaf uses only 150 words, that means, Chuck, if we want to go to Italy,
we can learn about 75 words, which is about 10 phone numbers, right, because a phone number is seven words, right?
And we can be half fluent.
I remember years ago you used to memorize phone numbers.
Now you don't anymore.
But anyway, you can learn.
You could pretty much learn how to string together about 100 words,
and you would be considered semi-fluent in any language.
Now, if that isn't one of the most inspirational things I've heard in a long time, I don't know what is,
because language seems to be a barrier for many people.
But you see, actually, what you're saying is actually agreeing with me.
And when you say an enormous string of Greek words, you know, I'm then in a position to say it's all Greek to me.
But when you make some claims and then move on from them as though I've agreed with those claims,
that's what I'm saying because it's just a few words.
Yeah, well, you make quite a few of them.
Hold on.
Maybe we're not communicating.
Here, let me look up this word here.
See, what I say is just like the God thing that you said and claim thing.
Okay, claim.
It's a noun.
It's a demand of a right, a right of claiming.
It is a thing claimed or demanded.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yeah, and so it's sort of like…
Why am I…
Go ahead.
Continue.
Well, I'm just saying, like, it's sort of like when you believe something to be true and you say,
I think this is true and now I'm talking from this position that I think it's true.
I think that's all very fair and reasonable.
But the main reason I wanted to talk to you, right, was something that you said last week
and so I tried to bring it up this time and I was actually hoping to come into the show
when you hit into that sort of opinion again and you did hit into that opinion again,
which is sort of like…
Because I think religion is important to some people
and I think they're better off with it than without it.
And I wouldn't take Jesus away from Jesus' grapes.
Well, before we get into the characters, though,
wouldn't it be useful to define and come to some understanding of what the word religion means?
Yep.
Wouldn't that help here?
Good idea.
Yep, brilliant.
Do that.
It's defined as something that is done regularly.
Now, there's a lot of immaturity out there that likes to take words and break them up,
like television means telling lies on your vision or history is his story
or religion is re-legion or whatever.
That, again, is mucking up the reference points.
So it just means something.
Like I'm very religious because I find myself tying shoelaces, brushing teeth,
and combing hair every day.
I do that so regularly that I would say that it's done religiously.
And the reason why religious is brought upon these groups, that title,
is because that's what you get your law from your God, right?
And the religious aspect was where you got your law
and then it was convened into the social aspect.
But you've got to realize you're still living under this cosmic censorship
that was put on humanity over 2,500 years ago
that we are at the precipice now when this seven-year period ends.
What do you mean when you're saying a cosmic censorship
that was put upon humanity 2,500 years ago?
Well, I say 2,500 years.
If anyone really wants to hold me to that number, it's not that accurate.
It would be around 700 B.C. to about 500 B.C.
So there's a 200-year spread there that would be around 25, 2600 years ago.
Maybe 27 is when it started, right?
And what is a cosmic censorship?
Well, it's very simple.
Put it on it.
Well, hold on a second.
Cosmic means the world and censorship means to censor, means to not show.
Okay.
So now at this point I would say to you where is it that you obtained that information?
Oh, very good.
If you go first class with ancient texts,
you will find the scriptures preserved in Hebrew and Greek have more information
than any other holy writ of any culture, right?
There are several prophets and several writings that have shown this to be put on mankind before it came,
so you knew it was coming.
And then things that were discussed after that were under that censorship, right?
Also, there are pseudo-academic –
No, I can't say right.
No, you don't have to.
I'm not saying I'm demanding.
This is not a claim.
I'm actually simply stating the facts.
Just because you don't agree, when I say right, meaning that if you look this up, you will find it.
But if you have no interest in it, then you won't find it.
Look, any information that you hear –
But it's just if what you've just said is that some censorship was put upon us –
Yes, all of humanity.
By whom or what?
You see, that's like going – that's still asking the question.
Let me just give a piece of advice.
You can ask all the questions you want and you'll just have questions and answers.
But how about just asking the answer?
Forget about asking the question.
Because I don't trust your answer, not because I don't trust you.
Well, one of the things that I've said with Chuck a while back is I really don't want to speak publicly.
Right, Chuck?
I really don't want to do this.
Right.
Why?
I'm the one who should shoot through because you're valuable to Chuck.
If you don't want to answer my questions –
No, but it's a matter of answering them.
But you see, what happens – the reason – let me just finish this quick thing.
The reason I don't want to speak publicly is because there's better things to do.
But the reason I feel compelled to do it is because I just can't hear any of this most basic stuff being reported.
If we could possibly, instead of having the Greek behind the microphone, do it with some computer generation, that would be fine with me.
I'd rather be completely anonymous.
But it needs to be said.
And once you find something out, you must say it.
Otherwise, you might be culpable for not speaking later.
But the other thing is this.
When certain questions are asked, there's this checkers mentality or this half-hour sitcom mentality that people think that you can just answer it.
Yes, you can.
But there's no understanding there because many things need a four-hour explanation, which is not good for quote-unquote radio like this.
Besides that, nobody in any media presentation has a four-hour attention span it seems like anyway.
So the thing is report on these things.
Go back and look at them.
There are some academics that did a cross-pollination of culture, meaning showing how this affected everyone throughout the entire planet around that time.
And the emergence of what's known as many modern cultures and traditions happened around that time as well.
It was known as the main axial period in history.
It was the main axial period.
We recently had an axial period with 9-11.
You know, before the – it was after.
It's a post-9-11 world.
You've heard that.
Axial periods are things and events that happen that change the world view.
And 9-11 was a small one because it only regards one small aspect, let's say the security apparatus that's put on society, right, and the financial apparatus.
But the main axial period, pretty much what it did – and let me just – who is – you will find out.
What it did was it cut off people's access to information regarding the society of the gods and their ways overtly.
Before that time period, you spoke to anyone on the planet regarding what happened, let's say, pre-flood or where man came from or who the gods were.
They were very well versed in that typically and also information was easily accessible about them if you didn't.
For example, you've heard of the burning of the Library of Alexandria, right, and that's when that happened, during that time period.
There were information depositories not only in northern Africa or that part of the world,
but in all parts of the world that were now eliminated from public view, including these people.
They're called aboriginal and native people.
They were also part of a worldwide communication system back then.
And all of that went away from public view.
It's as if someone just wiped it all away over a period of 200 years.
And what was put in its place was a very trivial, light, culture and traditions that allow man to not be engaged with information about spirituality as it really is on the higher levels,
basically dealing with elementals and minor imps and demons.
Well, right.
Now, I understand this concept full well, and you know that.
We've discussed it privately even.
Okay.
And I feel as though you've just given a very accurate report about what has occurred.
And this is – now, at this point, this is my opinion that your report is accurate.
Okay.
But we did miss one part of the discussion here, and I don't think I heard it.
Maybe I did, and maybe I'm being censored myself.
But the thing is, I did not hear you answer who or whom or what imposed the cosmic censorship.
Well, that's pretty obvious.
It's the head boss, el jefe, el bosse, el capitan, the great spirit, right?
And anything – the bigger the job, it has to go all the way to the top of the ladder, doesn't it?
Well, I appreciate your – yeah, I appreciate your explanation of the hierarchy,
and therefore, like the very simple and plain term of chief deity, that is what you assert imposed the cosmic censorship?
Well, anyone can assert that when you have a cosmic change as such.
The Earth is a very – here's the thing again.
Here's the four-hour explanation condensed to 30 seconds.
What people have done is they've discounted their position as humans
and their position of the Earth and importance in the world of the gods.
Humanity is one of the most precious – the most precious being in the universe to the gods, the benevolent ones,
and the Earth is also one of the most important places of the entire universe.
And these things have been discounted through millennia,
and especially now with the New Age movement and things like that.
So there is great care, and I've given the metaphor before, which is not really a metaphor,
but it's actually a pretty direct report on that anyone can find,
is that even the most loving parent, meaning the most loving to their child,
is nothing compared to the love that the benevolent gods have for children.
No human can imagine what kind of care, love, and – can be given to another unless you're in a god form, right?
And we – humanity itself is considered akin to the highest form of creation,
and the Earth housing and enabling humanity at this point during this time period
is considered one of the most precious, let's say, rocks or gemstones in the universe.
And this is really a concept that has been heavily discounted by many discussions,
because right now constantly people are looking at what's out there or inside of themselves,
and they don't see the situation and the value, the true value of what is going on universally here.
All right. Now, where did you learn this, is the question again?
You said –
Anywhere. Any of the holy writs of the world.
And also if you have a telescope, you can – here's the thing.
If you look at anything that – now again, let me just – I'm not a Bible thumper,
because it's never been translated, so if you go to the store and buy a Bible, you – I don't –
go ahead and try to read it, whatever, you're not going to get much out of it.
Right.
But the scriptures preserved in Hebrew and Greek are first class information,
and then we can go down from there.
Well, there you go.
And as we continue into the second hour of Ocelli and the Greek here on American Freedom Radio,
I'm sure it'll get just a bit deeper. Stay tuned.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
Oh, yes. I like this very much.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly, like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions, running my companies, and I hated feeling groggy and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret, the powers that be want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride, our brains are under siege, and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve, a revolutionary breakthrough in a category of cognitive enhancers called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself at dnaevolvesample.com.
That's dnaevolvesample.com.
Supplies are limited, so go to dnaevolvesample.com right now.
Contains 53% protein and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at hempusa.org.
Hempusa.org introduces three brand new detox formulations of micro plant powders.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at hempusa.org.
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
What about show business?
Show business, completely dishonest, corrupt, and full of shit, but in a nice way.
Plenty of expensive drugs and perverted sex.
If you're going to be full of shit, might as well enjoy your work.
Then you have the media.
Not just the news media, let's include them all.
The media are almost literally exploding with bullshit.
Because they're located right at the crossroads of all the other bullshit.
The media are made up of equal parts advertising, politics, business, public relations, and show business.
These people are sitting right at bullshit junction.
There's enough bullshit in the media for Texas to open a branch office.
And you still have enough left over to start two law firms and a Christian bookstore.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Providers for free education?
Well, that's obviously effective, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America...
All the information they provide is free?
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, man?
Exploiting commonplace corruption?
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice?
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
They never censor, hang up, or cut off their guests?
Well, that's no fun, is it?
They created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative, and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shills and scum?
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from,
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable people without a voice,
bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream, and alternative media shills and scum,
what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are.
American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information
So the second hour of this presentation, which would be the second episode of Ocelli and the Greek, reloaded.
I will call it chapter two when I type up the description later.
We had an entertaining hour, I believe, with Jillian, and it was certainly, well, interesting.
I'll put it that way.
But meanwhile, if you want to join into the conversation, once again,
218-339-8525.
Here we are communicating with some very logical and rational things like numbers, and you can do the same.
Hopefully you'll remain logical, rational, and stick to the rules.
218-339-8525.
Okay.
So, Greek, we've got a couple of questions in the chat room during the break, and if you don't mind, I'd like to kind of start off with those.
Would that be acceptable for you?
Yeah, I think one of us looking at the chat is enough of a distraction, so let us know.
Yeah, absolutely.
Here we go.
And here, you might want to take note for a second, because this is going to be more than one question,
so I'll throw them at you, and you can handle them how you see fit.
First of all, why is God censoring us is an interesting question.
The why is always the elusive thing when you study just about anything, in my observations over the years.
Right.
So the why question is always most fascinating.
Simple one.
So let me hear what you have to say about that.
Okay, go ahead.
A simple one to see on that is there's a level of spiritual maturity that mankind is lacking.
And, you know, like brush your teeth, go to bed before nine, eat your vegetables, learn to tie your shoelaces.
Why? Why?
Well, because those things are actually going to benefit you, right, as a child.
Mankind is a very juvenile state.
Even older people seem to be still very juvenile.
If you look at the history, whether you want to look at what's called scripture or mythology,
mankind has faced some very big calamities.
Mainly the flood was, let's say, the biggest one that most people can say was on a worldwide level.
And whether you want to deny it ever happened or not,
but there's enough mythology and scripture and all that stuff tied together to show the flood legend, right,
what's called the flood legend today.
And other things that have happened, destructions of certain places by the gods,
whether you're reading the Rig Vedas or the biblical texts or other things.
Even archaeological examination.
I mean, you can see that volcanic activity absolutely wiped out entire portions of civilizations rather quickly.
I mean, this is just one of those things that occurs.
Yes.
And also the gods use that as a tool.
And the thing is, if you look at what was memorialized about that event,
it was always attributed to caused by the gods, right?
Even now in Hawaii, when the volcano rumbles, guess what?
It's the god that is doing it, right, the volcano god, right?
It's not just some geological phenomenon to the people, right?
Yeah, I don't recall the entity's name, but there is an entity that is responsible for that.
Yeah, they say she, this god is, right, okay.
So people were much more, quote-unquote, spiritual back then.
This was because mankind had gained too much knowledge in how to be a, quote-unquote, god
and was ready to just jump out of the pot, if you know what I mean.
Right.
You can get off this planet, right, and do things perhaps.
You know, an undisciplined child can do a lot of evil things.
Have you ever heard the old saying, don't let children play with matches?
Why, do they deliberately want to burn the house down?
Actually, some children do.
Some do, some don't, but the fact is that if you allow too much freedom to the immature
and grant them, you know, you don't hand car keys to a 10-year-old,
they may be capable of driving the car, but you don't expect them to behave responsibly.
Right, I mean they can probably perform it, but how well are they going to perform it is questionable, right?
Right.
Right, so the thing with it is very, this is very easy.
Anyone can look up if you want to spend 10 years studying it, but I'd just like to give it away,
and this is not my opinion, it's just a simple report or a guideline,
is that, well, instead of giving all this access of knowledge to mankind
where we have to keep coming down here and putting a damper on them,
why don't we just cut off their ability to see and get the knowledge so they can kind of,
like, exist more in this immature state that they think they can set up governments
and have wars and have a medical system and a science system that means something.
Let them play around with their little play school, you know, easy bake ovens
and their little firecrackers known as nuclear bombs and all their bogus stuff like CERN and vaccines
and all these little demonic imps that they call, you know, whatever gods in their religions.
Let them play with that stuff for now until this time period, this curing period is over,
and then we're going to reveal everything to them.
The problem is most people can't handle it.
So, you know, so, anyway.
Totally understandable.
Let's get to a couple of the other things that were mentioned.
First of all, I'll give you this one in brief.
The Greek has mentioned in other discussions that a couple of females had disappointed the eternal.
Who were they?
Okay, that's one.
Now, hang on.
Let me give you the other one before we go there because this one actually, I think,
is the most often asked question that I get when I'm not with you.
Okay.
Here we go.
Hi, Greek and Chuck.
Thanks for broadcasting.
I have a question regarding lawful timekeeping.
If you have time to address it, I am interested in understanding the calculations
and measurements used to accurately calculate the seasons and the regularly occurring.
Stop.
Stop right there for a minute.
No calculations.
It's all observational and measurement, but go ahead.
Okay.
So, the measurement.
The measurement is what we need to ask then.
It's observational.
Okay.
And the regularly recurring 13-month phenomena.
Stop.
It's not regular.
It's intercalated.
It's observational.
Typically, you'll have three of them every nine or ten years.
And more detail on that is on the Book of Enoch, which is not the Book of Enoch, by the way.
It is a set of notes that were kept by the first temple priests to be read and paired with the Book of Jasher
or the Book of the Upright.
There we go.
Okay.
Any specifics you can impart or clues you can point me in the direction of would be much appreciated.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Very simple.
Let's use, you know how we, I wouldn't say mock because it demands a certain amount of respect, you know,
the Gregorian calendar, the Pope's work schedule.
Why?
You ever notice, Chuck, if you go on a construction site and you pick up one of those skill saws, you know,
they used to cut two-by-fours, they say you've got to respect that.
Because it could cut your arm off, right?
One of these days you could run into someone that believes in this hogwash so much that they might kill you, right,
because they don't like what you're saying.
You've got to have respect for a wild animal whose behavior you don't understand as well.
They're at large.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So that's the only thing that's worth respecting of that thing because it's atrocious.
But if you look, for example, if you look right now, it's about the middle of the month for the pagan calendar,
and it's already the beginning of the month lawfully.
And if when you see that kind of a drift usually, almost a whole half month, because the pagan calendar,
you ever notice that the full moons tend to come on the Gregorian calendar typically on the beginning of the,
what they call the month, even though it's not really, you know, it's the work schedule.
That's your first sign.
Now, like, why am I saying it this way?
It's because I'm explaining something that's happening in real time right now and check it out.
You know, this year there might be a 13th moon.
The other thing is to look at the size of the moons.
You ever hear, Chuck, through your life that certain moons are given names like the hunter's moon, the harvest moon.
You know, they kind of, through almanacs, they name the moons, right?
The super moon, all this stuff, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And the reason you name things is because they look distinctly different.
Because I've been doing this for so long, I can just, you know, look at any moon
and tell you what month it is based on its position in the sky and its shape and color.
And this is also done, you'll notice, for example, the first month, the first moon
and the seventh moon are the largest by far.
This year, typically when you have a 12-moon year, as you go higher in number count,
by the 12th moon it's really, really small.
This year, or the 11th moon, so in other words, the 7th moon is very large.
The 8th moon is a little smaller.
The 9th moon is a little smaller.
The 10th moon is a little smaller yet.
The 11th moon is a little smaller yet.
The 12th moon is the smallest.
And then comes the first month and it's huge.
Okay, you follow how that works?
Well, this year we just went into the 11th moon.
And you know what?
It ain't that small.
It's not as small as last year's 11th moon.
It's a little bit bigger, which means that this year the smallest moon will probably be the 13th moon.
So I'm predicting, which I don't like to do because it's almost unlawful to say that there will be a 13th moon
because we don't know, but everything seems to be set up close enough.
The mechanisms described in the Book of Enoch were basically, if you could wrap your head around it,
those were notations taken or chronicles taken over about 150 years that were compiled into the Book of Enoch
by a priesthood that it was their job to be timekeepers.
That's why I'm not stressing that you use that as a guideline, but it's a good place to start.
They talk about the gates, if you can define them, you know, where the moon rises.
You know, where the moon rises in the summer is where the sun rises in the winter.
And where the sun rises in the summer, the moon rises in the winter.
They switch places, right, through the sky.
So these are the gates, and usually on the first and seventh month,
the sun and the moon rise and track through the sky in the same location.
So that is another hint on how this drift takes place.
But the intercalation concept, I don't know where to send anyone for any accurate information online.
There are many quote-unquote groups, I hate to say it that way, or cults,
that try to use the astronomical bodies, and they read into it too much.
And when stuff doesn't work, they have no answer.
They say you either believe it or not.
And that's when I usually get in the car and drive away, when someone tells me that, you know.
So what I'm saying, when you stick to purely observational, it works every time, just by measuring.
The simplest observation about lawful timekeeping is that your first and your seventh moon
are equal in size and the largest of the year.
And that gives you a little bit of a hint.
Now, here's the thing.
How many times have you heard a concept that had to do with, let's say,
a skill or interacting with something physical?
Let's say, for example, you go into the military and you know what a rifle is, let's say,
and they just talk about it a little bit.
And now, like six months later, well, they hand you one, let's say,
and six months later, you're supposed to go into the field and use it just by a little talking.
You can't.
You actually have to be trained on how to take it apart, how to put it together,
and practice shooting, right, before you go.
Because the chances of you being able to use it successfully when you need it is almost zero to maybe 10%, right?
The same with lawful timekeeping.
Even if you get the concept down, it might take you six months to a year to figure it out
because you have to live it.
You have to start observing it.
You have to start doing it, just like astronomy or anything else.
I went out and purchased a very good telescope years ago, very good eyepieces.
And I said, great, now I know I've got all the equipment.
I really didn't know what the hell I was doing for about two years, until about two years, right?
Okay.
No, it makes sense.
Hands-on is the way to learn certain things.
Now, a private Skype question comes up.
If the first and the seventh moon and sun track the same way,
how do you know the difference between the first and the seventh when you're, I guess, laying out your calendar?
That's a good point.
On the northern part of the hemisphere, well, you know, we've never discussed this.
This is a question I was thinking in the back of my mind.
Ask, where are the four corners of the earth, right?
Right.
And it's a center point, a datum point.
Where does it start?
Typically, the first moon is in the spring and the seventh moon is in the harvest or the fall.
Okay.
So you might want to say if you're living upside down, you know, like down under somewhere,
right now they're going through, you know, the seventh moon up here was really the first moon for them seasonally.
But they're upside down.
That's strange.
It's a strange thought.
But it's not.
Here's the thing.
We've proven this too through measurement.
Do you know how if you call someone in New Zealand or Australia right now that they're in tomorrow,
according to the Pope's work schedule, right?
Right.
Well, lawfully, they're not.
They're actually behind us.
I've done the measurements on this based on when the moon and the other bodies start.
We actually have boots on the ground in Australia, and we've done the measurements observationally.
And they are not ahead of us.
They're actually behind.
So in other words, when the first day of the month comes around, it comes around here first, let's say,
into the U.S., then they get it.
But if you look at the Pope's work schedule, they already have them a day ahead.
Because where does it change?
The actual starting point is around where the four corners of the earth are.
Now, there's a question.
If anyone knows where the four corners of the earth are, it is a very specific thing, call in.
Tell us where they are.
Do I know where they are?
Absolutely.
Have I mentioned where they are before?
Yeah, absolutely I have.
I have it recorded.
I think I've done it with you, Chuck, and I've done it with other places.
I've been doing it for ten years publicly, maybe four years on five years on internet radio calls and things.
I don't recall us going over where the four corners of the earth are.
I've got to be honest with you.
Now, it could be just me, but I think you might have done that elsewhere.
And I'll say that I would be really fascinated to hear this answer because I've heard it described.
Yeah, but see, I've heard it described simply, and it's in more than one location.
So I would love to hear it.
Of the earth, the naval point, you know, where's the naval?
Well, it's in more than one location, you know.
Well, I don't know.
It means maybe you don't got it, right?
Right.
That's what I'm saying is that I've never heard anybody really nail that one down.
But it's accessible to everyone, but no one wants to look.
All right.
So that's pretty much any other questions, by the way,
other than we're inviting anyone to consider if they know where the four corners are.
Well, the other thing is we didn't go over.
You mentioned in another discussion that a couple of females had disappointed the eternal,
which is exactly how they phrased it.
Who were they?
Well, who are they?
There is a group of them.
It appears to be one main one, and she has cohorts, right?
There's references to them, and she crops her head up.
But she's very much, because of her stature, right, in that world,
she's not interacting with men.
Her cohorts do, like the goddesses that you hear about would be more of the cohorts,
you know, the lower associates.
I like using the military metaphor.
When an army sends an invading force to a country,
the inhabitants of that country do not encounter colonels and generals on first contact.
They encounter the infantry, which is basically boot camp grunts, right?
Oh, always first, yeah.
Yeah, and then maybe you might see a colonel, maybe.
You know, they don't interact with the people.
They stay back.
So, yeah, that's what I mean.
These would be low-level.
Have you heard of Justice, Justicia, Columbia, Britannia?
Astarte would be a little bit higher in their social ranks.
I know this, you know, sometimes I've briefly heard the other recordings
and things that we've done this week a little bit just to catch up,
and I said, man, people must think we're nuts discussing the gods like this, you know,
because this is still a very secular society and very much in denial,
not about what you believe in, but of the knowledge and the information that has been memorialized, right?
So, about it.
Yeah, and I'm also being told that apparently you did do this with me,
and it is my fault that I don't recall it.
Okay.
Thanks.
I guess I need to go back.
I never listen to the shows that I'm doing except when I'm doing them.
You know, we can do instructional shows.
Maybe we'll do one on how to improve memory.
I was doing Uncommon Radio before.
I took a few months off with Seth Michael, and we actually did two of them regarding cooking,
and I actually got some really good feedback, you know, how to make perfect rice,
how to prepare various things, water and other things properly so you do
and achieve a very good final product, right?
And thinking that, you know, we can do it on the radio and had excellent results.
I mean, I got a lot of feedback.
First time they made perfect rice and all this and things like that.
That was actually one of the episodes was called Perfect Rice.
Now, here's the thing about food, people, and just anything.
In order to prepare delicious food, you have to eat delicious food.
That's why.
What I call white people food, it has nothing to do with the color of your skin like in America.
I find that funny because, yeah, go ahead.
You know what I'm talking about?
Like, look, if you live in New York and you say you're going to move to Midwest,
everyone is going to make fun of you, and they're going to say,
you go to a restaurant to get pasta, it's spaghetti with ketchup.
They don't know anything about food.
You know what I mean?
So they make fun of you.
You're not going to get any good Italian food.
You're not going to get any good pizza.
You're not going to – right?
Okay.
Well, you don't in the southeast.
I'll tell you that right now.
Yeah, yeah.
But, you know, actually, right here in the southwest,
they just opened a fire brick oven type pizza.
I'll give them a plug if I may.
It's called Pionic Pizza.
You can look them up.
There's only one in the country.
Excellent pizza, five bucks for a pie, man.
Believe it.
It's like 1960s prices, and it's excellent quality.
But here's the thing.
In order to make delicious food, you have to eat delicious food.
That's why with the boom of cooking shows,
if you've noticed in the past 20 years on cable networks and things,
people still make crap preparation foods mostly.
Why?
Because they never get a chance to eat good food.
Just like information, right?
If you've got a crappy education and you're going to write a book,
that crappy education is going to show through, right?
That's why, right?
Okay, so whatever.
So in order to get better, it's almost a catch-22.
You have to be better to get better.
But how are you going to get better if you're not better now?
Well, that's kind of tough, isn't it?
It's really a tough situation that people are in,
this lie that they've been told that just keep improving.
How the hell are you going to improve?
The example is not enough.
You actually have to partake in it.
It's kind of like a guy goes to a nightclub, right?
And he says, look, I want to come in.
And the bouncer says, look, you can't come in without a pass.
And he says, well, where do I get a pass?
He says, inside.
But wait a second.
Okay, I get the pass inside, but I can't go inside.
So how the hell am I ever going to get in?
Too bad.
It's not my problem.
You get the situation, right?
So this is the problem that humanity has been – is it a catch-22?
I don't know if I'm using that phrase right.
Is that what it is, a catch-22?
It seems about the proper phrase the way I understand it, yeah.
Yeah.
So in other words, in order to make delicious food,
you have to already be eating delicious food.
That's why I tell people don't bother watching those cooking shows
because you're not going to learn anything from it
because you have to be eating good food already to make good food.
So anyway.
There you go.
I've got to be honest with you.
When I'm around better food, I do produce better food.
That I know.
And I don't know why that is exactly.
Well, musicians too, Chuck.
You've always got to jam.
Let's say you're a good guitarist.
And by the way, let me say this about music.
Look, friends don't let friends listen to bad music, right?
Okay, anyway.
Right.
And what makes good music good?
It sounds good.
It doesn't matter what genre it is.
If you like a particular genre and yet you're stuck in it
and you can't listen to something else because it's a different genre,
that's not a good place to be in terms of sonically enjoying what is available.
If it sounds good, it is good.
And where did I get that from?
I got it from – was it Armstrong, the trumpet player, Satchmo, right?
They asked him.
He says, what's good music?
He says, if it sounds good, it is good.
It doesn't matter what the genre is.
Really a very underrated individual as far as his plain
and simple approach to things that produced extremely wonderful, complex sonic elements.
Right.
Now, the other thing is, let's say you're a musician.
You always want to jam with good musicians.
So imagine, let's say, name a great, let's say, rock guitarist or something.
If he couldn't get any gigs and all he did was do guitar lessons to nine-year-olds,
guess what he'll start sounding like after a year of doing that?
Just like guitar lesson for a nine-year-old, right?
You got to jam.
You got to always –
Yeah, exactly.
Because you are influenced by that which you surround yourself by.
I mean that's just the way it works.
I mean I was a musician and I was at my best when I was around people that were better than me,
quite honestly.
When I tried to instruct people that didn't have any talent,
it caused me to digress, so to speak, in sophistication, in creativity, et cetera.
So again, the cooking show was used as a reality that can happen.
Learning – perhaps eventually if we – this is a limited event.
I like to keep things limited.
I don't know how many we're going to do.
But at this point, maybe getting into something a little more instructional, which works.
Basically, we did – I know the cooking has been a success.
We could do a pretty good talk about water, perhaps how to learn a language quickly, organically.
Let's just do that one right now.
You want to do that right now, Chuck, the language?
Very simple.
It's a few minutes to start.
Okay.
So we have like about 30 minutes to work with and you think you can fit that one in?
Three minutes.
Very easy how to learn a language and then we could refer to it back, more techniques later.
The easiest technique on learning a language – have you ever heard of the concept of doing something organically?
Even organic farming is considered to be better, right?
Of course.
All right.
What does that mean?
Now, how are you going to learn a language organically?
You ever notice that people that speak a second language or when they do speak any language,
the reason they do it organically is because they grew up.
That's what they spoke in the household, right?
Right.
They have no choice, right?
Like if you grew, you know.
So now speaking is not enough.
You have to be what's called literate.
Well, let's say you're in an Italian household and how does the child become literate?
Well, most likely today, even more than today, a few decades,
the child will probably get what's called a coloring book and they'll start coloring in the letters
and they'll give some basic words and then you move on from there.
So if you're unfamiliar with a language,
go to the country of origin of that language and download a coloring book for four-year-olds as an adult
and do that coloring book.
Yes, you heard me right.
And now you're going through the organic process versus all these other academic things that you subscribe to and buy.
Do you think you can go through that coloring book faster than a four-year-old?
Yeah, most likely, right?
Not being sarcastic there.
And you'll probably get more out of it, right?
And go ahead and color it in.
Trust me on that.
It works.
And then you start going to the basic primers, first grade, kindergarten, first grade, second grade.
By the time you get to third grade, let me ask you, Chuck, in any language, let's say in America or U.S.,
they speak American, right?
Do you think you can have a conversation with someone in the third grade?
Oh, easily.
Yeah, okay.
So if you, let's say, wanted to learn a language and you had a third grader's vocabulary in that country
that you were unfamiliar with a month ago, do you think you'll do okay?
I think you'll do splendidly.
No, absolutely.
In fact, I can tell you that I only was exposed to Italian at a very young age, the language,
which is why I never speak it because when I do, I sound like a child still.
And quite honestly, if I took your advice and picked up from the age of the toddler that was exposed to it
and walked through those steps, I'm very sure it would evolve from there.
I have a little bit of a jump start, and it would evolve.
It makes perfect sense to me.
Very organic and very quick, and instead of going through the direct memorization route,
which is another concept, you know how earlier I said briefly in passing that memorizing a phone number
without the area code is seven words?
Greg, wait a second, those are seven numbers.
Yeah, but you can write them numerically or you could write them alphanumerically, right?
Like the number one, O-N-E.
Think about it.
These are seven words per phone number, right?
That's true, but I've got to be honest with you.
I used to remember phone numbers by pattern.
Okay.
Whatever pattern – there you go.
If you develop a pattern for memorizing phone numbers because there's a rhythm,
you can develop a pattern for memorizing words.
Don't try to memorize words one by one in a language.
Try to memorize a string of them or a phrase and use words that are interchangeable in other phrases.
What happens then?
If you can memorize – if a commoner in any country typically uses 150 words in their day,
then we're not talking about technical professions and things like that have specialized words as well.
We're just talking about commoners, a bus driver, a commuter, someone interacting with the public.
You're only using about 150 words a day.
There are actually programs now where you can actually record yourself speaking all day
and have the computer sort out all the words you spoke and give you a list of them in category.
It usually be between 100 to 170 words per day that you speak,
unless you're having a specific subject matter type deal, right?
So if you memorize about that many or can string together at least 75,
you can pretty much get along commonly speaking, you see.
Now, what is the importance of language?
It's to show respect.
There's many countries, a few, that demand when you visit there,
you speak their language and not only their language, but you speak it perfectly or you're ignored.
Like France used to be like that in Paris.
If you thought you spoke French and you were American and it wasn't the perfect accent, they ignored you.
Even though you said everything correctly, you just didn't say it the way they wanted to hear it, right?
You've heard of things like this.
Vietnam is like that also.
I go around and I speak to – there's north and south Vietnamese and as a joke,
sometimes I say,
and they're like, oh, I don't know what you're talking about.
And then someone next – because they're very snobbish and someone in the background will say,
like they're not so snobbish, right?
Because what did I just say?
In northern – in Vietcong, you'd say,
in southern Vietnam, you'd say,
and basically I do that to stir them up when I try to do basic Vietnamese and they're ignoring me.
What does
Do you eat dog?
And actually I had one guy look at me and he says, not here.
You didn't say no, right?
You didn't say no, exactly.
Yeah, you're right.
So the reason – and the reason I bring that is when I have a basic communication in Vietnamese
and they're ignoring me, it's because I'm not saying it exactly.
Just like if you go to a patisserie in France and you try to order in French
and you're not speaking the Parisian dialect that they like,
they ignore you as if you're not saying anything, right?
That is still a problem.
But that is the disrespectful side of language.
But the respectful side of language is, for example,
give a hypothetical situation, more than hypothetical if you could read into it a little bit.
Someone has a client that just came to this country,
very high net worth individual and they're from Korea.
And you initially meet them and you realize their English is very, very poor,
almost no English other than yes, no, and hello, and goodbye.
Now, you're going to have to engage with this person in about a week.
And you want to engage a person like that as if they're royalty, let's say,
with high respect because that's the culture they come from, right?
So, what you do is you spend a week learning basic Korean.
So, when you engage them, you don't need an interpreter.
And even if you do, there's this cordiality, at least with the cordial politeness,
you could say hello, you know,
you know, you could say basic things like that, right?
You know, I speak very little Korean, you know.
So, you can engage them, right?
You do that out of respect, right?
Let's say, Chuck, we were going to go visit the king of Thailand.
We would want to know some basic phrases, you know, just out of respect, right?
Because let's say we were found with him for a little bit without the interpreter.
Interpreter needed to have a potty break.
What do you do?
We can't say anything but smile, right?
No, you want to be able to say, yeah, a few basic things.
Yes, no, yeah, of course.
Well, beyond that, yeah, I speak very little, but I'm glad to be here, let's say.
And this is so – it makes you a good emissary.
And it's not difficult to learn half a dozen languages part-time.
Now, when I say part-time, this – you know what?
I heard a statistic that still floored me the other day that the average, let's say,
westerner watches anywhere between four to eight hours of television a day.
Have you heard that?
Is that accurate?
I don't know how they do the eight-hour part.
They sleep with the TV on?
All right.
Yeah, I'm curious about that myself.
But, yeah, I've heard that before, though.
Yeah, all right.
So let's say an hour a day doing what we just discussed,
you'll be semi-fluent in more than one language, several languages at the end of the year, right?
Yeah, true.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, I'm not going to say how many languages I can speak or whatever.
It's irrelevant.
But many people are extremely surprised.
And also it's good to know bridge – there are certain languages that are bridge languages.
Like, for example, I was once in a situation, and it was actually people that were Thai came over,
and they were looking for a hotel.
No one knew how to speak Thai, and they couldn't speak to them.
But I found out one of the – they came to me, and I said,
do you speak Thai?
They were surprised when I said no.
But I said, no, I don't.
But I actually tried to communicate with the people, and I found out that one of them spoke Spanish, right?
Because he lived in Argentina.
He was an engineer.
Okay.
So now he didn't speak any English, but he spoke Thai and Spanish.
Now, I didn't speak any Thai, but I spoke Spanish.
Now we have a bridge language.
Now we speak communicating in Spanish fluently together.
Okay.
Well, that makes perfect sense.
It's a bridge language.
Spanish is one of those very effective bridge languages.
A lot of people speak some form of Spanish for one reason or another in a lot of locations.
South America.
South America is very industrious.
Chile, Argentina.
Chile, Brazil, Portuguese is okay also.
You have people from various parts of Asia and what's called the continent of Africa,
all the countries there in Europe that do engage in many places,
and you'll find that Portuguese and Spanish and sometimes German is a good bridge language, right?
Yeah, German is fairly effective, and quite honestly,
German is not something that is completely alien to the English speaker either
because many German words are reminiscent, let's say, of English words.
So quite honestly, you can begin to decipher at least part of what's being talked about.
But here's the thing.
With a couple of languages in hand,
you could probably strategically create a set of bridge languages
so that you wouldn't have too much trouble communicating with just about everyone who did not speak English, right?
And one hint would be look at the instructions you get when you buy things.
You notice they have several languages, right?
And it's based on where they distribute the product,
but you'll notice it's typically English, French, Spanish, right, still?
True.
Yeah, on this part of the world.
The other thing about, I don't know,
so I don't know how much we've eaten up about the 30 minutes,
but let's just say that these are simple things that one can do.
Now, let's just, you want to tie this in with the typical subject matter discussed is,
you ever heard of something called the Middle East Union,
a loose confederacy of ten nations that's going to be coming on the scene in the next decade?
What languages do they speak in that part of the world?
Let's see.
They speak Arabic, Hebrew, Aramaic, Farsi, right?
Hint, hint.
If the entire world-based power structure is going there,
and those are the languages generally spoken, known as the Meso-Chaldean tongues,
that would be like Latin would cover Portuguese, Italian, French, Spanish, right?
The Chaldean tongues would be the Aramaic, Hebrew, Arabic,
and then you have the Farsi, which is different, like what they speak in Iran, right?
Right.
And Afghanistan.
Which, by the way, speaking of the Middle East,
I actually got an answer in the Skype about the four corners of the world.
Go for it.
Okay.
So here we go.
The four corners is in the Middle East.
Yes.
Very good.
Crossing point of a map of Earth laid flat and divided into four.
Correct.
It's the navel of the Earth.
If you took the Earth and laid it out and you drew a diagonal across of it,
the center of the X, the two diagonals, sorry,
would be in the area of the Levant or Jerusalem around there,
maybe slightly to the east if you want to generally do like a 50-mile radius.
It would be the, let's say, the eastern shores of the Mediterranean
would be the center of the Earth.
So now why do we know that it's one spot?
Well, the four corners you also have in the U.S., don't you?
You can actually have two people standing in four states, one foot in each.
What is it, Colorado, Arizona, Utah, Nevada, right?
Something like that?
Okay.
Yes.
Yeah, and the four corners of the Earth or four corners of anything
that's referred to in ancient texts is typically symbolizing the center point,
not an outer like corners of a table, but usually a center point, right?
So that's more universal because the four corners,
you would think of a rectangle or a square on the outer points,
but anything could have four corners in the center, right,
if you just crisscross all the lines where they meet.
A simple thing would be a pie, an apple pie.
You know, cut it in half and then cut it in half again.
You'll see four large pieces, and where they all meet in the middle,
that is the four corners of the pie, right?
You can do four corners of any object.
That's why it's a really good central locating point.
And that point, that term four corners of the Earth originated, again,
in the scriptural sense, and why do we know that it's a central point
and not four corners of a table all the way far away from each other?
Why?
Why do we know that it refers to a central point?
Because it's the narrator in the text is saying that I saw four of these things
standing at the four corners of the Earth.
Now, how can someone see four things at the four corners of the Earth
if they're thousands of miles apart?
You can't, right?
So that means it denotes the center of something.
Okay.
So there you go, very simple.
By the way, people will want to beat you up about this and say that's not it,
but they don't know what it is, but definitely that's not it.
So you're not going to make friends being so simple about it.
In the chat room, somebody said Jerusalem.
Very close, yeah.
Okay.
So there you have it.
After going through all these different things, I do now recall, though,
since I read that, all of a sudden it comes back to my mind
that we had discussed this,
and exactly in the context of when you were talking about the Middle East Union.
Well, yeah, we were trying to dispel out of it.
It might have been with you or Seth at the previous show,
trying to dispel one cliché every show.
Also a lot of clichés that you hear being used,
especially biblical ones that are not true, that anyone could look up.
But dare you look it up?
How dare you look up what it means?
How dare you?
Don't you know that you have to go by what you think it is only?
Anyway.
Or not only what you think it is, but what you were told to think it is.
How about that?
Right.
Oh, man, yeah.
And then who told that person to tell you to think, right?
But we know –
There goes that telephone again.
Yeah, there you go.
So it's because it is all done by the adversary folks.
People don't like to hear –
It's not like you're sitting at a big family reunion
and you're like eight years old or whatever.
You jump up and you say,
Daddy is having an affair with Aunt Jenny.
That's kind of like it's the truth, isn't it, let's say?
Because you saw them in the backseat of the Eldorado, right?
Right.
But you don't yell that out as a child in a family affair.
But is it the truth?
Yes.
And some of these things that have been discussed are on that nature.
Because what?
What does that do?
It tears the family apart, doesn't it?
Yeah.
But is it the truth?
Absolutely.
That's why I think we've touched on it.
We spoke on languages and all that.
Years ago, if you were from a certain nationality or country,
immigrated, let's say, to America or anywhere else,
the children were raised speaking the original language of that family also.
Now they don't anymore.
And you hear a lot about families falling apart, right?
There's a complaint in the American conservative viewpoint, let's say, right?
Now if you understand scripture and you understand cosmic censorship
and how the earth is being controlled and what people are really doing,
what their festivities and why they get together,
what it really means, you will understand why the family is being torn apart.
I think we've discussed that before.
Very simply, because all of the holidays, not some of them,
but all of the holidays except for anniversaries,
that people get together for family are based on satanic or not satanic,
because satanic is actually bigger,
but based on human sacrifice and the eating and destruction of children
based on these lower imps and demons like Moloch
and all these other small gods that were around in the ancient times.
Yeah, I was going to say be fair to the satanic
because they're not the only ones that participate in.
Well, satanic, you see, Satan, we've mentioned this before in the hierarchy,
he doesn't deal with people.
The minor imps and demons do.
So even the satanists are ignorant.
Even if you look at what the satanists are saying,
they are reviving an ancient god by another name like Set or whatever else, right?
Behemoth or whatever, you know.
That's not Satan.
That's like saying Tiny Tim is John Wayne or Arnold Schwarzenegger is Elvis Presley
or no one has any right to start mixing identities.
But in order to defend – here's the other thing that I wanted to say.
I was thinking about this during the week.
You hear a lot about authoritarian discussion, especially on the Internet now,
because anyone can get a microphone.
That's why once I wrote I wish microphones cost a million bucks,
we'd get sanity again to some level, right?
Wait a minute.
I don't know that people that have a million bucks to spend on a microphone
would restore sanity to the airwaves or anything.
But it would clear out a lot of the riffraff for sure.
That's true.
When you hear a lot of discussions these days regarding people about the nature of religion,
Satanism or Christian speaking or stuff about political or anything like that,
they're just like magicians.
They are hoping and praying internally that the audience is completely ignorant of the subject
and the basis of that subject.
And typically that's true.
What I mean like magicians, like for example, if you're a magician putting on a trick on a stage
and you have an audience of 500 people, what's the worst thing that can happen?
I mean other than one of the illusions going wrong
is have another magician come and sit in the audience that you know.
Why?
Because he can maybe decide friend or foe, be your foe and start telling people how you did the trick.
Now what happens to – now that $50 ticket isn't worth it anymore, is it?
Because now you know how it was done.
As soon as you know how the trick is performed, the magic is over, yeah.
Yeah.
Now instead of the guy on stage lying and you swearing to it,
now the guy on stage is lying and now you know it's a lie.
That's why you're not getting the truth on Internet radio.
That's why you're not getting the truth in university.
That's why you're not getting in the mainstream.
And this is not something that you become initiated in.
In a group, this is something you have to do on your own.
And again here, I'll just read a comment here.
Someone said that, again, the Greek thinks he knows the truth of all religions
and all wise men cannot be possible.
No, I don't think I know the truth of all religions.
What I've done is I've looked at what they are based on a little bit
and I realized that it is not good based on any basic morality and you walk away.
The truth of all religions is very, very simple.
It's the crowd mentality.
All you have to do beyond the religion is look at how man structures his operating system.
For example, every country has a matron, meaning female, or patron, meaning male, deity over them,
always through society.
And no one is discussing this, right?
What is the matron deity for America?
It's Columbia or it's justice, justicia.
And if you want to know where the country's god comes from, it's where they get their law.
These gods that people talk about in their religions have nothing to do with what they tell the practitioners.
The purpose of the gods is to give you law.
You might call it the laws of physics, how to live, how to go into contract, what to eat, what to wear, how to keep time.
Those are all laws, right?
I'm not talking about traffic law and tax law.
That included.
And by the way, with taxes, only foreigners are taxed.
So if you're subject to tax, guess what your government considers you?
Oops.
Yeah, that's the truth too.
And also modern taxation is just theory.
So you're all subject to a theory.
Anyway, because it's credit.
But ultimately, you don't need to know much about religions.
All the religions do is get you away from the gods, plural, and the most high and knowing any law.
And you will find that it's just based on Gustave Le Bon.
He objectified the crowd.
Anyone wants to look it up?
It's called the crowd.
Well, I'll tell you something.
We are going to examine these things further, I assure the listener.
And it appears as though there are more than four, by the way, Greek.
But who knows what will happen as we go forward because, well, it does emerge as it's supposed to, I believe.
Well, it's a loose guide to those that are ready to visit this planet in a sense.
And I mean that facetiously and sarcastically because what we're discussing is accessible to anyone.
I don't think, Chuck, you can call me on this.
You don't have to call me on it now, perhaps in the future.
Have I ever mentioned or said anything or brought up anything, either general or detailed,
that couldn't be accessed or referenced outside of the conversation?
Because it's all a trick, a ludicrous trick.
Later it won't be.
When I say all, there's a little bit of stuff that's decent here and there.
But you don't want to, if you're hungry, you don't want to be sifting through someone's poop for undigested corn, do you?
Well, I've got to tell you this, though, as somebody who does participate in Internet radio fairly regularly, I do not.
So I guess you could almost call it my religion.
Sorry, I had to make that joke.
It's not a joke if you do it regularly.
Go ahead.
But it is effectively a religion for me, right, then, because I do actually participate in it regularly.
I've got to say that I am waiting for a time when there is better material available because I know it's coming.
Are you kidding, Chuck?
It's everywhere.
It's not the material.
It's the audience.
They asked Sarah Vaughan what makes a great jazz musician.
You know what she said?
The audience makes you great.
The audience, if you're accommodating, here's the thing.
I've told you this in private and I've told you in public.
If you start telling people the truth and give good reports, you're going to lose your audience.
That's an assurance.
You'll be down to like this audience of four people.
People don't want to.
You know what I mean?
You know what's funny about that is that I lost a ton of audience when I started to say things that I just knew were absolutely,
without fail, the best report that I could give.
Quite honestly, I did.
I lost a ton of audience.
Hey, welcome to planet Earth.
This is Earth.
This is how things are done.
What's amazing is I discussed it with you and we did have this discussion before you and I ever went on together.
I've got to be honest with you.
I thought you were wrong.
I really thought you were wrong.
Well, we talked about this being like a guidebook.
Forget about the people, the idiots on this planet.
Maybe for those that are listening that are thinking of coming here, stay back.
Just keep going.
You don't want to come here.
Why?
Well, first of all, no one knows how to keep time.
No one knows the energy direction of things or whatever.
No one knows the past or the present or the future, which is prerequisite.
But anything you say, anything you say is just going to confuse the shit out of them.
So now you have to say the opposite of anything, which is something like what they want to hear.
It's about accommodating the audience.
And right now, humanity is in a really piss poor shape because of the cosmic censorship.
But here, you can't make excuses for them, right?
It is what it is.
I found it – and this is funny because – and I know I shouldn't be talking about personal stuff.
But I need to address this with you real quick.
I found no reception for a statement that I made about I'm discussing warfare and I'm discussing the conduct of war
and I'm discussing how horrendous this and that and the third thing is.
And suddenly I stopped in the middle of a conversation.
It was on air.
And I said – and I've said it several times, but no one hears it.
I've said several times when mankind or humanity, however I describe it, when we – OK, the we.
Here we go with the we.
But when we mature as a species, this discussion won't need to be had anymore.
No, no, it won't.
But also, Chuck, do me a favor.
Observe the culture.
In many cultures and nationalities, the passage to manhood is through war and joining the military.
Like years ago, let's say if you grew up in the 50s, 60s and 70s, even that late of the 20th century,
and you had international discussions, people were surprised if you were of age of majority
and not in the military for a few years at least.
Like certain countries, 90% of their male population and 75% of the female population, men and women I should say,
enlist in the military for a short time.
It's almost like a passage into manhood or adulthood.
And also, stop being appalled by war.
It is a sport.
It is all a form of pranking.
Yes, people get killed, but you'll find out why it's going on later.
Here's the thing that people don't understand.
In order to learn the characteristic of something, you study what that something does,
and you could say it's one of its characteristics, right?
Like we really don't know what bears are, but we know enough about bears that we could say loosely
we know what bears are because of their character, right?
This is what they do.
Right. What do the gods do?
When the gods create, what do they do?
Every time they create, they create in large number, don't they?
How many grains of sand on the beach?
How many stars do you see in the sky at night?
How many cells in the body?
How many cells everywhere?
Atomic nature, you know?
Everything the gods do in creation is of large number.
People always get impressed with large numbers, and they're hypocritical about it.
I recently got someone sent me an email about 100-some-odd people dying when a church collapsed or whatever,
and it was so sad.
I'm like, are you kidding?
Are you joking?
American doctors kill 3,000 people a day through negligence and just outright homicide.
3,000 a day.
Where are you?
This is an easy statistic to look up.
Even in their own, you know, how they pat the numbers in their favor, it's three-quarters of a million a year.
The figure is way bigger than that.
Look at the, you know.
So what's wrong with you people?
You've got this selective prioritization, you know?
How is it sold to you, you know?
Wake up.
Look, I've said and I've been harsh on people.
This is what all people have in common.
They take up space, right?
You could displace volume.
You get a tank of water, you make a line, you dunk somebody in there.
The water level goes up, you make another line, you measure how much water there is.
That's exactly how much volume they take up.
That's the Archimedean method, right?
Right.
So everybody takes up space.
The other thing is everyone that's alive is giving off heat, right?
As far as I know, yes.
Right.
So if the general denominator of people on this planet is that they are space heaters.
They take up space and they give off heat.
Can't deny it.
Now, that's your baseline.
That's where you start and you can move up from there.
And every time I try to move up from there, Chuck, I've got a problem.
I can't.
I understand.
I'll tell you what.
We're running real low on that thing we call time.
I'll enter the question that was just dropped in the chat room.
It can't be 2016.
What year is it?
Wow.
Okay.
Good question.
What's your reference point?
All right.
Let's just spit it out.
There's this new kid on the block called Adam, right?
You notice what I said, right?
Right.
Okay.
And he came on roughly 6,019 years ago, right?
Since Adam.
You want to find another reference point to keep time from?
Have at it.
Let me know.
Contact me at uncommonradio.com.
But that's the safest and the best bet right now due to genealogy.
Okay.
Well, you know what?
It's as good a point of reference as any.
Absolutely, Greg.
And we will do this again next, what they call Thor's Day,
on the Pope's work schedule.
Ocelli and the Greek is done.
We will see you again.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions, running my companies,
and I hated feeling groggy and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret.
The powers that be want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride, our brains are under siege,
and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve, a revolutionary breakthrough
in a category of cognitive enhancers called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself at dnaevolvesample.com.
That's dnaevolvesample.com.
Supplies are limited, so go to dnaevolvesample.com right now.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion,
and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant
from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug
to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years,
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
Hempusa.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder
is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367.
888-910-4367.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at hempusa.org.
We all know that they're not telling us the truth.
So stand up for your rights, demand the real medicine,
and your right to use it and grow it.
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
The world is like a ride at an amusement park,
and when you choose to go on it, you think it's real
because that's how powerful our minds are.
And the ride goes up and down and round and round.
It has thrills and chills, and it's very brightly colored,
and it's very loud, and it's fun for a while.
Some people have been on the ride for a long time,
and they begin to question, is this real or is this just a ride?
And other people have remembered, and they come back to us,
and they say, hey, don't worry, don't be afraid ever
because this is just a ride, and we kill those people.
The eyes of fear want you to put bigger locks on your door,
buy guns, close yourself off.
The eyes of love instead see all of us as one.
Here's what we can do to change the world right now to a better ride.
Take all that money we spend on weapons and defense each year
and instead spend it feeding, clothing, and educating the poor of the world,
which it would many times over, not one human being excluded,
and we can explore space together, both inner and outer, forever in peace.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow, friendships to flourish
with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally for sharing your views
and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio at ymail.com.
Vaccines, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.