The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand would be the
sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
Still a dramatic introduction for Ocelli and the Greek reloaded.
Now, I used to describe this at the beginning by giving you an episode number.
I don't know if we need to number these anymore, do we Greek?
Greetings, perhaps not.
You know, these are interesting conversations.
They are never scripted, by the way.
In fact, the Greek and I have not had a conversation since we were last on air together.
But we did briefly speak just before going to air with about, what, two minutes to spare, something like that.
Sure, yeah.
Well, why do we do this, right?
Maybe I think that we need to give people that are going to visit this planet a fair chance to know what's going on on this planet
and with the people on this planet, because sure as hell the people on this planet don't want to know what's going on, right?
So we've got to give some kind of a broadcast, you know, a non-terrestrial radio internet, let's say,
might be good enough to let those that want to come to this planet know what it's about so they're not too much of a surprise.
So I guess that's the premise or let's say the metaphor of what is being said here, you know.
There you go.
And really that boils down to some interesting stuff.
Now, we're going to change this up, for those of you who have heard the show before, just a bit.
Now, why do I say that?
We're going to allow callers to join, okay?
And in fact, I have the board open right now in front of me, and you can call in.
Now, we didn't offer this all the time when we did it before, did we, Greg?
No, we didn't do it because essentially, you know, I mean, if you've been on this planet long enough,
you've met who's on this planet already, right?
You just stand outside your door.
You're probably going to run into a typical surface-dwelling Earth inhabitant.
But before we go on with maybe any more criticism, and what I want to get into is call-in etiquette,
why don't we give the call-in number so they could warm up the keypad.
Let's just say it's area code 218-339-8525.
Does that sound about right?
That sounds correct to me, 218-339-8525.
Yes, I have a habit of repeating myself.
218-339-8525 is the number to call in.
And you will be added, well, you know, when it is appropriate.
But I will try and get to everyone as quickly as possible, I assure you.
So I have this feeling, though, that you're going to require instruction for this show
because it's not like mine where, you know, basically I say, look,
if you want to call in and be abusive to the host, it's permissible.
Well, that's okay.
They could try that, too.
But here's the point, whoever they is, as they say.
I always noticed, you know, getting into one's personal things,
and this is one of the caller etiquette things that I'm going to bring up also.
I got involved with calling in the phenomenon known as Internet radio because it was suggested
that I listen to certain programs.
This is going on four, five, six, seven years ago, let's say.
And they were highly recommended as being informative, perhaps entertaining, perhaps whatever, right?
You know, how do people recommend programming?
You know, they have their own view on it.
So I started tuning into them, and I was like, wait a second.
This doesn't sound right.
This guy is talking about the economy, and everything that he's saying is unfounded, right?
I mean, unfounded meaning within the authorities that control the economy.
In other words, what these economists are talking about has absolutely no bearing
on how the economy works, but everyone is enjoying it.
I tuned into people discussing health matters, and I'm like, wait a second.
These people don't know how the body is working.
Wait a second.
You know, and on and on and on.
Conspiracy theorists, historians, and I said, wait a second.
Are these people mad?
Pretty much everything they're talking about is unfounded or baseless.
It is based on what the society has accepted, right?
So I started calling in to give some information, saying, hey, you might want to consider this.
And I was always, let's say, welcomed and graciously, but the minute you hang up,
it's like this amnesia kicks in, and they go right back to it, like you said, nothing.
No one wants to do any homework or whatever.
So I kind of retracted, and part of the thing about being a caller is that you get to interact
with those in doing the medium.
Now, I mentioned to Chuck earlier that maybe we'll discuss perhaps caller etiquette,
and there's really one real basic one, which is this.
People like to talk about their personal stuff, whether you hear it on call-in people, callers, let's say,
from a listening audience, you hear hosts discussing personal matters,
you hear guests discussing personal matters, and it may not be the crux of the show, but gets into.
And what I've discovered being on this planet, doing public speaking in person
or on various electronic groups or whatever, I started really just paying attention to what is going on.
And essentially when people start speaking about themselves, everyone else is acting as if they're interested
because it's the society that it's a polite thing to do.
But what they're really thinking is when are they going to shut up talking about themselves
so I can get the microphone and I can talk about myself, you see.
You know how true –
Yeah, no, this is very true, though.
I notice that there are a lot of people – and listen, you don't have to be a caller.
You can see this in your face-to-face interactions sometimes,
that really a person is not hearing what is being said.
Well, they're not listening for sure, and they might be hearing certain sounds
and they're waiting for the sounds to stop so they could start making sounds.
Right, exactly.
That's what the whole purpose of them being allegedly engaged in the conversation is.
It's part of the interaction.
Yeah, they're waiting for their turn.
That's the thing.
There's the Japanese concept of bushido where it's an old tradition where if someone asks you how you are,
you always said you're fine even if you're dying of stomach cancer, let's say, or you had a bullet wound.
You might say, by the way, do you have a Band-Aid?
You never discuss your personal things in public because it doesn't really concern the group as a whole.
Now, as you get smaller and smaller groups, then you might have a purpose for forming that group,
which is, you know, then it becomes advantageous to bring in one's personal effect.
Now, that's just basically the first concept to consider about caller etiquette.
No one really cares about your personal situation.
People say they do, but they don't.
Sorry, humanity.
This is just the way that I've seen them interact.
The second thing is real simple, the caller etiquette.
The second thing is if you're really stoned or really drunk or really whatever, altered on something, don't bother,
because you may not know that you're – you might think you sound straight, but you're really not, right?
And everyone else is realizing that you're high or drunk or whatever.
So if you feel like you're under the influence, maybe wait until the next episode.
Those are basically the two rules.
What do you think, Chuck?
Pretty simple?
I think that is simple enough instructions for anyone to follow if they speak this language.
Or recommendations, let's say.
I don't know if people like following instructions either, but yeah.
Okay.
You know what?
That's fine because they really are recommendations.
We obviously cannot exactly control the behavior of an individual when they decide to engage with a phone,
but we can control whether they remain on or not.
So understand that if for some reason patience on our side of the equation is lost due to one of the aforementioned problems,
please know that you – full disclosure here – you may very well just be hung up on for that reason.
So there's no mystery in why you hear the click, right?
Exactly.
So one more time.
Here we go.
And now I'm already being asked, by the way, if people can join in by Skype.
I don't know if you want to do that, but if you do, we could.
Sure.
Yeah, why not?
You have a red button on Skype also, so that's fine.
Well, that's true.
But because American Freedom Radio hosts the call, we're going to need to have you join their list.
Okay.
So you send a contact request to American Freedom Radio.
There you go.
And otherwise, if you wish to use a phone with a dialing mechanism somehow attached to it,
the number one more time is 218-339-8525.
Okay, I lied.
Two more times.
218-339-8525.
Okay, for those who have a different sense of rhythm,
because I think it's an even set of numbers there when you do the area code,
it would be 21-83-39-8525.
21-83-39-8525.
218-339-8525.
Or send a contact request on Skype to American Freedom Radio, and you spell it just like it sounds.
And that should leave us – that leaves the soft underside open, right?
Right now we are open and waiting.
So in the meantime, Chuck, I want to just maybe bring up the point of summing up what we did the last time on roughly 18 episodes,
what we called episodes or sonic events, is basically if anyone listens to that
and you were to categorize it, it would be a guide, a traveler's guide to planet Earth.
A good traveler's guide tells you what to expect from the culture, a little bit of their history,
what is pleasant and what to avoid, right?
So perhaps –
Just for clarification, real quick, sorry.
Just for clarification, if you're looking for American Freedom Radio on Skype,
the Skype ID is AFR and then the word one, O-N-E, AFR1.
That will be the correct Skype contact to search for.
I just wanted to interject that, dot one, AFR dot one.
So AFR, these are the literal letters, ready?
AFR and then a dot, you know, that thing we used to call a period, a dot, and the word one, O-N-E, AFR dot one.
Okay.
Good.
So we got that clarified.
Great.
Yes, wanted to make sure we clarified that.
We are encouraging input.
So we want to make this as easy as possible.
Well, we're encouraging input, but we're also encouraging clarification, I think.
And this is absolutely necessary when trying to communicate.
I think communication without clarity is what other than static noise, you know,
the interruption of silence for, well, no good purpose.
Excuse me for saying that, but that's how I feel a lot of times when I listen to certain other people talk,
who I will not mention by name.
Yeah, but Chuck, that goes along with all the justified savagery on the civilizations
or societies on this planet.
They've justified irrational behavior somehow, and they just keep doing it.
That's why I mentioned earlier, if you listened to the last Sonic Episodes,
you and I did together, anything pretty much that I've put out,
it's really metaphorically a guide to those visiting this planet,
because the people obviously in this planet don't want to know.
When I say obviously, it's because it's, you know, how many times do you hear about,
well, we need change, we need to change the world, right?
Well, guess what?
The world's going to change.
It's just that you're not going to be a part of that.
You're going to be on the tail end of the change, not on the front end.
And even when you're on the front end,
there are impetuses that have been put in place way before you were born that are affecting it.
So in other words, discussing the primary sources of things, I believe,
and what things are based on is the critical maybe clarification, right, moment.
But I know that the word clarification could be used in both senses here,
the caller and also what we're trying to say, perhaps callers calling in.
But nonetheless, I'm sure no one's called in yet, but we'll just carry on.
What do you think?
Yeah, absolutely.
And you know what?
We can do that whether a caller decides to join or not.
So it's fine if you don't want to, but I would certainly love to hear from people
and see what they have to say because, well, I'm just a glutton for punishment.
So, okay.
Well, you know, keeping it simple is really where it's at.
And I have several wagers out there that it's going to be very difficult for it to have anyone call
that's even slightly rational these days.
But the idea is let's just say it's just a basic idea.
Let's try it.
You know, that was suggested.
If you and I are going to do something again, let's make it more, let's say,
inviting the public into it, public however you want to spell that.
It sounds just like it is.
But nonetheless, you know, do you want to maybe think for a moment about things perhaps since the last time we spoke
and now and how things are pretty much the way we've discussed them and why?
Well, one might say that one of the interesting changes is the rise in the populist politician,
the rise in sentimentality over substance that many people have observed, including myself.
It seems to be, well, accelerating.
You know, these are my observations, mind you.
But is this something that is a surprise to you?
Well, I find everything to be in line as I imagined it to be.
Not really.
It's not a surprise.
It's just more of the distraction and the confusion that's been lingering for this part of this time period.
In other words, the sympathy and all that and the rise that you mentioned,
you notice that it doesn't lead to much.
Let's use the election, for example, this sense of, let's say, hope and dominion over the country.
And then you see when it starts to take place, it's pretty much the same as it was before, right, with minor changes.
Because this is a period of tension and distraction that will start to change in what's called the spring of 2018.
And by the way, let me just throw in the lawful day, if that's all right with you.
Well, you know, if you notice, I normally give the date at the beginning of my show,
but I don't necessarily do that when you and I get together because at some point I generally say to you,
actually, Greek, tell us what day it is.
Because, well, we're not really, you know, that thing that I often say is allegedly a calendar.
Okay.
Here we go.
Well, the calendar – well, the date – here's before it's clarified.
The day is lawful.
The date is legal.
Now we just lost 90% of the audience.
The date is a legal construct that, let's say, a corporation sets up for, you know, let's say you work at IBM.
You work on Green Day, the date of the green, red, blue, purple, and you take off on white, black and, you know, whatever.
The PAPL work schedule, known as the Gregorian calendar, is not a timepiece.
It's just a work schedule.
The day is lawful.
In other words, the whales, the fish, the tigers, the bees, the rivers, the human body, the dogs, the cats, the birds, the mice,
the planet goes on the day, the lawful day.
And that is ruled by the sun, the moon, and the stars.
So what that would put us, roughly, by observation, it appears to be around the 26th day of the 10th month.
So right now, on the – what I call the pagan or the – because, by the way, the pope, the papacy is a pagan – well, anyway,
this is for those visiting the Earth Guide.
We could cover it again.
It is pretty far behind.
When you look at disem meaning 10, it's what they call the 8th, right?
And it's really the 26th of the 10th month, 10th moon.
So what that means is that if you look at December 8th, what they call on the PAPL work schedule, last year, December,
if you were almost a week off, so whatever the birds, the fish, the planets, the moon, the sun was doing, you're a week off.
So if you're working in fishing, agriculture, medicine, pretty much any field that requires dealing with natural objects,
you're pretty confused by now, I'm sure.
But yeah, so in other words, lawfully, it's about the 26th of the 10th, and this has nothing to do with what you believe in.
This is reality.
Let's just bring up a point.
I was kind of bringing in the point of the election.
Maybe we could discuss that a little bit just to – because this is for the record, not the election, but what's happening.
Well, just a second because I want to get into that for sure.
But I think we can let that wait because we do have a caller on the line, and I'd like to bring them in, as I promised,
because I try to stick to what I say.
I want to bring them in as soon as possible, so let's do that.
We have 764 Area Code.
You're on the air with Ocelli and the Greek.
Hi, Ocelli.
Hi, Greek.
It's a pleasure to hear you guys back on.
I take it like a breath of fresh air, and I'm happy to hear you guys again.
I've never heard no one else anywhere else speak on these matters to such a level and degree, so profound and eloquent.
So I'd appreciate – you know, I'd definitely appreciate it.
So I'm back once again joining you guys and seeing what I can research, you know, when I'm home alone or whatnot.
But I was curious, since I enjoy being around when I hear the Greek speak,
if there was any direct way of me contributing to the Greek just to kind of support him along,
if, you know, if he felt that he's willing to accept it, I would like to be able to contribute to him directly.
If there's any way I can do that or anyone else, I might want to do that just to, you know, for you guys to let us know how.
I would appreciate that as well.
But that's about it for me now.
I thank you guys once again.
Thank you.
Well, the Greek in an easy way would be on the previous Sonic Project, which was – there's a courtesy website,
and it's called Uncommon Radio, and you just put in uncommonradio.com, and there's an email there.
And I'm looking forward to hearing from you again.
Sounds wonderful.
Very generous or gracious.
And, Chuck, your contact info?
Oh, well, he mentioned, you know, contributing to you directly, so I was staying out of that.
You know, my website, which I announce all the time, is ocelli.com, O-C-H-E-L-L-I.com.
Of course, I accept, you know, support and interaction input from the listener regardless of what Sonic Project I am, you know, engaged in.
So, you know, feel free to visit there and do appreciate your interest as well.
But basically, the gentleman wanted to know about supporting you, so I was going to just –
The best place to contact the Greek would be at uncommonradio.com.
It hasn't gotten that many hits, so it doesn't show up very high on the search engine query,
so it helps to put in www.uncommonradio, just like it sounds, .com.
It's a courtesy website.
You'll pretty much find just some archive material and an email there, and that's pretty much it.
The reason I do that is because years ago, if you worked in a field, let's say, and someone asked you, do you have a card?
Remember those days?
And if you didn't have one, you look kind of like unprepared.
So these days, if you say you're doing radio or speaking publicly anyway, they say, what's your website?
And if you don't have one, it's a little awkward.
So that's the only reason I have it up.
I don't really produce any writing or put any treatises or discussions.
There's also someone, a listener a while back, that did a Just Greek Speak blog
or Just Greek Speak blog spot that has actually put up some things there as well.
So, yeah, I appreciate it.
We're going to try to continue these discussions with Chuck a little further,
maybe get into more things that weren't discussed, for example, like the pranking that's going on,
a little bit more on how everything is debased and the justified savagery on this planet right now.
And we're not going to be discussing some conspiracy in Ivory Towers,
but we're going to show or I would like to illustrate how it is the everyday common man that is enabling this
and why it is not going to change because it is the everyday man enabling it.
And the only solution is to set yourself apart from it just as if you worked in the sewer
or just as if you had a job working with high voltage power lines.
You are subject to danger every moment of your life on this planet and how to deal with it in a peaceful way.
And also enjoy the wonderful things that are on this planet.
Right.
Well, lay it on us.
I mean, I don't think anyone else with such objectivity is commenting and informing as such anywhere else.
But, Chuck, you're good at what you do, too, talking on the air.
I appreciate you, too.
So I wish you guys good night and I'll listen as I can.
Take care.
All right.
Thank you so much.
So, again, you know that number.
It's 218-339-8525.
And as promised, I will introduce you into the conversation as soon as I can.
So, you know, you were beginning to talk about the election before I introduced the caller in.
And I dare say that I feel kind of pranked because here's where you and I will agree.
Not much really changed.
You know, I make the facetious comment that, wow, a rich white man got into the White House.
Headline.
You know, what are we talking about here, Greek?
How about you break it down?
Well, we're talking about a black family being evicted and a white family moving in.
Basically.
You ever think of it that way?
But, I mean, that's from the – but here's the point.
The point is there is no point to this.
And whether we agree on it or not may not be as relevant as are we giving a good report, right?
You might be a reporter working for, let's say, an agency, a media agency,
and the chief editor sends you out to do a story on something that may not be your specialty
or may not want to do.
You still have to give a good report, right?
So the report on this was this is a time period that anyone can look up, by the way,
if you spend a decade researching it or listen to some previous sonic events.
That will be ending around the fall of 2017 and the spring of 2018.
You're going to see a new building up period.
Now, what's interesting, the reason I brought up the election is because if you see how it was sold, right,
which we don't need to get into discussion on that.
That's already been hammered on everyone for almost a year.
You will see that around the 2018 period by summer when things grow,
that will be roughly the middle of that term, right, or near the middle of that term,
almost a year and a half if not into it, right?
And what you will see then typically in the middle of the term is when things tend to settle in
because whenever you have an administration, a bureaucratic form of government,
things that are enacted usually take months if not a year to put in place, minimum, right?
You've seen this through historical, you know,
unless there's a major emergency act that's signed in and mobilized very quickly, right?
Typically it takes a long time.
Realistically, yeah, realistically, look, it takes time to put things into position.
It doesn't matter if it's a military action or if it is a social change, a change of facility,
a business coming into existence or going out of business.
All of these things do not occur, well, in the blink of an eye, so to speak.
So usually it's six months to start a war, usually, you know, once they say they're going to do it, right?
Okay, so we're looking at this much on that.
So what's been propagandized by this administration is more of a nationalistic,
less international meddling in affairs, more of a stable introvert view on the policies, right?
Okay, what we've discussed here with you as well is when this new time period begins around 2018,
you're going to see things being put in place for the formation of a Middle East Union,
which will be in full swing within the end of that seven-year period,
which now let's not get confused with the math here,
but the Middle East Union will probably be in position around what you call 2025, 2024, the fall 2025, let's say.
Okay, that's when that seven-year period starts.
So this next seven-year period, which, by the way,
if they do hold true to even a third of what they said about the current, let's say,
let's mention the name Trump administration, by the 2018 springtime,
they will have already retracted many of the activities that were put out in the past eight,
what would you say, eight, maybe 12 years, maybe more, maybe 14 years since 9-11?
Exactly, exactly, possibly up to 15 years, yes.
Okay, so that will start to retract and allow the formation of these things to be put in place.
Now, the thing is maybe this is now we're discussing chess, not checkers.
Most humans like to hear checkers and tic-tac-toe.
When we're discussing the aspects of chess,
each piece has multiple movements and different ranks and category and importance, right?
So what you're going to see right now also ending, we've discussed this before, around the 2018,
is this period of distraction and frustration.
And the purpose of this past seven years, which will end around 2018,
you're into the sixth or so year of it right now, five and a half, six years almost,
is distraction and frustration.
It doesn't seem like anything can be done and it's just distraction and just making a mess,
kind of like spilling milk or babies pooping in their diapers or things like that,
or a dog leaving a pyramid in the living room kind of thing, you know what I mean?
That's all it's been for the past seven years.
No one is paying attention.
You're not supposed to.
But around 2018, there's going to be a flip of a switch
where some of this cosmic censorship is going to be lifted
and people are going to start to want to learn more about things, if that makes any sense.
Well, it makes perfect sense to me.
And really, what I think about that, you know,
what I said was sort of a facetious statement regarding the rich white man coming into the White House.
I think that's an accurate report as things stand.
Okay.
Credit rich, yeah.
Yeah, credit rich, right.
Because there is no money.
That's another point we've tried to bring.
Right.
But rich in the, well, in the most colloquial sense, right?
I mean, this is a guy who would, if you were to say, is this a rich man or a poor man,
most people would observe that Donald Trump is a rich, rich guy, you know, real simple.
Now, does that mean that he actually possesses anything of actual value?
Well, now that's questionable, isn't it?
Yeah, but that leads to another discussion.
Do you know that there still hasn't been any viable economic discussion?
I've heard, whether it's mainstream or alternative media,
you know, there's not one economic critic or reviewer that has anything that's accurate.
I get people say, you got to listen to this guy, and I go to a YouTube, and I'm like, are you joking?
There's some pretty popular financial, what do you call it, talking heads, and they've got members and all that.
And, you know, none of them ever discuss that it's a credit-based economy.
And recently, I had some correspondence with someone on – they were going to have someone discussing the economy,
and I said, well, it's a waste of time because there is no one discussing the economy accurately.
Ask them what a credit-based economy is at the opening of the show,
and you'll just pretty much destroy the entire show, and they did, and the person just fell on their face.
They couldn't answer, right?
Well, let me interrupt you with this thought for a second because on one of my recent shows,
I was a little startled by somebody that literally said that there is actually a credit-based economy.
And that this is a delusion about what is debt and what is owed and all of these things,
and I was a bit startled because the rest of the conversation seemed to not be in line with this.
Right.
But they sort of just recently came to this understanding.
Do you think it's possible that the emergence of this knowledge,
the emergence of people actually trying to learn about these realities, let's call them –
It will show itself now.
It's beginning to, right?
Yeah, just like – well, just think about – remember back in the days when movies were almost worth seeing,
like, you know, we're talking like maybe a long time ago, maybe.
You'd sit down for a two-hour feature and they show you a three-minute trailer for next year's movie, right?
Right.
It's kind of like that.
So people have these little moments of clarity.
But the reason I brought up this topic now for maybe for a short discussion
or we can go on with it a little bit more is that when people start thinking in terms of wealth,
they don't realize that the credit system is a great equalizer.
And what is happening is – or what is going to happen is that in the future,
the legal society is also going to fall from prominence
because they are the ones that have instigated the concept of debt, right?
Only an attorney – now, here's the other thing.
Someone also had sent me some information, sending me some stuff about how it's a debt-based economy.
And I said everything that you're sending me is not in the paperwork of any financial institution.
Those are what's called memorandum that are put out.
So if you're a banker, what you do is you activate the credit system to provide the industry you're working in.
But when you're dealing with outsiders, you start using the word debt as a memorandum because they don't know.
In other words, they're not initiated, right?
So you will never find any industrial financial paperwork that has the word debt on it anywhere.
They're either performing or non-performing instruments, right?
And you have things like liquidity, fungible, asset, liability, never debt, right?
But when you're communicating with the uninitiated or the public or the press or guess what?
The university, right?
You use the term debt as a loose memorandum.
It has no legal bearing.
So people have been convinced of these things.
Kind of like it has the same validity as, let's say, the tooth fairy or things like that.
But people know it's not really there, but they still use it.
But the problem with the debt is it's a level of pranking.
And that's one thing we've never really got into together is that the level of pranking on this planet has –
pranking, by the way, means a ludicrous trick.
That's the definition of it, a simple – what do you mean by pranking?
It's a ludicrous trick.
The level of pranking has gotten to the point and has been for millennia on this planet that you can lose your life to a prank.
It's not just simply someone spraying – putting itching powder on you or offering you a seat with a thumbtack or a whoopee cushion.
They've actually – the pranks have risen to the point where they can either lock you up in a cage or kill you.
So it is a very dangerous place because of that.
But anyway, that's – on the economic talk, I would say there still is no viable discussions on the economy at all.
I wouldn't say there's any place you can go other than source material.
And this is the same for the medical stuff.
This is the same – Chuck, we brought up the calendar, the Pope's work schedule.
If someone said, Greek, I don't understand what you're – maybe I'm censored.
I don't understand what's going on with the days you're talking about.
I say, well, before you maybe discover what you want, maybe – and you don't know what that is exactly.
You've heard of the process of elimination, right, Chuck?
Maybe discover what you don't want for sure and start narrowing it down, right?
So if we look at the date, today is what they call December 8th in this part of the world on this electronic convention, December 2016.
And next year, what they call 2017, November 8th is what they call a Friar's Day.
So it's not a Thursday or Thor's Day.
And if you go back to 2015, let's go through this real quick.
This is just a short exercise.
December 8th was what they call a Totten's Day or Tuesday.
So is December 8th a Tuesday, a Thursday or a Friday?
It's neither.
You've got to realize it's really far off.
So maybe realizing that there's something really wrong will get people motivated to learning what's right.
Because guess what, folks?
You really don't know what the right thing to do is.
You really don't.
All things that are made or created have instructions.
You can go out, Chuck, and buy a toaster or a blow dryer and I don't know about a screwdriver or so.
But when you open the package, they give you a little instruction manual, don't they?
Right.
And one of the first things that you see, let's say, on a blow dryer or toaster is all the warnings.
Like, you know, this could kill you.
Don't drop in water, you know, and all this other stuff, right?
Oh, yeah.
Or little pictures of somebody sticking a fork in it where they slashed through it, indicating don't do this.
Don't do this.
Yeah, stuff like that.
So we have access to information for thousands of years of what to do and what not to do.
But no one really, I want to say no one.
There are groups of people in the legal society and the religious societies and the scientific society that say that they're supposed to be pursuing knowledge,
but they have somehow discarded everything that has come, everything that was before them.
In other words, no one is really looking at anything that is less than 100 years old with accuracy or clarity.
Well, but the purpose of that I think is something that you already mentioned,
which is you don't use particular language with the uninitiated.
Now, I don't want to gloss over that statement because that is the problem with the language, isn't it?
That's the problem with how we're communicating about these things at this time because why?
Go ahead and explain that.
What do you mean exactly?
Because you sort of passed right by that.
Well, let's use the colloquial term.
The initiation is when you're brought in.
We initiate something as you're bringing something in from the beginning, right?
So it's like you've started at the beginning, square one, and you move your way through the entire process or procedure or group, right?
So how many times have you heard of, let's say, someone in the medical industry or a legal industry or religious industry,
they're very altruistic and they're genuine about what those things represent.
And once they join that field, they find out it has nothing to do with what they thought it was
and what they represent it is, right?
Have you ever heard of a doctor or a lawyer or a banker getting disillusioned
or someone in the education field, you know, they wanted to do these things,
but they found out once they got initiated into the group, it was really nothing about that, you see.
And once you see what is known, let's say, going back to the economic aspect that there's a concept of money,
but what has happened is being lawful, just like timekeeping, right?
And just like anything else really, food, clothing, most of the things that you see are not lawful, right?
You're not supposed to, for example, with food, take sawdust and add color to it and say that it's breakfast cereal.
That's not lawful, right?
You can't say it's grain that's lying, but you can call it breakfast cereal, let's say.
It's up to you if you want to eat it.
So these things are, again, they can be fashioned as a criticism against society,
but I think fashioning them, keeping one's perspective out of it
and putting the information together and rationalizing it so if someone were to visit this planet,
they would have a pretty good guide on what is going on here, right?
Because like I mentioned earlier, you can't really go to your typical surface-dwelling earth inhabitant
with 99% of the stuff you and I discuss on air.
They either implode or they can't hear it, right?
Now, that 1% leaves you a large amount of people, I think around 70 million, right?
So I'm being very liberal.
It might even be fewer.
It's really a one out of a million deal to really be able to pull yourself out of the situation
and see what is really going on based on your senses.
Even though your senses can be deceived, you have to fine-tune them.
Like if anyone who's had a turntable with a cartridge and a needle, that has to be fine-tuned in a line,
just like cap stands on the old tape machines and triple beam balances have to be scales, watches, clocks.
These things, they work, but they need tuning, right?
A guitar, an instrument needs tuning when it's out of tune.
So what you use to tune yourself is the information that has been memorialized in the past about anything.
And I'll invite people to consider, for example, this is a general statement, and as it sounds very general,
but it's actually, you will find it to be true if you do the homework.
And I'm going to say this, Chuck, and I believe I've said it with you once before,
is you know that everything that could have been known or was already known by the late 19th century
regarding the law field, the scientific field, the medical field, and all these other things,
think about that for a moment.
Everything that could have been known was already known by the end of the 19th century, not 20th century.
We're talking 1800s now.
So what happened?
Why was there in the 20th century this new emergence of research and discovery, as it was called?
Why, if everything was already known?
Think about it.
Yeah, not only that, but I mean if that was the time when everything was known,
how was that not preserved and simply just passed on to the next generation?
It is.
Going back, here's the crux of the matter.
Are you ready?
How many times have you heard the Greeks say, oh, I see still no one's paying any attention?
When I mean no one, I mean statistically.
You probably won't meet anyone, that is, but it's safe to say that there are others that are paying attention,
but you won't meet any of them if you are yourself.
That's how few there are.
Give me an example.
I think I brought up J.J. Thompson with you.
You know the term physicist and scientist?
That didn't exist before the 20th century.
So when you go to a Wikipedia page and look up Isaac Newton, you've heard of Isaac Newton, right?
A very common name.
Of course.
Yeah, Newtonian physics.
Well, they list him as a physicist.
Well, that's bullshit because that term did not exist back then.
All these men were not physicists or scientists.
They were natural philosophers.
So what does that mean now?
If you call yourself something, Chuck, or you are known as such, and now let's say 200 years in the future,
they have a different name for it.
Is it fit and proper to change what you were described yourself as to a modern term,
or should you preserve that term and then maybe in parentheses put the modern term next to it?
You see my point?
Yeah, I would think that it would be more proper to place the modern term, you know.
Secondary.
Right.
As secondary because it is more relatable, and in parentheses,
this is what you're supposed to take from this particular label, let's just say,
that is not in its right context at this time.
It would seem to me that that's the right way to go.
Right, just for the matter of preservation.
Because if you don't do that, it will slip so far away that, let's say, if you had 30 years,
the children's textbooks would read that Columbus discovered America using an iPhone.
Could you imagine that?
You might be old enough to see it if you had that much time, right?
Right.
Think about it.
How ludicrous would that be?
But how ludicrous, even more ludicrous, is it to accept it?
You see, what's happening is people's shallow thinking is getting them to dive off the deep end.
Right.
So let's go back to J.J. Thompson, give you an example how everything was known.
It's very easy to look up J.J. Thompson, the letter J, the letter J,
and then Thompson, however you want to spell it, it will come up.
And he has several books, about 900 to 1,200 pages thick,
on recent discoveries on electricity and magnetism is one of them.
Okay.
1890s.
And he discovered and was able to prove that what you call weight or momentum is independent of mass.
Now, that doesn't sound right because if I drop a brick on your foot,
that's going to feel different than if I drop a feather on your foot, right, Chuck?
Absolutely.
Because of the momentum and the weight.
He's saying that momentum and that weight that you're feeling has nothing to do with one being a brick
or the other one having to be a feather in the actual mass that it is.
What it has to do with is when an object starts to move,
these electrical lines of force that are in the environment connect to it.
And when you want to start it or stop it, these electrical lines of force don't readily disconnect,
so it gives you the illusion that certain materials are heavier than others
because there's more of these electrical lines of force.
See, when someone drops a brick on your foot and someone drops a feather,
you would rather they drop the feather than the brick, right?
Why? Because the brick has more electrical lines of force attached to it.
Think about it that way now.
Doesn't that change your whole paradigm?
Well, yeah, because…
In other words, so hold on.
If you reversed it and you removed some of the electrical lines of force from the brick
and you added more to the feather, now the brick wouldn't hurt your foot.
The feather would.
Now it becomes really combobulated in your mind, right?
Do you see what I mean?
These invisible lines of force.
So he was able to disconnect the lines of force from material
and be able to create instant start and instant stop with no momentum and no weight in 1895.
And this man lived until 1940-something, and he was a prolific writer and speaker,
but he went silent after this discovery.
Now let me ask you, Chuck, have you heard of in the modern contemporary culture of flying objects
that instantly start and instantly stop and make right turns at 9,000 miles an hour
and things called – I'm not going to say the word.
You know what it is, right?
This technology was made on the benchtop and by others by J.J. Thompson in the 1890s.
This is not science fiction, folks.
What happened to it?
Has it been brought forward?
It's been brought forward that I can see it and others can see it,
but maybe you haven't, Chuck, and others haven't, but now they've heard it again, you see.
That's why when we get – do you ever notice when we get together and speak,
we bring up things that are just so blaringly obvious or direct and give enough reference,
like that you can go find it.
Do you think I gave enough – sometimes I get criticism.
I don't give enough source material references.
Do you think it's easy enough with today's modern electronic convention
just by giving a name of a person and what to look for,
someone can find it on the Internet if it's available?
Oh, absolutely.
That's all you need, right?
Now we can get into a pedantic, redundant conversation about how the technology works,
but that's unnecessary for the two hours that we're here, you see.
So everything –
No, that's true, but let me just add something here.
This concept of force as opposed to mass is easily observable.
Something I've taken a lot of time to study is the impact of a bullet, all right?
It's not about the mass of the bullet.
It's not about the weight of the bullet.
It's actually about the velocity which is applied to it by force.
So it makes perfect sense to me that this would be correct.
Also, you have to understand the materials.
Like you cannot – for example, you cannot have an aluminum projectile
penetrate a steel target of equal mass.
The aluminum will always fail.
It will vaporize.
It will go into the surface.
You know what I'm bringing up here, right?
Oh, 9-11.
Don't talk about it.
Okay.
All right.
But, you know, since you – yeah, what would you call that?
Ballistics research?
Ballistics forensics?
Yeah.
Things like that?
Okay.
At this point, yeah, it's ballistics.
Ballistics generally covers it, yeah.
No, like we both said it with a Jersey accent there.
All right.
So the point here is this.
Here's something that I give advice to, and this is nothing on you, but younger people,
when they get into what the CIA has called the conspirology
or conspiracy theories and things, pull yourself out of that
and look at really what's going on, right?
Like let's bring up the JFK investigation.
You know, you don't want to get wrapped up in too much what's been fed the public.
You want to kind of like defrag and go back and look at it with fresh eyes,
which is nearly impossible because it was such a long time ago,
and there's so much on it, right?
Right.
But here's the point I'd make with something like that in 9-11 or whatever,
but 9-11 is very different.
9-11 is quite obvious if you study the architecture of buildings,
which no one is talking about.
But with the JFK assassination, it's very simple.
When an assassination or the murder of someone in public has taken place,
that is an art form known as the assassins,
and the assassins were people, I believe, in the Middle East.
There were a culture, there were a tribe of people that were called that,
and they were very good at it, right?
And now it has been dubbed as, you know, someone who does such a thing.
Right, and I briefly discussed this actually in the previous show I did.
Oh, did you?
Okay.
So let's not even get into that,
but the thing that I recently told a young person about the JFK,
I said look up to Ocelli because he's looking at it objectively,
at least the best as you say you would like to,
the only reason I'm saying you look at it objectively is because of how much you've disreferred most of the stuff
that's been going on, meaning not referred to or debunked it, right?
But the point that I made with this young person is the reason why you're not going to find out who killed JFK
is because when whoever did it got the right people.
And they asked me to do the job, and they said, well, what do you mean by the right people?
Well, the right people are those that won't get caught.
Exactly.
Right?
Yeah.
So leave it alone because that is a situation that was put together that is so tight that anything that is done that way,
there was actually a heist that was done, I think the JFK heist that was still very much like that, several things.
If you get the right people to do it, what makes them the right people is they're not going to get caught.
We're not talking about the Patsy's and all that.
That's part of the program.
Right.
I actually have firsthand testimony from someone in the San Francisco area in the early 90s
who was invited to be a Patsy for the assassination of Bill Clinton.
They were trying to do back then.
They said, hey, you'd make a good Patsy.
I was like, you've got to be kidding me.
I don't believe I'm hearing this.
So you've got to sometimes look at things that are wrapped up and nefarious.
And if you consider the nefarious forces that are controlling the planet, not the planet,
but the activities of mankind to be the predominant ones now, you're pretty accurate.
It's pretty correct to surmise that.
Absolutely.
And you know what the thing is here?
We're about to come up against the break.
And I think this is an excellent point to stop.
Why?
Because when we discuss what is nefarious versus what is benevolent, we may not be drawing the correct line.
And I know you've spoken about this in the past, but I do believe it is worth reiterating, if you will,
because a lot of people can't make a logical narrative out of what they're seeing emerge.
And the reason is you're not.
Cosmic.
Well, it's cosmic.
It's a lot of things going on.
And when you're dealing with aspects of great power, whether it's good or bad, you touch it, you're fried, right?
That's it.
Right.
So you're going to have to be very careful either way.
But let's see if we're doing this right.
Before we pose a liability on the sonic level, nefarious, adjective, Latin nefarious, wicked, abominable, impious.
There you go.
That's exactly it.
And we will be right back with Ocelli in the Greek reloaded here on American Freedom Radio.
It's bound to get just a little more deep.
I assure you.
Stay tuned.
I like an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions, running my companies, and I hated feeling groggy and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret.
The powers that be want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride.
Our brains are under siege and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve, a revolutionary breakthrough in a category of cognitive enhancers called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself at dnaevolvesample.com.
That's dnaevolvesample.com.
Supplies are limited, so go to dnaevolvesample.com right now.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at mpusa.org.
mpusa.org introduces three brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates, and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at mpusa.org.
We all know that they're not telling us the truth.
So stand up for your rights, demand the real medicine, and your right to use it and grow it.
This is Rick Sensen, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
What about show business?
Show business, completely dishonest, corrupt, and full of shit, but in a nice way.
Plenty of expensive drugs and perverted sex.
If you're going to be full of shit, might as well enjoy your work.
Then you have the media.
Not just the news media, let's include them all.
The media are almost literally exploding with bullshit.
Because they're located right at the crossroads of all the other bullshit.
The media are made up of equal parts advertising, politics, business, public relations, and show business.
These people are sitting right at bullshit junction.
There's enough bullshit in the media for Texas to open a branch office.
And you still have enough left over to start two law firms and a Christian bookstore.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us with free education?
Well, that's obviously effective, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America...
All the information they provide is free?
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, man?
Exploiting commonplace corruption?
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice?
Bringing light to important information nobody else does?
They never censor, hang up, or cut off their guests?
Well, that's no fun, is it?
They created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative, and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shows and scum?
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from,
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable people without a voice,
bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream, and alternative media shows and scum,
what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are.
American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
the only broadcast information no other...
And the second hour begins, according to that wind-up toy that we call a clock.
Ocelli in the Greek here on American Freedom Radio, originating from AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Yes, indeed, we are reloaded.
Now, where we left it off in the first hour
was that I kind of posed to the Greek the idea that maybe that which is seen as positive and negative
are, what, equally as damaging, and I wanted him to continue on that line of thought.
Oh, yeah, that's great.
You know, let's use the JFK metaphor and the American society as a metaphor.
Let's say we're just visiting this planet and looking over what happened to JFK
and what has happened to the American society at large, right?
What we could easily walk away from, I know most people don't want to hear this.
Let's say, do we want to start with the American society?
Or do you want to start with JFK himself?
Well, if you wouldn't mind, I would like to talk about what emerged in the aftermath
because the murder of one human being, if I put it in context, is generally not the big concern, right?
Well, no, it's not.
Okay, what's interesting, that's symbolic
because if they really wanted to go after the presidency, that could have been done legally, right?
It could have been done not necessarily with one man,
but actually taking out the geographical location as well as done in war, let's say, right?
So this was a level of, let's say, of surgical effect, right, to create an effect.
But before, let me just go into a thought real quick.
JFK was not the most righteous man by looking at his own personal life of adultery
and by looking at his family life, his father being in political position
and what they were involved with also.
So they were not pristine in that position.
So maybe something came back to haunt them from that.
Let's just say that's perhaps, I'm not a researcher on that,
but you could see the man was not the most righteous or the most pristine.
His intentions during the office were perhaps otherwise, right, openly.
Well, and the other thing to consider here is the not-so-open secret,
which a lot of people don't recognize when they think about a great conspiracy
jumping up and biting the leader who is sitting there innocently.
The point of fact is that he participated in exactly those types of operations.
He signed off on things that could have been seen as the type of operation
that might have allegedly taken him out.
In fact, one could objectively view it as fair play.
Sure, sure, right.
And instead of moving on him legally or judicially, they opposed him as they did.
Right.
Eliminating him.
As I said, participated in as well.
Most glaring example would be the operations against Fidel Castro
that occurred a leader of another nation, the attempts to kill him.
These things happened under Kennedy's watch as well.
I mean, you can't deny that.
Just not to go off, but Cuba was a very interesting thing that most people don't understand.
That was used as a marketing test society before things were brought to the U.S.
Like you've heard of products like Ajax and things like that.
They were tried in Cuba.
If the Cubans liked them, then the corporations invested in marketing them in the U.S.
And also, as the stories go, if you wanted next year's Cadillac, you went to Florida,
took the boat over to Cuba, you got next year's Cadillac because they got it first, right,
to work out the bugs.
So then it flipped over to Castro,
and I don't think that was done as independently as we're being told either.
But let's just flip over now to the American society.
What's interesting about the American society is ever since its inception,
it's basically a culture that has to have someone that they hate to motivate them.
Let me say it again.
The American culture has been based on, from its beginning, as you would say,
the beginning of the 19th century, a culture that has to have someone to hate.
It was either the monarchy, the Indians, the Spanish, the Germans, the Japanese,
then the Russians, and now they're trying to bring in – now it's Islam.
They always have to have someone to hate.
Right, which is what I often talk about, and I break it down into more childish terms
because I think it needs to be understood that way.
I call it the boogeyman syndrome.
The boogeymen were anarchists.
The boogeymen were the Spaniards.
The boogeymen were the Japanese, the Germans.
They were etc., etc., and this is not only tactically useful from a military standpoint,
but the society is literally driven, it seems, by this need for –
I know boogeyman may be one of those childish terms once again.
Well, it's a juvenile mentality on this planet that's adequate.
I think so as well, yeah.
Yeah, but you see the manipulation that's required to keep this culture of hate
or the boogeyman in place is one that is so used to being manipulated
that the actual assassination, although it was nefarious,
is also part of that manipulation and would be accepted because they accepted the rest, you see,
just like 9-11 was accepted, Oklahoma City, and all this stuff.
The other thing that sets JFK apart from Oklahoma City and 9-11
and other major things like Pearl Harbor is that it's really difficult to technically access
how or who did the JFK assassination because of the abscondence of evidence
because it was one of these momentary things.
It's just a human that was shot with a rifle or a projectile of some kind
that are both very, very common where if you look at other events,
let's say like Pearl Harbor, if you look at the Murrow building, the 9-11, things like that,
the things that were put in place prior to those events happening
are very easy to technically access today to really figure out what happened
where the JFK makes it set apart because it's very difficult to access
because the evidence did not exist before the assassination, and it didn't exist after,
so you have to look in that short moment of time to find everything you're looking for, right?
Right, right.
You know, 9-11 is very easy, the Murrow building is very easy, other events are very easy.
If you start at the foundation, like 9-11, what happened?
Well, buildings came down.
Airplanes went in, allegedly, and buildings came down.
Well, no one is discussing this group mentality.
I've also brought up, by the way, just to throw in here, look up Gustave Le Bon,
a L-E-B-O-N 1895 book called The Crowd and how the crowd mentality is formed,
but no one is discussing the architecture of 9-11.
They just show you this very simple popular mechanics,
computer animation of these floors buckling and that, no, that doesn't work.
No one is discussing these other events, like Pearl Harbor.
Why are there ships still left on the bottom there?
Aren't there EPA laws that those dregs would be considered environmental hazards?
Why were they quickly memorialized to be left as tombs?
Why?
Very, very simple.
So all of these other things that people still can't wrap their heads around are simple
if you go find what things are based on and how things function.
And then you have to understand there's a level of hypocrisy that society goes through.
Like, for example, the EPA with water,
if you've got more than 700 parts per million dissolved solids in water, it's considered toxic.
So if you drop it on the sidewalk, it's a $400 fine, right?
But yet the water that comes out of the taps out of Phoenix and places in Nevada is well above that.
Wait a second, right?
You see?
In certain parts of the year because they run it through concrete channels
and the concrete channels erode and the TDS goes up higher than EPA standards require.
But the thing is here, we wanted to discuss about what's an affair.
You see, this might sound like we just went around going around a merry-go-round at 60 miles per hour discussing these various things.
But you see, there's no clear-cut good and bad here until you figure out what really is going on, what really happened, right?
You know, most people would say a certain thing is bad, but when they look into why it happened, they'll say,
oh, wow, I guess it had to happen, right?
Because why?
Because if it didn't, something worse would have happened, right?
So that is not really the point of the discussion,
but the nefarious and the good being on a level of power on a cosmic level,
let's say cosmic meaning the world, what controls the world.
I think you and I, we got a brief discussion at the break.
People have been led down this juvenile mentality that the good is always pleasant and pleasurable
and the evil or the bad is always displeasurable.
And in reality, it's quite the contrast, right?
How many times have you heard people passing counterfeit money and not knowing it until someone at a store scans the bill
and says this is counterfeit, let's say.
It's not a Federal Reserve notice, right?
It looks very much, but the intent to make that was nefarious, right?
Where, you know, if you're going to counterfeit a hundred note, you don't get a crayon and a dinner napkin, right?
A lot of work goes in to the side of evil, for example,
to make it look like something that is passable and acceptable within the culture.
I'm going to say that again.
Well, yeah, do say it again because this contributes to the seduction,
which is what some people would call it, right, of sort of, you know, it's not a matter of the assault, right?
Evil is not necessarily an assault.
In fact, it's more of, wait, a trick.
In fact, it seems like pranking is a lot more evil than assault if you think about it.
Well, yeah, then there's, well, the assault doesn't have to be violent.
The assault can also be, for example, an end goal.
What is the end goal here?
Let's say, for example, you've got a wallet.
You're walking down the street and someone jumps out from around an alleyway, points a gun to your head,
says give me your wallet or I'm going to shoot you, and you get frightened and you give him the wallet.
Okay, that's an assault that could lead to violence.
Now, I'll give you another scenario.
You've got a wallet.
You're walking down the street and suddenly someone is very friendly and they befriend you only to pickpocket you
and pat you on the back and tell you have a great day.
Now, you were assaulted there, but it was not outward violence, was it?
The end result is the same.
By the time you got home, you had been separated from your wallet either way, right?
One was pleasant and the other one was not, but the pleasant one was complete deception, wasn't it?
Well, but even worse, I think, and here is my commentary and you can correct me,
but even worse I think is not the pickpocket which does it by deception
or even the assault which does it by the oppressive nature, the aggression,
but in reality, I think the worst one here is the individual who convinces you to hand it over against your own best interests.
What do you think of that?
That's the legal society.
That's the religious society.
The religious society and the legal society, when I say legal society, I'm not talking about law form.
It is a law form based on their deity and I'm talking also about the religious society.
It doesn't matter if it's Christian, Jewish, Hindu, Buddhist or whatever.
Those are the ones that go directly towards the mind or the spirit which is the same thing, right?
Mind and spirit, psyche, PSY, prefix, is the mind.
So when you go after the spirit or the mind, that's why it's called a mind-controlled slave will do whatever they're told.
Exactly.
You see?
Those are simple but the nefarious at this point, there's a term in scripture that says there will come a point when mankind will,
everything they consider good is really evil and everything that they consider evil is really good, right?
For example, go to an attorney, any attorney and start discussing law and if you do it for more than five minutes,
they're going to have a look on their eye like they want to put physical violence on you because why?
You thought you can discuss law with an attorney.
They don't know any law because if you're an attorney and you study law,
you will be disbarred or you'll find yourself sleeping on a park bench or eating out of a garbage can.
If you go to a religious figure, it doesn't matter if you've got 15 degrees from divinity school,
if you're the pope himself, a mufti, an imam, a guru or a Buddhist monk,
you start discussing anything that's immemorialized in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
Within five or ten minutes, they will have a look in their face like they want to put physical violence on you.
Why?
Because they don't know anything in that text.
What is going on here?
The same with a doctor.
Go to visit a doctor and what do they do?
They sit you down.
One of the first things they do is they strap a cuff on your arm and they start inflating it to create a block in the limb
to measure something called blood pressure that didn't exist until they inflated the cuff, right?
Right.
No one knows what's going on anymore.
It's just a matter of pranking.
We were going to discuss a little bit of the nefarious and the powers that are good,
almost being equal in power.
Ultimately, I'll say this.
This is all things that I usually reserve for private discussion, but we're having a private discussion.
We probably have four or five listeners anyway.
But when someone does research on what has been memorialized by those ancient stupid people,
those people that came before us, everyone that came before us, those are really ignorant people, right?
But anyway, what they've memorialized for thousands of years regarding evil and good is this,
and I usually reserve this for private conversation,
is that both evil and good come from ultimately the same source, and they both are being used for a purpose.
Yes?
Yes.
You heard me right.
And just like a young child, how many times have we said, at least in the past time that we've been on,
I brought up the notion and I keep referring to the society and the discussion and the thinking as being what?
Juvenile?
And I think that's very accurate, right?
How many times have you seen someone who's a juvenile, let's say, but in their formative years,
you know, between since the time they were born to about eight or nine, seven, eight, nine,
and when do you get your second set of teeth?
Until you get your second set of teeth, you're in what I call the formative years.
How many times have they actually, people in their formative years, little ones,
considered a form of discipline that would bring good, that juvenile individual considers it to be evil on them?
How many times have you heard that if you've ever been around young people, right?
A young person being disciplined will consider that discipline to be evil.
I don't need to eat what you guys eat.
I want to eat chocolate all day, every day, right, or whatever.
You see?
That's good.
You know, if I eat vegetables and meat and, let's say, starches or have whole food, that's evil to me.
You know, I go by my taste.
That's called heresy.
Have you ever heard the term heresy being a heretic?
Of course.
The word heresy is the Greek word aresios, which means what is your personal preference?
So when you hear people being burned at the stake for heresy,
it's because they were following their personal preference instead of the group.
You could look this up.
This is the true.
Now it's been used.
You know, they call someone a heretic, and no one really understands the position of that term.
But the level of heresy that humankind is engaged in in a juvenile sense,
how difficult would it be to engage in things that are evil
and then convincing themselves that they're actually good if you're in that juvenile state?
And that's the state of humanity at this point.
But ultimately—
Well, this is why the truest, most realistic villains anywhere presented
often believe they are the hero of the story, right?
It seems as though all things are inverted,
and I think it's interesting the idea of the child who does not understand
that they're not receiving nutrition.
They're going for what?
That particular thing which does seem desirable.
They're following their juvenile palate.
Only the palate, not the rest of the body.
Right, right.
The rest of the body would instruct them that vegetables, let's just say in general,
would be the preferable thing to ingest, right?
But they want this other stuff because the palate is more excited by it.
It does create a neurological reaction, so on and so forth,
and they're familiar with that, so therefore they desire it.
Yes?
Well, yeah.
It's because it's what they like, what they prefer.
Yeah.
It's a form of heresy.
I just want to jump here for a moment.
I just gave a glance to chat.
Since we haven't had much callers, we're going to interact.
The term pedophile has been coming up often, right, because of what's been going on?
Very often.
I don't know if we've had discussions prior.
Well, I know we didn't have discussions prior,
and you probably were not familiar with things that I've been saying prior to the initial sonic events
that we did almost a year and a half or two years ago, but for a while before that,
one of the things, and I've actually memorialized this,
is to watch out in the future that many things are going to be revealed because we're in the credits,
get it, the credits part of the movie.
What happens in the credits?
You get to see things that are behind the scenes that you didn't see on the screen, right?
That's right.
And this is a manifold, and it's also the end of the movie, but technically the film is still running.
All this stuff, I had more than one individual approach me and said,
Greek, the stuff you've been saying years ago is starting to come true, and I'm like, what?
You have to be specific because I'd say the majority of the things I discuss about are things to come, right?
And they said, well, all this pedophilia with the Pizzagate and all this, and I said,
well, can you please refresh my memory on what you think, you know,
what that has to do with me saying things to come?
And he says, well, no, just because you always mention that, you know,
people will find pedophilia and really the most horrible things, you know,
not only the pedophilia but the destruction of children and the eating of children,
it will be exposed in many circles that people didn't expect it.
And I said, okay, that's fine, but do you remember the rest of the things that I said?
And he said, no.
Well, if you go back to things that I've said, let's say four, five, six, seven, eight, nine years ago,
not only did I say that these things would be exposed as such in places that they didn't expect,
but what else do you think I said, Chuck, and that people miss?
And what I said was when they are exposed, it'll be no big deal to the mass populace.
Why? Because it's the credits.
And this is the part that people miss because people that bring up this topic have a sympathetic investment in the topic, right?
They're not denying it.
Like the everyday Joe on the street will say, oh, this can't be true.
That's fake news, right?
Well, what's interesting about the credits portion is this tells you exactly how the rest of the movie was laid out.
OK, this tells you who's responsible for let's just say visual effects.
Who's responsible for the music?
Who actually played a part in what particular role?
Stuff like that.
And just, you know, for the record, the Pizzagate thing, I am not satisfied is real.
But I will tell you this simply because it is revealed in the credits that somebody created the music.
It doesn't mean that there wasn't music going on during the entire film.
Right.
Well, this is a thousand.
Well, have you heard of a birthday cake?
Have you heard of Santa Claus?
These are things that people do.
And like I mentioned earlier, it's the common man that's the problem, what they're doing, not these people in ivory towers.
But let me just mention one more thing.
The credits thing is very important because it operates on many, many levels and has many facets.
And the reason why I mentioned it's the credits again and people will not do anything about it.
What I say about people not do anything about it.
Do you remember the end of the old Frankenstein movies when the people found out what Dr.
Frankenstein was doing?
What did they do at the end of the movie?
If you remember, they all showed up with pitchforks and torches to stop him, you know, to take over the place.
Right. Yeah.
I was going to say, I don't remember the exact last scene, but I do in the book as well.
Yeah. The people freaked out.
They freak out.
They destroy his lab.
They go after the monster.
This is what the villagers do because now they realize what's been going on.
Right. So now one of the things that I've said is when these things are brought to the revelation,
people will not react because it's the credits again.
But why is the credit so important to see?
During the film, if you talk or stand up or make a disturbance,
everyone tells you to shut up and sit down or get out of the theater.
But during the credits, you notice that people talk and stand up and no one is telling anyone anything
in a reactionary sense, like shut up and sit down.
The credits are rolling. You ever notice that?
Mm hmm. So what you're going to see all the way to the end is really,
really strange stuff and wicked stuff and abominable stuff, whether it's true or not.
At this point, it'll be coming to the forethought of society and people will not react.
Why? Because you're being set up. Right.
Why do you think, for example, how many times have people been in their foremind or forethought,
been made aware of decapitations or heads being cut off?
Not until recently with this ISIS thing in the Middle East. Right.
Now, whether that really happened or not, what they showed us,
because a lot of it is proven to be green screen,
but also there's a lot of boots on the ground that give good testimony that they did do these things
and they do these things. Right. Why is that being put in your mind now?
Because guess what, folks? In the future, in that 2025 period,
that will be commonly accepted not only by that radical aspect of society, but all society.
Why? Maybe we'll leave that for a future discussion and other things as well.
Just like, for example, when 9-11 happened,
it was very easy a minute and a half later to blame it on the Muslims because you were set up with,
what was it, Back to the Future, True Lies,
all these films for 30 or 20 years prior that the Muslims were the bad guys.
And then when it was time to install that image, it was already laid out. Right.
Not just in Hollywood, but don't forget that we had the imagery that was before it in the alleged news media.
You know what? The hostage crisis, the Ayatollah Khomeini, these are maniacs.
This is exactly what is being pushed for decades prior in a lot of circles. Yes.
So what you're seeing now is, take notes, you can discount it or whatever,
but you cannot deny it didn't hit the media. Right.
For example, you can't deny that there's people are discussing pedophilia.
Now, whether it's valid, you know, the actual target, you know,
these guys are doing it is valid or not,
is not as relevant as that it's being brought out into the forefront of people's minds,
of many people's minds. Right. Right. Take notes on them.
Yeah, absolutely. You're being set up.
Even with what it is I do, I felt compelled to address the subject.
And it was an odd thing because I really don't want to cover this topic.
You know, let's give a little guide.
Let's give a little bit of a guide to the people that are going to visit this planet here real quick.
OK, everyone, if you were born here, just, you know, turn off the radio, turn off the speakers.
Not for you. This is for those that are ready to visit this planet.
If you want to know the history of the obsession of children and what he called sexual innuendos and the temples,
I think I mentioned the last time we were on also in ancient times.
Now, this society has been here for thousands of years.
What they did was they prioritized in a divine sense or a cosmic sense.
What is most important? Because that's what we need to watch in order for anything to continue.
Like if you run out of oil in your car, your engine will burn out.
So you've got to make sure your oil level is fine.
Or if you're planting and you're a farmer, you've got to make sure you have seeds for next year or something.
So you have to prioritize certain aspects.
So what was determined was what is the most important organ of the body?
Well, there's many. Well, your lungs, your heart, your skin, all of it's important.
Greek, yeah, but what is the most important organ of the body in order for humanity to continue?
Well, it's the sexual organs, right? The flower, right? Where the seed is, right?
So what they did is they built temples to gynec and phallic symbols and fluids and ceremony based around that
because they were glorifying that event of copulation and all the symbology around it
is because it was considered the most important organ of the body for humanity to continue future generations
because if you lob off everyone's genitalia, guess what? In 40 years, there'll probably be no one left, right?
So what they did then was they said when they were worshipping the Lord, right?
You hear that being worshipped today, which is the Lord is a local demon or entity in divine sense.
When you bring an offering to a god, what do you bring?
Do you bring them like yesterday's supper or do you bring like the best food you've got, right?
The best of the best.
So on a higher level, these people thought what is the best of the best of the best of the best?
Well, the best of the best has to be the product of what is the most important organ, which is the right and the child.
So that's how they got into child sacrifice back in the early days by justifying these things in a divine sense,
divine meaning dealing with the spiritual realm, low entity demons and entities as they are today, right?
So this is how they have rationalized or justified savagery.
And now this has gone underground or it's still a symbolic to you.
If you've known anyone who's done a birthday cake with candles, guess what, folks?
That's the eating of a child's body. Lovely.
How about Santa Claus, Molech, a child being burned alive on the seat, being seated on a red hot statue that's red with bells ringing, right?
How about how many times have you heard of did you get her a heart shaped box of chocolates?
You know, that heart shape that people use. That's not a heart.
A heart looks like a fist. Do you know what that heart shape that everyone is using is?
It's the frontal view of a woman's genitalia. Right.
That is not a heart. So you have a society that is obsessed with sexuality because of its insurance of future generations.
And then it's obsessed with offering to the gods.
And this is what you're the root of your pedophilia and human sacrifice and all this stuff is.
This is the whatever guide to planet Earth. And sorry, folks, you're all mixed up in it.
It's really hard because you're addicted to it. So the nefarious.
No. And the thing is that you can't escape culpability with, you know, because, well, we're all contained in the same.
We're all in the same boat. I remember you discussing the boat before and.
Right. In terms of prophecy. Yeah. In terms of prophecy and what your free will is.
Yeah. That's the only way to look at it. If you have a better one, I'm open to it.
No, I don't. I actually don't. That's the thing is that, you know, sometimes and I may have been wrong to even cover the subject.
Right. Because it's just it's not something that I should be involved in discussing.
Really? Well, you mean the pedophilia or the boat?
No, not the boat, not the boat. I'm talking about, you know, the whole thing.
Yeah. Well, the humanity is deeply engrossed. Here's the other thing.
The you know, people don't like talking about the gods or anything about them because they like I said,
they're human society now is either all you're either in the pagan or in the atheists.
Pagan just means that you have no you're on operating on a low level. Right.
It's like you think McDonald's is five star stuff. You know, it's maybe we have to find another term for it.
No. And I recognize that because I ascribe that label to myself.
All right. I recognize that there is a great deal more, which is not known to me.
And therefore, I understand that there is this lower level of, you know, comprehension, let's call it, that I have.
I'm able to recognize that I can't quite break that censorship that is there.
I feel as though occasionally I get a glimpse of it. OK.
Like I noticed that you even mentioned the fact that instructions come along with the product.
This this is something that has come to me.
That's for sure. I'm not saying that I know how to read all the instructions.
I'm sure you don't. Well, then it's then it's a matter of do you really have to reinvent the wheel?
No. But, you know, making a wheel is hard. It's difficult.
You know, have you heard of someone someone going down the road and the car is vibrating violently because the wheels are out of balance?
You know, a little one of those little weights fell off or something. I mean, wheels are a bitch to deal with.
I mean, what do you mean? Just make something round.
Yeah. But once you start putting dynamics into it, the dynamics change it a lot. Right.
So that that's exactly how it is. If you acknowledge that we are not alone. Right.
And there are higher forces. Now, we society has been convinced at large that you have to either make it up as you go along.
And I mean, it's just like you will not go back and look and have an accumulative body of knowledge on anything,
because it's based on just belief that word belief and faith has destroyed mankind when it comes to knowing more than this,
the condition that they're in, because we've defined belief should be based on something that is going to happen.
And you have firm hopes or aspirations that it will happen based on evidence or that it's it's a, you know,
something that's based on something that's going to happen. And this faith, there is no such thing as faith.
It's which faith. Right. Or the faith of what?
And that's why I said it's pretty much atheism, because, for example, if you join any of these religious groups on the planet right now,
most people are under the misunderstanding that will bring you closer to what they call G.O.D.
That couldn't be further from the truth. If you want to go further away from what is what people refer to as G.O.D.,
you go ahead and join one of these organizations, any of them.
They will bring you further and further and further away and you will go deeper and deeper into the crowd mentality.
Right. How many times have you heard someone said, oh, I joined this church and I started reading the Bible
and I went back and started discussing what was in it and they kicked me out.
Actually, I've heard that a lot.
How about an attorney? You know, you know, I have this case. I showed him all this.
Oh, you know, I'll go to the judge and I'll bring up all these points.
Guess what happens to that attorney every time he gets disbarred? He ends up being a car salesman.
By the way, I find out that I've heard of three or four disbarred attorneys in the past few years and they all end up being car salesmen.
Just think about that for a minute.
No, I'm sorry. That's just funny.
I love that.
I'm sorry for them, but I'm just giving you testimony on that.
And doctors, by the way, when they leave that field, they end up going into the arts and crafts business.
So that I believe and I tell you this, look, give me 30 seconds.
I appreciated this particular interaction I had with somebody that called themselves a doctor.
And it was over vaccination, which, you know, you and I may have a slightly differing view on.
But here's the thing.
I saw it as my responsibility to say to a doctor, if you can explain to me what the risk is of my infant son getting hepatitis B.
Because to the best of my knowledge, this, according to your book of knowledge, is something that you can get from said behaviors.
And I laid them out. You know, is he going to get a tattoo?
Is he going to have unprotected sex? Is he going to engage in intravenous drug use?
These things, according to your literature, are the risk factors.
My infant will not participate in those things.
Therefore, I don't feel as though it's necessary to introduce this into his body.
The blank stare.
Because I realize this is still flawed logic.
But it's a lot more sensible than injecting an infant with something like that.
Okay.
Well, in their talk, maybe it might sound pedantic, but what it is, it's popularly plausible.
Right?
Because the popular census is that if the medical authorities say that if we do this, it'll cut back on disease, it's plausible.
Let's try it.
Anything to cut back on disease. Right?
So it's a popular plausibility.
But there is no, you cannot show me any study based on good science or real science that shows that vaccines have any effect that is positive.
Actually, the good science has shown the contrary.
That vaccines have a negative effect.
And then there is a reality above both of that, which is how the human body really works.
And let's put vaccines, just stick your arm out on the table, slide them all the way to the side.
You've got a clean table.
Right?
How the body really works.
Anytime anything, even saline solution, is injected into the body, it breaks the skin barrier, disturbs the vacuum that's in the body.
The body all of a sudden, you ever see on a submarine when they go red alert, all the red lights start flashing, red alert, all hands on deck.
Right?
Or whatever.
Or on a ship.
Anytime you inject anything through the skin, it doesn't matter what it is, the body goes through a shock condition.
Not an overall shock like you would see someone in a car accident, but it's something bad.
Period.
The body reacts to it as an invasion.
Invasion.
Period.
Exactly.
This is how the body really works.
You don't want to breach that vacuum.
Now, we've also discussed if bacteria causes disease, that renders all refrigeration useless.
Oh, yeah.
You see?
Because why is it that you get sick during the winter when bacteria are inert?
It can't be that.
Now, how simple is that?
Well, it has to be then that you're not eating right.
You're eating foods that come from a warm climate, and the body's trying to adjust.
Very simple.
And you know what?
Ten out of ten.
Well, whoever I've told this to and has applied it, it's worked.
Only one person in a decade came back and said, Greek, that thing about eating cross latitude or seasonally doesn't work.
And I said, well, how do you know?
I mean, what part of it – what did you do?
And he says, oh, I didn't do any of it.
It just doesn't work.
And I'm like, okay, you must be a scientist then.
In other words, they didn't try it.
So I have a hundred percent track record with whoever eats seasonally.
In other words, if you're living in northeastern America and there's snow on the ground, don't eat bananas.
Don't eat things from the tropics.
Eat things, right, because that will adjust your body to the tropics.
So that's why I said, Chuck, we did something, I think, episode two called The Container.
What is really going on, like the credit-based economy, right, and all these other things,
what is really going on has nothing to do with what people believe.
But if they check their beliefs to see what it's based on, just as simple as a common cold,
they will see that, hey, honey, we don't need the refrigerator anymore, right,
because it seems like the colder it gets, the more active bacteria it gets.
So let's get rid of the refrigerator because that seems to be spoiling the food.
Now how stupid is that?
Well, here's the punch line, by the way, to the whole – because first of all, let me just say this.
The act of injection is really what is at the root of my objection to this procedure.
You understand?
All right.
But hold on.
Look at the constituents, right, of the vaccine.
It's a witch's brew, right?
Like you said, put that aside.
Put that aside.
The simple use of that methodology is unsound in my mind.
That's it.
That's the end of the discussion.
That should be the end of the discussion.
But you know what the punch line was?
It's on the schedule.
The legal schedule.
Yeah.
It's on – that's what the doctor said.
It's on the schedule.
I say it.
I repeat it because it seems to be a recurring theme.
You know, we have another phone caller, and I'd like to add them in.
You mind if we do that?
Let's do that.
No.
All right.
I'd mind if you didn't.
Exactly.
That's what I thought.
Let's see.
Now we have 949 area code.
You're on the air.
Hey, Greek and Ocelli, it's Rectify.
I had a question, but I wanted to make a statement first.
I wanted to say, well, once again – is that once or again?
I just got through driving on the parkway and parked in my driveway.
I'm now sitting in my apartment.
That is really a togetherment.
I wanted to hear what Greek has to say about manifest destiny, faith,
and projecting what we want to receive.
I'll take the answer off the air.
Thank you very much.
That's good.
What is it?
Why do your feet smell and your nose run?
Thanks, Rectify.
Did you get that, Chuck?
Anyway.
Absolutely.
I was just muting.
Yeah.
Driving on the parkway and parking in the driveway,
why does your nose run and your feet smell?
It's just backwards again, you see.
Manifest destiny.
I think Chuck kind of alluded that earlier.
This happens a lot, deja vu.
Very simple, the cruise ship.
Everyone is on the ship, and they're going from London to New York,
and you can't do anything about it.
But while you're on the ship, you can manifest.
I don't know, Chuck.
Cruise ships are like cities now, aren't they?
You've got, what, theaters, movies, playrooms, spas on deck, pools, saunas.
You could go sleep in your cabin, right?
I mean, they've got a lot of choices.
What do they call that, accoutrements?
Would that be the right word?
So your manifest destiny, putting out what you want to do, let's say,
what you'd like to manifest is what do you want to do, man?
Do you want to go up on the deck and play skeet,
or do you want to go to the movies?
That is about as limited as it is.
But when you hear – let me just guide this thought,
because this is a recurrent theme that Chuck brought up on the ship again, Chuck.
Maybe we'll go into it a little bit more.
You're all going from one place to another, and when you hear about people,
let's say, at the spa in the hot tub on the whatever deck,
because they can have 12 decks on these ships now, I heard.
You're saying we're going to change the ship, not going from London.
We're going to go to New York.
We're going to go to, let's say, Florida instead.
That's not going to happen, buddy.
Sorry.
You hear a lot of discussion right now, especially –
I shouldn't say any group,
but you do hear discussion about we have to band together to change things
for making a better world.
You've heard this a lot, or change this.
That's not going to happen on a general sense.
You're not changing the general direction of society,
but we can change things in terms of manifesting.
Just like, for example, you and I got together a week or two ago,
and AFR said, hey, why don't you guys reload Bocelli and the Greek, and here we are.
If you told me that two weeks ago, I'd say probably never going to happen, right?
Or I don't see it.
I can't see how that's done.
But we're here, so we manifest that very quickly,
but we're not going to change the Internet.
You see, so the ship, again, for Manifest Destiny is it.
So, for example, people coming and starting a country, let's say known as America,
killing everyone that was here and resettling it and becoming a superpower
does not interfere at all with the entire path that humanity is on over periods of thousands of years.
You see?
Did I elaborate on that enough?
Anything you want to add to that, Chuck?
No, I think that you covered that quite well.
We only have a few minutes left,
so I want to once again give the opportunity for someone else to call in if they like
at 218-339-8525, 218-339-8525.
Without that, we'll just continue with the rather coherent discussion of where the ship is going.
And in this analogy, what would that ship be, just to clarify that point one more time?
Oh, you're ready?
It used to be called Atlantis.
Now it's called Earth.
That's why people that are looking for Atlantis will never find it, because they're standing on it.
They've misread the documentation.
I'm serious.
It sounds ridiculous on its face, but if you research it, you will find – it's like the JFK stuff.
If you're just getting into researching it, you think you really found out who did it,
and when you look at it, you'll see that it's not really tied together enough, right?
So this is planet Earth.
So what you're doing with this ship is manned society, not the planet itself through space,
but you're in the process of being tempered.
It's going to be great, but we can get into more discussions perhaps if we keep going with this.
I always like to make all sonic projects limited, so we'll probably cap this off at either 7 or 12
or whatever you think, right?
And then go on from there, maybe on another project, who knows?
Or maybe 18.
Let's see.
But maybe discussing what's coming in the future might be on people's minds.
It's what tips their ticket.
But right now, all I've been seeing is their shallow thinking is getting them to fall into the deep end,
and then when they get out of the deep end, you tell them you just fell into the deep end.
They said, oh, it doesn't matter.
So how many times can you do that with one's life without living a life of efficiency?
In essence, you've got another year and a half or so before some changes start to happen,
even though things are changing every day, but, I mean, on a big sense.
And we can get into a lot of specifics on that.
I believe I got into – this is just to bring this out.
I did a Freeman TV interview.
I was asked to discuss, maybe follow up on the first one,
because they said some things that I guess rang very true with him,
and he kind of fished me out to continue the thought, which I really didn't,
because he just let me go a little too much.
But I discussed a couple of things on the second hour, which is a members only,
on certain things that are going to be happening in the future.
One of them had to do with tattoos, people with tattoos.
Why are you seeing everyone getting tattoos in the past 10 years,
where previously it was only people that were in the Navy or hung out at bars
or motorcycle clubs, right?
And this is also in prophecy.
And many other things about what's coming with future society,
not because I believe in them or I predict them,
it's because it's just you're looking at the manual, right?
And we can get into more discussions like that
and things that I probably wouldn't want to discuss in public a year or two ago
that I believe that trying out at this point hopefully would be okay to try the public on them.
And not only that, you understand that people have the attention span of cats, right,
which is about three minutes or less.
I believe now it's less than 30 seconds.
So it doesn't matter.
So it would probably be good practice, and at least the information can be memorialized.
Well, that's for certain.
That's what we'll continue to try and do.
And, of course, we're down to the last few minutes here.
I think that the idea was to give people the primer for the reboot.
We're going to go into some different directions, I'm sure.
I want to get in-depth on the concept of tattoos because, well, I'm part of that.
It's a setup, again.
It's the setup.
You're all being set up for it.
People that have heard me discuss this that are secular-based, let's say,
have actually had them removed.
But some people have so many it's not practical.
But that's all right because the folks that do have tattoos,
when they get wrapped up in what's coming, the rest of the folks don't have a lot of time anyway.
But either way, this is not a level of checkers.
This is not a level of being bombasted with ridiculous stuff that you hear from economists
and health people.
How many times now have we all supposed to have died from a pandemic?
And how many times has the dollar already supposed to have collapsed, Chuck?
This is the ridiculousness, the checkers.
If you hear these economists and these people, the doom and gloomers,
if you ever listen to what they're saying, that's on tic-tac-toe checkers level.
They don't understand that these pieces have a variety of moves and a variety of ranking.
They don't understand how these things move.
So the checkers and tic-tac-toe mentality does not transfer over to the chessboard,
especially like a 3D chessboard.
But all these things, no matter how complex they might seem on the surface,
require skill and patience and discipline to learn.
And once you do learn them, you'll find there's a tremendous contrast.
Have you heard about the haves and have-nots, those who know and those who don't know?
It's not trivial.
It is massive.
And this is not something that you become initiated in.
In a group, this is something you have to do on your own.
And again here, I'll just read a comment here.
Someone said that, again, the Greek thinks he knows the truth of all religions
and all wise men cannot be possible.
No, I don't think I know the truth of all religions.
What I've done is I've looked at what they are based on a little bit,
and I realized that it is not good based on any basic morality, and you walk away.
The truth of all religions is very, very simple.
It's the crowd mentality.
All you have to do beyond the religion is look at how man structures his operating system.
For example, every country has a matron, meaning female, or patron, meaning male,
deity over them, always through society.
And no one is discussing this, right?
What is the matron deity for America?
It's Columbia or it's justice, justicia.
And if you want to know where the country's god comes from, it's where they get their law.
These gods that people talk about in their religions have nothing to do with what they tell the practitioners.
The purpose of the gods is to give you law.
You might call it the laws of physics, how to live, how to go into contract,
what to eat, what to wear, how to keep time.
Those are all laws, right?
I'm not talking about traffic law and tax law.
That included.
And by the way, with taxes, only foreigners are taxed.
So if you're subject to tax, guess what your government considers you?
Oops. Okay.
Yeah, that's the truth too.
And also modern taxation is just theory.
So you're all subject to a theory.
Anyway, because it's credit.
But ultimately, you don't need to know much about religions.
All the religions do is get you away from the gods, plural, and the most high, and knowing any law.
And you will find that it's just based on Gustave Le Bon.
He objectified the crowd.
Anyone who wants to look it up, it's called the crowd.
Well, I'll tell you something.
We are going to examine these things further, I assure the listener.
And it appears as though there are more than four, by the way, Greek.
But who knows what will happen as we go forward?
Because, well, it does emerge as it's supposed to, I believe.
Well, it's a loose guide to those that are ready to visit this planet, in a sense.
And I mean that facetiously and sarcastically, because what we're discussing is accessible to anyone.
I don't think, Chuck, you can call me on this.
You don't have to call me on it now, perhaps in the future.
Have I ever mentioned or said anything or brought up anything, either general or detailed,
that couldn't be accessed or referenced outside of the conversation?
I think very rarely, no.
You can look up anything I've said, yeah.
Very rarely.
There's a couple of questions that I do have, though, that I did not get to when we first did this.
And I'm looking forward to asking them regarding some of the things that you've said.
For instance, we discussed the hierarchy of the gods, which I think you're entirely accurate about.
And I – well, I don't think you're – I know you're accurate about that.
Well, you could look it up yourself, yeah.
Well, yeah, absolutely.
But I don't have to look it up because I've already been initiated into this type of thought.
And you don't even have to be convinced of it.
It's just so rational and basic, yeah.
Exactly.
That's the thing.
And as we go forward, I think we're going to examine some of the things that should be obvious,
that are actually obvious, but are still censored.
So we may not get way beyond the censorship, but I think we're going to at least scratch the surface.
What do you think?
Sure, sure.
And maybe we'll give people some homework.
Maybe we'll bring this up because as we get closer to what they call the holiday season,
which is predominantly, I guess, Christian, I think, and there are some other groups in there that do this,
maybe some homework for the listeners is look up the cult of Serapis, S-E-R-A-P-I-S, I believe.
That's like a phonetic spelling.
If you look up who Serapis was, you will probably, if you're living in the Bible Belt,
you probably see everyone behaving as if they're in the cult of Serapis.
Have you ever heard of Serapis before, Chuck?
Yes, I have.
And the spellings do vary a bit, but what you just gave people is relatively reasonable enough
to search it out on what we call the Internet at this point.
Yes. Okay, folks, thanks again.
Absolutely, Greg, and we will do this again next, what they call Thor's Day on the Pope's work schedule.
Ocelli and the Greek is done. We will see you again.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Are you feeling embarrassed and stuck because you can't focus or concentrate?
I have a confession to make.
I spent years unable to think clearly like I was in a fog.
I was going through the motions, running my companies, and I hated feeling groggy and mentally sluggish.
I couldn't get ahead like this.
It's no secret the powers that be want us dumbed down.
Chemicals, fluoride, our brains are under siege and we are experiencing lower IQs.
But now there's a weapon to fight back and win.
Introducing DNA Evolve, a revolutionary breakthrough in a category of cognitive enhancers called nootropics.
I've been using DNA Evolve and couldn't feel better.
For me, it works.
It feels great to get things done again and get ahead.
Try a free sample for yourself at dnaevolvesample.com.
That's dnaevolvesample.com.
Supplies are limited, so go to dnaevolvesample.com right now.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion, and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
Hempusa.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO, and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367,
and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at hempusa.org.
Yo, what's up? Check this out.
The voice of the revolution.
American Freedom Radio.
The world is like a ride at an amusement park.
And when you choose to go on it, you think it's real, because that's how powerful our minds are.
And the ride goes up and down and round and round.
It has thrills and chills and it's very brightly colored and it's very loud.
And it's fun for a while.
Some people have been on the ride for a long time and they begin to question,
is this real or is this just a ride?
And other people have remembered and they come back to us and they say,
hey, don't worry, don't be afraid, ever, because this is just a ride.
And we kill those people.
The eyes of fear want you to put bigger locks on your door, buy guns, close yourself off.
The eyes of love instead see all of us as one.
Here's what we can do to change the world right now to a better ride.
Take all that money we spend on weapons and defense each year
and instead spend it feeding, clothing, and educating the poor of the world,
which it would many times over, not one human being excluded,
and we can explore space together, both inner and outer, forever in peace.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow, friendships to flourish,
with a moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio at ymail.com.
Vaccines, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.