American Freedom Radio presents the only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ochoa airs every week.
If you're on the west coast of the United States, it is 9 p.m. according to that wind-up toy or the digital representation thereof.
And, well, guess what? Your Pope's work schedule still tells you it's the fifth day of the twelfth month, which is allegedly December.
This is Ocelli and the Greek, episode 10, and that much we know for certain.
Or not.
Yes, I figured we'd go through those machinations really quickly at the top of the show so that we don't have to revisit it again,
because in previous episodes we've discussed several times how people do not know how to tell time,
and there's a reason for that, and all of these other good things, and maybe we'll discuss it yet again,
because no matter how many times it's being said, it seems as though it's not being heard, Greg.
Do you think we want to use the mass use of media just to inform the five people on the planet that it might be interested?
No, that's okay.
Actually, it's more than that. I'm being sarcastic, but it's down to about five, I think.
Could be.
Anyway.
Let's just, why don't we throw in, it appears to be the 11th day of the 10th month.
Hint, deca, decim, December means 10, and why is it the 11th day?
Well, the moon came around new 11 days ago, very simple.
So, there you are.
Until noon, not midnight.
Until, yeah, what do they call that, the solar, how is that referenced again?
Well, it's solar noon.
Solar noon, right.
Yeah, wherever you are, just like you have time zones, it's, yeah, it's all observational.
Right. Of course, according to the Pope's work schedule, each day begins at the darkest time of the day,
what they call midnight, which is interesting.
All things, you know, having been dishonest are always committed in the darkness.
I do recall seeing something that could be paraphrased in exactly that way, well, several times over the years.
And their high holidays are in the darkest time of the year, at least on the northern part of the globe.
Yes, it's a globe.
And their year starts at the darkest time.
Correct.
Their day starts at the darkest time, you know.
Their moon, their new moon is a dark moon, which you can't see, that's why it's new.
That's why, you know, I've got a brand new car out there, you know, there's nothing there, but it's a brand new car, right?
Empty parking lot, you know, that's a new car.
Yeah.
We're talking about, yeah, and I think the topic tonight is going to be about dark matters,
and even the ones that allegedly fear or partake in those dark matters are dark about their own dark matters.
Wow.
Okay.
Right.
See, now, interesting correlation.
This is exactly where I was going, is I was leading into the darkness so that we could begin to talk about what is allegedly one of the darkest subjects on the planet, right?
What we would refer to as the adversary.
What people generally refer to as Satan, okay, now stop quivering and quaking in your boots out there, please, because we are talking about Satan and Satanism tonight on Ocelli and the Greek.
Now, why are we discussing this?
Do we want to talk about the devil worship and the ritualization of things and so on and so forth that people have convoluted with this concept of Satan?
Well, if you've ever listened to this show before, you know that that's not the way this is going to go down.
Bottom line, let's talk about, well, let's start with the very basics, Greek.
Satan, who is that?
Yeah, the who is, well, not the rock band The Who, but yeah, I think here's the thing.
Discussing these things, first of all, is not a matter of opinion.
We want to just preface this is not an academic discussion, right?
And if you want to know why I say that, look it up, what academic means.
This is just merely stating an objective view on any data or information or perspective that anyone can gather.
Now, who is he?
Do people really have the maturity to take definitions of things and words and concepts and apply them to their thoughts, right?
Because at this point, it seems like everything's been left to the imagination, trends, cultural memes, things that come in vogue and fall out of vogue.
And no one really knows, even though the definitions are right there, right?
And then if we go back to historical references, well, they were primitive and they didn't know.
And who wrote that anyway, right, is what you hear.
So all that stuff's got to be put aside and we have to be rational, objective individuals.
Let's just look at the word Satan.
Like I said, who is he, why is he called that?
It just means the adversary.
English is made up of many different base root tongues like Greek, Chaldean Hebrew, Germanic.
The word Satan, its root is in the Chaldean Hebrew, Shatan, which means the adversary.
It is an adjective, right?
It's describing the character of a character.
Well, wait a minute, Greg, because everybody that ever discusses this topic always points back to a manifestation that would be that of an individual.
And that's almost like saying, well, an animal is an individual.
But you're not describing anyone in particular.
An animal is a general description.
Or am I wrong?
Well, no, it's not.
This conversation can go on in many directions and also expose the stupidity of mankind at this point.
But I don't know if we would become popular by doing that.
I think the most popular thing to do is say the Luciferians are going to get us and play elevator music for the next hour and a half.
That's what people want to hear, but that's not what they're going to get.
What I'm saying is the term itself means adversary.
Okay, so is there a character that there is a tangible or intangible, ha-ha, being a spiritual realm?
We're going to have to go back to the foundational documents that are still available, which would be the biblical text and other ancient texts, right?
And the character of this particular entity is described as being not only the adversary to mankind, but a leader of a mindset and activities that are cosmic,
meaning in the spiritual realm that also manifests in the physical realm, a cosmic war, things like that, things we've discussed.
Okay, so yes, if we're going to take for face value and say there is validity in the ancient texts,
there is an entity that would be considered the head deity of this adversarial group.
And very little about him is known, it seems, because his level of interaction with mankind historically, according to ancient texts, is minimal.
Right.
You see, he would be like the general of an army.
He wouldn't be boots on the ground that mankind are dealing with, but it is adversarial.
Now, just to plant the reality of what that term actually means, Satan or Shaitan or the adversary is just that.
If you say pretty, he says ugly. If you say white, he says black.
Right, okay.
You say up, they say down.
And it also means attorney in Hebrew, by the way.
Right.
So technically and legally, Satanists are in every American neighborhood, almost every European neighborhood.
They're known as attorneys.
And this is not a criticism on attorneys.
This is how they are introduced in the native tongue.
For example, if you were to watch court TV in Israel, the prosecutor would always be introduced in mainstream television as Ha-Satan, the Satan, right?
So this is the reality of the functional part of it.
You know, when people say you're nice and I say no thanks, well, you know, they're wondering what I mean.
So now we're getting into the unused side of how things are defined.
And this is not going to make us popular, but it needs to be said.
Well, you know, that's true.
And it introduces or sort of rings a bell with me because, after all, people have discussed and I abandoned this after studying it for a while.
But, you know, what they call angelic lore or what they describe as the ancient ideas about the angels, right?
You know, and here I go using one of those very, very dummy loaded terms.
But when we start discussing angels, there was supposed to be this war in heaven, right?
And please give me give me a break about what I'm describing here.
OK, hold on.
Go for it. You're doing great.
I mean, go for it, man.
This is just it's exactly as you're saying it.
So, well, there was supposed to be this war in heaven where the the character of Satan is allegedly the same character as an angel described as Lucifer,
who is the adversary to the chief deity who is embattled with God himself, according to the interpretations of angelic scripture,
which, you know, which one can actually find if they wish.
And there's the concept of him falling to earth, the concept of being banished to what some people might describe as hell, all of these sorts of ideas.
And it gets really strange because actually when one takes a very strict sort of look at at the documentation, the story is not really quite as simple as that, is it?
No, the documentation is 100 percent contrary to that.
It's like. Yeah, it's like we've discussed voters and constitution and all that.
You know, people who, you know, praise that they know or shouting the loudest about these subjects know the least about them.
And in respect, you know, what you just mentioned is is the standard gripe with the with that adversarial character.
He's not against, by the way, the head god.
He's against mankind.
All right. He's because what people fail to realize, which you would get from reading the text, is that mankind is a new creation.
And what a big deal. You know, what's the big deal about a new creation?
Well, this new creation is declared to be of the same authority of the head deity, where none of that was ever granted to the other entities, quote unquote, in that realm.
Right. So that really made some of them upset.
Now, the other thing you mentioned is Lucifer.
Now, without sounding, you know, giving a biblical verse or reference, anyone can research now what where the word Lucifer comes from.
It's from the King James Bible. And it's only used once.
And it's it's not referring to a spiritual entity at all.
And I don't want to sound, you know, because whenever you bring up the biblical text, it's been hijacked by the Christians.
And, you know, they're you know, who wants to go look at a book about Santa Claus? Right.
So so so in this case, you'd have to go and research it on your own.
It's only used once. And it's referring to a man who is dead.
So next subject, you see how you see how ridiculous the the alternative and mainstream is about any information.
That's precisely right. But see, convoluted together is this concept of the adversary and this character known as Lucifer.
The concept of this spiritual warfare that, you know, as I said, in general descriptions from people who have studied these things, they will tell you that this was a war in heaven.
Yes. Where, you know, where the Satan character, the Lucifer angel was, you know, banished from heaven and therefore ended up ruling in hell, you know.
And then people say, yeah, and then concept of Dante even.
Yeah. There is no hell, by the way. Yeah. There is no hell. Yeah.
So but that's OK. Yeah. No, I understand.
But I'm saying that for the sake of the listener out there, I'm very sure that if you're vaguely aware of this topic, you're at the very least aware of the roots of why people protest so much against what they believe is Satanism.
What they believe is Luciferianism, what they also convoluted with devil worship.
And I argue that each one of these three things is literally three separate topics.
Oh, yeah, completely.
You know, and number two, the paranoia over it. Yeah, you have the Lucifer concept over somebody who has already left this plane, not part of the game anymore.
The adversary could be anyone. And as you pointed out, an adversary or one who is an attorney is also a Satanist, right?
By definition.
By definition. And this has nothing to do with my opinion. And I've got plenty of opinions on lawyers.
But the point is that it's got nothing to do with my opinion. It's got nothing to do with your opinion.
Literally speaking and even taking a completely neutral view of their profession, the damage they do on and on ad nauseum.
It doesn't matter because each one of them is employed with the sole purpose of being an adversary.
Are they not?
Correct.
So I wonder how.
And liars and thieves. But anyway, oops, did I say that? No. OK.
Yeah. Well, you know, lawyer and liar, they do sound rather.
And that's part of the thing. So but here I want to go back to one thing again, is that what we're doing now is a more mature subject matter than little children.
When they reach past their formative years, the parents kind of tell them, well, you're too old for Santa Claus and you're too old for the tooth fairy now.
Right. You see like kind of reserve the Santa Claus tooth fairy stories for young children, because once they develop more, they kind of cut them off without apologizing.
They've been lied to. These were in this case.
But we're discussing these what people are going to be quite surprised to find out that these entities or characters do exist.
Right. And they're going to say, oh, well, show me the proof. Well, you know, they're not in a tangible state right now.
But that's why I'm saying they're not going to there's no reason to convince anyone that these characters do exist now.
Because but what I what I'm saying is it's going to be interesting to see the look on people's faces when they do find out in the future that these characters exist.
We're speaking now, you know, out of time here.
But everything that they what you see out there being discussed is in the nature of the child being made aware that these things don't exist.
Let's say Santa Claus and the tooth fairy. But when you get into a little closer, they they're actually representations of other things.
You see, I think we've discussed how Santa Claus is the Moloch red child sacrificing type deal.
Right. And still resonates even in its ritualism.
At this point in time, you throw a screaming, fearful child onto his lap just like you would Moloch.
And voila, you have the homage to to the ancient deity, don't you?
Yeah, you could. That's why it's very simple to bring someone from ancient Canaan or Babylon or Phoenicia to this to modern day around what they call the Christmas holiday.
And they would they would understand everything that's going on because it's identical to what they were doing, but they were doing it more in 3D.
They were actually roasting children in public and it was acceptable.
And there will come a time within this society that that will be acceptable as well, which is kind of difficult to say.
But just to go back to the adversary, just to polish off the definition.
When when you say Satan or Satanism from the biblical Quranic or which would be Iblis and other texts, he is the head adversary.
He has minimal relations, minimum interactions with mankind.
Now, just to go on to the further thing you hear about Satanism and practicing Satanists.
What they are doing is evoking what's been memorialized as other ancient balls or lords.
Ball would be B-A-A-L, which is the Chaldean Hebrew term meaning Lord.
That's why when you go to church today, they tell you to worship the Lord.
You see, so what these balls or lords are the ones that dealt with people.
That's why when you look at modern, quote, unquote, practicing Satanism, you look at the temple of set temple of this.
They call them like the infernal names, which is also kind of they're not in the underworld.
How can they be in the underworld?
Do they have like an escalator that they come out of the underworld and come up to the surface?
And, you know, none of that is true.
Not only that, but, you know, aside from the temple of set, when you talk about what they literally call the modern church of Satan,
you know, you're not talking about Luciferianism.
You're not talking about devil worship.
You're actually talking about a rather extreme form of literally adhering to what Crowley said,
which was that, you know, do as thou wilt shall be the whole whole of the law.
OK, and we won't get into Crowley too deeply here.
But of course, he's worth mentioning during this topic.
He was a dummy load, by the way.
Oh, yeah, certainly.
But my point is that is that his simple statement there and what was allegedly codified by Anton LaVey into what they call the modern church of Satan,
literally has nothing to do with this character, even not not the one that you're talking about, not the adversary in truth and not this character,
which has been a composite created from all of these other resources.
They're truthfully about pretty much being their own God and literally being the adversary themselves.
So in a way, they adhere to the concept, the true concept of what Satan is without adopting the cartoon character with the red skin and the tail.
Yeah, well, that's yeah.
Then they're operating outside of the operating system, which is which, you know, they're operating in a what you might call a religious political system,
just like the church is part of the political system.
It's political.
In essence, just to jump around and we could throw in a few details here.
There's some famous, quote unquote, Satanists or people that worked for the military in various aspects and work.
They're behind the scenes in many things in clandestine forms.
What they do is a paint by numbers evocations.
They understand that the spiritual realm is real.
Right. And everyone around them doesn't.
And they know that there there's a technology or communication to evoke certain entities.
These are the balls or the Lords, whether they be of ancient Babylon or ancient Egypt.
You know, they're geographically pinned. Usually there are ones in Asia.
They as well. They there is a series of things or rules that need to be done before these entities can be evoked.
And this goes across the board for the positive entities as well as the negative.
That's why, for example, if you look in the biblical text, you'll see very clearly that prayer is a technology,
not unlike a radio or communications officer in the field would be.
You know, if you were in the military and you were tasked to be a communications officer,
they just don't hand you the equipment and tell you to go.
You have to have you have those certain protocols.
And I assure you what the quote unquote Christian and Muslim and major religions of the world are doing
are contrary to what is in the texts for communication.
But essentially, we've also discussed the concept of in previous shows, I believe, briefly.
When you look at people doing, let's say, these voodoo ceremonies were in state parks or even city parks,
they'll find a head of a goat or a chicken. Right.
If you look at the ordinances of the of the temples, there was also animal sacrifices.
So there's there's a sacrifice of an animal both in the in the positive and the negative or on for the high command
and for the adversary side, you see. So it's all who you're doing it for.
But just to go back to what power these, quote unquote, Satanists or temple of said or these other ones have,
is they do understand the spiritual world is a technology.
You see, the people have been completely cut off from it.
You know, right now, when I say the people, I mean, it's safe to say seven billion people have been cut off
and maybe a small handful are left on the planet that understand the real reality of the other side
or the realm of the spiritual, nonphysically tangible at the moment realm.
And what they've done from just even cursory study and hearing people commenting and even just cursory
commenting on what's been done with the Satanists is they have just discovered a technology
which has been handed down for thousands of years on how to evoke these particular lords or balls or dimmed devils,
imps, demons to do their bidding. Sometimes it's even an elemental.
So they are just doing a paint by numbers.
If they're going out in public and stating themselves as being gods, as you mentioned earlier,
they really don't understand the nature of the spiritual realm.
But they do understand enough that if I paint by numbers, in other words, you know, paint by numbers,
find in the Chromacon or something or a ritual and do it, I will gain some sort of power.
But they obviously do not understand it.
But they understand enough of it to use it just like a woman driving a car.
All she knows is there's a seat and a steering wheel, a brake pedal and accelerator.
She doesn't know anything about the car itself mechanically or how it's made or what it requires.
This is not a harsh criticism and this is not a mild criticism.
This is not a criticism on them at all.
It's just a quick objective observation on how they're functioning publicly.
Well, right, and that's what it comes down to is that there's also a public and a private version of what is being disseminated,
the acts that are being committed, you know, allegedly and realistically, you know, to evoke certain things,
to create scenarios, to satisfy, to state certain, what should we call them, entities.
Things like this are occurring all the time.
But it's got nothing to do with this nonsense that we hear about, you know.
And I'm sorry, I simply call it nonsense because I don't have a better word for it regarding the, you know, the great satanic agenda.
You know, the people that are truly the adversaries are not being called the adversaries.
You know, and the entities that are the adversaries are not being called out as the adversaries that they truly are.
You know, I see it as, truthfully, the behavior of individuals from, you know, from the proper church of Satan, let's just say,
is in a way, in a very strange way, to my mind, a whole lot more lawful than the conduct of the individuals who are running what we call churches.
Yeah, but, you know, again, regarding that aspect which you brought up, your law comes from your deity.
Right.
Right. So if you go to the mainstream religions and ask them where you get your law, hardly any of them ever say they're a deity.
So that's why I said earlier, the population of the earth right now has been almost completely cut off from the reality of themselves and the other side.
I guess that's what we try to do here, is try to say things.
We get a lot of commentary that, for example, a little side note on our emails on the Achillean, the Greek website, that it's about time these things are being said.
So we can clearly say, objectively, that mankind has been completely cut off from the reality of these things right now.
And our attempt to speak on this subject tonight is, I think, to add clarification, not because of our opinion, but because of what anyone can discover about the subject.
If you tie in the concept of the way people behave, that comes from your deity. That is part of the operating system.
And if, again, just to go back to how we stated earlier, or I stated earlier, that your law comes from your deity, what we mean by law is not traffic law or tax law or this or that or these legalistic values,
but what you eat, what you wear, how you behave, how you keep time, how you go into a contract, how you worship, how you do all these things, right, your daily behavior.
So to bring that back to what you were saying, that they're acting more lawful, well, your law comes from your deity.
So that's a really hard judgment call.
Like, for example, in certain parts of the world, let's say in Islam at least, they do acknowledge some laws in Judaism regarding dietary, let's say.
Let's just make it very loose there.
Oh, yeah. That's a very simple observation to make because anyone who knows anything, even the most dummy-loaded individual out there, is going to say that, well, neither one of them partake in swine.
Correct.
No pork on the fork, as you said once, which I found kind of funny in a way.
But based on those like-minded premises in a dietary sense, there's a couple of other things too.
It does get a little more complex, but because of those things, you can see the commonality between the two right away.
Right, and so if you were to go to, let's say, a quote-unquote Satanist, ask them, what about food?
What is fit and proper according to your deity?
And it would be very similar to the Christian.
It would be, we can eat anything, right?
Oh, well, I suppose.
Let's say, for an example, in other words, these things are, you know, yeah, well, these are the, you can see the level of development or operating system.
Like, you can go back, you might have heard me say that the reason I focus on the biblical text is because it's first class.
And it costs the same to study all the rest.
So just for a second here, when you read the Koran, there's only one verse that tells you about the food, what's fit and proper.
And it says, do not eat the flesh of a swine or of an animal that has been found dead, you know, or roadkill or something like that, right?
Like a carrion, right?
Well, in the biblical text, the reason, see, in the Koran, there's no discernment.
It's just this.
So they eat camel, they eat rabbit, they eat all kinds of things.
As long as it's been freshly killed in halal style, and it's not swine.
But in the biblical text, what's interesting is it's much more literary, and it actually not only tells you the swine or the rabbit or what have you,
but it actually gives you quite a bit of information how to discern what is fit and proper to eat.
It gets quite a bit into a four-legged animal having to chew the cud and have a cloven hoof, right?
So if you run into an animal, let's say you and I are on an expedition somewhere, and we have lost provisions and now it's time to hunt,
and we see a new species of animal that we have never seen before, well, does it chew the cud and does it have a cloven hoof?
Well, it qualifies.
Like a llama, for example.
You see, so it teaches discernment.
It's a much more first class.
The difference between sitting and coach are first class, you see.
So this is not a criticism on the Noble Quran, let's say, but this is just a criticism on the level of information that you get.
So in essence, the term here of discernment, if you go to the Satanists again, or these other guys,
that's why I said earlier, they're simply, by their actions and even by looking at what Crowley had wrote and all the history that they're basing it on,
it's a paint by numbers.
They basically did some research to discover a certain validity in the spiritual realm that can be accessed through technical means,
which would be evocation.
That's why very often they had gone through great lengths to retrieve documents that were in archive for hundreds, if not a thousand plus years,
you know, things written on blood and human skin to recite, to evoke certain entities, right?
Because it's technical.
So all of this, you know, this society currently on planet Earth that has been removed,
which we're addressing here on, you know, this is an internet radio.
We're addressing the public.
It's very difficult to actually say it without sarcasm that pretty much the entire planet has been removed from the spiritual realm or any reality or knowledge of it.
So how easy would it be to stumble across the notion that the spiritual realm is valid,
and you can use certain technical access, you know, with these recitations of evocations to evoke minor imps and demons from the ancient world?
That's very plausible and very factual, and it's actually very practical, and they do it.
Right.
But that's all.
That's about as far as they can get.
And you can almost see that by the way they present themselves, you see, that it's a mishmash of a sort of a realism that is for self-purpose and self-gain, you see, and that's all.
They cannot function in the realm on a higher, meaning higher.
It would be the infantry level in the military wouldn't be an officer class or higher, you see, in the spiritual realm.
They're dealing with the low entities or lords of ancient times.
See, now that makes a lot more sense considering the fact that in order to, say, have a direct communication, because it's always astounded me.
Individuals who are preachers and, you know, and soothsayers, they allege that they're prophets, things like this, they come out and they tell you that, you know, that God imparted information to them.
And, of course, when they're speaking of God, they're generally speaking of what you would refer to as the chief deity, right?
And, meanwhile, in order to have that type of communication, you know, you're not going to lean your head out of your window and all of a sudden receive information from Japan without some sort of assistance.
And they're not. These preachers and pastors in the mainstream Christian religions, even off mainstream, are at best, at best, not the worst ones, but the best ones, would be like going to a preschool finger paint level, not even nursery, and they're arguing about, you know, who's going to get the chocolate pudding or, you know, some red fire truck or something.
They're so immature and so far removed. Now, if they do seem like they're getting any power, for sure, at this point, I would say, as a general broad stroke, what they're doing in private is different from what they're showing in public.
They most likely are working with some base elemental entities, because if you look again at the text, the relation of the higher commands has been cut off from mankind at this point.
You're on your own. It's not that you're not going to get any help, but there is no direct specific contact until a certain time in the future.
So this is a hard thing to say and a hard thing for people to hear, but the reason, again, we're saying it is because they're going to find out about this in the future, so might as well say it.
Well, certainly, and, you know, while we're discussing this, I am keeping an eye on the chat room, and a good question comes up, which leads me to want to go into another part of this discussion, because we sort of passed by a couple of terms here that maybe are worth, you know, dissecting or vivisecting just a bit more.
I see the chat as well.
Okay, so the question about whether these lower entities are gods or elementals, I think that it's worthy of discussion.
There is a great deal of difference between what someone would refer to as a god and what someone would refer to as an elemental, and I think it would be a good idea to define what one means by an elemental,
and then also answer the question about these lower entities, what are they in the hierarchy would be a good thing to explain as well.
Well, we could go backwards. The lower entities would be, let's use the military analogy, would be the guy who gets into the military, 90 days boot camp, has a GED diploma or not, has nothing to do with your intelligence or whatever, and you end up in the lower ranks of the military doing really menial, dirty stuff with minimal amount of training, and you actually interact with the opposition the most.
As you'll notice in the military, the higher up you go, the less interaction they have with the opposition, right? So they get the infantry, the lower ranks have the most interaction.
The gods, these lower gods, would be like the ox driver or the farmer, and the elementals would be like the ox, if we're going to use an agricultural setting.
Yeah, an elemental is completely indifferent to mankind or humankind, or these, there's no negotiation, there's very limited communication, there's actually Native Americans that still have control of certain elemental entities, and they're like entropic bombs, you don't want to evoke them because once they're evoked, they would indiscriminately just do what they do.
You see, there's no friend or foe, it's just complete indifference is an elemental.
The minor gods do have characters, and they do have positions and specialties and desires, just like people have personality, but again, they're minor, and they're the ones that have been interacting with mankind very heavily for the past, gosh, would you say two millennia plus?
Actually, since the beginning, mostly, but most people would consider divine contact in recent time, all the way back, even to 2,000 years ago, was of these lower gods or imps or demons.
Not to be confused with the biblical text, again, because remember, there's no religion on the planet that knows or does anything that's out of their text, so we're talking now about the phenomenon and the evocations that you've heard about through the, let's say, past two millennia, is all with lower end entities.
Right, even when you're talking about things like concepts of possession and stuff like that, we're dealing with very much the lower entities.
Correct.
No one is possessed by the chief adversary, let's just say, because that's the type of thing, that's like trying to pour an ocean into a drinking glass, it's just not going to work.
And there's no interest in that.
His interest is, again, if you go back into the ancient texts, is to run all of the worldly mainstream institutions.
So all of your governments are influenced by these chief adversary.
All of your religions, mainstream religions, are basically ruled or influenced and inspired by the main adversary.
All of your sciences, all of the major institutions of mankind are what he manages directly, through proxy, again.
Yes.
Now the very low ones, the ones that get their dirt under their fingernails are the ones that the quote-unquote Satanists are dealing with, the quote-unquote fringe mainstream religious groups are dealing with.
There's many fringe groups that have broken off from the main Christian group.
Those guys are also dealing with the small minor imps and demons.
Now this is not to cast who's good or who's bad.
What we're discussing is the structure.
Right.
And even to go back to your analogy of the military service, let's remember also that not only do the lower ranks have more interaction with those they're opposed to, with those that are their adversaries, there's that word again.
Not only do they have more interaction, but also the lower ranks eat together, live together, right?
And as you move up the chain of command in any military that I've ever heard of, there's an officer's mess hall.
There are separate quarters for officers.
There are, you know what I'm saying?
Like in other words, they not only are in a practical and in a mechanical sense behaving differently for their primary purpose, let's just call it at the moment, but they also have a completely different lifestyle.
Yes.
So you are literally talking about another, you know, like there's a reason for the hierarchy.
Another class.
Yes, another class.
There you go.
And different rights, different privileges, different access.
Yeah.
All of that.
And less education about what they're doing and their culpability and their responsibility.
Exactly.
It's going to be quite amazing in the future society to see the look on people's faces or when they get the realization that what we're discussing tonight is real and it has nothing to do with religion.
Let me just preface this in a way.
This whole show is really a preface because I think we might want to touch on it again.
But, you know, there was a time where these toxic gases, you know, like carbon monoxide that are odorless, tasteless, and colorless were called ethers, you know, back in the 19th century, 18th century.
People didn't know.
They left some coals in the room and they died.
They didn't know that it was carbon monoxide.
They didn't have a carbon monoxide sensor or analyzer at the time.
So it was very mysterious.
So this is, quote, unquote, ethereal information.
There's a lot of people today, especially in academic, you know, even though everything academics say never comes to a conclusion, when you start discussing something, they say, well, show me.
Prove it to me.
Right?
So this is not a matter of creating a validation and it has nothing to do with your belief or your faith.
This is simply stating information that is not being discussed as objectively as possible.
And we're not making this up.
Yeah.
Well, right.
This isn't about my spiritual point of view or your spiritual point of view, even.
This is about what is available based on what we know, what has been memorialized.
You know, like you said when you initially came onto my show, listen, this isn't about me or what I feel or think about it, really.
This is merely the report of the culmination of the information, you know.
Yeah.
And that's the truth here regarding this, you know.
And I know that I'm going to wind up getting some communication later that we were softening, you know, the evil that is, you know, Satan and Lucifer and the devil and all this other convoluted composite whatever.
And we were putting it in such a way that makes it not so frightful.
Right.
Yeah, but Chuck, you know, you brought up the term evil.
What's interesting, if you look at the ancient texts, both evil and good come from the head deity, not from Satan.
Now, the outcome of what Satan does is evil because he is the master of deception and the lie and murder.
Murder is to kill unwarranted, right?
But it wouldn't be killed unwarranted where, like a psycho killer or a serial killer or someone on a rampage, it would be convincing you to go out and buy the gun.
And then once you buy the gun, convincing you to pull the trigger on yourself kind of thing.
So at the end, it's like, well, you know, I didn't pull the trigger.
He did, you see.
So but what people again, the lack that this is the lack of maturity of humankind right now to discuss this subject is unfathomable.
That's why I was kind of joking earlier.
There's only five people on the planet that are interested in what day it is.
You know, that's kind of sarcastic, but it's pretty close to the truth.
The level of maturity that is required to look at the information objectively, this would be like something in the military.
Again, using it as a metaphor, it would be reserved for the elite special forces information, you know, and it also requires a level of maturity and fortitude like it's not uncommon.
I think I could say this was some of the SEALS training used to be where they go into a submarine and they descend down to about 90 feet.
And the guys are basically shot out of the torpedo area of the submarine underwater.
You know, I mean, that's really a lot of fortitude and toughness, you know, and also knowledge.
You've got to know, you know, if something goes wrong while that's happening during that exercise, what to do.
So this is the level of spirituality that we're discussing tonight.
And anyone can access it, because I don't think we're speaking beyond a fourth or fifth grade level.
And very often one might get the comment, like, I don't understand what you're saying.
We don't use, quote, unquote, big words or things that are hard to define.
And we tend to give references and definitions as well.
What might be difficult for the audience to digest on what we're discussing is, A, part of the cosmic censorship.
It's not time for people to hear this and understand it.
And we're saying this humbly, not out of arrogance.
But it needs to be said, because, again, one of the purposes of us coming together and some of the feedback we've gotten, it's about time that someone is saying this.
And one of the reasons why you and I got together to be sonic partners on the Ocelli and the Greek show is because no one else is saying this.
If other people were able to discuss this on this level, I would not be doing the Ocelli and the Greek show with you.
Right. I mean, literally speaking, that bumper that I put together for the show was not a matter of bluster or trying to present us with some sort of swagger here.
Actually, it was quite literal.
You know, this is quite honestly the type of information that that no other media outlet is even attempting to understand.
Forget about relating, you know, forget about discussing exhibiting for the public.
But I mean, this is literally the type of information that not only won't they touch it, but they won't even begin to acknowledge that it needs to be discussed in any reasonable way or disclosed or disclosed.
And meanwhile, you know, people conduct themselves under a lot of false premises.
Now, wait a minute. Think about that for a moment.
People conducting themselves under false premise based on an ignorance to, you know, for lack of a better term here.
Yeah, it's not.
What does that sound like to you?
It sounds like everyday life on this planet.
You know, we've got about 10 minutes before the top of the hour break, and I just want to do a quick laundry list rehash of the topic tonight.
So this way we could probably either get some questions or actually I want to hear you maybe expand on the second hour from your experiences or your studies, Chuck.
But this is the laundry list of the topic tonight.
Would you?
We've got about 10 minutes.
I think I could do it in a few minutes.
Are you ready?
Sorry if I do it.
Got about like five or six before the bumper musical kick in, but go ahead.
OK.
Very simple.
Satan is the chief adversary.
The word Satan just means adversary.
Anyone taking an adversarial position is satanic.
In terms of the cosmic reality and how it relates to Earth, there is minimal if not any contact with this head adversary with mankind.
This head adversary to mankind inspires, controls both directly and indirectly all mainstream institutions on this planet right now, bar none.
OK?
Mainstream meaning more than three people involved.
So, yes, your alternative medicines and your alternative news and your alternative people are involved in that as well.
Yes.
Sorry, guys.
What people are calling satanic or Satanism that's in practice is nothing more than the revival of ancient imps and demons and lords from ancient Canaan, ancient Babylonian, ancient Egypt, thus the names if you look them up.
These people are not very familiar with the spiritual realm and they're actually performing what they're doing with a paint by numbers by reviving ancient necromacons and ancient prayers and things to evoke these beings.
But as a whole, they are just as clueless as the rest of the population.
And I would just leave it at that.
And just to finish off, when people are defining good and evil, what they have seemed to have forgotten or been obstructed from is that the head deity, right, is the one that brings both good and evil.
And that is the laundry list.
Well, right.
And just to punctuate that last point, after all, there is only one deity, according to the record, let's just call it, that claims to have created all things, it seems.
And not rebutted.
Yeah.
It's not been rebutted.
It's not been disputed in a significant way.
And quite honestly, one could say that if you have created all things, then you must have also created the good and the bad.
You know, much like people point out regarding a lot of different issues, when you set something into motion, the consequences and the benefits can become evident, but you still have the responsibility for having set this thing into motion.
Correct.
So therefore, in a very simple way, and I know I've now broken it down to kindergarten level for you, but the fact is that when you break it down in a very simple way like this, one could say, how could you even begin to argue with the concept that all of this actually emanates from the chief deity if there is in fact a chief deity which created all things,
which in my estimation also means that they may have actually created all of the other entities in fact.
Correct.
So there you have it.
The truth is that if you have everything stemming from one particular root, then it is nothing more than the leaves of the same tree, you know, to put it another way, right?
Yeah.
This doesn't taste very good in people's mouths.
They don't like that, right?
They want that sickly sweet candy stuff that puts holes in their teeth, you know?
So this is not, this is, what we're discussing is, it's not artificially sweetened or flavored, which is going to make it difficult for the audience, but, you know, we assure them that later on they will discover these things to be true.
Not at the moment.
Because if you try to live what we're discussing and function informationally with it, I assure you, you will not have any friends and no one will want to listen to you.
Unless you have a very dedicated spouse or a loyal dog at your side, you will be quite alone.
Yes.
That's the bottom line, see?
And there's that bumper music.
So when we get into the second hour, I think we're going to discuss some of the feedback that we got specifically.
And who knows where else it might go, but please feel free to give us some of that feedback in the chat room at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Go there and put it in.
Or message us any other way.
Ocelli and the Greek will be right back.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us with free education.
Well, that's obviously effective, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America.
All the information they provide is free.
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, then?
Exploiting commonplace corruption.
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
They never censor, hang up, or cut off their guests.
Well, that's no fun, is it?
Or they created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative, and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shills and scum.
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from.
Exposing commonplace corruption.
Helping vulnerable people without a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
And creating a fantastic commercial free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream and alternative media shills and scum.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the American
Practically narcotic
Freedom
Oh yes, I like it very much.
Radio
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth?
And none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant.
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC.
Is non-GMO.
And is 100% gluten free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat.
Builds muscle.
Contains 53% protein.
And feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel.
For depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care.
Anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate.
Invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
PTSD.
Anxiety.
Depression.
Epilepsy.
Vaccine injuries.
Cancer.
Alzheimer's.
Muscle and joint pain.
And even diabetes.
Introducing the world's strongest and purest CBD drops with zero THC.
Exalto delivers 5 times more CBD than other brands at a fraction of the cost.
One bottle lasts all month and can be used in any situation to maximize your body's own cannabinoid repair system.
No heavy metals.
No solvents.
No black hemp paste.
Just pure CBD crystals and organic hemp seed oil.
Pure.
Clean.
Powerful.
Exalto.
Use coupon code HALO20 to get 20% off your first order.
Go to crystalpurecbd.com and use HALO20 to see what Exalto can do for you.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
The network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents the only broadcast...
The second hour begins on Ocelli and the Greek episode 10.
And we have recapped it at the end of the last hour.
So if you missed it, I do advise that you go into the archives at American Freedom Radio under Ocelli and the Greek and catch up.
Because this show is most certainly different from even the other nine episodes, I assure you.
Because we have actually broken down and discussed a topic which is often on the tips of people's tongues.
Pardon the homage to the strange aspects there.
But either way it's often on the tips of people's tongues.
It's often out there on the media circuit in one way or another.
Whether it's the satanic panic that every once in a while in its proper cycle grips the mainstream media.
Or it is the continuous references to the Luciferian, the devil worship, the synagogue of Satan, etc. etc. out there.
That grips the alternative media.
I assure you that you have, if you missed that first hour, missed a discussion you would have heard nowhere else broken down in a unique fashion that is not being heard elsewhere.
So we're going to continue with that discussion, I assure you.
But I don't know, do you want to get into the listener feedback here?
Or would you like to just continue on with the discussion and we'll do that toward the end?
What do you think?
Go Greek.
Yeah, I'm here.
I thought I was unmuted.
Okay, what would be the most pertinent to the discussion perhaps, because we can get into specifics about the power on both sides.
Power meaning, again, not good or evil on that aspect, but what power is given for dealing with what's being dealt with right now and how it's being dealt with.
Yeah, and to me the definition of power essentially, and you can correct me if I'm wrong, is merely the force by which work can be done.
So there's no real positive or negative connotation to that.
It's simply the provocative force, if you will.
That's all power is.
Sure.
It's just like energy versus power.
Energy is everywhere, but it's the power's ability to do work.
Okay, actually on the quote-unquote good side, if you were in the evil side, let's look at it that way.
Let's call the good the higher up rank, up until the ultimate rank or highest deity, and let's say the evil would be the lowest.
This would be in the common people's mind, but that's not necessarily true.
Well, and it's not a quantitative judgment either, is it?
No, it is quantitative, but not qualitative.
There's more power with the higher deity obviously than the lower, like a sergeant in the field can only call on maybe a few more troops or a jeep or a tank,
but the four-star general could call on the entire air force and a fleet and a legion of troops.
Yeah, but depending on the purpose.
I mean you don't require an entire legion of troops to kill a single target, but you know what I'm saying.
One could call, the other one can't.
Right.
Okay.
So on the lower entities, by the way, like the Temple of Set and these other ones, because there's a half a dozen of them that have been functioning in the past 500 years or so.
Right.
They have discovered paint-by-numbers.
Paint-by-numbers means you're not an artist, you're not really qualified to produce something, you just happen to find something that pulls it off close enough.
It's like cheese, it's a cheese food, not a real cheese kind of thing, but it still passes when you order a cheeseburger kind of thing.
It's very functional, but not necessarily qualitative.
Yeah, or for instance, you go to Walmart and you buy yourself your cheap piece of furniture that you assemble based on the instructions and the materials provided.
It does not make you an artisan who can create furniture.
Exactly.
Very good.
That's the spot.
These guys have been used by militaries, by kings, by scientists.
They go and they do their  and financial people, by the way.
Pharmaceutical companies, governments, military, intelligence branches of the military, PSYOPs, branches of government.
Again, scientists would be some of the alchemists because scientists still call on them.
Pharmaceutical companies for sure, medical people, religious people.
What these guys do is they're called in for all those different purposes to come up with a new material, which might seem alchemical in the beginning, but then can be scientifically explained through rationalization.
Just like carbon monoxide could not be rationalized without a carbon monoxide detector.
So in the military, they're used to actually ward off armies.
They could be  these quote-unquote Satanists would be  and they're not Satanists, by the way.
They would be evoking local elementals or local lords or minor gods to evoke bad weather, evoke aerial phenomenon, sights, visions, things like that.
Well, right.
Now, didn't we discuss this on a previous conversation perhaps before we did this radio show actually where I told you that I was quite confident?
And you agreed with me actually about the idea that there were sort of magic men which were introduced into what we might refer to as ancient conflicts that would evoke the god of thunder, this kind of thing, create lightning and hailstorms and stuff like that based on their seemingly rarefied knowledge and stuff like that.
And people have taken it as a piece of mythology that there were these magic men that could hold back entire armies or decimate them with bad weather or storms rising or the seas swallowing boats, things like this during different  like I say, very ancient battle scenarios.
And people have taken it as the stuff of legends, but the reality is that these were true accounts that have been memorialized not even just in what you would call religious or spiritual text, but it's been memorialized in several different ways actually in multiple cultures all over the planet, right?
Oh, completely. There's rarefied knowledge that we would call scientific, which means knowledge of things, let's say.
But then there's the aspect of the deific aspect where there are gods that man have evoked to create things.
You might have an approaching army and you might want to evoke a deity that turns baby head-sized rocks into crabs for you.
And that would really be very effective on getting an army to stop.
This has been done. I mean, not necessarily that specific scenario. There might be a god that could be evoked that would bring a massive storm almost immediately, or that would bring screams coming from nowhere, blood-curdling screams that would scare people away, or gods that would asphyxiate an opponent.
We're talking about 20th century now. We're not talking about ancient legends.
Well, but that's the thing, though. You can find in many what they describe as legends sandstorms being evoked, provoked, created.
The Asian deity that they describe that actually manipulated lightning.
The Nordic, what they call legends or songs and stuff like that, talking about the evocation of, well, let's see, I believe Odin is one of them, right?
Raiden is another one. There's a bunch of different ones.
Thor, yeah.
Thor. All these different gods and their reactions, their influence over the atmosphere, over different physical elements, being witnessed on a massive scale.
Animals, people.
Animals. The influence of animals. That's another one. The influence of animals.
Yeah, the birds. Specifically, the birds are the most common. Birds and fish.
And even on occasion you find stampeding animals and things that were directed to do so by one of these, quote, magic men or shamans or whatever.
I just wanted to step on you there, but here's a concept. Have you heard about the bees? Everyone's discussing, oh, the GMO crops are making the bees go away.
The insecticides are making the bees go away.
What people fail to realize, and they will discover in the future, is that there is an elemental entity behind the bees.
And when that entity decides to pull the bees, the actual physical insect from this realm, the bees disappear.
The particular entity that's behind the bees is a very sensitive one, where the one that is behind the cockroaches is not.
And this is not a joke. I'm just stating that because have you heard how cockroaches can take 900 times the radiation of a human?
Oh, yeah. And they're also prolific. You've got a couple of them. Robust. There you go.
Yeah, and the locusts. And locusts have an entity behind them.
You see, this is why the problem is never the information. The problem is the maturity of the mindset of the audience.
You see, it's kind of like if you were to discuss these things by picking an audience that is relatively interested in the topic,
or do we discuss these things simply because they're not being said anywhere else?
I think the latter is what we're engaged in here.
So that's why I said maybe we could go either way, discuss more of the specifics or take some of the chat comments to see what feedback there is there.
I just briefly looked at it, but the point that you were making also about, I wanted you to continue perhaps if you can,
what you've studied about it, and we can maybe go back and forth on that.
Like you mentioned the Nordic entities and others and other things you might have discovered,
because that might be a good place to kind of let the topic flatten out a little bit,
because there's so many ways, so many directions we can go with it, you see.
Well, there are so many ways you can go with it, and here is the truth.
When one takes the time to study the customs and the belief systems, let's call them,
of various cultures all over the planet at various times in history,
you begin to recognize that there is a convergence of many, many ideas,
that a lot of these concepts, like I said, a magic man would be brought out.
This is the type of thing of myths at this point, according to the scientific,
or let's call it what it is, the science-ism that is the religion now,
that we see all over the planet, is that there is a concept that all of these things are just
a primitive thinker's way of trying to interpret things which they did not understand.
But in reality, there were individuals that had knowledge that is rare to the majority,
and quite often that was a priest class of sorts,
and I don't say this about one particular region of the planet.
I don't say this about one particular culture.
It is not any more profound, let's just say, among the Europeans than it is among the African cultures,
than it is among what we might call the aboriginal peoples on various continents.
All of these concepts seem to prevail, no matter what the language is being spoken,
no matter the alleged level of contact between individuals.
You'll find that the evocation of what you would refer to as lower entities,
being exactly as you described, mostly localized,
because let us not forget a lot of these lower deities are, truthfully,
only in particular geographic locations.
That's where you find the differences in language,
that's where you find the differences in the alleged character,
as it's being related to outsiders, let's just say.
They have jurisdictions in terms of geographical jurisdictions, the lower entities.
Not to be confused with angels, which is another topic.
Yeah, but definitely worthy of discussion here,
because again, there's this concept that this Lucifer character was that high angel and all that.
Should we define that real quick?
It was someone, you see, where does it come from, the biblical text?
There's a tripartite there.
There's one that, they're all men, there's three Lucifers, basically, a repetition.
They don't exist at the same time in three different periods, and they're all men,
and they all, if you find where it is in the biblical text, read it in context,
or you might have to read a chapter, yes, that means more than 50 words,
you will find out that what is used in common is the grave,
that this particular individual is in the grave, in the grave, in the grave,
and there's a repeat of him, and you won't find the repeat of him
in that particular part of the text.
In other parts of the text, you will see that there is a repeat,
but it is someone that is of fleshy concept, not of a spiritual concept.
When I say concept, meaning they're flesh and blood,
and they were born of a woman, just like a human, let's say.
So that is, have you ever heard the term,
just let, when someone who doesn't know what they're talking about,
just let them speak, and they actually reveal that what they're saying
isn't true or factual.
Yeah, the adage that a fool only becomes a fool
when he decides to open his mouth and reveal that he is,
like silence seems a lot more intelligent.
Yeah.
And the thing is, we're speaking only because the silence at this point
is deafening, and the need for saying these things, I believe,
is great for the five people that are willing to listen.
But what you, the reason I brought the, you brought up the,
you actually filled in what I was, I couldn't remember that it was
the fool aspect of it.
If you go into the media right now, alternative media especially,
all you hear about is this Luciferian thing, right?
And they don't know what they're talking about at all.
It's a very, very, very heavy dummy load.
And the reason why is because A, they're immature, and B,
they're cosmically, they're censored.
The chief deity does not want them to see it because it's not time yet.
And this pretty much puts the entire population of the world
under that blanket.
But I briefly just brought up angels.
Angels are messengers, and there are fallen messengers as well,
but we're not discussing the, not to confuse these lords or gods,
as the, quote-unquote, dubbed as Satanism,
with the angelic presence because, as I said earlier,
the head deity has said for two millennia there will be no contact,
direct contact from any of his agents,
but it doesn't mean that he won't send any angelic presence, you see.
There's, again, a difference there, and that could be...
Yeah, he's not coming to visit or have a conversation with you,
but there may be a message sent now and then via telegram.
Yeah, yeah, right.
So that's why all of these, quote-unquote, biblically-based mainstream religions
that say that they saw a particular biblical character,
that is a demonic figure, which I wanted to cover.
There's a couple of individuals in, I think, alternative media
that speak about how one of them was visited by Satan, right?
It looked just like the Hollywood Satan, and evoked the name of J-E-S-U-S,
and the thing went away, right?
So that means that, you know, evoking the name of J-E-S-U-S works.
Well, what was really going on in the background
is you have two minor imps or demons saying,
we're going to go play a trick tonight, let's go find this guy or whoever,
and you appear as the Hollywood Satan,
and he's going to most likely call on this J-E-S-U-S character,
and I'll appear as him, and you go away,
and we're going to just go have a drink after this, right?
Great, okay. This is exactly what they're doing.
They're playing on people right now.
So I just had to drop that in there, because you do hear that a lot.
People say they see these little aliens,
and they use the name of J-E-S-U-S, and they go away.
They have no idea that they're being pranked by both sides on that.
Well, yeah. Well, there is that aspect,
and then there's also the people that are just, you know,
let's be blunt, are quite full of some sort of manure.
Not sure if it's from the bull, or if it's from the pig,
or if it's from the human feces variety,
but one way or another, they're certainly full of some.
Okay, and that's something that happens as well,
but when they have a legitimate sighting,
yeah, this is a game being played, because...
Yeah, absolutely. And they fall for it every time,
because it keeps it going.
It's a false flag event. Wow. Go figure.
Wait a minute. A spiritual false flag.
Correct, and it's happening constantly.
Yeah, because here's the thing.
Where do you find out about a Christ figure,
and in a major religion, they'll say that it's from the Bible.
But if you actually ask them to tell you anything
about the Christ figure in the Bible,
you'll notice that they know absolutely nothing about it,
and anything that they think they know is not from the Biblical text.
It came from our old friend, Simon Magus.
So it's just an absurdity.
It would be as if, you know, here is a tall statement to make,
and it's difficult for people to hear,
but it is easier to find the nuclear launch codes
in your country's arsenal than discuss any Biblical character,
because every Biblical character is still 100% secret.
Why? Because you have to actually read the text to find out about them.
Anyway, I know that was a little sarcastic, but...
No, it might actually help if, you know,
you haven't actually seen the whole movie,
and someone presents you with the script to look beyond the cover.
That might help you.
Yeah, if you want to understand what the presentation is supposed to look like.
Here's the interesting part.
You will not find any iconography.
Let's not harp on the main religion, because this is the Christian era.
The first thing they put in front of you is a crucifix, right?
Or this character with long hair and a beard on a cross.
But it's very clear that if you're never really subject
to any of that iconography or statuary or story that they put on TV about that,
and you went to the text first,
you will see that during that scene that the iconography is based on,
you know, the crucifix and all that, right?
During that, what's memorialized in the text,
this has nothing to do with what you believe in or not, right?
This has to do with, you know, let's say you have a recipe for chocolate chip cookies.
You don't expect to have a turkey with stuffing and gravy if you follow it, right?
Well, yeah, look, if you're looking at a menu at McDonald's,
you know, and I know how repulsive that is, but bear with me.
If you're looking at a menu at McDonald's, you don't expect to be served tacos,
because it wasn't on the menu, you know.
And it's got nothing to do with whether you're a vegetarian or not.
That's really what it is, yeah.
So if you actually read the text about that particular scene that's put in front of you,
and it's amazing how people are still censored no matter how much you say it.
There's a scene in there where Pontius Pilate, the prefect governor,
the biblical Christ was surrendered to him for execution,
and he said, I am washing my hands of this matter.
I did a public hand washing. They even show that in Hollywood.
But then after that, it falls apart.
But if you read in the text, it says that I'm washing my hands of this matter.
I see no guilt in this man, and I'm returning him back to you,
meaning the Judean authorities.
You will never find the word Jewish in the Bible, or Christian, by the way.
The word Judean is used anyway.
So I'm returning him back to you, the Judean authorities, to use your law.
Now the Judean authorities operated under the law of Moses, not the law of Caesar.
And also there was something made a retort by the Judean authorities,
but we can't do it because we're under your law.
He says, I'm making this exception.
So under the law of Moses, it's death by stoning,
and we know that he was nailed to an almond tree with two other men,
and everything was burned after the execution, according to Deuteronomy.
But in this case, the Christ was taken down and put in a grave,
and the grave had to be guarded because the Judean authorities
wanted to claim the body to burn it, according to the law.
That's why if you see in the meme there that the Roman guards
were guarding the body for three days.
Hang on just a second, let's not gloss over that too quickly,
because I think you went a little fast.
So why would you say that?
What was the law regarding this?
Tell us about that.
Capital punishment in Mosaic law is death by stoning,
but a high crime is you're to be nailed to a tree and stoned to death.
So the crime that he was accused of was the highest crime,
which is blasphemy under Judaic law.
Murder and blasphemy would be the highest crime.
So in this case, there is no Roman crucifixion with three crosses.
So what I'm trying to say is the mainstream religion
is showing you something that was invented about 400 years after the fact.
It would be as if the U.S. Constitution was written today,
and George Washington has an iPhone, and he got his hair done by Vidal Sassoon,
and of course he had a Humvee, and he crossed the Delaware with a speedboat,
and Stinger missiles were fired at the British,
and people would say, oh yeah, that's what happened.
This is ridiculous, so out of context.
Yeah, this is the level of insanity on the planet today,
and we're talking about several billion insane people.
I think Christianity represents a billion plus,
and what's going to be a big surprise, and it's going to be peaceful,
is when the quote-unquote Christian faithful or believers find out,
let's say September 11, 3 B.C. is when the Christ was born around 6.40 P.M.,
not December 25th, let's say when they find out there was no crucifixion,
let's say when they find out this, that, and the other,
is it going to be peaceful, or are they going to hang all their pastors,
and preachers, and the Pope, and burn the churches, and all this stuff?
That's an interesting question, isn't it?
Because if you deceive one billion people so poorly,
because it's a very poor deception,
anyone, they all carry their Bibles around,
all they need to do is read a few pages in there,
and see that they've been totally defrauded.
The question is, how can a billion plus quote-unquote believers
be so blinded, so ignorant, of something so simple?
The only explanation is cosmic censorship.
They are not allowed to see it by the high command.
That is the only explanation. There is no worldly explanation.
Like in the cartoons, take a quote-unquote Christian believer,
strap them to a chair, and put toothpicks or something to prop their eyelids open,
and force them to read several verses in the Bible
regarding what we just said. They will not do it.
They will not do it at all.
They cannot.
It's cosmic censorship.
You cannot blame their ignorance and fall into such a trap on them.
There is no other explanation.
So, yeah.
Well, here we go.
And I want to introduce this in because, again, we're being interactive,
and we are live at the moment, and this is the benefit of hearing it live.
You know, there is some discussion as to what the name of the adversary is.
Is there a singular adversary, and is there a name by which it can be called?
My contention is there are some that are well aware of the proper name,
but they don't really know what to do with it.
Okay.
Yeah, there is a name, and why spoon-feed it?
Get yourself an interlinear, and go to Genesis chapter 2,
and start going through that, and look what the word in Hebrew is,
and that would be the name.
And what I mean by that is that all names are exempt from language.
If your name is Charles, and you move to China, and they write your name in Chinese,
when they speak it, it should sound like Charles.
That's why one of the most ridiculous things I've heard is like, you know,
a guy named Tony, hey, Tony, you know, you move to China,
and you've got a Chinese name that doesn't sound like Tony.
I'm like, no, you've got a new name.
That is not your name is Tony.
And if they write it in Chinese or Japanese or any other language with a different type of,
if they write it in Arabic or Hebrew or Japanese or, you know, different types of alphabets,
it should still sound phonetically like Tony.
What I mean is that all names are exempt from language.
Names are a sound that identify someone, or like when I say Chuck,
you respond because that is a sound that you identify with yourself, you see.
Which I have become accustomed to, and causes me to pay attention based on my conditioning.
Yes.
Right, so when you go to the biblical text, and why?
Because it's first class.
I do like flying first class if I were to, not coach or steerage in a ship or something.
I would, because it doesn't cost any extra.
There is, in the Koran, he is referred to also by a certain name.
But if you go to the biblical text, because this is a biblical nature,
it has nothing to do with whether you believe it or not.
It has to do with are we adhering to the chain of custody of information,
or are we changing it and making it up as we go?
We're not supposed to do that as rational people.
But if you want to figure out names, you just go to look at the language of preservation in Hebrew or Greek,
and you will find the names.
Most likely in the Hebrew, because what's considered the Greek New Testament,
that was originally written in Hebrew as well, but translated to Greek for recordation purposes.
So anyway, there's the answer, an indirect answer to that,
because we don't mind spoon feeding, but chewing your food and spoon feeding you,
that gets a little gross.
Right, and I'll give you a little hint about what we mean by the sounds of names and things like that.
When one studies Egyptian mysticism, which has been completely misrepresented as well,
but when you study that, you will find recurring sounds,
which are introduced into the language.
One of the most common ones would be the sound of Ra.
That sound, in and of itself, has particular connotations,
and it causes, in that system, certain entities to pay attention.
It's not a proper singular title necessarily.
It's resonance. It's the concept of resonance versus dissonance.
There you go.
Two tuning forks, yeah.
People will discover in the future, they've been so dumbed down and dummy loaded,
that spirituality is what you personally believe in, and it doesn't really exist,
or science is this, and all this other crap.
Humanity is going to be in a big surprise when they find out
that there are beings that are non-corporeal, non-physical,
and they do operate under a technology.
They have a system of science and methodology that humans can also access.
It's just not right now.
It's just like if you heard children shouldn't play with matches.
It's a level of technology that is based on ethereal concepts.
I'll throw this out.
If you read the biblical text with comprehension,
there are things in there that if there's a hurricane
on the other side of the planet, you can pretty much take it out
based on knowledge that's in the biblical text right there.
It's in front of everyone, and no one can see it.
It's the most interesting thing to see how everything is hidden in plain sight.
So anyway, I just thought I'd throw that in there.
Well, there you go.
Here's two concepts I'll throw out there really quickly
to get people to understand what you mean by that in a slightly different way.
Simply because you close your eyes and decide that in your belief system
there is no walls in front of you does not mean that if you walk forward,
you will not be injured by the wall you crash into, number one.
Number two, simply because you don't believe that carbon monoxide exists
and you don't believe it will harm you does not mean that if you are trapped
in a closed space with a good amount of it, that it will not knock you out
and potentially kill you just the same.
So it doesn't change.
Your beliefs change nothing about what is truly in the world around you,
and that stands to reason for the corporeal things that we're talking about
as well as what they might call the ethereal things that we are also discussing.
Would you say that's fair?
That's fair. An ether meaning of the sky or the heavens.
And the interesting thing here is anyone telling you things are based on their beliefs,
that is the work of the adversary.
The academia is work of the adversary.
The purpose of the adversary is to make sure that there is no consistency
in you finding out who you are.
If you keep, meaning you, meaning if every man, woman and child on the planet
knew who they are, who they were or who they are,
they will find a level of consistency that will grant them power
that would render the adversary powerless.
So what the adversary does, he gets you to believe that your beliefs are fine
and because he's in control of all the governments of the world,
all the governments say freedom of religion, right?
You could believe whatever you want.
So now you've divided and conquered, not by physically dividing and conquering,
but by mentally doing it, by actually giving the people a feeling
that there is this ambiguity that you have to create your own reality.
How many times have you heard that, you create your own reality, right?
Work of the adversary.
I mean, we can go, there's a list of like, you know, reincarnation.
You create your own reality, your intent, all this other,
these are all works of the adversary to make sure that you never have a firm grip
or a handle on anything that you can then share with the person next to you
that they can have a firm grip on and be sure-footed, you see.
So, and the aspect of pride and all these things.
So, yeah, so this is, one thing we didn't touch on real quick is the,
we've discussed the evocation and, you know, asking, getting power,
asking for power and evoking these lower end entities.
The higher deity, the highest, basically tells you to leave this all alone
and set yourself apart from it and shield yourself from it.
You see, the, you don't change anything if you assess the situation.
Like special forces, their whole thing is about, you know,
assessment and adaptation, right?
That would be the way the higher entity works according to the text.
The lower entities are the ones that want to change things
and through belief systems.
And, yeah, it's very interesting and it's not working out very well for them.
And, yeah, so how many times have you heard,
it doesn't matter what you do in private as long as you're not hurting anyone.
Well, that doesn't work either.
You know, all of these things that you hear out there in the alternative media
and the mainstream, forget it, the mainstream is irrelevant at this point,
are works of the adversary as well.
You create your own reality, reincarnation, your intention, your belief.
Yeah, all these things are still very much influenced by an adversarial goo, I call it.
You know, it's like nothing firm, there's no rules, there's no, yeah.
Right, and this type of methodology is extremely, you know, omnipresent, let's just say.
Oh, yeah.
Among all of these people that seem to have these great intentions,
that seem to be the adversary to the adversary, you know, so on and so forth.
But the truth is, and I'll bring it right back to the concept that we started the show with,
where you were talking about, you know, in a violent sense,
the adversary would be the one who turns around
and convinces someone to pick up a weapon
and then convinces them to pull the trigger on their own skull, you know,
in order to create the scenario where that person's death has now occurred.
Okay, as opposed to someone who charges at them, firing away and flailing with a knife
and et cetera, et cetera.
I always found it funny because once, when I was very early on on radio,
I had stated something very much like that.
That, you know, I would prefer to be the one who convinces someone else
to pick up their own gun and use it on themselves.
And I was told that that was probably one of the most evil things I could have possibly said.
But the reality is that when it comes to the weapons of mass distraction,
that are out there, and yeah, I use that term a lot.
The truth is that being led from the reality, being led from the provable,
plausible and, well, honestly, from the, you know, the inescapable, okay,
by all of these ideas, which are then transmuted into beliefs,
well, the same mechanism works, not only in the spiritual sense,
but when it comes to the examination of science, not science as they present it to you,
but science in a true sense, you know.
The same thing comes down to when you're studying historical events,
the very same thing occurs.
The people that really wreak the most havoc, the individuals that wreak the most havoc,
that keep people quite a bit far from the truth, quite a bit far from the reality of anything,
are always those that have a grand tale to tell, okay, that misleads everyone,
that involves them in the tale, as opposed to the actual situation,
the actual evidence, the actual reality that they allege to be presenting.
And I say, again, doesn't that sound very much like every church, every synagogue, every mosque, every temple?
Doesn't that sound very much like
Every cult.
Every cult group. You just mentioned these are all cult groups,
which is people are getting together because they feel like they have the same belief,
and they're very strong on their coming together and congregating,
but if you notice that what they're coming together for is completely fiat.
That's it. That's really the ultimate conclusion, yeah.
Based on inspiration from the adversary.
And later on, you know, people will find out, you know, there's no reincarnation, I got fooled.
Well, the adversary then will say, well, there was never any proof of it,
no ancients ever wrote about that or anything, that's stuff you guys made up,
it was, you know, you should have been more mature, you had access to all the information.
Holy crap.
Batman.
You know, this whole thing, you know, the crucifixion, right?
It doesn't matter who believes in it.
They go to war with both sides killing each other, bearing the same cross, right?
And, yeah, so, I mean, let them do that, you know.
Look at the Arab, in the Middle East part, they enforce that their women wear the uniform of the oldest profession, right?
And they think it's righteous.
By the way, speaking of that, if you read what they call the Noble Quran, there's over six or sixteen, I'm not sure,
I think, series or verses in the Quran that say that if you were to run into a Hebrew or an Israelite or a Judean
that is going back to the land that was given, you know, through the biblical sense, let's say,
you are not to disturb, you are to help him, you are not to get in his way.
It's actually a curse to fight them.
But what do they do?
They say Israel should be, everyone should be thrown into the ocean, because they've never read their text.
So that's their form of, that's just like the Christians have their Santa Claus, that's the, in the Islamic world, that's their Santa Claus.
They will not find it.
It's interesting when you push a Christian regarding that's not in the Bible, they always say, when I say always, 99%,
well, who wrote the Bible anyway?
Who knows? Who cares?
Now, if you push a Muslim regarding his, I'm mentioning these two major ones, you know,
about, you know, why is he fighting the quote-unquote Israelites or the Hebrews in Israel, he says,
well, that can't be in the Quran, because the Quran was written to be simple.
Well, okay, let's go take a look at it.
No, I don't need to look at it, it was written to be simple.
That's their litany.
They won't discredit it, they won't discredit the text that they allegedly subscribe to, like the Christians do.
And the Judeans, they don't, they're not familiar with it at all, and they just ignore it,
and they say, we have to do what the rabbis tell us to do.
So, you know, and the Hindus have their own litany, and the Buddhists have their own litany,
and every religion is just insane right now.
Why? Can you blame the people directly? No.
The only conclusion, in an Occam style, you know, Occam, the Occam's razor back in the 1300s,
is the simplest thing in this case is that they're cosmically censored.
And guess what? You will find it in the biblical text that does state that humanity will be censored until a certain point.
So, and you see the evidence of it right now.
There you go. So the dummy load prevails by design, really.
Correct. And yeah, it's very difficult.
And here's the thing, humanity requires a certain level of sympathy for it,
but because they're so ignorant, it makes them so violent and dangerous
that the sympathy thing kind of wears out real quick, you know,
and you just, the best thing to do is set yourself apart and just avoid them.
Other than, of course, you know, coming on internet radio late at night like this.
Thank you. That was great. I like how you threw that in there. Perfect.
Well, listen, we only have about 10 minutes left,
so I don't know what you want to dedicate those 10, 11 minutes to,
but I would definitely suggest that if you missed it up to this point,
you the listener out there, you need to take a good gander with your ears
at the previous discussion, because once again, you will never find a discussion about Satan, Satanism,
the adversary, Lucifer, Luciferianism, so concisely laid out,
and especially by two guys who didn't even script it out.
You know, I got to say that this almost felt like a presentation that we had prepared,
and yet it was not.
Well, yeah, I think 90% of it is just showing up, you know.
I always used to tell people, you know, well, I don't know what to do if you hire me.
I said, it doesn't matter. If you show up, it's 90% of the work.
You know, you're here, so we're here, and we just discuss things as we know them.
Nothing is scripted. You know, it's just from our little pea brains, you know.
There you go.
And also, you know, there's several emails we've gotten on the Ocelli and the Greek site, you know,
and there's a few requests, a lot of thanks.
I also want to give thanks because, you know, it shows that there are more than five people out there
listening and responding, and we try to reply to them timely.
There's questions for you and I both, which I believe we try to reply to.
We've gotten certain topical questions, which I think may not be ready for prime time, would you say?
We might want to do, later on, maybe a private section on the Ocelli.com.
Does that sound about right to you?
Yeah, that sounds great because, yeah, there are two websites that do contain some of this stuff
outside of American Freedom Radio, so Ocelli.com has a section on Ocelli and the Greek,
but there is also Ocelli and the Greek.com, and I think we're going to provide
some sort of special presentation, which, who knows, might be in part on AFR
and then in part on the websites regarding some of that feedback,
you know, and directly answering some of these things.
We've done it in a written form, really, truthfully, mostly you,
but, you know, you've let me in on it and I've looked at some of the emails myself.
I also want to take the time to thank our friend Edwin, who every week, actually,
makes a donation, you know, to this show, which...
Thank you, Edwin.
Truth be told, yeah, Edwin, I've got to say, I do appreciate you, sir.
His consistency is noble.
Absolutely, and he is the only one who has been consistent about that kind of thing,
and I'm very sure he's listened to all of the shows,
and I just wanted to show some appreciation for the effort which is being put forth by us
and also by Danny and American Freedom Radio,
because, after all, I just think it's one of those things that's incumbent upon us
that if we're going to do a presentation like this,
we should thank someone now and then who has taken the time, effort,
and given of some of their resources to support our efforts.
So, thank you, Edwin.
Anyway, I don't know what else you wanted to add.
We're down to those last few minutes, but...
Well, there's a question also to the Greek here in the email.
This is the second time it's been asked.
Can you please explain in detail what happens after death regarding our individuality
and if we lose it, and so on, you know?
I think that might be quite a bit to discuss in public.
We will keep that subject in the forethought,
as well as water and a couple of other things,
which we might touch on briefly, maybe in a future show,
but we will touch on it in great detail on ocelli.com and the members area in the future,
only because it'll be directed topically,
that you'll know that if you go to the members area, you'll see that specifically,
and also, we can give more detail and definition without laboring the public,
as we do every, what they call Saturday night,
with maybe details they don't want to hear,
which they could tune out, but I believe it'd be better done in private.
But, just real quick regarding death,
you have incarnation, where you come into the world,
excarnation, where you die,
and then there's reincarnation, where you're put back in.
And this is everyone's first time around,
sorry guys, sorry to tell you,
no one's ever debated me on this,
and I'm not looking for a debate,
but this is everyone's first time around,
and there is going to be a second time around as well,
and that's why, if you look where reincarnation comes from in the Eastern teachings,
it's always a singular form.
So there's incarnation being born,
excarnation being dying,
and reincarnation or resurrection.
So, these things will be discussed in the future,
maybe we'll touch on it on some show,
but I think water and this and a few other things,
we might reserve for private.
Well, Life After Death might actually be a good show to do in two parts,
one public and one private.
Correct.
Water is one of those things that might end up being quite extraneous,
you know, to the general audience,
and I think that's something that would be, you know,
a rarefied piece of information that might be worthy of that.
So, I think that's what we ought to do with that.
Yeah, and the most, just regarding, let's say, those two topics,
we can give some nuggets right now, gold nuggets,
they're actually short but heavy,
if you drop it on your foot, it'll break your big toe.
You guys ready?
In terms of, like you said, Chuck,
Life After Death is exactly it,
because the life after death will be a life without death,
because death will be put to death.
So, now you will have nature no longer subject to death.
So, go wrap your mind around that.
Now, with water, water is simple.
Keep it in the dark, keep it cool, and keep it moving,
and if you can't keep it moving, it must be in an ovoid-shaped container.
All liquids or fluids in nature that are not flowing or moving
from point A to point B, let's say, or beyond, are in an ovoid shape.
And the temperature is 4 degrees Celsius, 39 degrees Fahrenheit,
and keep it out of the light,
and that's how you increase all water quality,
and there's so much talk about water,
and these things are not mentioned.
That's why, you know, there's hundreds of things out there,
and people that are quote-unquote experts,
and I assure you that's just dummy loading you,
which is you've got all this energy to take in information,
and you're just wasting your time.
Out there, when I say out there,
the only place I would suggest is the principles of Victor Schauberger
is a good place to start, and we will get into those details in private,
or in the future.
Right, right, and, you know, again,
I want to thank everybody who decided to tune in,
whether you're catching it live,
hopefully you're catching it live,
but if you're not catching it live,
and you went to the American Freedom Radio archives
under Ocelli in the Greek,
or if you've caught this some other way,
you've gotten it from a friend, etc., etc.,
I do appreciate you giving us the time
to present this information,
which is not being spoken,
which is not being related by anyone else.
So, there we go,
and yes, we do pay attention to the emails,
and all of that.
I don't know, is there anything else that can be said before
the lightning comes in,
the sound of lightning, I should say,
the sound of thunder, excuse me,
that comes on, and that rain,
and all of that,
that will close the show on,
is there something we should kind of punctuate
this entire presentation with?
Avoid the dummy load, of course,
but first you have to recognize it.
You know, avoidance of a trap
is knowledge of its existence, right?
Exactly.
And you're not going to make any friends,
and there aren't any groups out there to join
regarding what is the truth at this point.
Still, you can pretty clearly say that
what is advertised is not necessarily what things are,
so we're just saying what we're saying
because they just need to be said at the moment.
And that is about all that can be said about that.
Or, you know, Forrest Gump,
I just thought of Forrest Gump
as that came out of my mouth, quite honestly.
That's pretty funny right there.
Yeah.
The truth is coming,
but it's not going to be what people like,
and the time isn't now
because there are still things that people like.
You know what I mean?
Right.
Yeah, but when he would say,
that's all I've got to say about that.
That's all I've got to say about that.
Or stupid is as stupid does or something.
The dummy load is as the dummy load
fixes or does.
Yes, thank you.
So, thanks once again,
and guys, like I said,
ocelliandthegreek.com and ocelli.com,
both of these websites will contain information
and all that kind of stuff.
And thanks once again to tuning in
to Ocelli and the Greek
at Americanfreedomradio.com.
We appreciate you.
The CIA are cutting into my drug running
and my gun running.
Big pharma, psychotropic drugs
are making my customers commit suicide
before my hitmen can even whack them.
And then they get depressed
and get prescribed psychotropic drugs
and commit suicide too.
They're trying to become the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money,
you don't even get protected.
I cannot pay taxes,
and if I can't find the money,
the IRS are going to take my thugs.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine
and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction
and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done
to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs,
and that's to support American Freedom Radio.
Capiche?
So what are you going to do?
You're going to go to Americanfreedomradio.com
and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
American Freedom Radio.
Freedom, freedom, American
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat,
improves digestion,
and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government
banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug
to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant
for over 80 years,
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana,
and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world
to know these basic facts
and to help people understand
that hemp protein powder
is the best kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder
contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory,
non-GMO,
and has no side effects.
call 888-910-4367.
888-910-4367.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil
can do for you,
only at hempUSA.org.
PTSD, anxiety, depression, epilepsy,
vaccine injuries, cancer, Alzheimer's,
muscle and joint pain,
even diabetes.
Introducing the world's strongest
and purest CBD drops
with zero THC.
This is five times more CBD
than other brands
at a fraction of the cost.
One bottle lasts all month
and can be used in any situation
to maximize your body's own
cannabinoid repair system.
No heavy metals, no solvents,
no black hemp paste,
just pure CBD crystals
and organic hemp seed oil.
Pure, clean, powerful.
Exalto.
Use coupon code HALO20
to get 20% off your first order.
Go to crystalpurecbd.com
and use HALO20
to see what Exalto can do for you.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
We all know that they're not telling us the truth.
So stand up for your rights,
demand the real medicine,
and your right to use it and grow it.
This is Rick Simpson,
and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres
in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue,
with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth
is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information
with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish
with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice
and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver
quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
Thank you for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role
in the future of America.
Be as generous with us
as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing
AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs,
and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.