American Freedom Radio presents the only broadcast information show of the media outlet
would dare to understand the sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
Episode 7, Ocelli and the Greek on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Yeah, it's me again. So, and I'm of course joined by the one and only individual who calls himself the Greek.
How you doing tonight?
Hey, pretty good. Thanks. But, you know, you got to remind everyone and myself sometimes I'm the only Greek I know.
So, let's, yeah.
See, having been from the northeast, I run into a lot of people who identify themselves as Greeks, but not necessarily because of their heritage.
Yeah.
Well, if you look up what that word really means, oh, the Hellenics are the people. Greeks could be something else.
But that's for another day, perhaps. So, how are you?
Well, you know, do I want to answer that question honestly or should I just give you the answer?
It's a cordial.
Yeah, exactly. It's one of those things, cordiality and, well, there you go.
It's a nicety. They call it niceties. You know, if anyone wants to know what the word nice means, look it up.
It's not what you think. And I'm looking for a day when people will say what they mean and mean what they say. How about that, you know?
Well, wouldn't that be fascinating? After all, a dictionary does not give you the actual definition.
It gives you a general usage just so you have a point of reference, but doesn't really tell you the meaning of the word.
Right. Diction.
Literally, diction. Right.
How to pronounce it.
Which is why it's phonetically spelled in there, right?
Yeah. Etymology would probably be the best thing to look for, but they've also discounted that because they said, well, this is what words used to mean or this is how they were used at one time, you know?
So, you know, forks and knives used to be for eating, but now they're automobile tools, you know? So, anyway.
Well, yeah, and they can be weapons, especially if you take them on a plane along with your box cutter.
Right. Yeah, sure. You ever see photographs of those large planes and it says, do not step here, you know?
Because what happens when you step on it, your foot goes through the plane, you know?
Yeah, well.
You know, that's maybe, I don't know, you know, if there's nothing new under the sun, how could there be anything new?
Well, I don't know if it's under the sun, but of course, the news out of Paris, out of France, out of all of these wonderful terrorist attacks, as per usual, you know, you got guys who go shooting places up and blowing themselves up with vests.
And it sounds like the opening barrage from a spy thriller movie almost, where that is the prelude to the massive attack that is about to be unleashed.
And, gee, is that art imitating life, life imitating art? Is it just BS? Did it actually happen? Is it simply just do for those that are French?
You know, what is the speculation and is it new and is it even relevant at this point?
It's not relevant other than it's on the planet.
And, I mean, look, gangs shoot each other. Remember the days in Chicago?
I mean, we don't remember them, but one could look them up historically. They've been memorialized in film as well.
I think someone wrote a book called The Gang That Couldn't Shoot Straight.
But, yeah, so this is all no news is good news.
But the thing about understanding that there's nothing new under the sun is what is it leading up to?
You know, it's like saying, hey, the ice cream truck will be here in an hour.
If you start hearing, you know, the traditional bells that they ring when they start coming down the street, let's say, you don't have to say, well, what's that?
Because we already said it'll be here in an hour, right?
So, you know, what'll be here in an hour or two or not that soon, but in the future, is a Middle East union.
And what's important is for something so new and so radical and so powerful to come on the scene, people are going to have to be desynthesized to it.
Or, you know, it's going to have to be in their common, let's say, daily lives as accepted to focus on that part of the world,
no matter how far away or how different it is, even though in secular history they do state that civilization, quote, unquote, originated there.
So, yeah, these are things that are no surprise.
You know, what is what is surprising and is not is probably what I'd like to talk about in a short fashion,
which would be the concept of responsibility and how it's escaped people's minds and how twisted it's become.
Whenever you have people in a responsible position, meaning they have a duty to others, OK, if something goes wrong,
usually they come out with a level of sympathy that garners what we might call not necessarily an apology,
but some remorse to the people that they're supposed to protect.
But instead, what we've been seeing for a long time now is who are we going to blame?
Right. And to muster up the anxious crowd into a certain direction, this has been going on for a very long time.
Now, just by simply observing humanity, one can see that that is common amongst children in a very young age.
So I think we've said before where even when you see someone that appears to be an adult,
I assure you their development was arrested at around the end of their formative years, between eight or nine.
You know, when your second set of teeth come in is when people typically on this planet have stopped maturing spiritually.
And what I mean by spiritually is their mind.
And this is why they're so susceptible to still being treated like children.
You see, you can teach a child to stay in their bed because they think that the bogeyman might, you know,
emerge from under it if they were to set foot on the floor.
And that way they'll stay in their beds, they'll do as they're told, and they'll cower in fear until they pass out,
which, well, that's kind of an accurate description for the way that people are heard about regarding these archetypal,
you know, bogeymen that they keep transposing from one demonized culture to another on the world stage.
Is that too complex of an idea I just gave out? I don't think so.
Well, you know, also, Chuck, my point was I was referring to the leadership first.
And second of all, you know, the average person on the planet, or man or woman, again, it also holds true for them.
They don't want to look at anything beyond, let's say, what they might have been intimidated not to look at.
They're actually intimidated into looking at things and not looking into others.
And they're, of course, motivated through penalty, you know.
Right. That was my point as well, is that whether it is actually substantial or it is imaginary,
it is still a matter of being motivated via penalty.
I mean, ask anyone the question, why is it you should not murder?
And believe it or not, normally their immediate knee-jerk response is to say,
well, I don't want to go to prison or I don't want to be put to death.
Not that it would be, well, the wrong thing to do or the right thing to do, right?
I mean, where is it, oh, it's about the penalty.
You know, why is it that you don't, I mean, I'll tell you what, we'll take it, we'll rope it in a little bit.
Why don't you beat your wife? Well, I don't want to go to jail.
Oh, boy.
Right? Hey, stop me when I'm lying.
No, no, I got you. Yeah, well, that's unlawful to do that, but either way, yeah, I get you.
It's just a silly-ass situation.
You know, and here's the thing.
People talk about enlightenment and being educated and whether it's secular or what have you.
It's just a complete joke.
When you look at society, the only way to actually perhaps achieve any of that
is to fully, completely set yourself apart and retract from society.
And it doesn't mean that you won't be able to function in society,
but you know, you shed yourself of what these things we just brought up are.
You know, and that's why you'll never find that quote-unquote enlightenment
that people seek in the Eastern culture within their groups.
You won't find not a one of them, being slightly as such.
You won't find quote-unquote spirituality in these groups in the Western world at all.
Not a one of them.
Even if you look at the folklore, when you had cities and villages,
when they were looking for the sage or the master,
and that's another thing mastership has done these days is no more mastership.
Very, very difficult.
Where did they go?
They had to go out of the city and into the forest or the desert, you see.
So the interesting thing here is, well, we're doing this sonically.
It's electronic, let's say.
It's a digital format, completely intangible.
Almost the listener decides to plug in and listen, you know.
And that's another idea that we could lead on to,
is that we now are actually just establishing,
and indirectly establishing a small franchise called Ocelli and the Greek.
And just to make a shameless plug, the site is ocelliandthegreek.com,
and you'll notice there's an eye chart and an ear and a yellow,
what do they call those, emojis, that is a donate button.
And we would greatly appreciate that.
We've got equipment to get, and Chuck needs compensation of some kind,
meaning something coming in to keep this thing going, if it's of value out there.
And yes, it is a credit-based economy.
All right, so shamelessly, if anyone or someone can shoot some credit this way,
it would be greatly appreciated.
All right, credit where credit is due.
Of course, American Freedom Radio also.
If you go to americanfreedomradio.com, there's that chat room,
and there's a donate button right above that as well.
So, you know, just to be fair and balanced about it, right?
Absolutely, and I figured I'll do you, you do the station.
And there's going to be an effort in that direction
with all the station hosts coming in about a week,
which would actually behoove anyone to join and tune in,
because it's going to be very interesting.
It's going to be actually a really good show
that's going to go on for perhaps the entire day, if not better than that.
Right, it could actually be two days worth, depending, I guess.
And it looks like Suzanne Posel will be involved in it.
I'll be involved in some way.
You'll be involved in some way.
I'm sure Vinny and some surprise guests will also arrive.
And, you know, it'll be a unique presentation at the very least,
and for a good cause, because, well, American Freedom Radio,
we'd like to make sure that we can do this without having to plug things
and without sponsorship and without the annoyance of having to listen to
doom and gloom and all that other stuff,
which is really against the ideals of the station here.
But, gee, people do sort of implant that stuff into their recorded spots and things.
It is the way of things anymore.
After all, what does sell anymore except fear and sex?
And, hey, for some people, they're interchangeable.
You know, it is what it is.
But there you go.
I mean, there's a reason why it's called fear porn, folks.
Anyway, we don't like to participate in that, and especially not on this show.
There's no point in fearing the inevitable, you know, so that's the way that is.
So setting oneself apart, though, is an interesting concept that you spoke to there.
How does one do that?
Well, you have to do it in your spirit, which is your mind first.
You know, there's an operating system.
We've discussed that, I think, in the first episode,
very basically using the metaphor of a computer.
The operating system is your law.
And I'm not talking about traffic law or tax law or things like that.
It's, you know, how you actually function.
And that comes from your deity, from your god.
And I know that's been a very bad word in, quote-unquote, modern society.
But sorry, folks, I'm not making this up, and it's not my belief.
It happens to be true.
You can have 100 people standing around a blinking computer,
and they all have different beliefs on how to get it going.
And if you suggest they need to load the operating system, you're going to catch flack
because they don't want to see that you know how it works, you see.
And anyone can know.
Well, and if you don't know, you just heard it.
It comes from your deity.
And if you don't have a deity, then if you believe in the laws of the state,
the state is your deity, and April 1st is your holiday.
It's very simple.
You cannot escape that.
If you're anthropomorphic, man or woman, your law comes from your god.
And that's, you know, you can actually say that a very young child in its formative years
until about it gets its second set of teeth has no concept of this,
and they actually view the parents as their deity.
So this is very simple.
This is, you know, we're addressing your average surface-dwelling earth inhabitants
been so far removed from these basics that there's going to be a slight return to it as we go into the future
and less of a denial of what is really going on even though it's not perceptible.
But once you establish a law form, you live by that law form.
And if you see that it's not congruent with, let's say, the person living next to you
or down the street or within the society that you're in,
you are to still exist in that society impeccably, you know, being good behavior, let's say,
but do things your own way if the freedom permits so.
You know, what you eat, what you wear, how you keep time, you know, how you do business,
how you raise a family, all these laws come from your deity.
Right. And something that's observable, by the way, in all of the texts of the alleged,
I say again, religious orders on the planet, you know, something that is consistent in all their texts
seems to me that you're supposed to abide by the laws of man and God both simultaneously.
I see that alluded to and suggested in just about every text I've ever read,
I mean, with the exception of possibly, you know, those that are the abomination to those said religions,
really the inverse reaction where you just simply flip everything on its head and work in reverse,
they do tell you to abide by the laws of, you know, man and God.
Yeah, and the reason why is because man was made initially to live in a society where he was lawful
and he just answered to his God, but they didn't want to answer to the God, so the gods put leaders over men.
I know this sounds kind of nutty, but you guys will find out that it's true in the future,
because one of the things about doing this show is telling people what's going to be coming in the future
and you don't have to be psychic or sensitive or all that other moronic stuff,
not to discount being psychic or sensitive as being moronic, but the time for that is over now.
That doesn't work anymore, and that's quite obvious to those who know.
So on the other hand, discussing about what's coming, people will see this,
but the leaders are put in by the gods, sorry, and the gods, they don't act in futility,
and they have an IQ of two million, so you're not going to outsmart them.
So at this point, if you've abandoned what people might refer to as natural law,
even though I've never heard anyone discuss natural law lawfully,
it's kind of like going into an abyss, like talking to a Buddhist about enlightenment or something.
You go into this abyss, there's just this level of ignorance that is predominant,
which is normal, because these religions and these philosophies are not there to enlighten you or enrich you.
They're there to entertain you. It's purely for entertainment purposes.
You can go to all of these religious practices and meditative practices.
I assure you, no one is going to leave better, other than the people running the operation,
because they'll have, you know, I like the gurus, you know, and the Swamis or whatever,
they got the brand-new Lexus out back, you know, and everyone else is riding the bus.
But anyway, so this is for 2,500 years, humankind has been under a massive censorship by a malevolent cosmic dictator.
Oh, yeah, you'll find out about that in the future.
There's no reason to discuss that in any detail at this point.
And all of these religions and philosophies are strictly for entertainment purposes, strictly.
I assure you, you're not going anywhere, and you're not going to be enlightened
or enriched by any of these organized groups simply because there's no law.
You could look at them, you know.
Right, that's true, and I'll tell you something else.
I used to be extremely entertained personally when, you know, in the days of the satellite dish
that you had to actually be able to point in certain directions in order to receive certain transmissions.
I used to marvel at the endless amount of televangelism that was out there,
and in many forms far beyond the best-known, you know, Christians, the Pat Robertsons of the world,
and, you know, et cetera, et cetera.
But there used to be all sorts of alleged televangelism of one form or another,
and not even all Christian, not even all Judeo-Christian.
A lot of religious programming, right, that used to be available via the satellite feeds.
And, you know, nowadays, of course, it's all handed to you via your service provider.
You know, the same guy that can bring you the pornography can also bring you that,
and it's just about as relevant and just about as truthful.
Well, that would be the circus, what they call the church.
Yeah.
And it has its benefits because, you know, if you look at, quote-unquote, holidays were always built around sports,
and the concept of the coliseum or the circus, by the way, circus means cirque, circus,
or church means circus, cirque, get over it, people.
Yes, you've been fooled for many, many, many generations.
It doesn't mean because you've been doing or believing in something for a thousand or plus years means that it's right.
It just means that your life is really short relative to the scam, okay?
You're right.
You see, there's the contrast, you know, people usually are scammed within a short period of their life,
and they get over it, but it's really hard to get over it when it's multi, multi-generational,
and over 2,500 years, they cannot see it.
And one of the purposes of you and I getting together here once a week is to pontificate on that, for lack of a better term,
and not that we really want to do that, but that the, I don't know if this show is terminal,
meaning how long we're going to be meeting here and discussing these things,
but starting in the next few years, there are going to be some changes,
and it's not going to be what people think right now.
And they're going to be extremely positive in their minds because when things get wrapped up,
you have to be aware of everything, you see, in a legal sense or in a lawful sense.
Before you go from one end of the procedure to the next,
you have to be fully aware of each consecutive cumulative procedure, you see.
You can't just keep moving through without finishing one side off.
So right now, you're going to be looking at a concentration of everything going to the Middle East.
So, and there's all these questions about, you know, all these different societies and these different religions,
and I'm telling yourself and the listeners,
everything that you know or think you know about these religions and these traditions is worthless at this point.
Now, why? Why would you make such a strong statement?
Because they were set up initially to take up your time.
There's absolutely nothing there.
You know, if you look at the Islam, it has nothing to do with the Koran at all.
If you look at Judeo-Christianity, it has nothing to do with the Bible at all.
And so on and so forth. All of the religions of the world are as such.
So the people have been successfully disconnected quite well and are on their own for quite a long time.
And it's going to be reversing in the near future.
It's going to be quite a thing to watch.
If you know what's coming, if you don't know what's coming, you'll be sucked up into the frenzy.
What do we call it when people get excited about something new that seems right?
Mm hmm.
So, yeah, it's it's really going to get interesting.
And the focus on the Middle East is going to increase by the day until this period ending around twenty eighteen.
What you call twenty eighteen on the Pope's work schedule, which we didn't.
What did we say? Well, today lawfully is the twenty first day of the ninth month observationally.
And by the Pope's work schedule, it's November, which is the eleventh month.
They call it 14th day, 2015.
Yeah. You know, it's funny when you see 2015 and you turn on the boob tube and they tell you these are the dinosaurs.
They lived 60 million years ago. How come it's not the year 60 million, 2015?
Interesting, because it doesn't matter. None of this matters. It's all for your entertainment.
In that case, all things are terminal, really. You said, you know, is this terminal? Is that terminal?
In fact, all things are terminal at this point.
And just like a terminal illness, we seem to be living in a terminal society without the velocity, you know, which is interesting.
Anything else?
We never just, you know, it's interesting when you read old docs and books and things and people didn't talk about time.
They do now because there was something called the age of clocks that came about three, four hundred years ago.
So just like people speak differently now with smartphones and computers, you know, I'm running Windows.
You know, OK, you're running Windows, OK, or you're running an Apple system.
You know, what the hell is that? See how the language changes with the technology.
Yeah. I do my work via the Apple. Somebody would think that you're making applesauce, you know, 30 years ago, 40 years ago.
You know, what are you doing, planting apples or what?
So what we're trying to do perhaps is discuss, make these discussions relevant to that point of view.
You know, is it really, how human is it, let's say?
And I keep using that word, even though I don't. It's kind of difficult to define that term and have it apply to men and women.
But it means when you say human, it kind of gives you a feeling that it goes beyond race, creed and color and religion.
It means the entire group on the surface, let's say. So that's why I like using that term.
It's a wholesale term. But the purpose of saying these things is, first of all, they're not even being said anywhere else.
It would be, you know, here's the thing, Chuck, if someone else was saying these things, you know, we've got better things to do.
I mean, it's late over there on the East Coast and it's getting late here.
So, you know, we would just sit back and hear someone else saying these things and be glad that someone is saying it.
But unfortunately, no one is. So feeling compelled to do it.
Oh, yeah. And that's the key here. I mean, after all, look, I have found it relevant to start speaking
because I didn't hear people saying what it was I know needed to be said.
Now, it might have been on a more rudimentary level when it came to historical revisionism that, you know, I started doing this radio thing that I do.
But the fact is that I found it remarkable that no one was addressing the very obvious deceptions in a direct fashion.
They were simply, you know, parroting one another and speaking to the same set of talking points without having any knowledge about what it was they were saying.
And in that way, I found that it didn't matter whether you were talking about alternative media, mainstream media, the fringe, you know,
the guy with a transmitter in his basement that you might be able to pick up on your long or short wave radio.
It really didn't matter. Everybody was behaving like a parrot instead of actually analyzing things.
And so I felt compelled to speak. And that was, you know, long before I imagined doing a presentation like we do here once a week, you know.
But I do find it remarkable and definitely worth mentioning that most people that would take the time to listen to what we're doing right now,
and I do mean you who's listening to us right now, most of you are extremely willing to understand that you have been deceived.
You're extremely willing to understand, to recognize, to admit, to fully accept the idea that you've been deceived about your history, about your culture,
about your government, about your monetary system, about your rights. Yeah, I held up air quotes.
About your privileges. Yes, I held up air quotes again. About the processes of law.
You're willing to believe all of that. And yet, most of you still adhere to the doctrines that are alleged to be attached to various spiritual orders,
which are handed down from the gurus, from the priests, from the individuals who are the, again, alleged authorities on, well, natural law, the truth of the universe,
what is correct or what is fit and proper to do as far as your conduct goes.
You accept these things without question, generally, and it doesn't matter. Once again, it's irrelevant as to which religious order, how you identify yourself.
Even those calling themselves atheists have now ascribed to a particular order. It doesn't matter because you're standing in opposition to your own order.
And atheists can't escape it either because it's part of the operating system. If you have a pulse and you're upright or sitting down and you can speak and think,
your law, your operating system comes from your God, period. And you can fight that all you want. You can disagree with it all you want. It's irrelevant.
It has to be said, and it's about the most subjective thing. If you're going to hear anything, that's about the most subjective thing that can be said to mankind at this point.
And the thing is, I guess I could speak for both of us, we're not anti-religion or anti-spirituality.
Religion just means something you do regularly, like what is lawful, and again, it comes from your deity.
And the problem that I see, the reason why I'm speaking, is because mankind was made. Yes, you don't like that idea.
And we can maybe talk about the schizophrenia of people discussing anthropology and problems with science in one breath and having their feet on both sides,
choosing what they like and then using what they, you know, anyway. But there's no schizophrenia here, I assure you.
Mankind was made to join a particular group of the highest order of the spiritual realm.
And just because he's been put under this censorship and flooded with these low-level entities, meaning spiritual beings that all the religions are based on,
and not to be confused with the texts, by the way, which makes it confusing, right?
And I think that people should, the people of the planet for 2,500 years have had this incredible inferiority complex by pursuing the traditions and religions that they do.
Now, again, not to be confused with what's memorialized in the texts themselves, right?
Like you won't find Easter Bunny and Santa Claus in the biblical texts, and you won't find women having face covers in the Koran, right?
And also, or if you're a member of quote-unquote Islam, you would be pro-Israel, not anti-Israel, right?
There's over half a dozen verses in the Koran that directly forbid anyone from being prohibitionary or anti-quote-unquote Hebrews, let's just use that term generally, occupying that part of the world, right?
Or quote-unquote what they call Jewish, which is not biblical either or whatever.
So this is very interesting, and that's why I brought up the term schizophrenia, which means split mind or a split state, and it should not, yeah, that should be left in the past, and it will be.
It's still a very high level of operation for most people on the planet.
So these are the things that we want to bring up, that people are a lot better than they think they are, and you deserve better, but not at the moment, obviously.
Well, right, and you know, the way that I look at things is a little bit different too.
It's just that, like I think it's extremely noteworthy, because you talk about the idea of putting a veil over a woman, and how a woman should be covered, and et cetera, et cetera,
and this is supposed to be, you know, something of purity, to promote chastity, and all this other nonsense, when in reality...
It's the opposite.
If you read the text very carefully, you'll understand that any woman who is completely covered up like that was actually a prostitute.
The uniform of that time, not just in that specific document, other documents that predate that as well, that was a normal uniform of the time.
A good reference, a very solid, clear reference would be in what's called the scriptural or biblical text, I believe it's in around Genesis 38, a woman was identified as being such by her covering.
And of course, you know what's interesting, if this is a shocker, we'll just install little shockers, even though no one cares.
It's a shocker for me.
There's several verses in the Koran that command the reader to acknowledge the laws that Moses had procured through the biblical text, and he has to go and study those.
Did you know that?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so how many Muslims, quote unquote, are doing that? None, zero.
And if they do, they would never call themselves Muslim, there's no way, because you would go and look at it and see that it has to do with a set of laws and a set of ways of behaving when your feet are on this planet, not to form a religion.
So all these things are, we're talking about a level of insanity, meaning not well, of humanity.
And again, speaking out right now is way too soon, but I think we're throwing in things that are specific enough that anyone who's listening can do a little bit of research, other than just being entertained.
Because I think I prefaced earlier, for 2,500 years under the spiritual or mental censorship that humanity has been under, all of these things that people are taking seriously are here for your entertainment, including war.
War is a sport, believe it or not.
In many older societies, it was even up until recently, it was considered as a rite of passage into manhood.
In many societies, it's still mandatory as a rite of passage into citizenship and what they call manhood.
And however you want to define that word, citizenship in all definitions, whether you're a slave or have a right to the, let's say, dominion.
So either way, these things are not understood and not taken as they should be.
And that's henceforth the Ocelli and the Greek show.
Right, and you know, if you really get down to the secrets behind a lot of things, let's acknowledge one thing.
When you discuss the proper way of keeping time and things like that, well, that's the proper way that you are supposed to keep time here on Earth.
It doesn't necessarily mean that that is the proper way to keep time.
Now, that sounds, again, almost schizophrenic, which schizophrenic isn't really of two minds or anything like that, although that's a common usage for it.
It's a torn, yeah.
Yeah, it's torn, and it's torn in such a way, really, where connectivity is actually encouraged.
A little bit overstimulated connectivity is what happens in a schizophrenic mind.
But we'll put that aside for the moment.
Time doesn't require a number and doesn't actually need to be quantified unless you're in a finite state of existence.
See, that's the thing. It's the subdivision of the finite.
Now, if something is immortal, eternal, without the, well, the handicap of death, then time is not even a relevant point, is it?
It is, only because it is a construct for recordation of events, right, number one.
And number two, it's to be able to keep accurate appointments or make appointments.
But, see, if you're not constrained to deal with something that is finite, right, if you're not dealing with it, then why is it even remotely relevant as to record keeping?
You don't require records if you know all things. You need no point of reference but yourself.
You see what I'm saying?
Yeah, but there isn't necessarily a requirement, but here there's two ways of looking at that.
On a neutral point of view, it would err towards keeping records.
On a benevolent point of view, for sure keeping records.
On a malevolent point of view, you wouldn't.
You see, even when you go and buy a very common object, you open the box, and it could be a toothbrush, believe it or not,
and there'll be an instruction manual in there, very simple, or a blow dryer, or something very common.
Because there's a benevolent creator, whoever made that, you know, and is benevolent.
And if you notice, certain items don't have it, and they're of a lesser quality.
Because remember, even in the future society, when entropy and death are done away with, eventually,
there will still be the level of creation going on, but on a different level.
And communication will still be, you know, going on.
Even if you look at the ancient texts, there's books, right?
You ever, you've heard of like, they call it the book of life, or the records, or this or that.
So they, obviously there's something more to it.
And one of the secrets in the quote-unquote, what people call the Bible, in the opening of the Bible, there are two trees.
There's a tree of life and a tree of knowledge of good and evil.
And those trees are defined in other places as not being of the botanical variety, but of the literal variety.
They're actually written objects that had writings on them.
So this is for, perhaps, another discussion, or maybe the members area one day.
To explain that, and show how it defines itself.
Like, really good code, by the way, has the primer within the code.
Well, right, but that's because all of it is the same, and there is no levels to it, you know.
What happens, in my mind, see, because I, again, approach things from a slightly different point of view than most do.
You know, where you mention quality, quality becomes an irrelevancy to the divinity, especially the supreme divinity.
Because, once again, if not constrained by, if not restrained by, any of these particular, you have no need to be constrained by laws, even.
If you are the end-all and be-all of all things, if there is no end, if there is no way that you can be measured in and of yourself,
then what is the point of measuring other things, right?
Because they are measured in quality based on exactly how much can be extracted, or how much usage can be applied to it,
how long it survives, how long it remains useful, how long it sustains itself.
But if there is no point at which, you know, a level of sustaining a particular way of being is even relevant because it just is sustainable on its own.
Well, it would be beyond, let's just say it's a level of quality that's beyond category,
and because it's such a beyond category of what we can comprehend at this time, we could say there's no quality there that we comprehend.
Because the one thing I want to remind everyone, including ourselves, is we're locked in a state of immaturity of the mind, you know,
because we're still attached to the soul and the body.
So there's a level of immaturity, meaning, you know, like fruit when it's not ripe, let's say.
But you can, I mean, you can conceive what I'm trying to approach here.
The fact is that we are still sort of bound, governed by the limitations of the observable, you know.
Sure. But in terms of the quality, just to interject another thought, is that there would be such a, on that high level,
there would be such an extreme level of consistency that it wouldn't be an issue as it is here.
Precisely. That's exactly my point, is that all things would become consistent to the one that is without need for different levels of quality, you see.
Right. Or degradation, right, because the consistency is flat line and it's always, it doesn't become an issue because there's nothing to contrast it with that's degraded.
Exactly. I mean, you know, for instance, if one ant, let's just go to the ants, and I do like ants, by the way.
They're really fascinating creatures. But ants, if one ant murders another ant, there is no weeping, there is no punishment,
there is no crime that has been committed, there is no sin, which sin is a thing that I think we should get into in the second hour, by the way.
But either way, there's no consequence, there's no level of consideration from a higher order of creature like, well, human beings.
By contrast, they are higher in, well, quality, I guess, than the ants, right?
Well, let's say the ants are the most noble in the insect kingdom when it comes to literary works.
Okay.
At least, you know.
But yeah, there's also an experience I've had discussing something with a quote-unquote Freemason about that, where he said, I'll paraphrase it,
you see, people that follow, let's say, a law from a god are following a tyrant, and they're lower than a cockroach,
because the cockroach doesn't have to follow those laws, and the cockroach has more sovereignty and freedom than those who follow laws.
And I was like, wow, that's one hell of a freaking logic.
And when you ever wonder why, when some of these guys are out in public, they don't hold a door open for other people.
You know, you can imagine what's going through their heads.
But either way, there's a level of logic, again, even that I see as a form of entertainment, because it has nothing to do with being in harmony.
The purpose of these laws is being in harmony with your environment.
You know, people believe in something they call ethics and morality, at least they used to.
Well, it changes.
But the earth hasn't changed.
So what happens, if you look at the ancient texts, it talks about if someone does something wrong, he can't bear the guilt until he knows he did something wrong.
Once you explain to them what they did was wrong, then they bear the guilt, you see.
So at this point, most of humanity is totally clueless of what is right and wrong.
They've been propagandized and politicized.
And this has nothing to do with the boots on the ground, even though they are the agents, you know, other human agents that have convinced them.
But it's part of this cosmic censorship and cosmic dictatorship that they've been under for two and a half millennia.
But what's happening now in the end of this cycle is that the actual planet itself and others are witnessing against people.
If you actually look at these ancient texts very carefully, it's the mountains, the oceans, the animals, the earth, the sun, the moon, and the stars that are going to be calling foul on humanity, because humanity is so far removed from these things, you see.
And that's enough.
And this sounds like the stuff of fairy tales and stuff you have to believe in.
No, but we're not saying that I believe in it, and I'm just reporting what I've studied.
And it's important to say it, because guess what?
It's not being said.
Well, right.
I mean, like, I found it extremely striking, and this is going to sound completely incongruous, but I'm very sure you're going to understand why I say it.
The cartoon, okay, years ago that I saw, which was about Mark Twain, and I think it was Huckleberry Finn or, hmm, let me think for a second.
Oh, Tom Sawyer, actually, and the girl from the story, whose name eludes me at the moment, going and visiting these different levels.
And at one point they go to a place where they visit Lucifer, and they start talking about the concept of evil, and the children are quaking about it, and this and that.
And Mark Twain just makes faces during this, and it's a claymation thing.
It's pretty interesting.
At one point, though, the figure depicted as essentially the devil, let's dumb it down as much as we can, turns around, and when the concept of evil is introduced in the conversation with this entity, the entity replies,
well, how can I be evil if I don't know what it is?
A concept that I'm very sure went way over everybody's head, but there you go.
But once again, if you don't have the contrast, if you don't have the concept, if you don't have the understanding that there is guilt to be had for committing an act, if you don't have that normalcy bias already introduced, loaded into the operating system, then...
Yeah, you go unabated. You keep going as you were.
Well, here's the interesting thing. You want to drop a shocker, because people look at scriptural and biblical texts, and they just look at them, and it's interesting.
There's a lot of people out there giving their own views on what these texts should say, or whether they're valid or not.
And most of these people speaking on these subjects sound like they're reasonably hunting for the truth and knowledge, but I feel for them on one end, because obviously they're looking at the text, and they don't understand anything in it.
So they build an entire career trying to explain it on a tangent, and I could hear their frustration.
But on the other hand, you have those that, I don't believe there are that many, that would deliberately get people away from the comprehension of these texts.
But what's interesting, just to drop this in, is that when you look at these texts, it states that the good and evil comes from the Supreme Being.
Anyone could look this up. The adversary, and that's not Lucifer, but that's used in a lot of context.
Unfortunately, that's the symbol that we're talking about.
His specialty is the lie and the deception.
Correct.
It's evil in itself as an outcome, but it's the Supreme Being that brings both good and evil.
People are in this fairytale thing about what came before them, again, because of this schizophrenia.
They're not well, and they're divided, and they're all over the place.
People really like to do cherry-picking.
This suits my agenda, even though they may not say I have an agenda when they go out, walk out their door, write a book, or do a radio show.
If something feels right, they pick this, and then they pick the antithesis of that, something else within the same body of work to pick at as being bad.
Now, it's obviously when they point out the flaws in the quote-unquote established institutions,
it's enlightening to those that actually might believe in those things as being facts, and they're not.
But the part that gets me is when they start using the rest of the stuff that is also false as part of their doctrine to support what they're doing,
and that's the level of schizophrenia that I see very often in the alternative media, people writing books, stories, websites, speaking on radio.
And, of course, in the mainstream, you don't get a lot of contradiction of anything because it's all about moving the flow.
So, yeah.
You know, as something came up, by the way, in the chat room, I don't usually want to introduce stuff from the chat room too often,
but the question was, so the tree of life that could allow one to live indefinitely is a book?
I replied in text, it depends, with a little smiley.
Okay.
And I was asked, depends on what?
Right.
What's interesting is, okay, well, the term book, let's say you can, it's a form of communication where you can communicate,
you know, okay, here's a simple way to deduce it to really simple terms.
They have these Kindle things now that you could read a book and it looks like a book, right?
Sure.
It's electronic, right?
So it's not necessarily a book as we consider it a book, but it is a method of communication.
And those things will reveal in the future, and it's quite shocking when you see how the text defines those things.
And I would probably be hesitant on doing it publicly right now,
because I have been for the past 10 years approaching people that are biblical scholars, priests, rabbis,
you know, people that subscribe to the text, and no one can give me an answer on what these two things were,
and yet it's defined in the text itself.
So whenever you hear anyone saying, well, I have a degree from this in biblical studies, run the other way.
You know, it's like, yeah.
So anyway, because I've learned to do that, you know, and it's good advice to get away from it.
It's just like attorneys don't know anything about law.
Doctors don't know anything about medicine, so on and so forth.
That's about as right as you can get.
Now, there's still some chefs that do know how to cook, by the way.
So you can't completely discount everything that people are doing,
but most of these entitled classes are fairly worthless,
and actually if they aren't helping, they're actually hindering humanity at this point.
All right, and it's really no surprise that, you know,
the most warlike president in a very long time ends up getting a Nobel Peace Prize.
You know, this is the kind of society in which we live.
Which is twisted, which is, I think, Nobel's claim to fame was the formula for dynamite, let's say, right?
Right.
And he wanted to give back, you know, from his fortune to the Peace Prize.
So, well, you know, here's the concept of a peacemaker.
You know, again, in the ancient texts, there's something called the Beatitudes that talk about, you know,
blessed are the peacemakers because they will have peace, right, and things like that, right?
Those things are, it's not, a peacemaker is not this, you know, flower child guy with the peace sign, you know,
and the bandana, you know, or Gandhi or whatever.
Right, I was just going to say it's not the ancient hippie class.
No, no, no, a peacemaker is, a quick example would be, there's two guys having a knife fight.
You show up with a machine gun.
You're a peacemaker.
There you go.
Show up with incredible ordinance, so, yeah.
Precisely.
So, hopefully, we're keeping some peace in your minds right now.
This is Ocelli in the Greek, and believe it or not, we will be back for a second hour,
and we'll continue this discussion here on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
I'm telling you, you got to support American Freedom Radio because this government is getting out of hand.
Wall Street won't loan them my money.
The CIA are cutting into my drug running and my gun running.
Big pharma, psychotropic drugs are making my customers commit suicide before my hitmen can even lock them.
And then they get depressed and get prescribed psychotropic drugs and commit suicide, too.
They're trying to become the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected.
I get unpaid taxes, and if I can't find the money, the IRS are going to take my thumbs.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine, and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction, and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs, and that's to support American Freedom Radio.
Capisce?
So, what are you going to do?
You're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
Welcome.
Institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth, and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein, and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel, for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit, and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape.
Various pain related health care costs, epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders, and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer, and it saves you over 1 third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information the sonic entity knows has
Definitely not the dummy load right now.
Second hour of Ocelli in the Greek beginning here on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Not sure if it's going to be one or two days next weekend or what they call next weekend
but you will be treated to an interesting marathon of programming
that will be unique not only to the rest of what's available on the internet
but unique even to this particular broadcast entity.
And just like this show is and of course if we show up that day and do our thing as we do it
it'll be something well in and of itself just by its nature
will be different than what you're hearing anywhere else I assure you.
So all of that being said I mean where should we resume?
From the tree of life or should we...
No let's keep moving forward. You see I put something in the text
it said read where it's first introduced the clues are there then continue reading.
You know how we've said how many times now more than we have fingers and toes
that there's no religion on the planet bar none that knows or does anything
in the books that they allegedly subscribe to and at all period.
That is the truth the fact it's not debatable very simple to observe.
The thing is that there's the only way to really find out is by reading it right.
And it just like a film most religions will do a study on some alleged text
that they subscribe to in part and it'll be such a small part that it'll be as if
I said Chuck let's go watch this movie we're going to watch from 1 hour 42 minutes
and 36 seconds to 1 hour 43 minutes and 25 seconds okay.
Who the hell watches a movie and who the hell speaks like that?
Well in certain religions they say well this whatever chapter 14 to verse 33 to 45
you know it's like what? It's like wait a second like spewing out names of books
and chapters and verses that were put in there by a Canterbury monk in the 1300s
so he could communicate certain things as being used at people.
You know when you hear these quote unquote Christians quote scripture
it reminds me of the old Burger King commercial what was it?
McDonald's had two patties sesame seed bun special sauce hot whatever.
I think I got it wrong but whatever.
It's okay it was the formula for a Big Mac and that was McDonald's.
Leave it to me to drag it right back into the gutter
so that people can fully understand the simplicity of it.
But yeah that was a McDonald's thing.
So I'm not going to give those specifics at this point because it's useless
because then you end up sounding like them heaven forbid
you know who them are anyone in any religious circle
and I put in the text box read where the concept is introduced and there are clues there
and then if you continue reading the text any text no matter what book
how many times you heard people saying well I don't have the time.
Well a thousand page book if you read three pages a day in a year you'll go through it
and you can do the math on that 300 page less than a year if you read a page a day
and just you have to go through the whole thing and then you'll see how the order works
and this is with any of the older books and of course people don't want to go back more than 150 years
because of course dinosaurs were invented 150 years ago right
fossils were invented 150 years ago and this is a good tangent to go on for a moment
if you wouldn't indulge me on that.
You see back in the 1800s archaeology there was a boom in archaeology let's say
and the main universities were left out of it just like when there was a boom in computers
other than the start of the internet which was Stanford EDU and government
a lot of the colleges lost out on the computer movement in the early days
it was done in basically people's garages and things
a la Steve Jobs and what he did yeah
yeah so they missed the initial movement and the same was with archaeology
it was well funded by private people because they wanted trinkets you know
and they wanted like Schlieman who discovered Troy
they wanted to be the next famous quote unquote in the history books for discovering something interesting
so a lot of the especially the English universities got left out
and they said we need to get into it and we need to reinvent it
so things that were called mineralized which is what we call petrified
now you know it was commonly known that those things
the mineralization process started within 15 years
and you could have something fully mineralized in less than a thousand or two thousand let's say
well instead of just being mineralized now they call them fossils
and all fossils are 60 million years old
and if you look at ancient records where certain large creatures
had their natural habitat encroached on by humanity they became violent
just like a grizzly bear would be violent if you encroached on its territory
so these were pretty large what we call lizards today
and by the way I like to call them the original terrorists
because if you do some research on the counties and districts in middle Europe
what would have been called the Austrian-Hungarian Empire
that area they still have records from the 12, 13, 14, 15 hundreds
the governments were issuing silver to well abled bodied men that could hunt these terrorists at night
and I was looking at these documents that were scanned in
and I'm like what the hell are these terrorists
and they were these large lizards
so what they did was they changed all of that
now they became the dragons, the mythology
so we have a system now that this happened about 150 years ago
where they have the gall, academia and mainstream
to say that these things existed 60 million years ago
and of course there is no more foreshadowing of anything
all these things were very recent in comparison to 60 million years
and no one is actually looking there anymore
there are some radical quote unquote religious groups
that are trying to say everything was created 6,000 years ago
that's not the point and that's false also by the way
so we're addressing a society that has no concept of anything beyond 150 years ago
within its natural sense
yeah they might talk about July 4th, 1776
or Columbus sailed the whatever
that kind of just minor
the ocean blew in 1492
and if time goes on in a decade I'm sure he had GPS
and it was all this, they're going to change that as well
so we're addressing the arrogance of humanity
to not want to go beyond 150 years let's say
and think that all of these ancient societies
or older people were primitives
and they're so shocked like how were the pyramids built
how was this done, how did they move those stones
simple, very easy, they used forms of leverage
that are no longer used today
just like you have certain skills that have died out
if the skill itself has died out there's no more mastery
these were masters at moving heavy objects
if anyone is curious about that
if you really want a shocker to the mind
there's a guy named Wally Wallington in the Midwest somewhere
Wally Wallington, I just put in Wally Wallington pyramids
and he's a guy that can move a 20 ton block
300, 400 feet in a couple of hours by himself
using rollers and leverage and the weight of the block itself
so just planting these mind viruses into people
no one knows how it was built
if you plant a virus like that long enough
people start believing that no one can know these things
it's the same thing with these, let's say the biblical texts
or other writings, no one understands that
that's your interpretation
so if you keep that mind virus going
and keep plugging that into society
eventually you'll have someone like the emperor has no clothes
eventually, right?
everyone will believe it's invisible thread
and the child says, wait a second, he's naked
all these things can be simply rationalized
so this is a really long explanation
far away from what is the tree of life
and the tree of knowledge of good and evil
but the clues are there and all that is there
and I believe that is very proprietary information at this point
I brought it up only because I wanted to show the simplicity
but if all of these quote-unquote scholars and priests
and religious captains of industry
because it is an industry
don't know, why should we give it out on air for now?
I mean, I don't think it's relevant to just give it away
but it should be in the near future
right, that'll have to come to pass
where this knowledge will be freely available
but not just now
that's one point
the next point that I wanted to get to
calls back to your mentioning
that individuals reference things
and they'll tell you it was in this book, this chapter, this verse
where they justify things
and they pull things exactly out of context
and simply give you a location
a locale for the alleged information
and they bombard you with this as if it were knowledge itself
it very much reminds me of this individual
that used to call himself Mr. Skin
that would, and I know that you're going to find this kind of funny
but there used to be this guy that called himself Mr. Skin
and what Mr. Skin did
is tell you at exactly which point in which movie
you could see a woman or a man
fully naked
exactly when breasts would be
and he would tell you at exactly 4 minutes and 38 seconds
you get to see nipple
this kind of thing
and that was the deal
every single time
at 14 minutes and 38 seconds
you get to see two women kiss
and meanwhile did you actually know
what was going on in the movie at all
no, but you have these points of reference
that allegedly bring you to it
now if you're fool enough to sit there
and wind to these particular moments on the counter
you may encounter exactly what the gentleman was referencing
but it doesn't mean that you understand the movie
or the context or anything
if they were on a ship, a plane, or in the living room or what
a ship, a plane, the world's about to end
and maybe that's why they're having sex
it really doesn't matter
because all you did was go to that particular point
and accept that that's what you were going to see
and therefore you saw it
and it's literally the same concept
and the problem with a lot of these older texts
from the Mahabharata, the Rig Veda, the Koran
well the Koran kind of leaves out
because in certain countries it's illegal
to have it in any other language
it's almost like contraband to have one
that's an interlinear
the first time that I was ever handed
an English translation of the Koran
was from an older Pakistani man
who was actually shaking when he handed me the thing
because he had stated that it was
not something that was normal
he's doing this and handing it to me in the United States
where this particular piece of literature is not banned
is not illegal to translate or anything like that
but he still was quite familiar with the fact
that there was a penalty of law
for possessing this thing
I guess in many countries
and sort of with a great deal of trepidation
handed me that English translation of the Koran
which is what I read myself
but anyway
with the Judeo-Christian aspect of it
whatever they're reading from out of English
or any other language
they don't even have the text
because it's never been translated outside of
Hebrew and Greek
which are the languages of preservation
so when you have what's called an English
by the way
English, Spanish, French, Chinese or Japanese Bible
they're all based on King James
and King James
even though it's authorized King James version
it's not the scripture by far
there's
throw an example
there's about three quarter of a million words
in the scripture
Hebrew and Greek
and there's another hundred thousand
in the King James
and you might think they've added
a hundred thousand
but they've actually taken away about that many also
so it's really a bizarre twist
but again it's there for your entertainment
at least you'll walk away knowing the story
like you know
Noah's flood had something to do with water
and there was a big boat
then they'll do a cartoon on it
where you know there's a little boat
with a tether in the back
with the skunks
and everybody's got the clothespin on their nose
you know stuff like that
is about the most you're going to get out of
what you're going to read
or literally understand that
you know the veggie tale version of the Bible
is really what you're
what you're looking at when you're
examining the King James version anyway
yeah it's really in very bad shape
and you know
it's like
if you go to these people that study
these Bibles as if they're
adequate
you know
remember
this is
I'll just say it in a joke
you know I said well you know
I was at a Bible study
and I said you know
that's not really what it says
and this woman gets up
and she says well
it was good enough for the Apostle Paul
it was good enough for me
so I was like
what?
Apostle Paul supposedly is around
first century A.D.
and King James is 1611
I'm out of here
these people are so dumb
it's dangerous
anyway
okay
right
so
yeah I mean
there's got to be
and what we're saying is not necessarily
supported in mass
but I'll tell you for sure
the level of support that's needed
to keep this information going
will be requested
because it's
it's very novel at this point
it's way ahead of its time
even though there's a little bit of talk
about it here and there
but I believe that
the more we discuss this
it's kind of like the initial opening
of the vacuum seal
kind of thing
you know
and then it's easier to open the rest of the jar
for others
and so we'll see
we'll see how it goes
at least in a sonic form
you know
right
I mean and I
I had these types of observations
many years ago
except I illustrated them
with more of a
smart ass kind of
response to requests
being given to me at one point
I'll give you a for instance
when I was in junior high school
I was asked
and they told you to take a piece of
well-known literature
this was literally the description of the assignment
take a piece of well-known literature
and rewrite it
so that the words are different
but the sentiment is still carried
right
this was effectively the assignment
the way it was described
I mean it was probably
six, eight more sentences to it
but I'm giving you the short version
fact is
I took the book of Genesis
and rewrote it
and presented it
now
it wasn't allowed to be read
it wasn't allowed to be discussed
and I was basically
discouraged from ever doing something like that again
it was like this big shocking thing
and they stated
you know that this was the kind of thing
that could offend individuals who
you know believed in etc etc
and I said well
fact is
what they already have
is
less filled with
integrity than what I just presented
by comparison
you know and they said
well that's just you know you got to realize
that's going to offend people who have a great sensitivity
to this because they adhere to this
book and I said well they actually don't
and the
mistranslation that has
already been given to them
like I said
is further away from the original
text than what I have
done by comparison to it
I assure you and it's not a
matter of opinion it's not a matter of
religiosity it is
simply an observation
based on what the assignment
was which was take a well known piece of
literature and you can't say that
the Old Testament is not
a well known piece of literature
and to re
basically reformulate it
so that you have changed the
sentences you have changed the words which
you have kept the integrity
of the intent being
you know ushered forward
by the written work
so guess what
I do believe that I qualify
as having completed the assignment
and it
might have been much far off
because the intent is very
simple to get if you see
if you look at it
no it's ok
because what it came down to is I mean I did
write something that ended up being much
shorter but I was using common language
that made more sense to the
class than what was in there
you know you don't have all those
that
yeah the Shakespearean
you know affect to the English
right so I gave
them American English I shortened things
and
I thought
that that was a valid exercise
and to prove both points
one that you could move the
sentiment forward into
a different context
of the same language but two
to reverse engineer the
process and understand that what
you have there is not the original
and is probably
lacking in a great deal of
information
here's some of the information
to do a comprehensive study
on just the first
chapter which shouldn't end where they
end it by the way those chapters and
verses are there to get the reader
away from and the books
are by the way never put in the right order
except for the first five
because they couldn't
mess that up but if you
just want to go through the first chapter
of Genesis which would also have to include
the first two or three verses of chapter
two because that's where it should end
it would be a full
time job for a month and a half or part
time for about a year if you're
doing it with good comprehension of the
language of preservation
and you will find out that
the level of specificity
of what went on
is very high and
it's not necessarily to explain the
process of creation but it's
actually it has
all the elements of an
affidavit a legal affidavit
that you would require to have
to submit into a court case in the evidence
file
if you want to know more about
creation how it actually happened you would have to
go to another book which has
a trajectory in there so
what's interesting about that it's not
that's why I say that
you've said before the creationists
are wrong and the evolutionists are wrong
the biblical account still stands
by itself and
it's not being discussed at all
at all and there's tons of
commentary and it's all false and it's
amazing to see what's going on
when I say all of it
you'll have
a general
scholar or someone write about it
and he might have a little needle in the
haystack in there of truth
so you have to sift through
ages of crap
so why bother when you can just look at it
yourself is what the encouragement
is going to be in the future and this is with
everything you know I mean
how many people actually read a dollar
bill what they call a dollar bill and by the way
if these are bills let's change the subject for a
moment who's going to pay those bills
right how many people actually sit down
and study what's on there and not the occult
symbolism with the little owl and the engraving
and the pyramid with the eye on
it what is actually going on what
it really is what is a note what is
going on there what is that thing really
symbolized virtually
no one out there
very few
and they're taking liability
for all of these things they don't understand
which is the worst kind of liability
to take
and that's part of the problem
is even those that are studying it
and believe that they've examined
the symbols believe
that they've examined the art that they know the
history of it or whatever else
are still ignoring
the majority of the information
which has been
ingrained in the document
after all it is a
piece of paper it has writing on it I can call
it a document
there's a lot of information
on there
it's a receipt it's to evidence a transaction
and the transaction is closed
and that would be documentation
I mean
these are all forms
of communication
communication knowing what words mean
understanding the relevance of
the lawful
relevance of order
claims are very important
if someone claims to do
something you hold them to it
if someone just comes out and makes a very tall
or a very large claim
and it's not disputed
or outwardly
rebutted properly as the claim
was made so if a claim was made on paper
in affidavit form it needs to be
rebutted accordingly you can't just bark
at it
so when you look at let's say
the biblical text and you have something that's a massive
claim like you'd find
in Genesis
and it hasn't been rebutted in like
kind it needs to be taken
seriously
from an objective
point of view and once
someone does the research you'll find that
it is actually pretty true
because the information to back
it up is relevant so
this has nothing to do with what you believe in
it has nothing to do with your religion
and there's again
sympathies
go out to people that want to gather
knowledge and information there's a lot of
people out there especially now with the advent of
electrical electronics
and digital format
there's many many people out there speaking
writing and all this that really
want to honestly get truthfully
get the information of let's say
the biblical text and because
they feel that they've
given up on it because they don't understand it
they start going off on a tangent making
up porcupines as the
British say
it goes anywhere from
oh this is just poetry
or it's astro theology or you can't
take it literally or it really means this
or this is my interpretation
this is their interpretation it was written by
Caesar or whatever it's all bunk all of it
because
I could sense their frustration
that they are
knowledge seekers let's say
but they've given up on doing it properly
right
it's kind of like what will happen is they'll all get
caught in the end because
for example
this is explaining these
works is almost like
an Olympic event you can tell people
that you're going to be going to the
Olympics and if you don't have the training
and the discipline you show up at the Olympics
and you won't even make the tryouts right
so the tryouts right now
for society is going to be coming
and when this Middle East Union
forms
the BS level is going to
go down very low you know
the BS that the doctors are
you know administering
pharmaceuticals that are toxic and they don't
care the attorneys
that don't know anything about law just do what
the judge says and the judge doesn't know anything
about law right
the finance the guys that talk about the
economy don't even know
that it's a credit based economy they don't even know
what that means on and on
all the way to the engineers you know
there hasn't been any electrical
engineering since the 1920s
so right and look
in defense of the astrotheologist
point of view though
there is
a synergy between
the story arc
and
astrology I mean but it's not just
that it exists it may not
be simply that but
it is that once
again that
one flavorful
chunk of rice among the
rice shaped styrofoam
if you will that is
there it is part of it
it is part of the story
here's the main reason why it's there it's to
communicate because you don't need to go buy
a clock you don't need to go
and buy a calendar you don't need to tell
for someone else to tell you how to reckon
time and also what's
interesting in the future people will be
shocked I'd like to take a flat
earther and put him in a capsule and
send him beyond earth's atmosphere
and they're going to be so
freaked out they'll probably pee and poop
in their pants you'd have to bring them back and sedate
them because they'll be in such a panic
because when you leave the earth's atmosphere you can't
see any of the stars and you cannot see
the sun it's just
black and the only thing you see
is the earth being lit and the moon
and that's it and maybe a planet
in the distance you cannot see these
objects only through the atmosphere so
it's an interesting set up how we are here
on earth to look up in the sky
and see the story of
pretty much everything
through the constellations
which bears
fact and truth
in what's going on on the planet as well
so from that point of view but to say
what I hear being
said all the way since the Levosky days
with Crowley
on and on and all that it's just the
you've got to remember this is a
rehashing and a revival of
rubbish
mysticism but
they're accommodating
you see all of these quote unquote interpretations
and versions are accommodating the audience
you know
people that invest their whole life
in doing these things want to get something
in return they want sales they want members
they want donations they want to be able to
speak and get paid
for it you know allegedly
and if they're saying things that has not
been ingrained in the mind of the people
for thousands of years they're not
going to be able to succeed financially
or they're not going to be able to feed themselves
and once again here's
what the challenge is
again not to fully discount
mysticism in its entirety
the fact is that there are
certain workable tenets of what
people do identify as black magic
etc. etc. I know this factually
but here's
the problem when someone
comes to you and shows you something that is
a legitimate
expression of those
practices the
misunderstandings are virtually
the same for those type
of what you might call
lesser spiritual
organisms or organizations
regarding
stuff in rank like when
they talk about
you brought up an excellent
point the sun
turning black is
referenced in the ritualistic
magic yes and there's
no way you could know that without leaving
earth's atmosphere so how did they do it
well that's the thing though they're not
talking about literally turning
the sun black
they're talking about the realistic
state of
what would be observable if
you left the earth's atmosphere
direct observation exactly
right how did you accomplish
that previous to space
travel well there
is your problem there's
actually some real things in there
but yeah or someone who's been
there right someone who's been out there
that's giving good testimony trustworthy
testimony to it yeah right
you know like when somebody sits there and tries
to tell me all about you
know somebody who's lived in suburbia
their whole life never served in the military
and might have fired a
pop gun at the
state fair turns around and
tries to explain to me what happens
when a bullet hits
a human body
okay and exactly how the body
reacts what the bullet does and everything else
based on a text that they've read
where they have now entrusted their
point of view to the knowledge of
an alleged expert that's been immortalized
on paper i say to them
you know sometimes well have you
actually ever observed
that situation
and they are generally
dumbfounded it's the truth
if you've observed the situation your point
of view is going to be different
and also how is it titled because
if you observe a woman being sawed in half
and put back together at a magic
show even though you saw it you know it didn't
happen but you walk befuddled that's the mysticism
that I'm speaking about
but while you were speaking I had a thought
and for example with the black
magic and the white magic and all this other
stuff let's just keep it really simple
if you're doing voodoo or
in some recess of
whatever state park
or whatever and you're sacrificing a goat
that procedure what's the
difference of sacrificing
a lamb or a goat at the
temple in jerusalem let's say
in the biblical text it's the same
act it's who you're doing it for
right
right so
that's the whole contention
here that will be addressed in the
future that humanity has been
looking for the quick fix
versus you know understanding the story
so but
then again the point you brought up with direct
observation not to be discounted like
earlier you might want to
study a subject and
read a 700 page document
on it and you're like this is
crap but you know two paragraphs were
really good and worth the read so you wouldn't
have gotten them unless you read
the whole thing so there's a lot of time involved
so with the mysticism
you got to realize everything is a
parody because everything comes from the same
place right
so you know things
that are good and evil you know are parodies
you know look at the
birthday cake people have a great time with
it you know and they don't want to know what it means
and right now we have coming up
an american holiday known
as thanksgiving that has to be on every
last thors day because
you i think it's called
blot where you
something like that where you it's the festival
of thor it's called blot
but anyway yeah and you slaughter
you have this feast yeah okay so
so anyway people
the thing is it's not that
that they're doing that
and previous to feasting you slaughter
an animal to serve it
during that feast and
and thor specifically has to be
a winged beast you know as he has them on
in his figure but the
problem here is not that the people
are doing that is that when you ask them what
it is they've got this really dumb look on
their face you know what i mean
they don't know and they don't want to know and they don't care
and that's the category
that most of mankind is in right now that's being
taken advantage of as we
open the program maybe briefly
discussing some of the news that happened
here recently
the lack of responsibility
but the fact is
that when you take a lack of responsibility
over the Easter Bunny
and the implications
thereof well you know
it's virtually the same thing as
as you know
treating the
public sacrifice
of some individuals
in a far away land as
if it is earth shattering news
i mean it's really
well the thing
is they don't want to know why they're doing
it right and they don't care
so if you
society is being carefully watched on what
traditions and celebrations
and holidays they have
and hold dear and close
and the more bizarre and the less
attached they are to the reality
of those things the more
the few that know
how these things
work in society will be taking
advantage of them
and you'll have the magic bullets
and the buildings that turn to dust
because of this magic
diesel fuel
jet fuel and then you'll have
all this magic happening and all
these events and of course
there's dead people
to sympathize with how dare you
speak of this event that way
people died all this stuff
death tied in with the deception
very interesting
time period
that's been not necessarily
contemporary but going on for a long
time that is going to come to an end
in the near future
right and in its simplicity here's
the thing you know
the worship the
worship i say again of death
is what is really
prevalent everywhere
and the fact is
if you stop
appeasing the entities
that feed
off of this particular
worship
gee wouldn't that mean
that death in and of itself
might be a weakened
reality
hmm well it will
you know double negatives work
in a certain rational sense in the
spiritual realm so if you put death to
death there's no more
death and if there's no more death then there's
only you see
right well
precisely i mean two
negative numbers
coming together to equal a positive
you know it's just
it's part of
what is
so
yes so yeah the concept
of death is it's all around and it's
even in the medical society
they take cells from living things
and they make sure that they're
viewed in a clinical situation or
a lab and they're
decomposing and all their pharmaceuticals
are based to counteract decomposition
so
well right and you know
as we come toward the last 20
minutes or so it does occur
to me that
we have you know kind
of gone through episode 7 in
a rather interesting way
you begin to
well 7 would be what
the number of divinity so much as
in as much as in numbers count
you know regarding
things like this and
we passed the
number of man last week which
is the six you know
therefore three sixes together
just kind of looks like a three way
but
the reality of
this particular episode to me
is the consideration
that
whether you wish to believe it
or not
in one sense
a singular man
could just as easily
be identified as a god
depending on a perspective
and a god could be just as easily
identified as a singular man
depending on your given perspective
I mean after all if you are the supreme
being
in comparison
I'm going to stop you right there for a minute
only because if you're going to
look at it objectively
and people think well these guys talk about religion
in the biblical text and all that no no no
it has nothing to do with that
it has to do with can you show me anywhere else
where you have
that kind of a paramount
claim being made I have not found
it anywhere the claims that are made in the
biblical text are not even
approached or surpassed or not even
forget about surpassing them
anywhere else and again
the sympathies that I gave out to those
that try to study these texts and clearly
don't understand them and make up stories about
that these things actually mean something else
putting
all that aside we're looking at it
objectively and I assure you
there's no one discussing this
on the internet sonically as we are
right now the objectification
I mean let's just put it this way you've got to
have some kind of cojones to say
that you created everything
and have it unrebutted for so long
I mean come on
and if it stays unrebutted
like this and it stands
it needs to be looked at objectively
not what you think you
interpret it as or what we think
or anybody but what it actually
says first
you know if you say you know
a limerick or a poem
you could say well it really means this but you know what
you have to actually read it first
before you can interpret it and I assure
you everyone out there discussing
the biblical text it doesn't matter from what
angle they have not read it it's pretty clear
it's kind of like if you
if you've watched a film and you
see someone else and you
try to discuss it with them you can tell right
away if they've seen the film or not
if you mention the scene
that is important and
and they give
that real dumb look on their face
guess what they didn't see the film
so this is what's interesting
about this discussion
is it has to be objectified
it's not what we think
it has to be looked at objectively
again I had interrupted just to throw
that in there I don't have to take it
somewhere else or whatever but you're saying
a god can be a man yes absolutely
how else are you going to communicate
you know and actually when
they do take men form
in a carnal way they can be killed
and if you're killed in a carnal form
you're dead spiritually as well
yeah right
to put it another way you know if you die
in the matrix you know you die in
real life that was the best part of the
film at that point I had
when that film came out and
I saw Larry doing movies
again I was quite happy a big film
like that and
everyone
was always discussing you know it's the
financial system or the whatever
I was just yeah it is also
but look they actually gave up
a serious
pearl of wisdom here that
just when no one really
discusses and that is
one of the major points
to be understood in all the
ancient texts is if you die in carnal
form you actually die but the thing
is now that most people you'll ever
meet cannot define
what the soul is
versus the spirit or what
the spirit is and the soul
and they get very upset that's how you know
the censorship is still
very high they're not interchangeable
the soul is your breath and the spirit
is your mind period
that's the easiest way to say it
and you wouldn't believe how many people
whether they're educated or not will fight you
tooth and nail and don't debate them
on it if you do your own research you'll find that
to be true
don't debate them on it because
they can't do anything about it they're heavily
heavily heavily censored
and they would rather give up
their physical flesh and die
before they acknowledge that they're being
censored
and the truth
truth be told I say that
quite objectively
that once again
you can find many kernels of truth
among the large buckets
of popcorn
when it comes to many
speculations regarding
these different
concepts for instance
those that would say
that all things which are
life or in this
particular realm
are simply expressions of the
divine
they have oversimplified something
but the fact
is that if you
imagine for a moment
that all things
could be at that root
and not only have their
origin but
their entire existence
tethered to the one
particular thing in existence
therefore all things are all
part of the same thing
it's not mutually exclusive
to state that
as opposed to
looking at the great
hierarchy
it could be that the hierarchy
is just something that is incomprehensible
to us given our
limitation at the time
however the answer to
all things is not that they are
unknowable
well it's laziness Chuck
again I'm going to say it again tonight
there's a lot of people out there that want to seek
knowledge and the truth of the matter and when they come
across something that might
in their own mind might be seemingly
a daunting task and they don't understand
it and don't know where to turn and they don't
want to invest the time in it they start
making things up how many times have you heard
people say well I believe
God is in
the creation and God is
everything in the creation no
that's your belief that is
nothing to do with reality
that is someone there
trying to poach someone else's
subjects because that's how religions are started
you have someone making up a story
that's based on nothing
and well an
impulse that's brought in
and then they start getting
subjects around them people that believe
in the same thing right so now
they're poaching now they're taking
the other people's subjects
away right so you ever wonder why there's
so many wars
with these religious matters
because they're all different subjects
moving around that's poaching man
you know if you look at
what's interesting and especially
in most of the ancient texts there is no
conversion you know where
the Christians they send out
ministries and what are their missions
and all that to convert that's totally
unlawful in the biblical text
and the new test
what they discuss is the new testament
that was a very short time to go out
and give a message to those who knew what just
happened and one of the
people that was
very confused about what just happened was
Simon Magus and he took advantage
of the worldwide frenzy going on at the
time and created this religion
called Christianity or Gnosticism
and all the other stuff that
goes with it you know so
yeah
it's really it's an interesting
saga you know
the entire situation
um
it's very sad by the way
at the same time it's kind of like
having a Ferrari and not
knowing that it goes more than 30 miles
per hour and you're always complaining why
it can't go fast on it
so you just gotta hit that lever to the next
gear and people just refuse
to do it
until
this middle east union comes together
right
well
I gotta say that we're down to
what they might call the last
10 minutes of this
episode which is number 7 of
Bocelli and the Greek
and I'm wondering
how it is we should wrap this
one up
for people you know finally
put the bow on the package
which is another subject
one of these days we'll have to cover
but how is it
that we would put that bow on the
package we'll just be
what that meaning is right at the moment
but you know
what do you think we should say here in
closing and you know do you want to
leave anybody with any particular
sort of
well anecdotal thought
regarding all of what we've discussed
tonight oh man
did you have to say that
well it looks like we've been hammering the same
thought process for
7 weeks now
which is be objective
let's just sit back and look at it
yeah let's just look at this you know
we started off by maybe saying
if there's nothing new under the sun
then what is the news
how can anything be the news right
maybe current events is more accurate
but you know what the real news is
let's just throw this in
the real news is
you ever notice when you heat or cool
a room indoors the heat goes to the ceiling
and the cold goes to the floor
so you have a hot head and cold feet
all year round indoors
but when you go outside
when it's hot in the valley
it's cool up at the mountain top
and if you get into an airplane
and go towards the sun which is allegedly
a heat source it gets colder and colder
and colder
and you know if you called a medical man
and said you know my feet are ice cold
and my head is red hot
he doesn't need to see you
tell you you're not feeling well
because your feet should be warm
and your head should be cool
but wait a second
how come people are only acknowledging
that heat rises and cold goes down
when in all natural biological systems
you have a rarefied ascending cold
and a descending densifying heat
witness the snow covered mountain tops
of many places
even in the body
you should have warm feet cool head
someone got a hot head he's not doing well
cold feet right no good
but I thought cold is supposed to go down
heat is supposed to rise
now wait a second
that's the news believe it or not
and this is a secret don't tell anybody
even though we're on radio
it's a secret
it's the news believe it or not
why is it the news
well because when was the last time
you heard someone demanding
air conditioning units and heaters
that produce an ascending cold
and a descending heat like in nature
so you don't have a hot head
and cold feet in your house or the car
no one is asking for this
and it's well
why should they ask for a heat that goes down
and a cold that rises because obviously
it's a secret
do you see my point
and I'm not being sarcastic
no and you know
to wrap up that point I gotta say
this you know how they always say
cooler heads will prevail
yes well
that's a wonder
but now in all
systems that degrade
right that's why when you
make a campfire the heat rises
and the cold goes down
because you're degrading
you've got whatever wood
so you're burning
something you're using electricity
the type of electricity you use yeah you have that type
why aren't people demanding
a natural form of comfort
you see
and
there's talk about water
if water
is H2O and the periodic
table of elements is accurate
why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air
because according to the periodic table
if it's accurate H2O oxygen being
16 and hydrogen being 1
should weigh 18
but you could look up the constituents of air
as a molecular weight of 29
and don't say 1 is a liquid
1 is a gas because we're talking about a molecule
the irrelevant of phase and no gas
water does not have a gas phase
so now we establish that water can't be
H2O and you got all these people talking
about this type of structured hydrogen
and that ridiculous
now here's the way
you handle water
you ever notice how
the blood vessels in your eye
or the roots of a tree
or the rivers have the same geometry
because that's
the shape water wants to take
and guess what
at 39 degrees Fahrenheit or 4 degrees Celsius
water is its densest
it's still a liquid
if you drop it below 39
it gets colder and colder
it starts to expand
right
that's why ice floats
so people want to talk about
water and how much they know about water
how many times they talk about the
importance of the shape of how it flows
in the container and the temperature
never
these things need to be discussed
when are people
going to start looking at the obvious
maybe we can help
them along
sure as hell don't want to beat it into them
even though it might sound like we do it
for two hours or at least I do
I understand and you know what
perhaps the next episode should be
about water
and the various
directions that that can go in
because what you just gave us there
is a very
simple synopsis of one aspect
of that
because I've had more than one person
tell me that
the secret of the universe
could be revealed to you
if you understood water
in truth
so
I don't fully understand that
myself but I would like to
and I think that would be a worthy subject
for discussion
I've been hounded for maybe
years just by being around different
internet call and
shows and forums
people saying oh Greek are you the guy that talks about
why does a bucket of water
wait why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air and it shouldn't
when I first heard that it sounded ridiculous
and I looked into it and I said holy crap
this guy it's true it shouldn't
a bucket of air should weigh
more than a bucket of water regardless of
one as a gas and one as liquid
and what's going on well
misdirection and misinformation
so that could
be discussed it's not what you think
it is and it's
if you want to go into the realm of
magic the reality
of water is beyond
anything you've conceived of being
quote unquote magic
it's yeah
and this is the reality of it that anyone
can witness and no one
is discussing it at all
the only one that I would tip my hat to
like if someone asked me who do I want to interview
I said I don't know everybody I want to interview
is dead already
one of those people is Victor
Schauberger he's a German
naturalist that
died in 19 what they call 1958
and he would be the
champion of this type of
and he was not a scientist neither am I
and you know what's interesting
the level of censorship is so high
that people say Greek you know I need
babble fish to listen to you you sound too
technical I'm like are you kidding
are you kidding
it can't get any easier than this
yeah technicality has not been introduced
into the equation just yet
but we may get there
eventually well with things that sound
technical see humans think in the
mid range if you speak in
complex things it's too technical
if you speak too simple it's too technical
because they're mid range thinkers
so
that's you know it's all mid range
too simple too
complicated no good
either extreme so yeah maybe the
oversimplification aspect
is
is sounds technical so there's got
to be a mid ground you know we've got to make up
some kind of story to maybe give us a metaphor
of these things
oh that almost sounds like a parable
yeah
but remember with the parables it was not
given to the masses it was
it was only given to a
few in private
that was there
so the parable that's all
true and we're going to run right on
at a time so
once again
that's the end of episode 7
and it has been
one interesting journey
in my estimation
so I want to thank you once again
for doing this with me once a week
well thank you
you know and by the way people if you
want to stop by at ocellianthegreek.com
I would definitely appreciate it
if you did that
there are some videos there
there are some other things there
now hold on Chuck
why would you appreciate it because
I would suggest that when you do click
on the donate button
it will go to the ocelli effect
and Chuck has
equipment to get
he has personal expenses
he has all the things that go along
with the needs and requirements
of anyone doing anything full time
and anything is
appreciated at this point because
if you think you can't give but just
a couple of bucks or something
and it's not going to do
anything it does as a matter of fact
we have someone who has been just consistently
doing that
it's making paypal rich
but just two bucks at a
time or five bucks or ten bucks
or twenty whatever number
anything will help
at this point and it's quite
needed
it does actually make a difference and hopefully
we made a difference with you tonight
the listener out there
and given you something else to
consider that is not part
of the greater dummy load
and I think that's our music
coming in although it's rather low
so I guess we will bid
everyone a safe journey
for the rest of what they call the night
and
take care
what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us
provide us with free education
well that's obviously effective
but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America
all the information they provide is free
what about the free podium for
broadcast activists to speak from
exploiting commonplace corruption
they help vulnerable people who
don't have a voice
bringing light to important information nobody else does
they never censor, hang up or
cut off their guests
well that's no fun is it
they created a fantastic alternative media source
during an era of bad, manipulative and infiltrated
mainstream and alternative media shows and scum
okay well apart from the free education
free information, free podium
for broadcast activists to speak from
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable
people without a voice, bringing light to important
information nobody else does and creating
a fantastic commercial free alternative
media source in a sea of bad, manipulative
mainstream and alternative media shows
and scum, what has American
Freedom Radio ever done for us
donate to American Freedom Radio
today
news and information you
can trust, this is
American Freedom Radio
freedom, freedom, American
Freedom Radio
Radio
American Freedom Radio
nutritious food is real body
armor, it builds muscle, burns
fat, improves digestion and
feeds the entire body the nutrients
it needs, did you know the US government
banned the hemp plant from growing in the United
States and classified it as a schedule
one drug to hide it behind the marijuana
plant, people have been confused about
this plant for over 80 years
and many still don't know what hemp is
so now you know hemp is not
marijuana and marijuana is not
hemp, they are different varieties of
the same species, hempusa.org
wants the world to know these basic
facts and to help people understand
that hemp protein powder is the best
kept health secret you need to know about
remember, hemp protein powder
contains 53% protein
is gluten free, anti-inflammatory
non-gmo and is loaded
with nutrients, call
888-910-4367
and see what our powder
seeds and oil can do for you
only at hempusa.org
we are
living in a new era, partnerships
are more important than profit
and gratitude is more respected than greed
as the millennial generation
involves the corporate landscape
our company aims to maximize the achievements
of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible
by 2020, our core product
matrix and careful cannabidiol
purification process are uniquely
designed to be privately made in different
regions of the world and is geared to assist
the efforts of different nations
to change the landscape, various pain
related health care costs, epilepsy
and autism, rising mental
disorders and even soldier
suicides, crystal pure CBD
is made with the industry's
finest 99.9%
pure CBD
crystals, no paste
no filler, our solution
is a permanent answer and
it saves you over 1 third in cost
crystal pure CBD
come join us
you're listening to
americanfreedomradio.com, the network
who perseveres in delivering intelligent
debate, constructive dialogue with true
independence, the freedom to broadcast
the truth is not free at all
so what is American Freedom Radio
worth to you? The empowering information
with fun, honest and pure
integrity behind it provides an example to
follow, friendships to flourish
with the moral altruism that pulls no
punches, the host sacrifice
and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service
to the community with strength
wisdom and loyalty
the founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights to make
the best radio and alternative media
now it's time for you to give
something back and play a vital role
in the future of America
be as generous with us as we've
been with you, click on the donate
banner at americanfreedomradio.com
or volunteer by emailing
americanfreedomradio.com
vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery
batteries not included
no rules, no rules
no taboo topics
taboo topics
no fear of doom
we are
American Freedom Radio