American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
For the first time on a Friars Day evening, or Friday evening as they decide to call it,
the eighth day of the first month according to the Pope's work schedule,
this is Ocelli and the Greek broadcast live on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and we do welcome you.
So, that is the way it is, and yeah, it is the first time that it's being broadcast at this particular time of day,
but truthfully, what day is it, Greg?
Hey Chuck, I'd say it's around the 17th of the 11th.
Now that gets people scratching their head.
17th day of the 11th month until noon for the five people that care.
Isn't that true?
And yeah, allegedly November, which sounds to me like the number nine,
is certainly what they call the 11th month according to the Pope's work schedule.
And gee, people are going, well how could it possibly be the 11th month?
But then again, I say refer back to one of the earlier episodes.
By the way, this would be, according to my account anyway, episode 14 of Ocelli and the Greek.
Interesting number in and of itself, but hey, let's put that aside.
That's just for your notes at home if you're keeping track or score at home, I guess.
It is the 14th time we have come together to do this.
And it is interesting.
It is interesting.
You know what I was thinking of, oddly enough, and I always find this really fascinating
and people argue with me about it.
But you ever notice that all of those months of the year that are on that thing we call a calendar,
you ever notice every last one of them is actually a woman's name in one way or another?
Say that part again?
A woman's name?
Yeah, it's a woman's name in some way or another.
Now you might say, okay, well Jan, January, Janet, right, okay.
You could find the root in all of these things.
March is Marcia, right.
You've got April is April, obviously.
May is May.
June is June, et cetera, et cetera.
July is Julie.
Okay, if you want to really get strange about it, well, what is August?
Well, Augustine, things like this.
You could translate it into what they would call a feminine name at some point or another,
and I've always found that kind of fascinating.
That's like trying to figure out how to walk and chew gum.
Yeah, yeah.
But anyway, yeah, it's arbitrary, but I see what you mean.
The arbitrariness of it, though,
is the part that's unnerving for anyone who discovers what's going on with the Pope's work schedule.
It's completely arbitrary.
The first day of any month, the last day of any month, any holiday,
any day that's memorialized on that thing, it's based on nothing.
It's whatever they decide to print out the next year.
If anyone recalls, let's say growing up in the 50s, 60s, 70s, maybe even the 80s,
or prior to the electronic conventions that we so much enjoy today,
you had to run to the hardware store or the card shop to get a calendar to hang up on the wall.
Why?
To know what day it was.
How ridiculous is that?
When you think about these things, it's quite, can we say pathetic, on how unnoticeable it's gone.
Now, on one aspect, yes, it's very bad, but on the other aspect, it's very good.
It means that it is possible, through something as subtle as that, that goes unnoticed,
even though it's more than subtle if you think about the implications of keeping time,
has been able to be thrusted and wielded across every head of humanity.
And the reason I said head of humanity, as in farm animal heads, but anyway, did I say that?
Okay.
Yes, you did.
And they have followed along with it as if it doesn't even exist.
And the best thing is when you talk to most people, say, well, time doesn't exist.
Another person says, oh, well, this, oh, well, that.
So we've accomplished, when I say we, meaning the head count on this planet right now,
of throwing pretty much anything that can be discussed into a sense of arbitrary opinion
or uninformed, unconfirmable, unverifiable speak.
And it gets tiring after a while.
So that's why the simple thing is to set oneself apart from it.
People who don't get it want to get involved politically.
People who don't get it want to make something to make the world a better place.
People who don't get it, may I say it this way, want to inform other people.
There's a big difference between what we're doing, coming on, doing this show.
It's a sense of responsibility more than informing.
Now, personally, I could say it doesn't mean anything if anybody gets anything that we're saying.
Most people won't.
And I don't mean that arrogantly.
I mean that truthfully and objectively.
But when you discover certain things that are not being said and are on the positive side of the column
or the good, yes, there is good and bad or positive and negative,
or on the helpful side of the, let's say, the ledger book, you know, you can't keep it to yourself.
You have to voice it publicly.
So we have a forum here on AFR, and I'm very grateful to AFR and yourself
for putting up with someone like me every week
and giving the adult supervision necessary to get this information out from someone
who has really pretty much thrown their hands up on what's been going on on this planet for over a decade.
Right.
And I want to say that I have always felt a responsibility to accurately account for things.
I don't know what that is, but it has always been just part of my being, it seems,
to try and account for anything that I can observe in the most reasonable and responsible manner.
And I don't know why. I have no clue why.
I mean, that is part of why I elected to go into doing stuff like this to begin with.
Of course, I find that you're extremely right, no matter which direction you're coming from,
no matter what type of information, reality, truth, or whatever it is you want to describe it as,
there is always this very serious path of resistance, and it's the oddest thing.
The first thing is that no matter what you say or how you say it,
it has very little to do with the interpretation of the audience in a lot of cases.
They will interpret it as they will.
So we could give them literally the secret of the universe in the palm of their hand tonight,
and it doesn't mean that anyone will grasp it.
I mean, it's just that simple.
And it is a frustration, and of course, it's one of those things that I strive to do better at all the time.
I know a lot of the stuff I cover on the rest of the shows I do are kind of pointless and mundane to you,
but the fact is that no matter what it is I'm talking about,
and I don't care if it's relationships or chemicals or the interactions of other human beings or historical events,
I mean, I do my best to give people a fair and accurate report as my facilities and abilities allow me to.
So I understand that feeling of responsibility.
I think it is incumbent upon all of those who have the ability to communicate to do the same.
Unfortunately, it seems as though that is not the prevalent –
And if you're too fair and accurate, you're going to lose the audience
because they're used to hearing stuff like taxpayer dollars, the economy, oh, this or that.
Yeah, it's just really, really stuff that doesn't even exist, and they've turned –
you've heard of the term molehill into a mountain.
They've turned nothing into a mountain.
They fail to comprehend the very basics of reality that humankind is an agricultural-based creature.
I'm not going to call them an animal because we're not animals, but far from it.
Now, the basis of that has been obscured.
Any alignment or any resonance with what that means, that we're agriculturally based, has been lost.
What I mean by that is like birds fly and fish swim.
Man is agriculturally based.
It's very simple.
Not all birds fly.
Actually, birds don't really fly.
Birds are flown, and fish don't really swim.
Fish are swum.
And the reason those two animals do those incredible feats in the corresponding mediums
is because they know how to affect the environment around them, you see.
And so a bird doesn't really fly by flopping its wings.
People tried that.
You've seen old black-and-white photos on how they just fall off a cliff.
It has nothing to do with flapping wings.
And just like fish with fins and scales, it has nothing to do with them moving their body with fins and scales.
It's how these beings interact with the fluid medium around them.
Humanity has disconnected themselves from how they should be interacting with the medium or the environment around them.
So, yeah.
And this is across the board.
This is an indictment for 7.1 or 7.2 billion people on the planet.
This is not just some.
We're not talking about the mainstream.
We're talking everyone at this point, except for a very small, fine group.
We're talking a group that might be just in the few hundreds or thousands on the entire planet.
That is a really poor assumption, if you were to be taken that way.
But I think that it's very educated to say that it's fairly true.
Another quick truth here, just to be taken note of before we get too far away from it.
You said there are many who turn nothing into mountains.
Well, I assure you that there are also those who would seek to turn mountains into nothing and mountains into molehills as well.
They have obscured the really tremendously fascinating, wondrous parts of the world with nonsense in a lot of cases.
Appealing to emotions, appealing to reaction as opposed to actually engaging in a valuable discussion about the reality around us.
One of these things that I find really fascinating when you talk about the agricultural base that mankind – and I use that term loosely, but you know what I'm saying.
The human creature is supposed to be participating, and this is a mechanism that is part of their nature.
I've often said, although it is for various other reasons, that a lot of things would improve instantaneously on this planet if we acted according to our design in a whole lot more of a responsible fashion.
The agricultural part doesn't mean getting dirt under your fingernails and planting seeds.
It means that you understand the cycles that surround such an existence and correspond with them accordingly.
One thing that I hear consecutively on almost every alternative, especially alternative media is that when money comes up, they say, well, money isn't really anything.
It's just based on energy. It doesn't really mean anything.
Like, oh, well, here we go with the moronic discourses again.
People have even lost the – forget about keeping time.
You can't even find anyone anymore that can tell you in five words or less what money is.
Suffice to say what you hear.
And let's just drop that.
I think we've done it once on The Ocelli Effect before months ago when we first started discussing on the show that you called The Ocelli Effect or is called The Ocelli Effect.
What money is, it's portable land.
That's all it is.
And when you make something portable and it's so portable that it could fit in your pocket, it would have to be a condensed version of all of its value, right?
So that's why it's been deemed lawful that gold and silver is lawful money because it represents portable land.
It is the finest metal, let's say, that can be extracted practically and used.
Right.
And that's all it is.
It's portable land.
And how many times have you ever heard anyone discuss, well, money is portable land?
No one ever.
What's going on here?
I've got to say, yeah, I've never heard that phrase anywhere else.
That's all it is.
Yeah.
And here's the thing.
If you're basing it on agricultural cycles and agricultural meme, you would be able to garner most of your provisions, meaning not only for food, but also for clothing and shelter locally.
Right.
And you also did commerce where things were brought in from places abroad or far away.
All right.
So you were pretty much self-sustaining.
As people are today, no matter how many products are imported or exported around the world, they're used where you are, like wherever you go, there you are.
And when you were to travel, you couldn't bring the value of what you actually stood on with you.
So you had a representation of it.
And it's called money.
Money represents locally the land that you stand on or collectively there would be the county or the district or the state or the country.
That's why you hear of foreign exchanges.
Right.
One country's money is against another country's money.
You hear that typically.
And what does that represent?
What is a country supposed to?
Let's set aside the corporate statehood for a moment.
A country represents its national sovereignty based on its geographic region and what it could provide.
Like for when you think of a country that is covered in ice, you think of what it could provide differently than a country that has four feet of topsoil, for example.
So this, and this has escaped humanity now wholeheartedly across the board.
It's fascinating to see how keeping time, what time is, what money is, what health is, all these, what is lawful has escaped almost everyone you can come in contact with.
And I'm not saying, you know, someone who's plugged in front of the TV watching the stupid bowl and drinking cheap beer.
I'm talking about everyone across the board.
I mean, alternative mainstream spirit.
People call themselves spiritual.
People call themselves this or that.
It's just fascinating to see how humanity has taken the plunge into complete darkness at this point.
And if you're fortunate enough to run into the 5, 10 or 100 people or 1,000 people left on this planet, you're quite fortunate.
And that's, I believe, the message that we're discussing is for those.
So hopefully, you know, those are random thoughts from the Greek, I guess.
And thanks for indulging.
But I wanted to also, Chuck, maybe talk a little bit about what's going on and have a quick rehash on what people call the news and what's going on these days.
Well, certainly.
But I don't think it's very fair to call it random thoughts.
That was actually extremely coherent and gave people a whole new explanation as to what is being constantly argued about, which makes a whole lot more sense.
You know, when you take a look at why is an exchange rate this way or that way?
I mean, you and I had a discussion at one point off the air about the value of the Australian money versus the American money.
And it was kind of odd.
Right.
There was this – and I'll give people the numeric example.
There was a $15 amount that we were talking about that had been exchanged.
Okay.
I'm not going to tell you who, where, what, what.
It doesn't matter.
The point is that there was this 15 units Australian that translated into, well, less than 10 American.
And I thought that that was really fascinating.
Now, I know that this is a really mundane kind of topic.
But when one considers what you just said regarding what it represents and how it is basically the portable representation of the land, I guess that makes a whole lot more sense.
I mean you could talk about the natural resources, the availability, the country's stability, this and that and the third thing.
But the reality is you don't find a real continuity as to – by comparison, let's just say, when you take a look at these exchange rates, there is something else at play.
And that means that almost every one of these people who claims to be like a financial guru explaining to you what this means and why it is.
Why it is the yuan is tanking right now as we speak and all of these other things.
They give you all of these prognostications based on all of these extremely sophisticated – you would have to nearly spend every moment of your life observing the continuous changes across the globe regarding the political, the social, the manufacturing, the industrial, the agricultural techniques that are being employed by all of these allegedly sovereign nations across the planet.
And watch the interplay between them and who is trading with who and all of this stuff.
And meanwhile, it still doesn't make sense based on the crap they give you if you take some time and try and follow their reasoning.
Because the reasoning is unlawful. I invite any financial guru on radio or especially all of them on radio right now.
Everything that I've ever seen, YouTubes, radio shows, any network, mainstream, alternative, morons, every single one of them and it is open invitation.
If you would like to have a conversation, ocelliumthegreek.com, send us an email.
You are a moron if you are doing financial commentary and the first thing out of your mouth every time you do a commentary is that you don't remind people that it is a credit-based economy and it is a private credit-based economy.
It is not a lawful money-based economy and none of them.
They have had opportunities. There's no reason to name names. They know who they are and the people here listening might have heard some of these morons.
Yes, it's the morons with a capital R because that's where you put the tone and pronunciation when you say the word to describe them.
And all of them are, bar none, without exception, none of them ever for all the years or months or weeks they've spent on the internet pontificating the rubbish that they pontificate.
Have I ever heard them ever discuss that it is a credit-based economy and it is unlawful, not a one.
And this is the type of service that people are getting on this informational medium and it's rubbish.
It doesn't matter. The alternative guys are no better than the tune in to CNBC or whatever to explain what's going on in the markets and why your money is no longer quite as valuable as it was two weeks ago.
You know what? It's all the same.
My favorite is the credentials that a lot of people on the internet are using.
Oh, this guy worked for an intelligence agency. This guy worked for this. This guy used to do this. Who cares?
It's really funny. Whenever you're in a business where experience is required and someone says they've got 10 years experience, I wonder if it's just one year experience 10 times because they're stuck.
This is humanity but the thing is what's criminal and here's the thing.
When the criminality is high, it requires harsh language and that's what might sound like we're harsh.
It's not because we're just harsh because we got up on the wrong side of the bed or whatever or the shoes are not comfortable.
It's because the level of criminality right now that all of humanity, not some of humanity is very high.
There's an easy way out. You see a lot of people that go and make speeches on this president or that world leader or this financial institution and none of them have even for a moment put in the thoughts of themselves or their listeners or who they're making the presentation to that they need to set themselves apart before they address anything.
All of these people that are going out and been discussing, I've been looking at what's on the internet for the past let's say two dozen years can be memorialized easily.
It's all rubbish, all of it because the very people that are protesting it are also endorsing it.
So what is one to do? Well, maybe taking a cosmic approach because it doesn't seem like the politics and the methodology that they're using makes any sense and the cosmic approach is very simple.
The society that humans are experiencing right now are men and women is going to be wrapped up in a bundle with a bow on it let's say and that bundle and that final package is going to be all centered in the Middle East.
I think like we've discussed and I've been discussing this on roundtables publicly on air for years that you're going to see the emergence of a new country in the Middle East.
It doesn't exist right now. It had existed 2,300 years ago and it's called Assyria, not Syria, Assyria.
It's going to be in northern Iraq and what I've also discussed in the past few years is when this new country is formed, it's going to also occupy land or its borders will also take land from what is currently known as Syria and Turkey.
Now, when was the last time a new country is formed and not only let's say in the middle of nowhere in a desert or something but it also takes lands and pushes the borders back up to other established countries without a fight or without turmoil?
When has that ever happened? Hardly ever. Now, what's in the news? Syria has been in the news and Turkey has been in the news recently but the Greek has been saying for the past four years watch Turkey, watch Syria, watch Lebanon, watch Jordan, watch northern Iraq, watch Greece and no one is inquiring.
Isn't that fascinating? And this is not just to watch them like dots on the wall or something but for very specific reasons and it's all coming to fruition and no one is inquiring. Isn't that fascinating?
But not that they should for anyone else's benefit let's say but it's just so novel. So, here's the thing. Right now, I think you and I, Chuck, once maybe what they call October the 8th month roughly when we first started having discussions, I was first discussing with you this new country coming on the scene probably by 2018, 2019 and it's going to also take land from Turkey and Syria.
Well, guess who's in the news these days? Turkey and Syria but this new country is not in the news yet, is it? Because it's a new country. How would you know it's new? It doesn't even exist yet. The people exist but you know what people are not up at arms at yet, right? It's Jordan. Have you heard of that country, little country Jordan? It's got a real funky looking shape on the map too.
Wait till you see the carnage that's going to befall that country and it's going to be divided into at least two or three jurisdictions with the expulsion of the current monarchy. So, this is interesting and this is all, where do you get this from? These are new ideas gotten from a really old book because in order to have a Middle East Union, you have to have a grouping of countries that work very closely together.
What they're going to look like is the way they looked 2,000 years ago. So, if anyone wants to know what the Middle East is going to look like in the next five years, pull out a map of what it looked like 2,000 plus years ago and also overlap a map of what it looked like 3,000 years ago and average it out.
You could pretty much be a political genius. Well, politics doesn't even exist anymore. I don't think it really. It's just a name only. But these are the things that are coming. So, don't be surprised when you start to see turmoil in Jordan and don't be surprised when you start to see extremely heavy investment being put into Lebanon and having the port cities of Lebanon rebuilt to be like some kind of French Riviera.
Real interesting stuff that's coming and these things, the details on this needs to go out to multinational corporations and governments and private when these things are going to happen and how they happen.
But the reason we voiced them here is because for posterity, guess what? We said it here first. How many people, Chuck, on the internet or radio, mainstream or not, are discussing about a new country's coming in the near future in the Middle East to form a Middle East Union taking land from Syria and Turkey? None. None.
Well, no. The only thing that they're talking about is this alleged Islamic state, this concept that there will be a combination of territories which will be woven together based on this radical concept of Islam.
I can barely say this stuff with a straight face, by the way, guys, because I think it's an absolute ridiculous notion what they're pushing out there regarding this.
Now, here's the funny thing. You mentioned to me and you only just really now mentioned publicly about this concept of what's going on in Lebanon.
Now, I thought about that some months ago when you first mentioned it to me privately and I started to ask questions because I've known more than one Lebanese person, so I asked questions of those people to see what was happening over there and what has transpired in recent times.
Nobody would expect this based on what the public's knowledge is of Lebanon. Lebanon is not even being discussed publicly at this point. It was a hot-button issue.
We had, of course, everybody remembers the marine barracks and the absolute punishment of really some ancient and wonderful places that were present in Lebanon before the surrogate struggles that occurred over there.
There was really just a lot of, I don't know how to explain it, like turmoil in the course of my lifetime.
You haven't recovered, by the way, since the 70s when they had their civil war or whatever they had there.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking of exactly was that in the 1970s, this stuff was going on and it was vaguely sort of mentioned in Western news and things like that.
But oddly enough, months before, I had heard from you this concept that there would be this industry that would sort of rise up and it's kind of a strange thought.
Only in recent days, somebody mentioned to me that it seems as though there is evidence that there will be investment in that area.
These people that try to determine trends ahead of time and things like that told me that this was the kind of thing that was going to happen.
So in the next 10 years or so, we will see Lebanon re-emerging in the global financial scheme of things.
Yes, it will be whatever an illustrious, incredibly advanced port city would have.
Not only tourism and shipping and political and resort type, but it would be the best at those things.
And it's really difficult to see that now.
What we're doing is we're giving information on what the trading price of a stock is going to be in two or three years in the stock of a company.
And that company hasn't even been formed yet.
Right.
Can you imagine how crazy this sounds?
But the thing is if anyone has all the wiser, they would record this and put it aside.
But the details, I prefer not to give in public because there are specific details on how it will come together.
And that is where the think tank comes in, the consulting group or any other structure that is done for those that need to hear the specifics.
But for the general public at the moment, they lack any efficiency when they're looking at what is being discussed on the world scene.
It's sort of like driving a car down the road or conveyance, let's say, and you're just looking at the hood ornament.
You're not even looking 10 feet ahead of you or you don't even acknowledge that there's a rear view mirror or even side mirrors.
This is the state of all of humanity.
When I say all of humanity, we're talking about 7,100,000,000,000, whatever, according to the World Bank, their cattle that they have documented.
So, yeah, this is really sad.
I mean, the condition that they're in.
But there's no reason to fray about it because if you read the ancient text, it says that you're going to come in a time period where all these things can be revealed.
And no one's going to care.
No one's going to listen.
But you've got to say it anyway.
So anyway, yeah, it's quite, quite fantastic when you see the situation.
But thanks for engaging the Greek on this for a few minutes because, you know, every so often we've got to tell the world what's coming.
And I think as time goes on, a little more detail, a little more detail, a little more detail.
And any kind of turmoil.
How many times have you heard of people being, quote, unquote, worried about what's going on in the news?
And it just blows over.
And you go back and say, hey, you were really worried about this a month ago.
What? No.
What? Huh?
That was a month ago.
No, it doesn't matter.
Well, if it was so trivial now, why was it so important then?
See, that shows, like, the epitome of lack of efficiency.
And this is your average surface-dwelling Earth inhabitant right now.
And even with the slightest bit of reasoning and common sense, people are not supposed to live life so inefficiently.
You see?
Right.
And I do constantly preach the idea that giving in to anxiety is, you know, that's the best way I can describe it.
Because, of course, I'm left with these psychological terms to engage in the discussion.
But I always say that, you know, anxiety and the panic attacks that are being encouraged by individuals,
these are exactly the people that you don't need to be listening to,
that you don't need to be, you know, emotionally investing in, let's just say,
because they have absolutely no clue about what's really happening.
They have absolutely no clue about what has transpired.
They don't know their history.
They don't know the current situation.
And they certainly have no understanding of the future.
I mean, that's just blatantly obvious.
And how do you know?
Well, go ahead.
Take a look back at what has been memorialized.
How many of these guys have told you that, you know, the economy is crashing?
You know, how many people have told you that, you know,
the United States will end as a nation, you know, in the next 60 days, in the next 30 days?
Yeah, all of those things already happened and no one's noticed.
Well, that's the funny part.
The economy crashed in the 30s, and the U.S. has now become a territory of Washington, D.C.
Right.
I'm completely with you.
The thing is that even the secondary, you know, the second incarnation of what was an economy for the rest of us,
actually collapsed and ended in 2008.
It's gone.
Well, sort of.
You see, the economy, there is no more economy.
Like Greenspan said a few years ago, more than 20 years ago, he might have said this,
that what people miss – I'm going to paraphrase here.
People have a misunderstanding of the economy.
What they call the economy is just a disbursement and distribution system.
There's no more economy because it's all based on credit.
It comes out of your signature.
That's why when you hear a moron say taxpayer dollars are paying for anything, that is a moron with a capital R.
This is from firsthand experience with correspondence and face-to-face discussions with pretty,
let's say, mid-level government officials.
What classifies someone as a taxpayer is a birth certificate.
It's like when you go and play, you're the red team or the blue team.
You haven't played anything on the field yet.
When you get a birth certificate, that creates a limited liability relationship between you
and the financial agencies, not the government.
So you can't pay taxes.
There is no money to pay anything with.
What it is, if you want to fast forward, what the Federal Reserve
and all the taxing agencies are are nothing more than divine retribution on a human society
that has gone totally to the dark side.
So they poke at you and they're like, you're working for nothing.
I don't know anyone who's alive today who's been paid.
Getting checks and what they call cash is not getting paid.
It's mere promise to be paid, right?
And no one is paying any attention.
So if you cannot see that that is done by a divine force and it's not mankind that's doing it, you're blind.
So you're not going to fight that divine force, especially if people negate its existence.
No, we're not talking about Santa Claus or all those other things and the Easter rabbit and all that stuff.
No, we're not talking about that or things that they tell you in the circus or churches
or whatever you want to call them or whatever.
So we're looking at a society that is really, really, really just completely removed
from anything that is not arbitrary.
Everything has to be arbitrary, like throwing the dice, rolling the dice now.
And I believe that when you find out something that is firm and sure, I think it needs to be voiced.
And that's the purpose of you and I coming together, I believe.
And it's all right to call an entire group without exception morons,
which are all the financial analysts and all these other people with a capital R,
because that term, if you look up what it means, it's actually quite accurate.
And, yeah, they're not discussing the obvious.
You know, just like I mean, here you want to really talk about something moronic.
It's New Year's. And it's really saddening to see that the entire world has accepted it.
Just, oh, it's interesting when you read the ancient writings, it says the entire world will be deceived.
And when you look at these writings, did you first thing when I read that,
I ran to the bottom of the page to see if there was a footnote except for the Greek.
You know, no, I didn't see that.
Did you ever read any ancient document talking about the ancient, the entire world will be deceived?
And don't you want to run to the bottom of the page and see if there's a footnote with the name you're using on it?
Not you also. No, I didn't see any footnotes.
No, I definitely didn't. And I always look for the exception to the grand deception.
And there really isn't one. There is.
Yeah. Yeah. Unfortunately, we're all on the same, you know, ship, as you said before.
And, you know, this is this is the activity menu.
And guess what? We're all still eating off of the same preselected menu.
It's what it is. The other analogy is the man behind the curtain.
There is no man behind the curtain. Everybody is under the curtain in the dark.
You know, it's a veil. You know, what is a curtain? You know, so, yeah, it's fascinating.
So, you know, it's it really is therapeutic for hopefully anyone that can internalize and rationalize what we're saying,
because we're speaking plainly and therapeutic, meaning don't worry about all this stuff.
There's we've been looking at every I think either privately or on the show openly in public,
discussing certain matters and issues that people find noteworthy in the alternative media.
And have we ever come across anything that we said, Chuck, we need to discuss this in greater detail,
because, yes, this is a true and correct description of the issue or situation.
Or do we always say, oh, boy, look at this crap again?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. And always seems to be the latter, because, well, unfortunately, that's all there is.
Oh, yeah, it's just. Yeah, it's it is.
Yeah. So the thing is, there there's a certain type of thought process that anyone can indulge in.
And it's just if it has to be simple, it has to be applicable to everyone.
And you have to be able to perceive it and discern it with using the most basic factors of cognitive discernment.
You know, you know, we never speak in complex terms or anything.
We might just eventually say, go look what that word means, you know, etymologically.
Why not? I think it's it's doing the right thing. Right.
Right. I mean, that's about it.
Know what the meaning of the word actually carries, because after all, language in and of itself is part of the grand deception.
You know, you are meant to believe that certain words have a particular meaning that they don't over and over again.
I mean, so the etymology is the evidence of it. It's just what's left over.
Truthfully, there's a whole lot more to it that is not accessible that that one can study as well to understand that there are rudimentary truths which are contained in languages.
Yes, believe it or not, doesn't matter which language we're talking about here that that you can find if you can, you know, find the cipher, as it were.
But I haven't seen one. I have not seen one publicly shared anywhere.
You notice that? Yeah, it's well, you know, even when you will we mean publicly, meaning through audible sonically,
or do you think in Web pages or anything like that or memorialized in books as well?
You mean, or I would say all of the above, you know, from the literature that the literature that I've been able to access,
the the audible sources that I've been able to access, I have never seen an understanding of really, you know,
they tell you about where this word came from.
Sure, etymology is useful because it does tell you what the weight of the word carried.
But the actual sounds and the fact that there is commonality and there is a reality to the sounds that are made in language is is it's it's absent.
It's not out there. I don't see it.
It's not because people just they what they want to do is just show up to the feeding trough and see what kind of corn or whatever they threw in there that day.
You know what I mean?
You know, and if you don't want to eat that corn, well, guess what?
You go you don't go you go hungry.
So if you start you don't want to eat that corn that the pig swallow or whatever they're dumping out for everybody to eat.
You're you're going to go you are not going to be able to communicate.
You say. Right, right. And then an anonymous person in the chat room said the crap is always cheap and deep.
And yes, I think that that is a is a really solid way of looking at it.
Of course, what is cheap and deep is readily available and there is plenty of it, but it's not necessarily very useful.
And I think that was the the core of what we were talking about here for the past.
It's much about minutes. It's what's mud on the wheels, everything on the Internet.
Now, if you're not using the Internet for entertainment as a telephone book or telephony, you're you're getting wrapped around the axle as an old term or it's mud on your wheels.
You know, you know, it breaks traction in the there's a lot of good services offered on it.
But the new services are just, in other words, do it's the opposite.
And it's not only the opposite of what's being regarded as news on the Internet or mainstream, because we're saying it,
we can go through a veritable plethora of financial disasters or planetary disasters and events that it should have occurred even the past year.
That haven't occurred. Right. You see. So never mind the past five, 10 or 20.
But here's the thing. What they catch on to is that in any time in mankind's history, if you preach doom and gloom,
that will be a very desirable message or successful message to many.
If you're preaching doom and gloom, everyone wants to hear it. You see.
So that's what they've latched on to and they don't know it. But essentially the inefficiency it was that was put on humanity is still lingering.
And now it's been electronically delivered because, you know, the yellow journalism and all this other stuff that existed and the gossiping and rumors.
I think you're familiar with the term of the rumors of wars and such.
So, yeah. So, yeah, it's just the inefficiency is what we maybe can get together every week and discuss how to avoid that.
You know, or we used to call it the dummy load. Right. That's true, too.
The dummy load is all. But the reason why it exists as it does is because of the cosmic censorship.
Now, censorship is a word that most people who would bother to tune in to us would would understand full well.
However, I think it's worthy of time here to sort of explain what you mean by cosmic in a plain sense.
Cosmic would mean when you have these geocentric satellites.
Right. And you bounce off. You know, there's no direct line of sight.
So you bounce around this daisy chain, let's say, of satellites to go around the globe. Right.
Cosmic would mean in that sense, it's not doesn't just affect one group of people.
It affects everyone. It's broadcast across the entire spectrum.
And here's the thing, you know, getting into a discussion. I've tried this both publicly and privately.
Well, we'll explain cosmic censorship. If the word is very telling, it's self-explanatory.
And if you need to if you need that explained, I tell people, guess what?
You're subject to it. So, well, it's, you know, to explain it.
You're cosmically being censored, which goes back to a lot of the things that we discussed.
It's all external input. Right. People think their thoughts are their own because they're used to it.
You know, the reason why people ride a bike or know how to walk or even walk and chew gum is because they're used to it.
They take it for granted. If your lights were just turned on and you were in a full adult body,
you would fall to the ground and you if this happened to two of you, you'd be looking at each other saying,
why are we crawling on the ground? This is well, because we haven't learned how to walk yet.
I mean, you better get up and learn how to walk quick because someone is going to walk in here and wonder what the hell is going on.
You see, that's why, you know, there's TBI, traumatic brain injury, people recover and they have to learn how to walk again.
You know, I think the receiver. So the point here is that we are taking too much for granted.
And that's how it's supposed to be right now. So I don't know, is it are we badgering the public by saying that?
No. In other words, you're supposed to be censored. Yes, you are supposed to be censored,
but you really don't have to because it's a very thin veil. It's a very thin.
It's not that thick to break out of it. But the timekeeping is one way, you know.
Right. That's certainly one way. And I do appreciate the concept of, you know, being subject in in in your entirety to to external input, essentially.
And we discussed that earlier. And but you know what? An odd concept did come up.
And I want to use kind of the remainder of the show because we've kind of went all around here a bit.
But I want to use the remainder of the show to discuss something that was that was asked of us in a communication by a listener.
And this was about the concept of dreams. Now. Of course, when you start to discuss dreams and psychology,
the first thing that strikes you is is the the word psychology and how this is usually the the the fools that end up studying this stuff
is those that allege to be psychologists, although just like most things on the planet,
they're not actually what they say they are. In most cases, you know, you would think that.
Well, hold on. But a PSY means spirit. The PSY prefix. So they're really spiritualists.
Ah, yes. And there's a quality of spirit in the universe.
It goes from low quality grunt to mid level, to upper level, to high level and to the highest ultimate level in a ranking quality system.
And that's why, again, anyone and everything you've heard on the Internet regarding spirituality is rubbish with a capital B,
because they never discern the quality. So anyway.
Well, right. But but the thing is that a psychologist allegedly studies the mind,
which is supposed to be separate from the body and also separate from the spirit.
Well, the mind is the spirit. I didn't say what it was. I said what it is they allege to study. Right.
So if I'm wrong, it's not that you're wrong. It's just that the quality of things.
There's there's there's everything is quantity, quantitative. Now, how many degrees have you got?
How many years you spend in school? How many how much money have you got? You know, how old are you?
You know, no quality. There's no more quality. Right. Quality is not being taken into account anymore.
So the PSY prefix, it means mind. That's in the Greek system.
And just like the PNAU or I think it's PNU prefix means air like pneumatic or pneumonia.
Right. PNAU or PNU prefix. And that is the soul or the breath.
It's very simple. And that's part of the cosmic censorship.
And it's also been put on through spoiling the reference books.
Look up spirit in an etymological or anywhere else dictionary.
Say, well, the spirit is the mind, but it could also be the soul or this.
And then look up soul and they say, well, the soul is your breath, but it could also be the spirit.
They're really trying to hide something there, you know.
Mm hmm. You know, but it's in the here's the thing.
If you don't know what the anyone what the body, the mind and the soul is, that is what makes up your HQ, your headquarters.
Right. So if you're deceived about the body, which most people are, they think they absorb things like a sponge or they're like some kind of filter bag.
They're deceived about the mind. They think it's something, you know, in the spirit of something else.
And they're deceived about the soul because they might think it's the breath, but it's also the mind or the spirit.
So they're deceived about all these three components that make them up.
If you're just if so, headquarters is full of deception.
Anything that comes out of headquarters is going to be prone to deception.
You see, most headquarters is not full of deception.
You were understanding that you're supposed to be able to take in from the alleged learned people out there is what's full of deception.
The truth is, the order is rather evident if you break it down for a moment, because the mind in and of itself, they talk about it.
You know, being a mechanism of the brain all the time. Right.
You know, they talk about how, you know, the mind causes the brain to do this or the brain causes the mind to do that.
Yeah. But hold on.
You're kept in a particular area of the brain, et cetera, et cetera.
So I'm not saying that I agree with any of that. You understand.
It's just an antenna. It's just an antenna. It's just like a member of the old television sets where you need an antenna.
You know, you take TV set out of the room and and out of the closet, let's say plug it in.
It's just you get the rasper, you know, the snow. And so you look at the backwards as antenna.
There's nothing there. So you grab a clothes hanger, a copper wire, jam it in there.
You get a picture, a better and then a proper antenna gives you a better picture.
Oh, you know why? Because all that signal is inside the wire hanger.
That's why. That's ridiculous.
Well, no. And it's an aerial yourself.
Yeah. You go and get yourself some rabbit ears and do a little better.
And then you take one and you put it outside and it's much larger and has a greater sort of span and array.
Wow. Boy, are we dating ourselves here?
Because there's a lot of people that, you know, were born post antenna reality.
As far as the television goes, the Wi-Fi, the Wi-Fi still are using something like that and they use fractal ones.
But here's the thing. Until Crackerjack starts giving out brains.
Now you stuck with the one you've got, whoever you are.
And you're going to have to relax about it because it's not there's nothing in your head.
It's an antenna. So anyway, you know, the these quack academics and scientists,
they've done extensive research on new new new neuron reading and all this other stuff.
And by the way, they look at the electrical side of the body.
Any more on MD will tell you that the muscles are fired electrically, the intestines and the brain.
But do they have any electro therapy? None. But anyway, these guys have studied the brain.
You know, where is memory? Where is it? Where is they can't see it?
This is their conclusions. And I'm talking about real scientific studies,
not the crap that has been put out to the public that you can still find something that's tangible and rational.
They'll tell you that we find nothing in the brain.
But but if you if you cut off a part of the brain, you lose a motor function or an involuntary motor skill
or voluntary motor skill or memory, just like as if you cut off a part of the antenna.
You're not going to be tuning into, let's say, Channel 66 somewhere else, you know, whatever.
So what what happens is, look, you twist that thing around, move it around.
You might actually pick up stuff you're not even supposed to pick up.
That's the interesting thing about it. And the brain has been proven to rewire itself.
Yeah. And there's there's a couple of people out there.
They're still doing fine without a brain, without the physical organ, believe it or not.
You can see now that that I've never heard of. Yeah. Look it up.
There's a couple of people out there that don't have much of a brain left or they can't be classified as a brain.
I think it's like a medulla or anything or something like that is left in there and they're still functioning.
Yeah. So anyway, but the dreaming part, you know, to bring up there's a there's a very the cosmic censorship is so thick
that I have been saying for over 10 years how simple it is to discover that you are made up of a body, a spirit and a soul.
And I have yet to meet more than two people that can grasp that concept.
Now, anyone will say, yeah, of course, have a body, a soul and a spirit.
But when you start discussing the definitions of soul and spirit, they can't handle it. They run away.
It's just you just can't do it. It's just it's just not going to happen.
That's the first sign of your censorship. The spirit and the soul are not the same thing.
They're very different. Right. And we will continue this discussion.
Obviously, that is the music for the end of the second hour of the sonic entity we call Ocelli and the Greek and Greek.
I think we've done pretty good in the first hour to set a lot of things straight, but more to come in the second.
What do you say? I say so. All right. Stay tuned.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us? Provide us with free education.
Well, that's obviously effective. But apart from reversing the dumbing down of America, all the information they provide is free.
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from and exploiting our commonplace corruption?
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
Well, they never censor, hang up or cut off their guests.
Well, that's no fun, is it?
Well, they created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shills and scum.
OK, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, exposing commonplace corruption,
helping vulnerable people without a voice, bringing light to important information nobody else does
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative mainstream and alternative media shills and scum,
what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the American.
Oh, yes, I like.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand-new detox formulations of micro plant powder, brain fuel for depression, bipolar disorders and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
Tell the truth. Don't be bullshitting people.
There's enough bullshit as it is. In fact, there's just enough.
Did you know that?
There's just enough bullshit to hold things together in this country.
Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation.
Where would we be without our safe, familiar American bullshit?
Land of the free, home of the brave, the American dream.
All men are equal. Justice is blind. The press is free.
Your vote counts.
Business is honest. The good guys win.
The police are on your side.
God is watching you.
Your standard of living will never decline.
And everything is gonna be just fine.
The official national bullshit story.
I call it the American Okie Doke.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
The network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast that would dare to under...
So the second hour is here.
Aboucelli in the Greek for the first time on Friars Day.
Yes, Friday evening.
This is the oddity that has come up.
We used to do this on Saturn Day.
Yeah, that's true.
But I actually feel pretty good about this one so far
and I think if you missed the first hour
you're going to need to go into the archives and take a listen.
It will be the first show of 2016
according to the Pope's work schedule.
So take a listen when it goes up there
and check it out.
And mind you, there are 13 previous episodes
on the 2015 archive as well at American Freedom Radio.
And oh, by the way, don't forget that there's also
the Aboucelli in the Greek website
which pretty much will wind up directing you also back to that.
And hey, also to my website, aboucelli.com
where we did actually record something for members only
over there this week.
Just so you guys know, that was on the very essential
and necessary topic of water
which we won't comment on here tonight about it
but if you are a member over there, you heard it
and you know that that was very much in the vein of this show
which is very much about saying things
that are not being said elsewhere.
And here we go, hour number two, Greg.
You with me?
Yeah, I'm here. Can you hear me?
Yep. Okay.
The thing about the water, I just want to digress for a moment
is we can give them an outline of what to expect
if they do attend the membership.
And I think there's seven quick points.
I could just go down there and maybe wet their palate
and see if, no pun intended, to see if they can find it interesting.
I think the pun was intended, but go ahead.
Yes, but one is why does a bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air?
Two, water may not be H2O.
Three, the history of water storage.
Four, Victor Shawberger's principle discovery.
That should be plural as well.
Five, proper handling of water.
Six, the enrichment of water.
And seven, the effects of water on health.
And it's not what you think it is.
No, certainly not.
Nothing like what you hear elsewhere.
But, you know, speaking of things that you don't hear elsewhere,
yes, we are discussing this concept that was, well,
semi-inspired by listener input regarding dreams,
and we've only really laid the groundwork here about it.
We started to discuss, you know, obviously the PSY prefix,
things like that in the first hour.
So, like I said, tune to the archive to catch it if you missed it.
But if you are with us so far, you know, let's continue on.
You know, the mind, the spirit, and the soul, yes,
we've defined that many, many times.
We've discussed it many, many times.
And hopefully you've grasped it.
Now, dreams, this is from an outline, by the way, that you passed to me.
Dreams are downloaded, okay, from grunts up to high command.
Now, kind of a loaded statement because you're wondering who the grunts are,
who the high command is, and what the system of download is.
And I think that is something that is certainly worthy of discussing
because people talk about dreams as being unfinished psychological problems
from the day or from earlier in their lives or whatever else,
and because they've gone into another state,
which I don't think you would argue that when you are dreaming,
you are in a decidedly different state than you are when you are conscious, right?
Yeah, and it's pure telepathy, by the way.
That's why if anyone can remember any dreaming scenes, quote-unquote, or scenery,
if you are having a dream of someone having a conversation or speaking to you or at you,
you might recall that mouths never move.
So just throw that in there.
So for the next time if you're paying attention
and someone is speaking to you in a dream, their mouths are not moving.
So anyway, that's maybe a small sign that Hollywood is big.
Well, yeah, oddly enough, right, there is this – and I've got to tell you,
I have extremely vivid dream states on occasion.
And what I recall from them is quite often that I have ideas that sort of are received by me,
regardless of what is going on in the dream sometimes.
I may suddenly have a feeling that something is going to happen in the dream,
and lo and behold, it does, or I'm worried about something happening or carrying forward,
and I realize I'm in the dream, and things like that usually end the experience
or the experience seems to end at just about that point where I say to myself,
this is not an awake state.
Things like that happen.
And I'm sure plenty of people can identify with those particular feelings,
but the truth is that you are imparted with many ideas in a different way
than you would be in your normal awake state.
For instance, like you said, somebody's mouth not moving,
but you'll still get the impression, the idea, an emotion, a transmission seemingly
from the figure who is represented in that dream state, and sometimes, I mean,
quite often, to tell you the truth, I dream of people who are no longer alive,
and I'm given ideas by them that sometimes are relevant to something that is going on
and sometimes not, but the ideas are transmitted to me,
not necessarily based solely on the actions I'm observing
or the activity that I am sort of participating in.
For instance, I may be engaged in, and I'll just give you a strange, for instance,
and throw it at you, and who knows what you'll want to do with it,
but I may be engaged in a fist fight based on what I see in my dream
with someone who is dead.
Meanwhile, I don't feel as though I am locked in mortal combat with them,
but they are literally trying to pound an idea into my head,
is the impression that I take from it.
And this happens.
Now, many people say that there's all sorts of ways to interpret it,
and like I said, what they call psychology gives you one view of it.
What individuals who describe themselves as spiritualists give you another view of it.
Same.
But, well, yes, the same, but one is meant to be representative of something,
and the other is, yes, representative,
but is not really driven by anything else except yourself.
Like psychologists would say that you have sort of dreamed up a figure
in order to represent something in your own mind.
Yeah, but you've got to discern the institutionalized knowledge base
versus the more free-flowing.
Like the ancient spiritualists, they were also institutionalized, believe it or not,
just as much as any thought that was in large numbers, any group think,
is always institutionalized.
But the current institutionalized,
because a psychologist and a spiritualist are the same thing,
it's just using a different prefix, right?
The spiritualist would be using the word and the PSY prefix
in front of the psychiatrist or psychologist is using the Greek phonetic prefix
for the same term.
The modern psychology is pretty much birthed from a group of pretty twisted individuals
from the turn of the 20th century.
And if anyone wants to know who they are,
you can just go ahead and research the history of modern psychiatry and psychology
and look at who these individuals were.
So you're not going to, you know, it's not that, again,
this harkens back to what number that item was,
which is dreams or downloads from grunts up to high command.
Not only is what I meant by the grunts and high command is on the spiritual realm,
there's also that level of informational and interpretational interchange here in society, right?
So you have low-level stuff and then you've got the more high-level stuff
that's not open to the public.
And sometimes now in human society, the higher you go, actually the lower you're going.
Yeah, those who are successful or allegedly the movers and shakers in society
are not necessarily the same people who are on a higher level spiritually, emotionally, etc., etc.,
which by the way, hopefully you're not hearing a train go by right now.
We are, but it sounds melodic.
So here's the thing.
Everyone is on the same spiritual level, believe it or not.
And these things will be discovered in the future because spiritual means mind level.
And to put this in some form of, let's say, tangibility of thought or perspective,
Chuck, have you ever been to China?
Physically, no.
No, okay.
You've heard of China.
You can see it on the map.
You hear a lot of things about them, a billion, billion-plus people.
And so, okay, we haven't been to China, right?
But you know, for example, there's different levels of society, okay,
and then you have a high command.
But you've never been there, but you're sure as day that it exists,
that it's tangible to some degree, even though you haven't been there.
You might have met people from China, right?
Right.
Okay, this is the spiritual realm.
People are – one of the things that was written years ago is that during these days that we live in now,
people will deny the existence of the spiritual realm, which is quite interesting.
And some of the explanations you get about the spiritual realm are so obscure,
obscene, and stupid that you might as well deny it as well from the explanations that you get.
Just on the face of the idiocy that's being pushed.
It's another denial.
So we're talking about a realm, just like China, let's say.
There are billions – when I say, have you been to China?
No, and do you know China exists?
Yes, do you know there are people in China?
Well, it's not just one or two or five.
We're talking about a very large plurality of population.
The spiritual realm also has a very large plurality of population.
And within that population, there is also a hierarchy, just like you see on Earth, of people.
You have from the grunts, and when I say grunts, I mean this is self-professed.
I've met people that are ex-military, and I ask them how did they do in the military?
They say, I don't know, I just did what I was told.
I was just a grunt.
So I'm like, wow, okay, so this is a common term used amongst some individuals.
So why not use it?
This is not to offend anyone.
And it goes all the way up to – within the grunt level, they've got their own hierarchy.
Then you switch over to a mid-level hierarchy, and they've got their own hierarchy.
Then you have the high-level hierarchy, and they have their own hierarchy within the high levels.
And then it goes up to the high command.
So we're looking at – just to cover back some of the things you mentioned in the dreaming,
there's imagery and messaging and whatever.
The reason this is done the way it is, and it is the way it is,
is because we discussed on the previous time we got together about the cosmic censorship on the second hour.
I think I brought up the concept that all of your perception exists in the imagination.
All of the five senses that you're taking in, including what you were thinking about,
all happens in the imagination.
So like you could look at a red dot on the wall and close your eyes
and know that that red dot will be there even when you open your eyes,
even when your eyes are closed, because now it's in the imagination.
And even when you're looking at something, it's in the imagination.
And if this is not true, then ledger domain or what's called magic, performance magic, would not be possible.
Sleight of hand would not be possible.
The credit economy wouldn't be possible.
Alternative media wouldn't be possible.
Oops, did I say that?
Sorry.
Yes, you did.
Okay.
Yeah, so it's all in the imagination.
So what happens when you're sleeping is, guess what?
You're unconscious, right?
Okay.
Just like in medical terms, he's unconscious, but he's breathing.
If he's unconscious and not breathing, well, you know, now you've got a big problem.
But when you're unconscious, guess what?
There's no imagination.
You're not very imaginative when you are asleep.
So because there is no imagination and you cannot discern or perceive what you consider or people consider,
humans consider reality, now you are subject to input.
And it's very different.
And because it's so different, we call it, it's the dream world.
And this might sound kind of obtuse to many.
This is sort of like discussing, you know, you can get in public, go in public now and discuss computers, you know,
Windows, Apple, Linux, all this stuff, various programs and things because it's become very user-friendly.
And so what we're discussing now is C++, right?
Machine code.
Right.
Not very popular subject to discuss C++ in public.
No one wants to hear it.
But if you start talking about some new program, yeah, they want to hear it, right?
So discussing the cause and what dreams are in public is not very popular because it's like discussing machine code.
And I just want to preface this in mid-stride.
When you are asleep and when you are dreaming, even when you're awake, you can be in a dream state, semi-dream state.
You're being plugged.
You're being plugged in.
It's input.
And to discern where that comes from, whether it's a lower spiritual entity that is anywhere from malevolent to apathetic to indifferent to wanting to introduce things just to play around with you,
just like children put thumbtacks and itching powder on other children.
The spiritual realm is full of those critters.
Okay?
Now, this is a lower realm.
And then as you go higher, dreams change and they become maybe more profound and more accurate.
But here's the interesting part.
We're addressing a society that is so far removed from anything that's been memorialized for thousands of years by those primitive ignorant savages known as our ancestors.
Right?
How many times have you heard that?
Oh, that's old.
We're modern now.
That doesn't really apply anymore.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Sure.
If you look at the ancient texts, there was a lot of information about what the mind, the spirit is, what happens after you die, who you are, what you're doing here and all that.
But no one wants to access this.
It seems like to be really taboo to form any accurate perception and conveyance or be able to impart anything accurately or precisely.
So this is what we discussed in the first show we did.
It's like people have an aversion to precision and accuracy.
They hate it.
They want to be in the realm of opinion.
So who's to say what dreaming is?
What kind of arrogance are we trying to put out here?
Well, folks, it's really simple.
You're going to have to grasp who you are, where you are and what you are and that there is an entire society of intangible beings that exist in the universe.
Yes, they're intangible at this point, not forever.
There is no concept of forever, by the way, I mean for this age.
And when this intangibility ends and the perception of the human realm into the spiritual realm opens and it is now visible, boy, are people going to be in for a surprise.
You're going to be truly surprised.
But essentially, the dreaming concept is cannot ever be put in order.
If one believes when you die, you go to an infernal hell or plucking a harp up in some heavenly realm or you're reincarnated as someone, which is the most ridiculous thing also.
By the way, you will not find reincarnation in any ancient text anywhere as being a multiple thing.
When you die, you keep coming back.
That is a recent thing that has been revived by the New Age movement.
And it was actually revived thousands of years ago for a short time.
The Gnostics fell into that crap, Simon Magus crap.
You know, he tried to revive it and it's still lingering.
And I wish it would just go away.
So but but that's not going to happen.
Right. So just like fleas on a dog, dogs get fleas.
You know, people believe in stupid things.
So the concept of the C++, the machine code that humankind is running, is not a popular topic to be discussing.
And discussing what people have as reality, which all is in their imagination, taking that word, you know, as an image in the in the mind that you can manipulate.
Like we could be doing this radio show right now.
And also in the back of our minds, imagine reclining on a on a pearly white sand beach holding a cocktail with a little paper umbrella in it.
You can do that. Right.
Sure. I usually have about I've described this to one of these people.
They call themselves psychologists.
And they're absolutely astounded that that I've actually got multiple channels of the imagination happening all at once, no matter what I'm doing.
I am imagining a whole bunch of different things.
But but I'm sort of focused on the one that that we would call reality for the most part.
You know, unless it becomes extremely tedious, in which case I become a little more involved in something else that that I also feel as though I have some input on.
But but each of them sort of organically evolve.
And, you know, the emotion and the interchanges happen on about I would say personally for me, there's about 13 discernible levels in my mind at all times of different scenarios and things occurring and images.
That I could easily turn my attention to.
And they're continuously running like tabs on a computer program.
Yeah. Right. Right. And it's not anything extraordinary in my estimation.
It seems like everybody should be pretty much able to access something like that.
We've all heard of daydreams. Right.
So, yeah, you are sitting there washing the dishes.
But I guarantee you, you're not only thinking about washing the dishes, you know, whatever.
There is other things going on in your mind.
And, yeah, yeah, that is the consciousness part, you know, and again, how many times you heard of consciousness and awake?
I mean, you know, it's just like when you hear about people increasing consciousness or what is consciousness or being awake or all this stuff, this is trash.
It's tripe. It's rubbish. It's all over the Internet.
I've been listening to the Internet now, looking at it for over a decade to see if there's anything sensible.
And there isn't. It's all rubbish.
And you people out there doing websites and YouTubes and writing books, you know who you are.
It's not some of you. It's all of you.
Sorry. You know, you suck.
You're doing a big disservice.
But on one hand, that's that's from an objective point of view on a subjective point of view.
Oh, well, you know, there's cosmic censorship.
This is the best they're doing.
Most people that go out and talk about spirituality and consciousness and being awake do not have malicious intent.
Most people don't. Their intent is to help other people.
But sometimes it's the wrong thing to do.
Just like people that are in emergency medicine.
If someone is thrown out of a windshield of a car, 30 feet land on the street, you don't want to go and pick them up right away because you could do more damage moving their body.
Right. Out of place. You see.
So. So what we have is a popular a certain segment of the population, alternative or mainstream, whatever that wants to do help.
And what they're doing is they're moving a severely injured group or individual around and breaking their spine.
You know, so now they're permanently damaged.
Yeah. They're putting out there about spirituality, consciousness and being awake.
Well, this harkens. Yeah, this harkens back to one of my favorite statements you ever made, which was, you know, because with with good intent, I have often said that I would like to see people become awake and aware.
However, your commentary about that really did stick with me.
And I got to say that it gave me sort of a texture to that sentiment that that changed it a bit.
Because after all, would you want to wake up, you know, every fool that is completely uneducated, unwilling to participate on the planet?
If they're asleep, let them stay asleep.
Some of them, you know, because they're doing less damage being, you know, fully immersed in the matrix.
You know what I mean? They really are.
I don't want to wake everybody up.
Yeah. The taxpayer dollars crowd or the Fukushima crowd or the flat earth crowd.
Yeah. Let them sleep.
You know, I mean, you've got to keep every crowd.
I mean, look at the tripe that's being put out in the alternative media, the mainstream also.
But what's interesting about the mainstream media is they speak in code very often, which you don't find in the alternative.
The alternative is just dumb people pouring their guts out on electronic medium.
But in the mainstream media, you there is a level of chicanery and conniving and open communication in code, by the way, on a global level, even though it's really tripe and dumb.
But if you look at it very close, they're speaking in code certain times.
It's quite interesting. It's kind of like there are a few films on that where these intelligence agents were going around,
picking up newspapers and looking at things because their directions were being broadcast publicly.
Right. So it's quite interesting to see that sometimes.
Right. Once again, like I say, I love the concept of the cipher because, yeah, a publicly published article,
let's just say in a newspaper. Well, if you turn around and skip, you know,
equal distant amounts in between letters and things like that, then they're actual instructions.
Correct. One person could actually be be decoded in a sense.
And I think that that still goes on. Oh, yeah. In a much more sophisticated manner.
Now, I think that there's a lot of direction which is being issued through the what they call the mainstream media.
I think, however, you're being a little too kind to the alternative because some of them are very much involved in this type of deception,
misdirection and manipulation as well. I personally never have that intent to do anything like that.
You know, when I'm doing my presentations, but or this presentation or any presentation, I think.
Yeah. Right. I very much try to plainly speak and to to be as efficient about the reports I'm giving, no matter what it is I'm covering.
But but I would say that you're being too kind to the alternative to sort of exclude them from this coded messaging.
Yeah. Completely dismiss it out. Yeah, it's possible. Yeah. Let's just let's just let's just grant that.
Yeah. Thank you. You know, but but anyway, back to it, it does have a lot to do with the cosmic censorship.
Like you said, there would be no way to escape the broadcast of the daisy chains of of the satellites which are orbiting the Earth and and disseminating all of these signals.
Let's just call them signals to break it down to its most elementary sort of understanding.
And in my opinion, mind you, you know, and and this makes a lot of sense.
This explains why you have, you know, predictive programming and things like that, which people have pointed out.
You know, you see things emerge in entertainment or in other media long before they come to physical fruition, stuff like that.
I mean, you know, one of my favorite examples, which I do find entertaining, is is the behavior of certain things in old television shows like Star Trek.
You know, and we've talked about that regarding the food replicators.
But I mean, if you take a look at the information, the way that they exchanged information and access their computers, you know, in the 1980s incarnation of what they called Star Trek.
Well, gee, those things look a lot like the tablets we have, you know, 20, 30 years later.
Hmm. Well, all of that technology was to to depict something.
You know, even now, if someone wants to write a factual book on technology, they'll no publisher will take it.
They'll say, well, we'll let you publish it as fiction. Right.
So that's what that was done there. And that was from his imagination.
Well, right. I mean, Roddenberry, whether he received it through imagination or he was given some sort of direct information regarding what was yet to come one way or another, it was externally imparted upon him.
And and I think that there's something to be said about the significance of that predictive sort of revelation of what was to come.
Mind you, certain to a certain level, like Aldous Huxley with Brave New World and 1984, the other author of his name escaped me.
So, yeah, these things are not going to happen as such, but they're primers.
Yeah. George Orwell or his real name was his real name was Eric Blair.
And he was actually an intelligence guy for the for Britain, Britain. But anyway. Yeah.
No, but those things were designed as as a twofold primer to explain how the physical manifestation of censorship was going to come to fruition.
I think the two of them put together explain a lot.
And I always find it laughable that even in a very literal and particular and precise sense, certain things were were birthed in those in those allegedly fictional constructs like the drug Soma.
There's literally a drug called Soma, which didn't exist at the time the author allegedly imagined it.
That is utilized to do almost what that drug did, except, of course, it was available on a much more wider sort of spectrum.
And who knows? Stay tuned. We may get there yet, but it may not.
In other words, the reality that was in those novels or books is not going to be pushed into the future of this reality is what I wanted to impart.
But but slices or profiles of certain subjects in those books can be can be seen. Right.
Yeah, because what's coming is is almost the perfect society on this planet in about a decade or so.
But don't fall for it. I mean, when it when it does come, enjoy it.
But all the promises that are going to be made are going to be false.
That is the grand deception, by the way. And that's I think we've just touched on that previously.
But if you want to go back to dreams and the concept of of discernment, perhaps, which we didn't put in there.
But the reason I put in the list dreams or downloads from grunts up to the high command.
Well, how would you know what's a grunt and how how would you know what's high command?
Wouldn't a malicious grunt want to dress up in a four star general's uniform just to get you to do something he wants you to do?
You see what I mean? Yeah. So you have to be able to discern it.
You discern this directly and indirectly from things that have been memorialized in the past.
For example, in special operations, in the military, in any country, those men that are sent on a mission,
they are given a very high grade crash course on what they're going in all aspects of what they're going to be engaging in.
They just don't drop them in there without any information, do they?
So. Humanity is it does not want to know anything about the reality around them other than what they've already established.
They should know, you know, coming from certain authorities or such.
They don't want to do any research and check up on anything.
But but if you want to know what what the grunts are and what the high command is, go start reading old ancient books, not Aleister Crowley and stuff.
Don't read a book that was written by someone who read a book, who wrote a book about another book that someone read about a book.
And don't read any books about any religion either, because that is a complete waste of time.
Unless you want to look at the history on how that institution was formed for political, economic and social reasons.
Right. Because there's no religion on the planet that does anything at all.
That is in any of the texts that they allegedly subscribe to or know anything about any of the characters that are allegedly memorialized in those texts at all.
At all. Period. That is an absolute. Right.
Sorry, guys, because people who have studied the ancient quote unquote texts that religions are based on are not religious in those in those groups, period.
They don't exist. Cannot happen. No way, no how.
So the interesting part there is.
This is insane. So anyway, well, but it's a continuous contradiction, right?
Because like I said earlier, nothing represents itself as what it actually is, not even the spiritual realm.
And the dreams are very important again, because to go just to bounce around a little, I send the thing pagans and non pagans both regard dreams as important. Why?
Mm hmm. Let's just use the metaphor like with China.
You've never been to China and you know, you've heard of it. You know, it exists to some tangible degree.
Right. You could send a letter and get a letter back. Right. Or something.
You've seen it on television like it makes it real, at least for most of the people. Right.
So either way, when there's a plurality of beings in China, this is how we're discussing the spiritual realm.
So pagans and non pagans both regard dreams as important because a dream, once you understand that it is a communication from a spiritual realm.
I mean, this gives you the other analogy which I wanted to give, which is they've spent what it's called the SETI program, capital S E T I,
where they set up these large antennas to get a message from some. Is there any life in outer space?
Right. The government set up all these big radio antennas allegedly to hear some stray radio signal to prove that there is life in outer space.
Well, if you've ever dreamt you've got proof that there is another society or another group or beings out there that are communicating with you.
Duh. You know how we mentioned we take things for granted, you know.
So, well, this is true. And, you know, speaking as someone who identifies themselves as a pagan,
my understanding of dreams, no matter who's, you know, bizarre sort of interpretation is, you know, is applied to it.
Here's the bottom line. They are literally communications that you are receiving from elsewhere.
Correct.
That is the most simple and clear definition that I have ever taken in from any of that, you know,
alleged spiritual grouping of individuals is that you are being communicated with.
Absolutely. And everyone who's had a dream is. Yeah.
Yeah. And some people will say, OK, well, who is communicating with you?
This is always where the, you know, the arguments come in. Right.
Because there are people that adhere to certain mainstream kind of religious systems.
Which are irrelevant.
Which are irrelevant. He will tell you that all of this is a message from the God on high.
This is as ludicrous. OK.
As someone who tells you that it is merely the messages from all of your dead relatives. OK.
It is just as ludicrous.
But in some degree, it is not because it's allowed for the most high.
See, they follow rules out there, no matter how big and bad or evil they are.
They still have certain limitations to a certain degree.
But see, the highest G.O.D., let's say, also what people fail to realize is that he's the one that sends evil and good.
Right. To say that he's only good sends only good and doesn't do evil.
Well, that's just you just taking away half of the universe.
And if he's all empowering, this is the part that, you know, this is where the rabbit's foot,
the Easter bunny and Santa Claus and all this other stuff you hear about gets the virus.
Pain and pleasure have the same origin. It's that simple.
Yeah. So those origins are fine.
But the thing is, do you know how to navigate it?
And you're never going to give in anything more than you can handle, even if it kills you.
So the point is, can you discern it?
Like when you said, you know, the dreams are simply a communication, right?
Can you discern it?
And if you want it within that category of discernment, there's also can you interpret it?
You see, now you have to be if you're given a dream that you don't understand, it's in code.
Do you have the cipher to break the code?
You see, that's where you know how you know what level you're coming from.
Right. Or it's coming from, I should say.
And the person boots on the ground being able to interpret it.
Do you think we're doing OK describing dreams or do you think we've been obscure so far or obtuse?
Well, you know what? Yes and no.
We've gone back and forth between the two, in my estimation.
OK. Let's draw us back.
Let's draw ourselves back to the most basic that we can and still continue the conversation.
Because all of this could take up hours and hours of discussion and it's not going to accomplish anything.
That's the fun part, because once again, you know, like you said, if you can't interpret it, if you don't have the cipher, you've got a problem.
You know, because the bottom line is, I could tell you the entire secret of the universe and broadcast it to you for the next 24 hours straight and speak it in a plain language.
But if you don't speak English, you're not going to get it.
You know what I'm saying? It's that simple.
You might think you're someone saying something important, but you don't know about what.
How do you apply it?
Right. So that means that you have no clue as to the details.
You may be able to internally understand that something important is being said, that this is significant.
You may begin to identify certain terms.
And in a real sense, I think that's what's happened to every one of these subjects that we've discussed, is that people understand that there may be a level of importance.
There may be a level of understanding that could be gleaned, etc., etc.
But truthfully, it has all been obscured by the interpretation and the opinions of the speaker.
And obscured by the emotional and mindful laziness of humanity.
That too.
Because in order to be able to do this, like the old adage of the TV repairman, everyone watches TV, but not everyone can fix one.
Well, what does it take to be a TV repairman?
You would have to, at some point in your life, amass as much knowledge about TVs, practical and theoretical, as possible.
And experience and apply in experimentation also, and within study, to be able to fix the thing.
Whether it's a car, a TV, or whatever.
And most people are too emotionally and spiritually lazy, mindfully lazy, to research anything.
They want to be told, that's why you have institutionalized everything.
They want to subscribe to something and have it given to them.
So they don't want to research this stuff, or look into it at all.
And when I say at all, I mean at all, by the majority of people who have ever lived on this planet, not just now.
Because right now, people have access to almost anything, if they really choose to.
And the amount of laziness is the problem.
Now, here's the thing.
Even a middle-aged woman in a fur coat, in a $200,000 Mercedes, that Mercedes is a luxury item.
And guess what? It has a spare tire, and it has a wrench and a jack built into it.
And at some point, with her fur coat and her well-manicured nails and her Fiorucci shoes,
she might have to pull over the car, break out the tools, and change that spare tire.
You see?
And she doesn't need to know how to overhaul the upper cylinders, the head of the engine, or even change the oil, any of that.
But certain things that one encounters with, it's going to have to have certain knowledge on how to troubleshoot.
Right?
So is it unreasonable to ask such a person in a luxury, what they call vehicle, to be able to change a tire?
Is that too much to ask for?
Well, see, I don't think so, but at the same time…
But hold on.
They have these featured insurance things now where you just call them, and they show up with a truck, and they do it for you.
And now that's called psychiatrists, churches, temples, mosques, rabbis.
Yeah, we're going to punch them all in the eye once in a while, yes, because they deserve it.
They deserve a good punch in the eye, because they're all lying to you, all of them.
That's some of them.
Why do we say all of them are lying to you?
Because if they're not lying to you, they wouldn't be in that position.
They would quit it.
They would quit that position.
They would deny ever being it.
So all of those people…
Either that, or even if they attempted to do so, they would be destroyed, because nobody wants it.
Nobody, and I do mean not humanity, not the spiritual realm, nobody actually wants this to…
There are absolutes, and people are going to be shocked to find out what they find to be in the realm of opinion to actually be an absolute.
Like no attorneys know anything about any law, period.
Because if they did, they would be ousted by their own colleagues, and no doctors know anything about the body, period.
Because if they did, they wouldn't be called doctors.
This goes in every field.
It doesn't matter if it's religious or technical or anything.
This is the state of humanity.
It's really bad.
We can just show up every Friday and just punch these guys in the nose, all the institutions, two hours every week,
and it needs to be done, and no one's really doing it.
We can give specifics.
If anyone in any of those fields wants to come in and discuss it openly, we'll be glad to do it.
You won't last very long, but we'll be glad to do it.
And you won't last very long, because the very basis of what you're supposed to be doing doesn't exist in the realm that they say that it is.
Right, and as a matter of fact, let me just take this moment to say this.
I will be more than happy, because I'm a lot more accessible, let's just say, through social media and things like that.
And I'll tell you, even if you want to contact me, just get on my Skype list, Charles.Ocelli, and then Ocelli again.
You can contact me on my Skype list.
The reason why I give this out and tell you I'm on Facebook, Twitter, and all these other places,
or you can go to OcelliInTheGreek.com, send an email there.
Either you or me, one of us, has access to that email.
And we both do, actually, jointly.
But the thing is, you can communicate to us, and if you feel as though you are participating in a spiritual religious doctrine
that is what it advertises to be, I'll be more than happy to welcome them as a guest.
They may not feel very welcome on this show after a short amount of time.
But they are welcomed indeed.
I said they wouldn't feel welcome.
It doesn't mean they aren't.
But you are more than welcome to join us as a guest and try and defend the unmitigated, absolutely ridiculous position
that I feel every single one of you occupies.
Which is about 7 billion plus people on this planet.
That's why going back to the retarded alternative media, which are saying,
Oh, there's 7 billion of us.
We're the majority.
They're a minority.
We can change it.
I'm like, no, shut up.
Sit down.
Go drink some cheap beer.
Go surf the net.
Go plant some flowers.
No, please.
The people that are in charge.
Watch some porn and some football and get involved in that.
Or whatever.
Read some tarot cards or talk about how you were some Dean Martin in the past life
or some ridiculous koala bear in the past life or whatever.
The thing is, the people that are running the show, whether you know who they are or not,
secret shadow government, whatever, are there because the universe is in perfect balance.
And if you don't believe that, go out into nature.
Look up at the sky.
Even the chemtrails are in perfect balance with the level of quality of society that is here now.
Yes, mercury in your vaccines is there.
Because whenever they give you any kind of a medicine, they give you a cut sheet.
It's in very fine print.
You're supposed to read all of it.
And telling people that they can't do chemtrails or mercury in vaccines or rat poison in your sweetener is interfering with commerce.
Don't interfere with commerce.
Sorry, guys.
If they want to sell 20,000 tow missiles to al-Qaeda because it makes money, too bad.
Sorry.
It is.
And you're not going to change it.
No one's going to change it until the course of that event runs out.
It's none of your business.
So most of the alternative media just needs to go away.
And we're not saying this because it shouldn't be there.
Because if they have commerce, they can do it.
They could sell little survival kits and all the little stupid things that they sell,
just like everything else that's pretty much stupid in this society at this point.
Let them do it.
And, you know, this is the level of, I mean, look, they don't even know what day it is.
And they're complaining about vaccines and chemtrails and bad GMO.
That's the other thing.
And all this stuff in Fukushima, it's just gotten to the point of ridiculousness right now.
Go on to nature and show me anything that is out of place or not perfect.
Every blade of grass, every cell in your body, everything is in a form of harmony.
If you don't like all of the covert stuff that's been going on with your food, with your air,
with your politics and stuff, you know how you change it?
You go look in the mirror.
Ask yourself, who am I? Where am I? Where am I? And when am I?
And you can't answer any of that.
You're not going to change anything.
Go back to sleep, lay down, and whatever you got to do, just will it out
because everyone has a limited amount of heartbeats.
And just be thankful that someone didn't come in, break in through your door last night
and rip your liver out while you were sleeping.
Because that is the level of violence that the earth is under.
And it's always been under that level of violence.
So now that we've punched the alternative media in the eye also,
I don't think we're going to get too many replays on this because it's just dumb.
And here we are also discussing the C++ of how the mind works with dreams.
So let's maybe just jump back to the dreaming part of it.
And let me just say really quickly that it is indicative of the quality of the people on this planet
what is being visited upon them.
That's what the reality is. It's unfortunate. I don't like it.
I would like to do something about it personally, and that's why I do what I do.
But at the same time, I really do understand what you're saying.
And I can give it to you a different way for those listening who maybe just went,
what the hell did he just say? Here's the deal.
You don't have to defend me. That's fine.
I'm not. I'm not defending you.
I'm agreeing with you, but I'm pulling back a little bit
because I say that I do believe that there is a way to change this.
It is going to change.
Yes, big time.
And the thing is, I really want to see it.
I want to see it happen.
I want to see that nearly perfect society that you're talking about.
I want to see.
Hold on. I'm just reporting on it.
People need to go and do their own study on that.
I'm just giving the hint on it.
But I want to see that concept of utopia that's now beginning to be discussed in a lot of circles.
And I would love to see that. I really would.
Well, but here's the thing.
When it comes and everything seems honky dory, that's when you get ready to run for the hills.
You can have about three years to get away from everyone and anyone
because when the demands are made at that time to put everything back on track,
people are going to be promised that this is how it's going to be for the next thousand years
and they're all going to fall for it.
And only after about a few years, the glitches are going to start showing up
and the high command on the planet, the leaders of the nations,
are going to make very unreasonable requests of their populations to put them back on track
so they can have this thousand-year golden age and everyone's going to buy into it.
That's the point where it will be very easy to prep because everything will be in abundance
and no one is prepping.
Put it this way.
Could you imagine being promised that no one will have – in the alternative as well,
you will never have to prep for any kind of a disaster ever again for the next thousand years.
That's the time when you prep.
It's like the stock market.
All the rookies, they go and buy when the stock market is doing well, when it's high.
Anyone who knows anything about stock when it's high is when you start dumping.
And that's totally unlawful and the only reason you have a stock market
is because you have a prison system, sorry folks, and birth certificates being issued.
If you eliminated the prison system, the bonds, even traffic tickets and birth certificates,
the stock market would be nothing there.
You would open the door and the two crickets that I have here sometimes
would probably go over there and keep company with the crickets in the stock market.
There would be no stock market at all.
We didn't hear from your crickets tonight.
No, they haven't.
They're good little creatures.
The thing about this is all I see in the alternative media again is they're interfering with commerce.
You can't do that, man.
You'll get in trouble because all of your gods, these lower entities that people worship
are commercial gods, by the way.
People sacrifice their children, not just because they wanted to sacrifice their children.
Nobody really wants to do that, but because of the love of prosperity or the love of money
because they were told if they sacrifice their children, they got prosperity.
That's why when you make a birthday cake, you wish for make your wish.
That's why they sit you on a red guy that's glowing red.
Make a wish.
What do you want Santa to bring you?
This is all parodies and gestures of human sacrifice.
Right now, I think on the dark side of the moon, there's a big billboard.
If you're approaching the earth, it says you're approaching earth.
Turn back.
This is your last chance to turn back.
Get away.
If people on this planet were able to get off this planet and have a spiritual eye or spiritual mind
where they can see the rest of the world, if they said they were from planet earth,
let me give you the Latin phrase for that.
In Spanish, they say, oh, pobre si.
It means like, oh, I feel sorry for you that you came from that place right now in this time period.
It's still a beautiful place, but spiritually, it's a cesspool.
It has been for a very, very, very long time.
There are no Anunnaki or whatever aliens that made you and came here to enslave you,
to mine the gold and all that other retarded crap you hear.
If you want to believe that, go for it.
But this is insane at this point.
So I think that tying this back to the dreamland stuff in this rant is quite appropriate
because everything's in the imagination, you see.
So if you are living in an imagination, which is correct, by the way,
no imagination lights out your dreaming.
This is when you get your cosmic input, but you have to learn how to discern it.
Who is it coming from?
And unfortunately, just like being a TV repairman,
if you haven't done your homework and your study, you don't know why it doesn't work.
So you're going to have to study.
And I'm not going to tell you where to go and where to study.
That should be obvious by now.
But at the same point, without study, you're going to fall for the deceptions,
including with the dreams and what they are.
Well, absolutely.
And listen, we're beginning to run out of time on this presentation.
Believe it or not, we've only got a few minutes left.
And, you know, I want to thank everybody who decided to tune into this,
whether you caught it live on American Freedom Radio
or you caught it elsewhere downstream or went to the archives.
I do appreciate you giving us the time to impart these rather simple ideas,
realities and the reports that the Greek gives during these shows.
So we are closing out what we would call episode 14.
And it's been eventful.
I'll give it that because I didn't expect to go into some of the areas we went into.
And who knows, we might have to discuss dreams just a little more in another episode.
Well, one can expect the unexpected, but you can't foresee the unforeseeable.
Well, the unforeseeable, by definition, is unforeseeable.
So there you go.
What cannot be expected?
Well, expectations are a whole different.
Right. Yeah.
And when you yeah, there was a skit, a comedy skit once,
Lowered Expectations.
I don't know if you remember that.
Oh, yes.
Comedy skit, I think it was a late night TV show that did that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Don't that that goes away here.
Expect a lot because you're going to get a lot here.
And it's it's it's it's very simple.
Just tell it like it is and give a good report.
Absolutely.
And by the way, just as a quick aside, as a personal aside,
kudos on the use of the word retarded three times.
I really appreciate that.
You know what?
It is an ethical word in my estimation.
It's one of those things that that I think needs to be used a little more often,
not less, because we are discouraged.
But then again, the truth is, when you use anything that that appears to be efficient and proper,
you're often discouraged.
So the cosmic censorship continues.
And we will join you again next week on what they call a Friars Day.
Excuse me, Friday.
Once again, the Greek.
Anything you want to say in closing till the next time?
Thank you, folks.
Absolutely. Take care.
I'm telling you, you've got to support American Freedom Radio
because this government is getting out of hand.
Wall Street won't run my money.
The CIA are cutting into my drug running and my gun running.
Big pharma psychotropic drugs are making my customers commit suicide
before my hitmen can even lock them.
And then they get depressed and get prescribed psychotropic drugs and commit suicide, too.
They're trying to become the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected.
I cannot pay taxes, and if I can't find the money, the IRS are going to take my tops.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine, and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction, and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs,
and that's to support American Freedom Radio.
Capisce? So what are you going to do?
You're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion,
and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years,
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder
is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367,
and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
HempUSA.org
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
What is the big deal about swearing to God in the first place?
Why does swearing to God mean you're going to tell the truth?
Wouldn't affect me.
If they said to me, you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth, so help me God,
I'd say, yeah.
I'll tell you about as much truth as the people who wrote the Bible.
How do you like that?
Swearing to God is kid stuff.
Swearing to God doesn't mean anything.
Swearing on the Bible doesn't mean anything.
You know why? Because Bible or no Bible, God or no God,
if it suits their purposes, people are going to lie in court.
The police do it all the time.
All the time.
Yes, they do.
It's part of their job to protect, to serve, and to commit perjury
whenever it supports the state's case.
Swearing on the Bible is just one more way of controlling people and keeping them in line,
and it's one more thing that holds us back as a species.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.