American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
With no deficiency in protein or nicotine at the moment, it is episode 17 of Ocelli and the Greek, broadcast live, originally,
on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
So, I am one half of the sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
I am Chuck Cochelli, and with me, as always, on Friars Day, as it's called, is the Greek.
How are you doing tonight, sir?
Hey, man, doing all right. Let's do it again.
Absolutely. Now, just for, you know, just for the sake of mentioning it.
According to the, yeah, well, first, first, let's do this.
According to the Pope's work schedule, it would be the 29th day of the first month of the year 2016, allegedly.
And according to the wind-up toy, it's just after 8 p.m. Eastern, 5 p.m. Pacific time.
According to that wind-up toy, or the digital representation thereof, that you may know as a clock.
However, Greek, lawfully, it's the end of the first week of the 12th month.
Ah.
Yeah. And so, yeah, which is lawfully meaning that you don't have to rely on what someone else is telling you to do,
or think, or say, or whatever.
Where someone else, in this case, would be yourself, right?
Let's say you're not bipolar, and you just go outside, and you reckon events with precision using astronomics,
which would be your sun and the moon, and the Earth, of course, is in the middle of that.
Yeah. And this is how it's been always done, always been done, and this is how it will be.
But fortunately, or unfortunately, right now, most people don't have any idea about it,
because it's a completely unlawful society.
So, anyway, yeah, that wrapped up to pretty much the reason why we come here,
and try to give reports on that there is something else.
Right, right. And that's why I start out the show with that observation every time now,
because it is certainly worthwhile, and gives people an idea of possibly how to reckon things in a lawful fashion.
And, gee, I think actually presents the contrast between what is, and what should be, and, in fact, what will be, etc., etc.
So, more on that at a later date, I assure you.
Or, yeah, no pun intended.
And you know that there's a difference, there's a big difference between the date and a day.
A date has been restricted to a commercial legal term for notations, let's say, on bookkeeping per given system.
You know, you might have the, let's say, the current, let's say we'd call it still the Greek system.
There's a lot of people out there still pontificating that it's a Roman system.
You know, if you look closely, you know, it makes...
Well, to me, the Greek system gave birth to, in a sense, the Roman system anyway,
or you could say that the Roman system is merely an adaptation of the Greek system.
So, truthfully, down to its essence, the difference is what?
Well, the difference is the Greek system after, let's evoke the character Alexander the Great,
divided into four particular groups, East-West predominantly,
and then you had the East-West in micro-Asia Europe,
and the East-West in what's called North Africa in the Middle East was also divided that way into four regions.
And not to forget, also, there is leftover Babylonian influence in the South American system.
You know, what current Western civilization is familiar with is the Mayan exam paradigm.
So, all of these little systems have their own way of dating things, but it has nothing to do with the day.
What has to do with the day is astronomical observance,
where the sun being at high noon is the beginning of the day, and the moon being the beginning of the month.
Now, why is it important to sort of understand that?
It's because plants, flowers, fish, birds, the earth itself, seasons and all that go on that system.
So, if you have any interest in growing anything, or animal husbandry, or what's called nature at large,
you would behoove anyone to understand how lawful timekeeping works, and that's all it is.
It just shows you the hypocrisy.
I want to bring up something that's really, I find distasteful in society, if I may.
Have you ever heard of organic food?
You know, like, this is organic, you know, so you pay more or it's better for you.
Well, yet another bastardized term, really, because I see the word organic being applied to many things,
and they don't seem to share common elements in a lot of cases, and I wonder a lot about what that term really means.
Right, well, from a lawful perspective, it shows there is a severe illness in society, deranged.
Why would you allow, okay, now I'll say this really slowly,
why would you allow a certain group of agricultural producers to produce food that is harmful,
let's say, or tainted, right, and then allow another group to produce food that isn't?
It's totally sick, and everyone's missing the point.
There shouldn't be any food labeled organic.
That shows that you are accepting a group of, let's say, producers of agricultural food products,
because there are meats as well and fish and other things like that, that is tainted,
and then you have a choice to get tainted food or untainted food.
How sick is that?
You know, it's just, so what else is going to be accepted, right?
Okay, so that shows you that anything could be accepted in an unlawful society as long as you give people a choice.
How many times have you heard that, you have the choice, right?
And you do.
Well, an alleged choice, really.
I mean, you and I had a conversation off the air, and I'll reference this because it personally, you know,
sort of pertained to me, but the fact is I started talking to you about what was available in the local grocery stores, right?
And I started describing it, and then I said, wait a minute.
I can save us a lot of time and tell you that since I live in a certain neighborhood,
you can already extrapolate from that what is actually available in those grocery stores.
The alleged choices on the shelves and the racks and et cetera are already limited,
and I can tell you that they've done it in an ethnic fashion because I live in a primarily black area,
which means that automatically, you know, certain things are in abundance and certain other things are absent,
and, well, a wide range of things are actually very difficult to find in an area that has sort of been deemed
to require certain things by those distributing food, right?
I mean, this is a true story.
This is a conversation we had.
Yeah, yeah.
But the thing is there's something about culture.
You know, every country sort of has a group, an area where it caters to a particular cultural group where that has their own traditions, right?
Like you love the Chinatowns and the little Italys and this and that and the other, right?
Little Japan, little Brazil.
Yeah, so that is, yeah, I deem that to be fair to a certain degree.
You know what I mean?
For instance, you may find a greater variety of fish in primarily Asian communities because there's a lot of that in the diet, right?
So you'll also find a variety of rice that you might not find in, you know, and that does sound a little racist, I guess, on my part,
but I'm not going to worry about that.
But that's the truth.
This is one of the staples of just about any Asian diet that I have observed is rice.
And I do mean Asian by even Indians use a lot of rice.
And by Indian, I do mean people from India, you know, to clarify.
But, I mean, people are aware that Chinese food and stuff like that, there's loads and loads of rice involved.
That association, by the way, is fairly recent, 100, 150 years.
Prior to that, throughout Asia, the common staple was millet and barley because rice was a luxury item.
Think about how much easier it is to grow millet and barley versus rice, especially on that type of terrain.
Rice was always considered a luxury item hundreds of years ago in that part of the world.
It was through the Industrial Revolution and using certain Western techniques that allowed them to cultivate rice in abundance as we find it today.
Oh, right. I'm talking about, obviously, current observations.
I mean, truthfully, when one looks at limitations or things that are associated with ethnic foods, in a lot of cases, it's gone quite askew.
You know, people, a lot of them think that, for instance, here's a good example.
In Italy, they must eat tons of pizza.
They really don't.
And specifically, when you're talking about Sicilians, you know, their diet is very much loaded with fish.
Roasted meats, fish, soupy stews, yeah.
Yeah, well, that's the thing.
You see, you look at the culture and you'll notice that it's a lot of local influence.
You know, what can be garnered agriculturally, animal husbandry and all that.
Just as a comment, you know, in the American culture, you know, you've got, let's say the nickname is Breadbasket of the World and all that,
and hot dogs and hamburgers, maybe apple pie.
It shows you a real poor use of the ethos or the culture or the tradition or what can be garnered from the land.
You know, it shows you there's a certain mindset that is very poor.
Not broke.
There's a difference between broke and poor.
It's just very poor, low quality.
I mean, you know, that's why personally I always preferred being near the East Coast or the West Coast
because you had a huge influence of European and Asian.
And before coming out to the Southwest, you know, especially I had friends that were Italian.
They were like, man, you're not going to be able to get any good food.
They put ketchup on spaghetti out there, you know.
And so I was like, yeah, well, okay, you know, fortunately I can cook well.
But, yeah, unfortunately, from a cultural perspective, American culture is some of the poorest in the world when you look at the food.
And, you know, good food and good drink breed good character.
So if you understand the reputation that Americans have, even before the political scenarios that have been unfolding in the past several decades,
Americans were always frowned on because there's a certain character that they were considered to have by Europeans and Asians.
And I believe that if you want to, quote, unquote, judge the character, you look at the food traditions, right?
Hamburgers and hot dogs are a very poor staple.
Another one would be the English.
Where have you gone and seen an English restaurant?
You've got Indian, Chinese, Mexican, Italian, Greek.
Where do you see a chain or a franchise or even anyone saying, I'm going to open a British restaurant, not a pub?
You know, you'll have British type pubs, right?
Where do you see that?
Never, right?
No, you don't.
And the reason is, I mean, quite honestly, I mean, I traveled to Europe when I was much younger.
And truthfully, I don't even know how the English are still alive based on the stuff they eat.
It's awful.
And you look at the character as well.
It comes through.
It's very dry humor.
You know, they have their own remarks.
But, you know, the rest of the world around them makes about them.
And it's very interesting.
We're bringing this up.
This is trying to be objective again, that the quality of the individual or individuals or population can be easily judged by looking at their tradition and culture regarding food.
You know, how rich or how well the preparations, you know, how the land is used to produce various things and then transferred to the table.
So, yeah, this is an interesting subject on its own because it's not considered.
People think a country is defined by its political stance.
It should be defined by the way the people actually live.
And other than, you know, food, clothing and shelter, food is the easiest thing to observe as the cultural aspect of a society.
Well, right.
And I mean, hey, the old adage proves to be a little more true than one might imagine.
You are actually what you eat in a lot of cases.
And, hey, you know, I know that we went through physically, you know, the concept on this show.
We talked about the container and we talked about, you know, the process by which the body takes in food.
But in a spiritual sense, I would say that in a lot of cases, you you are what you eat.
So there you go.
Or you are what you ate.
Yeah.
There you go.
That's even better.
And, you know, with the food also, we've briefly touched on it.
There's lawful and unlawful ways of eating.
Like if you work, get a job in a pet food or a pet shop, you know, and they tell you it's five bucks an hour all you could steal.
And you feed the dog food to the dogs, the bird food to the birds and the fish food to the fish.
But, you know, you know, you want to do whatever you want to do.
So you give the bird food to the fish and the fish food to the dog and the dog food to the fish.
Now, all those animals are going to eat that.
But is it fit and proper?
No, it's not.
Right.
Exactly.
I was just I was just slightly distracted because I heard my son singing in the other room again.
He seems to do this when we're on the air, you and me.
And I'm not sure what is going on.
Maybe.
Perhaps.
Sorry.
But, no, it is correct.
And I say that that you know what?
There's a whole lot more to that.
And it would be an interesting subject in and of itself.
But I think it leads us straight into what we discussed yesterday and right before we went on air,
because we had one of those rare in-between show conversations, you and I, as I referenced earlier.
But here's an amazing thought.
And it falls right in line, obviously, with what we've talked about several times.
OK.
But and and by the way, Lulu in the chat room who said your food should be your medicine, too.
You know what?
I have no objection to that kind of line of thinking.
What do you think about that, Greg?
No, that leads into doing a cooking show.
But that's a worthwhile thing.
I think just simple.
You know, I mean, it could even be an episode on how to prepare food, which is novel.
You know, that might be that might be something to do in the future.
Who knows? Maybe episode 18 will be a cooking show.
All right. But but it leads directly into what it was we were talking about.
And and I find this I find this concept anyway, because it's only a concept we didn't actually have the discussion.
But the concept is extremely valid.
And and that is that truthfully, nobody researches what they worship.
OK. Now, that sounds like a pretty interesting blanket statement and worship the word worship.
I mean, first of all, let's talk about what it means to worship something anyway,
because I think people might be a little bit confused about what that actually means.
Well, it's it's an old etymologically. Let's see.
I just brought it up as you asked.
It's a condition of being worthy, dignity, glory, distinction, honor, renown, worthy.
Mm hmm. So like reverence paid to a supernatural or divine being, for example, first recorded in 1300.
The original sense is preserved in the worship full or honorable.
So things that people find to be honorable.
You know, here's here's just a little thing about like when you're writing legal legal documents or you're being trained as an attorney to do so.
There have been some retired judges writing, you know, handbooks on how to be, you know, do successful legal writing.
And one of the retired judges says, stop calling the court honorable and the judges honorable,
because if they're already honorable, why do you have to say it? Right.
So, you know, and that's a whole other thing there.
But I always find that interesting, too, because you notice that mayors of towns are often called the honorable so and so as well.
Yeah. You know, it's a ranking system typically because the mayor sits in the there's a concept of ruling the thousands,
ruling the hundreds and ruling the tens like the tens would be the county.
The hundreds would be the state and ruling the thousands would be the country.
Right. In groups like that. So typically it's when you call someone honorable, it shows a ranking.
Usually it's between the tens or hundreds.
And then when you go into the thousands or the ruler of a country or a large domain, they're usually your eminence.
These are things that are no longer being used, but they still can be.
Yeah. Yeah, absolutely. But I want to throw one more thing in about the mayor.
Do you ever see where they hand someone the keys to the city, you know, and they have this.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Sometimes they give him a symbolic key.
I've actually seen him hand him a little ring of keys before, but usually there's a giant key, though.
Yeah. Yeah. The giant key is accurate. If anyone does any research, it's kind of hard to find on the Internet.
But if you do some research in the ancient days when you had walled cities, fortified cities,
they had these things called gates and these gates were very large and they had their large and very heavy.
And in order for them to be durable, they had complex mechanisms to lock them in complex hardware to hold them up.
They were they literally weighed tens of tons and they did have very large keys that look very much like the.
Would you say almost in parity? Yes.
They don't make a large key and spray painted gold for the camera.
It's something that goes back. And should we say the bad word biblical times?
That's why there's there's two things I want to bring up about that.
Just as a side note, one thing is there's a couple of verses that people don't know.
He'll carry the keys of the authority on his shoulder and they try to look.
What does that mean? It means this or that. Right.
No, actually, if you are ruling a place and you holding the key, it's so big you do have to carry it on your shoulder.
Right. And the other thing, have you ever heard of the saying it is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle than a rich man to enter the kingdom of heaven, let's say.
And I've heard that a lot of people and no one seems to know what that means.
And when I say no one, I mean, there's just only a handful of people out there, but it's very simple.
When you approach the gates of a city and you need to let if they wanted to inspect you or they weren't sure they opened another little door was called the eye of the needle.
And the door was big enough to just let an animal go through a donkey or a camel without its portage.
So you had to unload everything and put it down on the ground and send the animal through.
So it was very risky because if they didn't like you, they took the animal.
Now you were left without an animal or you would have to put all the bags through.
And the animal stays outside or, you know, it's a very narrow gate.
Right. And so what's similar like you see today at customs where they kind of narrow everything down, you know, or going through a turnstile, let's say.
So these things exist today as well, but the connections have not been made.
So, well, right. Entrance is sort of funneled into into an entrance into anything of significance is funneled into a particular sort of doorway.
Literally, you know, what what that's saying, by the way, just in closing, interrupt.
I stepped on you there for a minute.
It's easier for a camel to go through the eye of the needle because you have to be very trusting to do that,
because when you once you unload the animal or all of your belongings and you go through a narrow gate,
you can't be too attached to that because there's a good chance you might lose it.
That's all it means. It's very practical.
And these things I think we once said we might do a show on cliches or certain things or verses that people use,
like the kingdom of heaven is in you or this and that and all these old things.
You know what came first, the chicken or the egg.
And all these things are so simple and people use them as paradoxes and they try to put their own meanings to these things.
And it's often ridiculous to those who do a little bit of study.
And what I mean about study, it's not listening necessarily to contemporary stuff.
Give an example without naming individuals.
There's a lot of movement about all things ancient and the stuff you hear is just absurd and ridiculous.
And some people have been doing it for a very long time and have created a tremendous following.
And I find it to be pretty bewildering to see how so many people can be distracted with nonsense about what old things mean,
whether it's religious or science or cliche.
So I think that's why we get together here to give a report on that.
Well, we certainly do.
And that's why I thought it was extremely valid to first begin with the concept of worship so we know what it is we're talking about.
And to take a look at the etymology, it does put it in a perspective that one can sort of begin to wrap their mind around.
Now, as far as how really extensive or how rich that definition is, you know, that's precisely for you to consider out there.
And I do mean you as a listener to consider out there because, after all, no matter what we say, it's very difficult to know what you just heard.
But I do appreciate it.
And it is extremely relevant, all of this.
But the opening statement, let's not lose it, is that nobody researches.
Nobody really knows what it is they're worshiping.
And worship comes in many forms.
I mean, we talked about something being honorable or worthy.
Right. I mean, this is this seems very subjective.
Yeah. And they use the term sacred and all these other things.
And like with certain American groups, they use they think some document is a living, breathing document.
I mean, you're talking about ridiculous stuff.
And the note, I guess, is people will never find out anything about things that they say they worship.
And, you know, I did a short little short list.
And, you know, the four things that I put on there that are that are major, one of them is religion.
People that are quote unquote religious know nothing about what they're doing at all.
That's why I've said in private and publicly, if you find someone who is religious, any religion, when I say religious now,
let's just say the main world's religions, those people are either ignorant or evil.
Think about that. And it's a Greek. That's a really strong statement.
Well, because if you run into any kind of religious believer of any of the major faiths and you say, like, why are you doing that?
You know, the leaders will even tell you that's tradition. We don't go by those books. Right.
So the followers are just totally ignorant. And those that do know that it's totally false go along with it because they're evil.
So when you meet someone who is of a particular faith, the immediate judgment call on that individual.
This is harsh, by the way. Most people can't handle this. And they'll think I'm bizarre or obtuse for saying it.
You're either evil or ignorant. There is no middle ground.
You know, the middle ground is if you're evil and you repent, you say, I'm not going to fleece these dumb people anymore.
There might be a little break in there of about a week or two where you got to figure out what you're going to do with your life now.
Right. Yeah. So there's a little pause there.
Or if you're ignorant and you start researching the religion you allegedly subscribe to and find out that that religion doesn't do anything that it's supposed to subscribe to.
There's a little area there about maybe a week or two or a month or a year where you start researching it and go to the other people that you used to congregate with
and say, hey, you know, the stuff they're telling us and the stuff that we're doing is 100 percent contrary to what we're supposed to be doing.
According to this, what's been memorialized. So there's a little there's a little breaks when I say you're either evil or ignorant.
If you subscribe to these religions on the planet, this is, you know, the major ones.
You know, you have Islam, Christianity and was a Judaism.
And then you have the Buddhism and then you've got the Hindi, which is basically an area of the world.
All these things change and they're contrary to what is memorialized that the believers should do or the followers should do.
So when I say you're either evil or ignorant, there's probably during what's called an axial period, a big change in that people going away.
Let's say from the Catholic Church, you've heard that there's a lot of articles written about that.
We've got to get the people to come back, you know, and then you hear about, you know, all the problems religions are having.
And so those are the groups that are moving out of that stupidity.
And the books or let's see, let's not even use the term book.
The information that's been memorialized through the ages that these religions allegedly subscribe to,
which none of them do, are not observed at all.
And there's what you'll find is they all have very common elements.
So there shouldn't be any discrepancy between what the followers are doing.
But we brought up there are several other items.
One of them is the religion, which is the main one.
The other one is the atom or nuclear energy or anything nuclear or atomic.
How many times have you heard those terms used almost to mean the same thing?
And the other one is money.
And finally, because this is the states or America, it's the Constitution.
And I think we even did a show on the Constitution.
But all of these things.
We surely did.
Yeah, we sure did.
I think I called it, you know, I usually give slightly snarky titles to these.
But I think we actually called it.
What was it?
Holy.
Holy Constitution.
Greek man or something.
Yeah.
Holy Constitution.
Greek man.
Yeah.
Kind of mocking the old, you know, Robin, the sidekick to Batman, you know.
Franchise.
Yeah.
And but there was some serious information contained in there that that is not being
considered by anyone else.
You don't hear it anywhere else.
That's for sure.
No.
I don't know if it's the bad food in the water or it's aspects of fear or the education system.
Right.
Or a combination thereof.
Yeah.
And, you know, fear and love, by the way, is something we can discuss on how action and
feeling and love and all that as well ties in with this.
But the idea here that making a statement like people really don't research or want to know
anything about things that they have idolized, right, or worship or consider sacred, they
might eventually come across something like, for example, in many religions, they'll extract
a verse out of context and throw it at someone.
You know, this is you should be doing this.
And it's completely out of context.
And they don't know what what the context, what context it should be.
That piece of information should be held in.
And it's used for their advantage, let's say.
Right.
Whether it's a debate, an argument, instruction or political reason or whatever.
It's actually used as leverage.
And in most cases, not only is the context missed, but the but the actual wording is
out of place, too, when you when one examines it, even though they're quoting from.
So, well, that's the problem, obviously, the source they're quoting from is the problem
is not.
Yeah, it's not a good source, of course, from any perspective.
But and then you have you see the idea of here.
I'm ready to say it again.
And we bring this up very often.
Cosmic censorship.
This is a time period of just here.
Let's give a little bit more on the cosmic censorship.
It's a chance for men to do things his way.
Right.
Just like a child, when you give him enough toys and enough leeway, let him do, you know,
give him a sandbox or red fire truck or whatever and let them play.
And then eventually it comes down to serious business.
You've got to wash your hands, eat, go to sleep, you know, all that stuff, you know,
that you have to do.
Yeah.
So this this has been millennia of mankind applying his idiocy on his own without instruction,
cosmic instruction.
And one of the things what I mean by cosmic instruction is how do we start off the show,
the day and the date?
You see, it is a big difference between the two, one being cosmic and the other one being
just do what you're told as a subject.
But again, the religions.
Now, this is part of the censorship, by the way, in the near future, when this seven year
period ends around what you call, let's say people call the twenty eighteen roughly the
fall of twenty seventeen, the spring of twenty eighteen and twenty eighteen will be a time
period when things will start changing again.
We will get out of this almost decade, a little less than a decade of just taking up time in
a waiting room, confusion and just poking and prodding of the psyche.
There's going to be a time of more like nuts and bolts reality coming around the corner
here and people will start to look at these religions a little more objectively, not completely,
but more objectively.
And right now I could clearly say clearly and unequivocally and like we were saying
before, this is a fact and not only a fact, it's the truth, because, you know, a fact
doesn't necessarily have to be the truth, by the way, because wearing a pink baseball
cap in New York City keeps the elephants away as a fact because you don't see any elephants
around, do you?
But the truth of the matter is a little more deeper than that.
So from a superficial point of view and factual to a truthful point of view, there is actually
there has not been any serious discourse, discussion or enlightenment or information
regarding any religions right now.
And, you know, you hear all of these things.
You hear about the behavior.
Yeah, like, you know, Catholic priests raping children, you know, because that's part of
the religion, not the Catholic religion.
Yes, the Catholic religion in a sense, because Catholic means universal.
Like they've syncretized everything together.
You know, they've taken a little bit of this, a little bit of that.
And one of the orders in that higher ranking system adheres to a particular entity, which
is also one of the entities adhered to by Scientology, by the way.
And part of it, the way you satisfy this entity when he's evoked by name is to inflict pain
on a child via anal sex.
And wait till people find this out.
Right now, you just read about thousands of priests doing it.
Right. And there's also old literature that goes back hundreds of years describing them as pedophiles.
You know, this people think this is just some private personal desire.
This is part of the religion, folks.
And what we're talking about now is just a little precursor of things just to a heads up.
There's no sense in giving information about religions, because what did we just say?
There is no information out there that's been given.
There's this ridiculous science of astro theology.
It's just absurd.
There's a lot of the revival of these real degenerate people in the 19th century that wrote books on occult mysticism.
Not only were they degenerate, but their writings are degenerate and they're brought forward to this date.
There's a lot of stuff regarding the political movements that were inspired by these religions.
Right. Which is rubbish as well.
So you have all this junk that are filtrating through people right now.
And they're loaded or dummy loaded, but it's more than a dummy load.
It's just junk. Everything. Not some of it. All of it.
Because really, Chuck, if there was anyone at all, at all, even though how minor they were,
saying anything that was worth listening to, really, you know what?
We wouldn't be doing this show. I would just plug them.
I'd say, hey, go privately or publicly.
Go to this website. You've got to read this.
This is a good place to get a general idea of what's happening on this planet with society right now.
And I think you and I discussed this is why we need to come together and do this show.
So there's this junk that's out there and people will die for it.
And people go head over heels and they don't research it.
So we're looking at, in terms of religion, all of the religions, bar none,
the followers and leaders know nothing about what the religion really should be about.
Because if you look at the text, you'll find out all of the characters held within are still secret.
Right. So when you hear someone speaking about Muhammad or Buddha or the Christ or Abraham or this or that,
all that stuff is is not what they're discussing is what they've gotten out of some occult mysticism,
rubbish from 100 years ago or Hollywood or from the place of worship.
But it's not in the text in context. Right.
Because the thing about religion and the beauty of that, those are predatory.
You know, if you're a predator and a psychopath or sociopath and you want to take advantage of people overtly,
you know, overtly, you know, you become a religious.
You start a church or a temple or whatever, any religion to do that.
And it's quite simple because all you have to do is gather a couple of things that people might gravitate to,
which is all rubbish. And and you apply it.
And and you're and you're touching the nerve, which is the category of something that they worship.
You know, they're not going to research it. You see, just like with to go to the next thing here is money.
Right. You know, well, yeah, there you go, because once again,
you have something that is represented as a variety of different mechanisms.
But but the the basis for which it is created, et cetera, et cetera,
actually has a whole lot more of a logical and simple explanation when one really boils it down,
because I've always understood it as a marker to represent something.
OK, that's fair. It is the representation of something else.
It is not something in and of itself. OK, that's fine.
The paper money, of course, I'm talking about this type of thing that we circulate nowadays as money in quotes.
Right. I've always understood that part of it. But here's the thing.
People begin to argue about what it actually represents. Does it represent, you know, the amount of people?
Is it something that is simply created out of thin air that has nothing to do with anything and therefore is a complete fiction?
I'm sure you're familiar with all these lines of thinking. What it comes down to in reality is.
Well, what it comes down to is there is a group.
There are groups of people that know that I can be say I could be a predator and I can just attach to a certain concept
and have everyone do things for me so I don't have to do anything and get very rich at it.
And just like the religious aspect, all of the believers don't know anything about it.
They go along with it. And I'm not, again, discussing those that are on their way out of it because they're finding out what it's about.
Money is the same way. You can even discuss it with people who are supposedly educated.
I don't care as long as I can go to the store and get what I want. Right.
Yeah, that's that's basically the answer. And those that are crafty enough.
Let's use that term because it is a craft to take advantage of that psyche,
because the religions of the world take advantage of the worst aspects of humanity. Right.
Well, that that I absolutely I mean, there's no way to argue with that.
I see it as a very predatory thing. The institutions always taking advantage of, well, everything, really.
I mean, the thinking what matters is the money does as well. Now, here's the thing.
You know, I've said again, we've we've discussed money and I wish I could say, hey, go to this guy's website.
This guy is an economist or an author on economic papers or reports. Right.
Some of them do it daily. Some of them do it weekly. Some do it monthly.
It's all rubbish. These guys are morons. That's some of them. All of them.
What's a lot. Many of them have radio shows, alternative and mainstream. Right.
And what not what they never do is differentiate between lawful and legal money,
private credit versus public money and what money is.
Ask any economic expert moron because they're all morons, not some of them, all of them.
And the ones that are not morons leave the field because there's no audience.
If you start getting into economy, the study of it and and speaking accurately and delineating what it is, you have no audience.
You'll have 20,000 subscribers and it'll be down to like five in a week if you start telling people reality of it.
Right. So what they do, just like the religious orders, they don't want to know.
And they just keep going with their rubbish.
It's just rubbish from the point of view that anyone factually and truthfully can access the laws of a nation's money system in their codes or their constitutions.
Right. It's fair enough. Like in America, it's Title 12 of the U.S.
Code or in the Constitution that has various things regarding lawful money.
Right. But no one seems to care because people just the worst aspect of humanity is as long as I get what I want, I don't care.
You see. So they don't research it and then they complain about when they don't have it or when they have to pay it in the form of taxes or it's lost or whatever.
So they have no concept or they work for it and they're not getting enough of it, you know.
So the study of money itself and let's just lay it one more time.
Money is just portable land because in a perfect society, which is not utopia, utopia is the Greek word for prefix EU or you means health and topos meaning good place.
But the EU by itself means nowhere. So utopia literally means nowhere, just like Nirvana.
Someone once texted me. Hope you find your Nirvana. I mean, like I piss on Nirvana. I don't want to go there.
You kidding? No man's land. Nirvana in the in the common vernacular now is completely perverse compared to its original notion.
And that's but isn't everything sort of like this? Those words literally mean no man's land.
And the last place you want to be is a no man's land. So. So in a well-organized society, you garner everything you need from the earth.
And when you're going to travel, you can't bring everything with you. So you need a representation of it.
Well, see, that's where we get into, like I said, I know that it's the representation of something other than.
Yeah, it's it's the representation of something that actually does have substance.
Now, you know, some people say it's a representation of labor. It's a representation.
But in truth, it's exchanged for that purpose. But what does it actually represent in and of itself?
Well, what is it? It's a lawful representation, because what is lawful?
We were we've discussed prior. You get your law from your deity.
Not and here's the the other thing is when you hear anyone mention God, just God like that,
they're a moron because there's no such thing as a singular God in existence as such.
It is a society and they have a hierarchy. So, you know, in God, we trust.
You see that on the Federal Reserve note that is either written by morons for morons or written by some smart people want to play a joke on morons and people let it go.
And if you let something go for so long, like in many traditions, it becomes the fact or tradition or culture of a society.
You know, look at the religions, they talk about God, even in when someone mentions that to me.
So which one are you talking about? It shows you how ignorant people are and, you know, tying in the money again.
I don't care as long as I get what I want with it. Well, wow.
You know, where's your ethics in your moral standing in that kind of rhetoric? Very, very low.
Right. Well, low quality at any rate. There is a standing. There is a standing.
It's just not of the highest caliber or quality, I would say.
And here's the thing. Also, this is a credit based economy.
There's something called taxation. And this is what people don't know.
That's a maximum of law goes back thousands of years, meaning it's a maximum.
Everyone knows this. You don't have to write it down.
Is that the sovereigns of the worlds or the kings or the governments only tax foreigners?
This is a maximum of law, period. So if you believe in a country and you're paying taxes,
your government considers you to be a foreigner. Now, that's interesting.
And we don't need to expand on that. And this is an archive.
Anyone can figure that out if they listen to it about 150 times.
The other thing is that how are you going to pay for anything in a credit based economy?
So what's going on with taxation is you are being you're what you're using as conversion.
Private credit is being taken away from you to limit the supply. That's all it is.
Taxes don't pay for anything. Banks don't transfer funds.
You know, checks are not money. What you call cash is not cash.
It has a cash value of two cents. It doesn't matter if it has a one or ten or a hundred on it.
It's two and a half cents cash value in cotton because people think it's paper money.
It's mostly cotton fiber. Right. Right.
Even if it's a even if it's a coupon for dog food, it's got what even on plain paper.
What is it? But here's the thing, the center, whatever in value.
Yeah, it does. Yeah, they do list that. But here's the interesting thing about the shopping coupons.
They're redeemable where the money is not. Here's the other thing.
You know, people think banks actually transfer money.
We've never discussed this on air, but banks don't transfer money.
They never do. They just when the transaction is done, one bank tells the other bank,
we just did a transaction and you got to take the money out of the account that this guy has his name on or gal.
Let them know that. So they keep the illusion going that something's been transferred, but nothing has ever transferred.
I mean, you know, you could write a million dollar check, you know, on a napkin, take it to a bank.
They'll they'll take it and use the million. They won't give it to you because if they do it for you,
they have to do it for everyone is what they say. You see.
Well, you know, this is the point at which I've always got to stop and say something.
Right. You see these, you know, what do you call those trucks now?
There are trucks that go around to different banks and distribute the notes that actually seem to transfer.
They seem to transfer physically what is called cash. Right.
So what's going on there? Well, the cash, you know, here's the interesting part in the vault.
They keep all the papers that have people's signatures, promissory notes, certificates, things like that.
What they call cash is kept in the hallway on the way to the bathroom with ink pellets in case someone takes out too much at one time.
You know, the ink explodes. Right. Right. Yeah.
So it's a matter of perceived shortage, because if you look at a note, a note is just a promise to pay.
Right. But no one cares because the merchants see everyone's trying to fault the Federal Reserve.
It's not the Federal Reserve is just a middleman. Like, how are you going to fault a used car dealer?
Let's just say we need to edit all the used car dealers. They screwed up the country.
What are you talking about, man? You know, these guys are just merchants.
It's like how many times have you heard people buying and selling stocks?
The stockbroker doesn't care if the stock goes up or down because he gets a percentage for the transaction.
No one knows anything to the Federal Reserve. We're talking a society of morons,
because how many places can you go on the Internet and find commentators writing books and websites about the ills of the Federal Reserve?
What are you talking about, man? They're just middlemen. They couldn't care less if you're doing well or not.
You just move money. They get a percentage whether you lose it or not.
And this is this is we're talking a bizarre, bizarro world in a way here.
But no one wants to research this. Henry Ford said if people found out how the money system works,
they'd be blood in the streets in a day. Right. And a good correction, by the way, in the chat room,
the anonymous person that said Brinks Armored Cars, that that was the company I was looking for.
All of a sudden, I found myself lost between Pinkerton and stuff like that because I was reading about them earlier this week.
You know what's fun? If you some of these armored car companies, they have they have depots, you know,
where they maintain them and such. Right. And you go in the back building and they have all the ones that people try to get to what was inside.
And you see holes in them. And it's quite interesting. You know, some are smashed up, you know,
and you see little round holes in the glass and all this. It's quite it's quite an interesting story.
I've actually yeah, I've actually seen a couple of the salvage yards where these things wind up eventually after they strip certain things out of them.
So, yeah, I know what you're talking about further down the line.
Yeah, we're talking about a society that is so dumb. They actually go into a bank, what they call a bank, which is not a bank.
All the banks have been closed for 80 years and they try to get that cash because not because it's worth anything,
because they know if they give it to someone else, they'll get something for it. Right.
It's kind of, you know, crappy. And here's the other thing I heard.
And I haven't confirmed that the FBI no longer investigates bank robberies. Why should they?
It's a it's the whole thing is ridiculous. Right now. The problem is, is the merchants.
Either the mom and pop or the big superstores, because they're, you know, someone goes into the store and they buy what they want with this private credit,
which is worthless on its face, not because you can get something with it and the merchants accept it.
It's not the Federal Reserve or the government. That's the problem.
If you see the private credit system as being a problem, it's the merchants that accept it.
People don't. It's all misguided. It's all ridiculous. So if this is the truth and the fact.
Now, the thing is, oh, Greek. Oh, here he comes again saying this is the truth and the facts.
But no one else. You know, we know. Why isn't anyone else saying it? This guy's full of crap. Right.
Well, that's what a lot of people say, because, hey, it is the minority voice at the moment.
It's not. It's it's the merchants, not the Federal Reserve or the government or the fake private credit.
And it's it's you and the merchants. So how many protests have you heard about the merchants accepting money
and people's desire to use the Federal Reserve note or private credit in all the countries to buy things?
Like I said once, if you want to know where the problem is with the monetary system, get yourself a mirror.
Right. And then when you go to the merchants, that's you know, they're the ones, not the federal.
They're just accommodating you just like, you know, the Federal Reserve is just to accommodate,
just like the guys that sell T-shirts outside of a concert. You think they would be there if there was no concert?
No, that's that's the truth. The you know, the the services that sprout up around anything are there for a reason.
They generally would not be there without the root cause of, you know, in other words,
let's just say there wouldn't be a guy selling you sandwiches outside of a place that doesn't have food in it, you know, etc.
Yeah, there wouldn't be gas stations in the middle of long stretches of highway where there's desert and coyotes.
You know, you do that because but once the highway closed down, it closes down that they you know, now there's no one to accommodate.
So it's just misguided. I mean, the whole thing, the whole scenario, I mean, mainstream alternative, this, that fringe.
It's all just a one big ball of ridiculousness, you know, and if it wasn't, we wouldn't be here talking about it.
And it's not going to change. What are the chances of there being a movement?
People saying, you know, I'm not going to use private credit to make purchases and I'm going to start a protest movement with the merchants not to.
What are the chances of that happening? There's a little bit of it with Bitcoin. Right. Going on.
Well, sort of. Yeah. But still, they missed the point. It's not lawful, you know.
And here's the thing. The other thing that I can't stand listening to, oh, they do the war because of money.
Haven't you noticed there hasn't been any money pretty much anywhere in the world for the past 80 years?
What was and how can they be doing war for money when there is no money?
Well, see, I use I use the word profit, you know, and what they profit is a little bit different than money.
So I hope you understand the difference when I say that. See, sometimes things are hidden in the language a little bit.
And what you may profit by something is not necessarily having anything to do with anybody's monetary system.
It does have something to do with another system, though.
And, you know, we're just about up against the end of this hour, believe it or not.
And I want to say this when people talk about, you know, the concept of, you know, for the love of money.
Well, there's a lot of things that people discuss, right?
They say all the time somebody loves money, loves their luxury.
They love their things. They love, you know, what's fascinating to me.
And I think we should devote the very next hour to this concept because it is in need of address.
And the deal is, I think that the concept of love itself is something that we should break down in the second hour.
Because people talk about love or the lack thereof and the motivations for doing many things.
And after all, hatred and war seem to go along with this equation.
So I think if you guys stick around, we're going to really dissect it for you here in the second hour of Ocelli and the Greek on American Freedom Radio.
We'll be right back.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us with free education.
Well, that's obviously effective, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America.
All the information they provide is free.
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, then?
Exploiting commonplace corruption.
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
They never censor, hang up or cut off their guests.
Well, that's no fun, is it?
Well, they created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shills and scum.
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from.
Exposing commonplace corruption.
Helping vulnerable people without a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
And creating a fantastic commercial free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative mainstream and alternative media shills and scum.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotic.
Freedom.
Oh yes, I like this very much.
Radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO and is 100% gluten free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
Tell the truth, don't be bullshitting people.
There's enough bullshit as it is.
In fact, there's just enough.
Did you know that?
There's just enough bullshit to hold things together in this country.
Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation.
Where would we be without our safe, familiar American bullshit?
Land of the free, home of the brave, the American dream.
All men are equal, justice is blind, the press is free.
Your vote counts.
Business is honest, the good guys win.
The police are on your side.
God is watching you.
Your standard of living will never decline.
And everything is gonna be just fine.
The official national bullshit story.
I call it the American Okie Doke.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
The network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information you would dare to understand.
So the second hour begins here on American Freedom Radio
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
The sonic entity you have decided to allow into your ear hole
by whatever it is you're utilizing
is Ocelli and the Greek.
Of course, if you go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and you notice there is a banner there
that says help us grow.
There is a button of sorts.
I call it a button.
Who knows?
Button, link, whatever you want to call it
where you can donate and show your approval
for shows like this
and the rest of what American Freedom Radio has to offer
and also help to keep things running
by making a donation.
One time running donations.
Any amounts.
All is appreciated.
And the fact is you should, in my mind anyway
and I'm just speaking for myself,
support what it is that you find to be of value
and apply value to it.
So do that.
Tell friends about this show and this network
as often as you can.
Okay.
So we began the show by discussing the concept of worship
and I got to tell you that poetically
or in a prose fashion
because who knows what's poetic at this point.
I haven't seen very much poetry in several years
quite honestly and maybe that's just my opinion
but the truth is that the word worship
often comes up when one is composing
well, sonnets, love poems, prose of all sorts
relating to the concept of love in one way or another
and I think that the two words for certain
do belong together
but there's kind of a misunderstanding I would say
as to what love actually is.
You know the old Tina Turner song, right?
Of course there was a movie I think named after it as well
and all that and excuse me for liking something
with a touch of soul to it
but I did like Tina and all that kind of stuff
and I like that very raspy kind of character filled voice.
I always loved that stuff myself personally
but what's love got to do with it, right?
Well, how about we dissect that here in the second hour.
Greek, you up for it?
Oh, sure.
But the thing is dissecting it is interesting
because if you were just going to dissect
what people consider to be love
it's just feeling.
It's a biochemical feeling, a surge
it's a heartfelt thing that they say
I love this, I love that
I love ice cream, I love my car
or I love you or I love my wife
or I love my children
and relationships, right?
and all this stuff based on love
how many times have you heard about falling in love, right?
All of these things are tied in
love and hate
hate being used as an opposite
which it can be on one side
and on the other it clearly is not.
I always think about the
I'm sorry, I always think about the concept of falling in love
and from a very young age
I did make the observation
and I say this is again one of my childish observations
and I do share those with you on here
that when you fall
generally speaking
the fall might not be so bad
however the end result
the thing that concludes the fall
seems to be unpleasant.
Yeah, when people
well falling regarding anything isn't good
even in common vernacular the fall of man
from a spiritual perspective
when something falls it's not necessarily good
it's quite the opposite, right?
So what we have is when people fall in love
they think it's something good and jovial
and some young people do
or people congratulate others for doing that
and when they come and speak to the Greek
I'm like that's the last thing you want to do
is you want to be in control
of that to a certain degree
Why? Because this concept of falling in love
tied in with infatuation
starts very high on the curve
and it goes down from there
typically
that's why you look at most cultures
that embrace that concept
as having a very high divorce rate
and a very low success rate
in useful and fruitful and long-lasting relationship
where if you look at places
where people almost have no say in the matter
in their courtship and long-term bonding
they have let's say arranged marriages
in many parts of the world or did
have a 90% success rate of staying together
for a lifelong
because the difference there is one
where they fall in love
they think they know what love is
where in the other
where they have no say in the matter
they have to learn to love
you see
Well you see what's weird to me though
is that marriage, right?
and the coupling of two people
to my experience unfortunately
has quite often been
a whole lot more akin to a business partnership
that quite honestly
again from my experiences
has been fraught with problems
no matter how you do it
and factually speaking
it seems to me as though
there could be an argument made
that high intensity emotional rush
that comes along with
what they call falling in love
could be in and of itself
regardless of the amount of success
that a coupling that is born of it comes out of
could be in and of itself
a positive thing
I mean
think about this, right?
if the chief deity
and I pose this question to you
which created all things
according to
what is proposed, right?
created all things
then they created this circumstance
to be there
it seems like a natural thing that does happen
so
yes
is it something that should be viewed
in kind of a
I mean because it almost sounds like
you're immediately negative about that
so
no, no, it's not about her being negative
it's a criticism on the current society
there seems to be a
well, we've discussed the loss of definition of terms
and there's also a loss of definition of action
right?
oh, true, very true
like here's a simple one
the difference between love and hate
people think they're opposite
but it takes a lot of passion and energy to love
based reaction
and it takes a lot of passion and energy to hate
the opposite of love
let's propose this quickly
may not be hate but might be apathy
imagine
someone says I hate this guy
and he goes into the room where this guy is
and he starts yelling at him
and doing all this other stuff
that's quite a bit of energy
expended into that hate moniker
but what if
there was two people in the room
and the third one was the one that was hated
and the person went in there
and just greeted the two
and totally ignored them
the other one
the sense of apathy
that person then
his heart would drop to his stomach
see, so necessarily from one aspect
the opposite
from a spiritual sense
or a high form
of love is not hate
but is an aspect of apathy
but this is just an aspect of it
again, but you see how oversimplified
it is
and we also mentioned learning to love
and the success of a relationship
comes together
in its fruition
based on the covenant
that people have together
what rules they have
what rules they live together
so if you go into the
together with
so if you go into
most western civilizations
and you ask people
what covenant they live by
they look at you
like you have four heads
and eat razorblades for breakfast
they don't know what you're talking about
or it's very, very odd
right
so it's very simple
it's sets of rules
and sometimes
let's say you have a couple
once you agree on what rules
you're going to live by
what covenant you live by
what that means
your set of laws
how you keep time
what you eat
what you wear
how you're going to do business
what days you have as holidays
how you raise a family
how you deal with neighbors
how you deal
you see it just goes on
and on and on
when I say laws
I don't mean traffic law
or tax law
and stuff like that
I mean the laws that govern
just like for example
when you start looking at
the laws of physics
they try to explain
everything in the physical
natural world
and they call them laws as such
because it's an explanation
or a guideline
to show how things work
right
in a very detached
and you know
objective sense
I would say
what you're talking about
is more of a set of guidelines
that are agreed upon
for conduct
right
I mean in a wide sense
is that about covering
behavior, conduct, intent
right
like let's say
you live by a certain covenant
and this is what's
fit and proper to eat
before you go shopping
you intend to buy
these items
and not these others
so
yeah
it's behavior
present and future
as well
you know if you have
a set of rules
just like for example
sports teams
when they're playing
let's say football
there's sets of rules
and before they do
the next play
they know the rules
of the game
and the next play
has to be in accordance
with those rules
and then you have
harmony
within the game
right
so
or within the situation
or whatever
so there's a set of things
that people seem to have
left aside
but
based on the operating
system concept
people do have
let's say
a covenants
and arrangements
through what we might
call an operating system
it's called
magazines
psychotherapists
television
school
that's where they're
getting their operating
system
you know
what's fit and proper
to eat
how do you deal
with your
spouse
how do you raise
children
what clothing do you wear
you see
all these things
come from your deity
but
so the people
because they have
no concept
of the spiritual world
and they think
there's just God
and they shove it
to the side
they
look at television
to see what to
think
or schools
and one could even
say
ok
in earlier times
in television
and movies
not very long ago
but in television
and movies
it was
sort of demonstrated
to people
that it was a whole lot
more
acceptable
to say
strike your mate
actually
right
I mean
a woman getting
smacked by a man
in the face
during a movie
I can recall
a few of those
that's not lawful
by the way
not lawful at all
but I'm saying
that because
it was sort of
out there
as part of the
general consensus
in a way
it became
popular
or unpopularly popular
right
like for
another example
would be
the
all of the
external influence
that people get
from their society
and what they
look up to
or worship
takes the place
of their deity
you see
so
it's quite interesting
but
the aspect of love
you know
like for example
in Greek
there's four words
to describe love
there's the
there's like a divine love
which is based on action
you know
not just saying
you love
and then there's the
the love that
from a familial aspect
that parents have
for children
then there's like
a brotherly love
that you would have
with a friend
and then there is
the love
that is the lustful
the
what they call
lust
or
eros
right
so
and these four terms
you know
are very clear
and concise
in my mind
and they identify
and here I go
you know
speaking from the
personal perspective
once again
because you try
and give the objective report
a lot of times
I interject
my personal
situation into it
but I would say
that
that I understand
each of these concepts
and
feel
each of them
do experience them
and therefore
it seems to me
to be a relatively good way
to explain it
yet in English language
we're confronted constantly
by one word
to describe
all of these things
sure
and
and it's based again
on feeling
like in
in a high form of love
where you know
you do something
because it's to help
you may not feel like
doing it
right
you might go against
your feelings
it might be like
highly inconvenient
right
but you do
you do it because
it you
based on your law form
you know it's the right thing to do
this is
the word
agape
which is divine love
which are
you know
it's sort of like
almost
towards a deity
or it's a very high form of love
that even though
something
it goes against
your feeling
or your heart
you do it because
it's the right thing to do
and this is another thing
I wanted to throw in
which we will
get into
how can you not
is the concept of
the heart
if you study
any of
what's been memorialized
as
through history
of mankind
you will find
the heart is a very
negative place
but yet
all you hear
popularized
is that the heart
is a positive place
to be
follow your heart
the heart is
deceiving
like for example
like we said
that people
don't know
anything about
or they don't research
things that they worship
you know
it's just not
to get political
but if you look at
the long list
of false flags
that have been going
on politically
all of that
the authorities
were able to
take advantage
of the population
in mass
because of
the heart
not the mind
you know
see
so you have
to be very careful
and even today
in alternative media
they tell you
follow your heart
anyone that says
that just run
the other way
don't walk
run
because
they're just
continuing
this miserable
existence
that people
are always
complaining about
yet don't want
to lift a finger
to mitigate
you see
so the heart
what's also
interesting
biologically
has brain tissue
in it
and just to get
into a little bit
of it
it does not
it's not on the
left side
of your chest
it's directly
in the center
in a cubic form
there's a man
named Frank Chester
that I invite
anyone to research
Frank
and the last name
is Chester
as in Chester
drawers
and he has
something called
the
seven-sided figure
it's a lawful
geometric figure
and
his work
actually works
with
advancing cardiology
and he discovered
and it's
very much a fact
and the truth
that the heart
sits directly
in the center
of the body
on a diagonal
inside of a cube
which is 36 degrees
not 45
because most people
would think a diagonal
across a square
is 45 degrees
from point to point
but the diagonal
inside of a cube
is at 36
which sounds
counterintuitive
so once you factor
in the work
of Frank Chester
and people like
Rudolf Steiner
there are things
that you will
discover about
the heart
that are not known
even by the professionals
professing to be
experts on that
so if the
why did I go
through all of this
it sounded
quite boring
maybe to some people
if the people
that you go to
that are your
leading world authorities
on the
what's known
as the heart
and can easily
be proven wrong
what kind of a chance
does the common man
who just wants to go
about his life
have about getting
true and accurate
information about the heart
next to nothing
right
if the
if the authorities
in that field
know nothing
or about it
or so little
that they could easily
be disproved
using what might
be called
proper science
imagine
that's why
very often
we bring up
the concept
that everyone
wants to do
what they like to do
and if they have
curiosity about
the world around them
they have to go to
the entitled classes
known as experts
or professionals
in their fields
to get information
about that
right
how many times
do we reference
things that is not
our specialty
very often
now these people
that are being trusted
whether it's legal
scientific
religious
spiritual
just across the board
if they're putting
out information
that is false
what chance does a
person have
who doesn't study
that
let's say
and has other things
to do to get
anything accurate
or truthful
very little chance
and the reason
love is so important
to consider
is because
it is
something that
drives people
you know
if someone says
I love my car
they're going to be
a little more
hot-headed
if something
happens
to the car
than someone
who says
well I don't really
like that car
you see
so love is
almost like
something that
will set people off
and it's very
important to people
but they know
very little about it
most people
that you'll ever meet
that say they love
something
what they really
are saying
is that they
like something
very much
there's a big
difference
between love
and liking
but most people
are not familiar
with the concept
that you need
to learn to love
why?
why do you need
to learn to love?
because again
like the long
thing about the heart
even though it was
not very long
we didn't spend an hour
on it
but a few minutes
is that
they believe
that this thing
the concept called love
comes from the heart
and the heart
actually if you read it
in some ancient text
it's a wicked place
you don't want to go there
I understand that
but you know
here's the thing
bluntly
you know
if you say
to like something
very much
is different
than loving
and you need
to learn to love
and you've said
that that's a contrast
right?
well in that case
one would say
well what is
the actual difference
between liking something
so much that you
end up loving it
or learning
to love something
there seems
to be
an odd
kind of
discontinuity there
you know
on the face of it
because it's been
debased
if you ask
all things
have all things
apparently
sure
it's completely debased
and it goes on feeling
and then you mix in
a lot of the
modern social things
and what I mean by that
is when you look
at basis
you know
in ancient Greece
they had a saying
that fashion
is irrelevant
because
the human body
doesn't change that much
why do we need to
change the style
of clothing we wear?
just do it right
you know
car, automobiles
and airplanes
and things like that
are very much
you know
like cars
or what they call
automobiles
or motorized wagons
or engine-driven wagons
why do they have to
I always joke around
with people
in that business
I say
well you got a new model
coming out this year
maybe you'll figure out
how to build them
because if you knew
you wouldn't come out
with a new model
every year
I mean
when was the last time
you saw like
this is this year's
screwdriver
this model screwdriver
you know
screwdrivers?
no
they settled on
yeah
they settled on a design
and
it seems to be efficient
and therefore
it's been replicated
that's about
the end of that
yeah
so
the automobile
again I keep
let's just say
automobile
is
on what people like
again
and some people
do love them
as well
what I mean
by the
learning to love
is that
once you
start studying
what it takes
to
sometimes exert
one's efforts
mentally
physically
and such
against the feeling
that one might have
which a feeling would be
a feeling of pleasure
and
being relaxed
conservatively
let's say
where you're not
what do you call it
when you're
when someone bothers you
let's say
when you're not inconvenienced
right
when you transcend that
then you're operating
in the learned love position
where you're doing something
because it's lawful
and the right thing
you know
what's interesting
is
when you look at
certain ancient texts
about acting lawfully
like I'll just bring something up
if you're
if you have an enemy
because let's say you
it's possible to
have land
and draw a border
and the people
on the other side of that line
decide they don't like you anymore
and they want to be your enemy
right
this has happened
throughout history
right
of course
if there are animals
across that border
you're to return those animals
unharmed
now
if you look at a lot of western
especially American
other
unlawful societies
like Hatfields and McCoys
they take shots
at their enemies' animals
just for fun
don't they
and harm each other
so
and that means
they do not understand
what love is
why
because they do not have a sense
of lawfulness
where
well where does lawfulness come from
it comes from your God
let's just say that
your God
not God
because there is no such thing
as a singular God
see
so
this is again
you notice how these shows
always go back
to the spiritual realm
why
we go back
to the spiritual realm
because
that spiritual society
is vast
in number
compared to the human numbers
so
it bears
significance
in merit
from that perspective
and if we look at
ancient
memorialized texts
regarding love
you will see
that love is brought up
in many different ways
that is
basically unfamiliar
to people today
on how they use it
and
is it
going back to
how
let's say
the human body
hasn't changed
why do we need fashion
every year
right
why don't they just
you see
so have we changed
that much
that we need to
redefine
what love is
you know
or why
can't we go
and see how it's
always been memorialized
and consider it
not that you have to do it
but it's called an inquiry
alright
just inquire
because it might enrich you
right
so when we
start looking at this
and even as a parent
you
would probably consider
that you've been inconvenienced
or
having a spouse
you might have been inconvenienced
more than once
to do something
for someone else
in your family
and
if anyone asked you
why do
why did you allow yourself
to be so inconvenienced
to do it
even though it was against
your feeling
the answer would be because
I love them
well see now
here's the problem
within myself
I don't feel
any inconvenience
for having
done what
I perceive as
is the best thing
I could
for my son
at various points
I do things
for him
in fact that I would not do
for myself
right
I've told you several times
and I know I've mentioned this
to others
that
I feed him
the best food
that I can find
that he will consume
right
I don't necessarily
make that
same adjustment
in what is
you know he literally
has separate food for me
right
for me
I try and pick
what is efficient
and in some cases
I don't make the best decisions
for myself
and I knowingly do that
but I insist
that for him
I give him the best things
that I can
so this isn't an inconvenience
this is based on
what
what needs to be
I'm compelled to do so
and I feel as though
I love my son very much
and the idea of being inconvenienced
is for example
with newborns
you know they have a
three hour schedule
three hours on
three hours off
and let's say the parents
have to go to work
the next day
and they can't sleep
because they have to
take care of the baby
right
and if you're wealthy enough
you know if you have others
do it for you
right
live in nanny
or something like that
but there's a level of dedication
through action
that is
that shows
the higher forms of love
like for example
the aspect of love
being a generic term
based on feeling
has
is part of the misguidance
that society as a whole
has endured
and has suffered
meaning willingly
that is
many of the ills
that they do experience
otherwise
within their society
see
and because it's never been taught
that their
their
the concept of love
and their feelings
of love
are very different
in some cases
especially
in relationships
you see
when you look at the
the
let's say the spouse
situation
or the relationship
the pairing of people
when they base it strictly
on feeling
you'll notice
there's a lack
of efficiency there
there's arguing
there's debating
there's
well I'll do it my way
you do it your way
kind of thing
because there was
no common way
that they came together with
and this is
there are exceptions to this
by the way
and most of the exceptions
you will find in most
more traditional
older European
or Asian societies
but lacking in the western world
meaning
what most of the world
is trying to adapt today anyway
so what's interesting about
the concept of discussing love
is that
it is so debased
on what has been memorialized
through the ages about love
especially when we
think of
the pagan holiday
known as Valentine's Day
right
which people are
sort of dedicated
a day towards it
and that is based on feeling
again
or the form of love
known as Eros
which is the physical
right
and they've forgotten
that there is a non-physical aspect
of love
which is purely based on action
well okay
and I get that
that's for certain
you know
people often say
don't tell me you love me
but show me
right
exactly
and then there's various forms
of love within that
you know
how far is someone willing
to go to do
what needs to be done
for you
or themselves
well you know
and see that's the thing
so I wonder
based on what you're saying
you know
the situation
like I was describing
with myself
and my son
what am I leaving
out of that equation
except that
I don't feel as though
there's any sort of inconvenience
that doesn't even enter my mind
it is what must be done
because
this is
this is just simply
the way it is
and even when he used to
keep me awake at night
and everything else
this wasn't the
you know what I'm saying
I don't perceive an inconvenience
it was just
well this is what comes along
okay so we're going to give parental advice
from the
Chelly in the Greek show
okay here's a very simple way to do it
how many times have you heard parents say
if I would have known
what I know now
I would have raised the children differently
I would have done this differently
or even without children
how many times have you heard people say
in general
if I would have known
what I know now
back then
I would have done things
maybe a little differently
and typically differently
meaning that it would have been
a better
you know
a qualitative difference
meaning the quality
would have been higher
okay
yeah well observably
I could say that again for myself
because I had children
at a different time period
and I've told you that in fact
that I would have done things differently
had I had
a better set of knowledge
but at that time
correct
it was that
so here's the point
the point here
on any advice for anyone
at any time
is this
well what do you know now
that didn't exist back then
was it like the wheel
was not invented until later
was it the sky
was a different color
no everything pretty much
is still the same
it was the lack of inquiry
or the lack
what you might call experience
because inquiring about knowledge
is actually an experience
like before the internet
you might say
I want to learn about something
and you went to a library
and that's the experience
is the actual traveling
to the library
and while you're there
what it took to extract
or impart the information
to oneself or others
so
what
this is also like
part of the hidden meaning
of doing the show
is that there is a lack of inquiry
across the board with humanity
that's been going on
for a very long time
that is brought about
through time
and cumulative events
a lot of misery
and a lot of
let's say reduction of quality
right
so when most people say
I would have done things differently
right
there was a lack of inquiry
or
they might say
well I didn't know this back then
well why don't you inquire now
you see
so
and there's a very interesting aspect
to acquiring knowledge
because again
as we said earlier
if
if for example
if you look at
let's say the biblical text
is an example
actually they're all similar
if you hear anyone discussing
anything
regarding those texts
pretty much
on the internet
or what's been written about it
and you actually
study the text yourself
you'll find that
it's all crap
none of that stuff
is in there in context
you see
and that's
that's not inquiring
you know
you see
so there's many levels to it
and that's
the same as love
there's the
the feeling
well yeah
this guy said that
you know
this religion's based on the planets
and you won't find that anywhere
other than
what this guy said
and
and then you're like
okay so I know now
the religion's based on
people go around
saying this kind of stuff
and the same with food
you know
or disease
oh yeah
this bacteria
that got us cold
you know
all this misinformation
that's been going on
for such a long time
is through lack of inquiry
and when one inquires
into the study of love
which is heavily
tainted and debased
because it's based on
the feeling
you know
the Romeo and Juliet
the Valentine's Day
right
all this stuff
is feeling
and it's the lower form
not the lower
but the physical feeling
part of love
and not the part
that requires
a cognitive
organized
decision making
well informed
about what is lawful
and again
which is difficult
to say what is lawful
for people
if they're not aware
of what God they
have within their realm
right
sure
because your law
comes from your deity
and we ask most people
you know
the most annoying thing
sometimes is
God bless
and I'm like
well which God
are you talking about
you know
it's like
you almost cannot
communicate anymore
because the level
of debasement
in all things
has reached a peak
I mean
it'll go even
it'll get even more
debased as time goes on
slightly more
see
I understand that
I'm sorry to keep
hearkening back to the same thing
because I want to use
something that's an
observable example
to me
here
you know
yes you're right
it was a lack of inquiry
on my part
that caused me
to not
do certain things
or to do certain things
earlier on
and then I learned
by inquiring
you know
but I didn't have
the intent to
it wasn't like negligence
on my part
intentionally
to begin with
to not say
you know
to not do the best things
I could
the first time around
let's say
but truthfully
actually
some of those experiences
taught me
differently
and everything
seems to be a learning
experience
you know
I mean
I can't consume
all of the knowledge
in the world
I do my
I did my best
you know
given what I thought
I needed to be aware of
but
it really
made me feel
as though
there was a censorship
involved there
because
you know
you're completely unaware
of the knowledge
that you should
probably have
for the
for proper care
for proper
things of all sorts
consideration
when it comes to
teaching
and
well I have no other word for it
but care
of like a child
right
so
that doesn't mean
that
that I intentionally
just you know
now I'm ignorant here
and that's fine
I'm ignorant
and I'll just do this
you know
I didn't do it
in that fashion
but
but I did learn
and I did change
based on
you know
information
which was new to me
later on
oh yeah
the thing here is not
whether it's intentional
or not
because there's many things
well you know
if you look at the
entire scheme
of human history
whether you look at it
in a positive light
or a negative light
you'll see that
you can
cut it down the middle
and say
maybe half of it
was intentionally done
and the other half
just happened
right
through
through ignorance
or just
the sign of the times
right
but there's a compression
of
when
of information
or
how would you say
when
when something
has a basis
there's no guesswork
right
like let's say
with the money
right
you know
or with anything
if it's baseless
then it goes wishy-washy
and it goes all over the place
and until it finds balance
and it lands in one thing
right
very much
like we said
people
no matter how educated
or not they are
they don't care to learn
anything about money
and the repercussions
of using the type of money
they're using
as long as it gets them
what they want
now when we go to
the aspect of love
what is
sort of celebrated
as being
love
openly
in society
today
is a mere
scant
basis
of it
on feeling
and there's not much
discussion
or impartment
of the quality
of love
regarding let's say
parents
right
parenting
or when you look at
let's say a divine
aspect of it
or even the brotherly
love
right
you know like Philadelphia
like Philia
would be the brotherly
aspect
you know
in many places
of the world
for example
especially the Middle East
it is common for men
to kiss each other
on the cheek
twice
men
across both
sexes
let's say
genders
if you watch
any of the
let's say
foreign ministers
in that part of the world
greeting each other
they do so
also it's common
for men
to
when they meet each other
or a group
they hold hands
when they're speaking
to each other
because it's kind of hard
to drift off
and not pay attention
when someone's holding your hand
and you're speaking to them
right
and in many
both practices
are common
in Mediterranean
cultures
of all sorts
yeah
typically the southern
European rim
and throughout the Middle East
across that latitude
but here's the interesting
thing
when you have a culture
that is just based on the
feeling
part
based on the eros
which is the
physical part
they'll
they'll say
oh no
two guys shouldn't kiss
or two guys can't hold hands
that's you know
whatever you know
so because they
right away gravitate
towards that aspect
you see
it's got to be strictly
erotic
right
so
there's a lot of
misunderstanding
and these older cultures
seem to have preserved
a certain level
of
let's say forgiveness
and what other
you know
physical contact
even
even in
in language
like for example
in England
where you know
everyone's love
you know
you go
you get on the bus
in London
and you don't have enough
fare back when it was all
coin
they said love
it's another pence
you know
or another shilling
or whatever
right
love
bus driver
called you love
right
so there's an
interesting aspect
where
that
when a society
becomes just fixated
on the word love
meaning feeling
and the erotic
aspect
they lose
the sensibility
of how it's incorporated
in the rest of society
and their lives as well
from a qualitative
point of view
again
we brought up the
parentage aspect
and that
there's another
form of love
for that
as well
and we brought
I brought up
you seem to have not
seen it as such
but the aspect
of inconveniencing
oneself to exhibit
love through action
right
there's many levels
to that
you know
when someone says
love is all you need
I'm like well
what kind of love
are you talking about
because if you go to
the national pedophile
convention
there's a lot of love
there
I mean is that lawful
love
you know what I mean
it's
it's kind of
become debased
and become very
generic
and in the western world
especially the American
world
the term love
only denotes
the erotic
side of it
and
you know
as you will see
with the coming
pagan holiday
known as
Valentine's Day
right
which is
almost super erotic
because
we did mention
the heart
a little bit
and one of the
symbols that they
like to use
is the
what they call
the heart
symbol
which doesn't
resemble the
physical heart
in any shape or form
at all
because
what that is
this is
gotten out of
Babylonian
all the way through the
Greek and through the
Roman
that is the frontal view
of a woman's genitalia
and
people that do know
this
that are
somehow
behind the scenes
and
in positions of power
must be laughing at the
masses saying
look
these people are so
devoid of any
knowledge of anything
that they're actually
printing
this
thing they call a
heart symbol
all over
in their society
and what we're doing is
we've given them
the image of a frontal view
of a woman's genitalia
and they think it's the heart
it's just a prank
I think we've also discussed
how
humanity is so immature
that
a lot of people talking about
these big bad Illuminati
and all these people
running the world
those people are a
third grade mentality
pretty much
all of these
leaders that you see
and even the ones you don't see
the hidden hand
we're talking about
tops
third to fourth grade
mentality
just like third or fourth
graders would play
pranks on each other
looking at a very
prank like society
across the board
where
again
just to tie it in
with love
with most people
in the western world
when you say the word
love
they
immediately
connect it to
some form of
eroticism
and the
one regarding
parentage
and
brotherly love
or friendly love
and other
forms of love
are almost not discussed
and just a given
oh yeah
I just do that
because I love my children
but they cannot define it
well
see here you go
right
so let's move on
to that
that concept
of brotherly love
I
again
I'll use myself
for the example
I feel as though
I
express that
quite often
in fact
I think that
that's one of the things
that
caused me to be a
broadcaster
I think that is
one of the things
that causes me to
when I see someone
in distress
regardless of
any previous relationship
or lack thereof
I often have a tendency
to wish to help them
things like that
I mean
if I have food to spare
I will feed someone
who's hungry
if I have
anything to spare
that I think could be beneficial
to someone
that I see lacking it
I have this tendency
to
to give it to them
to make something better for them
even if just for the moment
right
sometimes I'll even just
share a kind word
with someone
that I find noticeably distressed
when I'm in public
which isn't very often
but
when I am out in public
and I do interact with people
if I see someone
in distress
I will quite often
make an effort
which
maybe that's something
to talk about
regarding convenience
to
alleviate that
to sort of
I mean
would you think
that that is
yeah
clearly
okay
yeah
well the thing is
the
the concept of
do you like people
most people will
because it's popular
say yes
you like people
but they have no love
like for example
it happens often
if you convey
in an engine powered wagon
you'll be at an intersection
and the light
will turn green to go
and all of a sudden
you hear people
leaning on their horns
sticking their head
out of their
window cursing
at someone
who
they think
deliberately parked
in front of the
intersection
to ruin their day
and it turns out
that person's car
broke down
and
so the thing to do
if you have any love
is get out
and help them
push the car
to the side
ask them if they need
any help
and all those people
around them
you know
I sometimes do
when I'm involved
in a situation like that
I'm like
do you think the guy
deliberately parked there
to ruin your day
what's wrong with you
and if you ask
those people
do you like people
they say yes I do
do you love people
yes I do
see because
that's all they know
is like
but they have no love
well see now
I answer that question
a little differently
right
I tell you that
truthfully
no I don't like
most people
do I love
do I love them though
unfortunately
sometimes yes
so
that sounds to me
more
you know
that's my honest response
I mean I don't know
what you think of that
but
yeah well the thing is
the reason not to like people
is because of their behavior
sometimes you might
find certain behavior
unacceptable right
how many times
have you heard that
in society
right
exactly
like that leads to the concept
let's say
because it's a Christian era
and they use a lot of
Christian metaphors
about forgiving
your brother
you know you've heard that
right
and that's a
it's stated in the
New Testament
what they call
but if you actually look
outside of the King James
into what the King James
was supposed to be
that word that they're using
for forgive
is aphesis
and in Greek
that means
to get away from
or leave it alone
there's a really big difference
so
this concept of forgiveness
you will not find
in scripture
or what they call
the Bible
if you look at the
original language
of preservation
it's very interesting
so that
so
when you are
in a situation
for example
where people are
distasteful
or whatever
there's this
sort of cultural thing
because the biblical
text is
forgive them
is to stick around
and let them keep doing it
to you
where if you actually
study the biblical text
when some
there is an offense
put on you
it
states
to get away from them
leave them alone
quite a contrast there
isn't it
right
the reason I brought that up
is because it's a metaphor
right
forgive your brother
how many times do you hear that
in western civilization
I hear that a lot
yeah
you can do that
but where are you getting that from
and if you actually
look at the source
it doesn't say that at all
in its original form
so the reason I brought that up
is because
again
there
you know
the term suffering
means to
be inconvenienced
even sometimes with pain
or harm to yourself
but you did it willingly
right
when you suffer
like something
that's why if you
if you've ever watched
any court cases
where let's say
a cop
beats up someone
really bad
and then the person
who was
beaten up
goes to court
against the cop
what's the first thing
the judge
asks the person
who was beaten up
suing the cop
did you suffer
and the person says
yes I did
case dismissed
no case
because that means
you willingly accepted it
right
it's a play on words
but words are very important
isn't it
so
aren't they
I should
say
okay
so
again
it's okay
yeah
so
the concept of love
again
when you get outside
of the feeling aspect
you know
which is
basically
it seems to have
become all erotic
now
especially with
what's coming up
known as Valentine's
Day
when you start
inquiring and
seeing
and you could
put it more
clearly
not as
just not just
for a parent
right
because there are also
some parents that are
malevolent to their
children
believe it or not
and
you can hear about it
often
yes
so
when
the term love
to be defined
and the many aspects
of it
and to be
knowingly and
willfully
administering them
right
is important
and
bringing that topic
up again
is important
to state that
clearly
especially
when love is
limited to the
feeling aspect
or the erotic aspect
that's clearly
debased as a whole
especially when you
compare it to the
Greek paradigm
which were
in the Greek paradigm
there are four words
for love
and each one
describes a different
aspect
so
the concept here is
you know again
when
you hear that word
being used a lot
you know
love
is a good thing
you know
I always
yeah
it is
but what are you
talking about
you know
is it
you see
why has it been
limited now
especially
popularized commercially
as the erotic
type only
and the others
are not
discussed
even though
there's a city
in America
called Philadelphia
named after
one of the
types of love
right
literally
nicknamed
the city
of brotherly love
yeah
but
no
and that's
absolutely true
and that's why
I'm glad we
explored this
it's just that
it's interesting
to me sometimes
though
the level
at which
people don't
internalize
the
differences
and consider
their actions
along with
their words
of course
well
we constantly
discuss that
on this show
but yeah
the words
are one aspect
and they are
important
but there are
other actions
aside from
speaking
that are also
quite characteristic
of what it is
one is expressing
as well
well clear
concise
communication
because prior to
action
there's communication
you know
a general
will be
at headquarters
in one country
and communicate
to execute
an action
in another country
in wartime
or a leader
of a country
could be
at the capital
and communicate
to execute
an order
in another part
of the country
so
there has to be
a viable
communication
for certain actions
or in other words
if you tell
someone up
and they go up
and you say
well I meant down
well why didn't
you say
why didn't you
say down
do you mean
what you say
and say what you mean
and I believe
that when you look
at a word
like love
it's been debased
and only denoted
with the concept
of feeling good
or the erotic
and the other aspects
are not
discussed
and it's clear
especially
when you look
at the term
of falling in love
and I think
for more than
what
three decades
in the
American culture
there has been
a notable
increase
in what's
known as
divorce rate
right at least
three or four
decades maybe now
I'd say
started in the mid
70s or so
and on
yeah minimally
sure
yeah because
that was the time
of this free love
concept you know
if it feels good
do it
if it smells good
eat it
you know
all that stuff
the women's movement
yeah
so that was part
of the debasing
so one warning
that maybe we can
give to humanity
just like we brought up
when they tell you
the heart
is a good thing
is when
when you're told
something is
really good
guess what
it's
the
it might seem good
at the moment
but guess what the
result is going to be
not very good
in the long run
and this is just
a general rule
that you will
discover
the order of business
of how things have been
on this planet
for a very long time
and it's
lack of inquiry
lack of communication
or substantiating
what things mean
you know
and this is
again
attaches to
the word
love
as well
right
and of course
it does all seem
quite upside down
that which is
alleged to
protect you
is actually harmful
to you
that which is
supposed to be
healthy for you
or good for you
seems to be
rather bad for you
and everything
is
labeled
by a completely
misleading
set of letters
let's just say
in any language
doesn't matter
seems to be
the
constant
here
all the way around
so I would say
in a lot of cases
that which is also
labeled love
is not very
loving
how about that
yes
pretty much
or again
it's a very
narrow aspect
and
it's
applied
in a way
that's
debased
where the meaning
again is
based on feeling
or the heart
and there's
not much
definition
on the
action
aspect of it
you know
the thing is
again
one of the main
criticisms of society
is that
there are
many people
that are
supposedly
giving good
information to the
masses
both mainstream
and alternative
and they're
getting away
with
following the
same stuff
that didn't
work in the
first place
and people
are still
buying it
and eating it up
and absorbing it as
what they call
gospel
you know
and fortunately
I will feel
personally
a sign of relief
in the next few years
when
this paradigm
change
starts to happen
where people
will start
actually listening
to what they're hearing
and
doing a little bit
of referencing
and saying
you know
we've been hearing
all this stuff
and doing all this stuff
for so long
and it's not
serving us well
I think we need to go
a little bit further
on our own
this is a time period
that's coming
in the near future
so I guess
what we're doing here
by speaking out
the way we are
is probably just
giving a little bit
of a lift
of the veil
to see
or to show
that there's more
to these simple
topics that we cover
than people think about
well absolutely
and
I don't know
you know
we're just about
out of time
here on
episode 17
and
I think
we kicked
this one around
pretty well
I would say
to the person
in the chat room
that thinks I was
starting to sound
defensive
I assure you
one thing
that
if I was being
defensive
or taking this
all very personal
it would not
sound so calm
it's not
the way
that I function
believe me
I'm sitting here
trying to be
as objective
as possible
but
sometimes
I find it helpful
to utilize myself
as an example
just because
I can easily
relate to it
and discuss
different aspects
because after all
I know where I'm at
with a lot of things
so
there you go
it's just
convenience
that allows me
to seize upon it
as an example
and also
a call on humanity
at this point
across the entire planet
is that
if you get too
objective
and truthful
you're going to
lose your audience
there's very few people
that could
sit down in one place
and meditate
on very simple things
and saying
why are we doing
what we're doing
and what does this mean
and what is this based on
very few people
can do that
and it's a very
unpopular stance
throughout human history
by the way
well it certainly is
and you've said it
several times
that if you actually
adapted every single
thing that you
are talking about
into your character
into your daily life
you will discover
rather quickly
that you'll be
sitting alone
because this is not
the way
that other people
are functioning
because after all
we are living
in a rather
unlawful society
under a cosmic
censorship
so anything
you want to say
as we close?
Sure
being alone
just for the sake
of being alone
is not good
but being alone
to set yourself
apart from the muck
and the
and just the junk
is a good thing
there's a big
difference there
you know if you look
at history
at all the sages
and the people
that were sought after
did they live in the
middle of town
or did they have to
go out into the desert
or the jungle
or the forest
to find them
where they lived alone
you see
because they needed
to set themselves
apart
so
setting yourself
apart is
is the way to go
that's true
because even the shamans
in what they call
Native American culture
usually did not
live with the rest
of the tribe
no they did not
so keep that in mind
I thank you once again
for tuning in to the show
Ocelli and the Greek
episode 17 is in the can
of course you can go to
ocelliandthegreek.com
and also to the archives
at americanfreedomradio.com
and check out a lot more
thank you once again sir
I'm telling ya
you gotta support
American Freedom Radio
because this government
is getting out of hand
Wall Street won't
loan them my money
the CIA are cutting
into my drug running
and my gun running
big pharma
psychotropic drugs
are making my customers
commit suicide
before my hitmen
can even lock them
and then they get depressed
and get prescribed
psychotropic drugs
and commit suicide too
they're trying to become
the biggest game in town
when you're paying
protection money
you don't even get
protected
I get unpaid taxes
and if I can't find
the money
the IRS are gonna
take my thugs
I got a mandatory
flu vaccine
and now I'm autistic
I reported a vaccine
reaction
and the doctor told me
to forget about it
what have I ever done
to have them
treat me so disrespectfully
there's only one way
to get the government
off our backs
and that's to support
American Freedom Radio
capisce?
so what are you gonna do?
you're gonna go to
americanfreedomradio.com
and give them some
legal tender
they can't refuse
news and information
you can trust
this is
American Freedom Radio
Freedom Freedom
American
Freedom Radio
Radio
American
Freedom Radio
to protect, to serve, and to commit perjury whenever it supports the state's case.
Swearing on the Bible is just one more way of controlling people and keeping them in
line and it's one more thing that holds us back as a species.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com, the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent
debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it provides an example
to follow, friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in
service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make
the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
American Freedom Radio.