The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Coachella and the Greek.
It would be 5 p.m. on a Friars Day or as you might call it Friday according to the Pope's work schedule.
It is well the first month and the 15th day.
However, according to the way one should tell time it is what Greek?
Hey, I'd say it's the last week of the 11th month lawfully.
And who are we to tell anybody what they should do?
But anyway, hey, of course, right?
It could be the third day of the 82nd month.
You know, it doesn't matter because no one knows how to tell time.
It seems on the planet except possibly five people and they are with all due respect probably our listeners.
And I heard it's gone up to about seven now.
So might even be a movement as long as it's not a bowel movement.
But anyway, the whole idea is, you know, in ancient days people settled their debts with every full moon, which is the new moon.
And that's why today don't you get a monthly bill to settle debts?
And so but there's lawful stuff and there's unlawful stuff.
And right now it's all unlawful.
But, you know, hey, that's just the sign of the times, as they say.
What is one to do?
That's why we're trying to give a cosmic approach.
What I mean by that, again, that word always comes up is objective.
If we were just dropped here as visitors and we had to go back and report what was going on here.
Well, we can't say, you know, well, you know, the grass is really nice.
You know, we enjoyed time at the bar.
That doesn't give any information back to where we're sent from to get information for.
So all the things that we do express here, as I've heard in private conversations, like, well, your opinions are interesting.
I'm like, since when did I ever give an opinion?
If I do, I qualify it that I am giving one, which is very rare.
I've maybe given maybe five or 10 opinions in the last decade.
Those words that ever left my mouth and maybe 10 years.
So the thing is about being objective.
So just a reminder, this is, I think, the Ides of the Greek Ocelli and the Greek show, isn't it?
The 15th, isn't it?
That's right.
It is the 15th episode.
If you want to, you know, episodically methodically identify them, because, of course, we're not doing them by date.
But this would be the 15th meeting live where we've done this particular type of presentation with this purpose under this title.
So, yes, you're right.
Episode 15 on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com, where, by the way, if you're hearing us otherwise, besides catching us on the website,
there is a chat room as well where there are some interesting people that are consistently arriving to hear these conversations
and comment on them as well, just for the information of the listener out there.
Speaking of comments, just in private, we've gotten a couple of them about maybe a request that we should perhaps get right into the topic.
Like, for example, the last time we discussed dreams, I had an individual reach out and say that, amongst other things,
they liked the concept of speaking about dreams, because, you know, even just the name itself doesn't really speculate.
It's speculative because a dream isn't really a dream.
It's a direct communication.
He said he would have preferred that we would have discussed the topic more, and we did spend a good part just discussing general things.
So maybe tonight we'll just dig right into what we decided to or what has come up to be discussed.
But before that, you know, I just want to, again, plug in shamelessly that the efforts being made behind the scenes,
not just the presentation, are all done by those involved.
Yeah, what does he mean by that?
There are donate buttons on websites all over, ocelli.com, on AFR and Ocelli and the Greek,
which by default sends you back to ocelli.com.
So if anyone is so kind enough to help out with a cup of coffee or a pack of smokes or whatever is needed to keep the show going,
because, yes, it runs on caffeine and nicotine sometimes, and that would be very much appreciated.
So just wanted to throw that in.
Any contributions?
Until the million credit button goes up, which hasn't been put up yet, anything is appreciated, anything and everything.
Well, absolutely.
And also because both of, you know, two of the three websites mentioned actually are personally helpful to me,
but American Freedom Radio also accepts donations of all sizes, and there are many programs on here.
Of course, the regular listeners are aware of that,
and helping to keep that on the air is a worthwhile reason to dispense with one's credits if you are so inclined and able to do it.
Right.
And just because you're not listening live and it's somewhere down the stream, as Chuck says,
and you end up pulling up an archive here or there, yes, we do offer the archives at no cost to access.
It doesn't mean that if you hear this episode or any episode in the future,
you can't come back and find the sites and make a donation as well.
So we're kind of qualifying it that way.
Absolutely.
It is an option to do it at any time,
especially if you've received value for the value that you are going to dispense to the individuals who are involved here, as you said.
So moving forward, we will get right into the topic because, after all, when you talk about making reports,
the concept we have gone over many times and you have eloquently provided for people is the idea that one can imagine that you were on a spaceship somewhere.
You landed on Earth.
You know nothing of the language, the history, anything else,
but you would have to give reports about what's happening on the planet.
Now, one of the aspects that one might observe and comes up quite often in conversation on many media platforms of all types,
alternative, mainstream, fringe, whatever it is you want to describe it as, is the concept of education.
Now, this is often bandied about as a political issue.
This is often bandied about as a social issue.
This is most vehemently sort of attacked.
You know, obviously, there are people who are anti-common core, and that's what they're telling you about.
And meanwhile, they don't tell you about what common core is.
Of course, I've always found that particular euphemism for a style or a curriculum to be rather interesting.
Common core almost sounds innocuous, but anyway, leaving that all aside,
we take a step back on this show, actually, and take an objective point of view regarding things like this and give you a different report.
In other words, once again, you will hear things on this show that I assure you are not being said elsewhere.
And if they are being said elsewhere, I certainly haven't heard of it.
Chuck, I just want to throw something in.
You know, we could build a little bit upon this just for maybe five seconds.
I've heard of common core, and I've brought up education in a topical sense and basic conversation.
People bring up common core, and I can honestly tell you I do not know what that is.
I know it has something to do with a program that's being implied.
And I stopped researching the education system over a decade ago because that's all, you know, nothing.
In other words, it had already reached its far down the line of its point of decomposition.
In other words, it died a long time ago.
It's decomposing, and it's just a rotten corpse at this point.
So anything that's put on top of it now, other than daisies or tulips, you know, it doesn't.
You see, it's completely dead, and it has been, and there is no chance of it being revived in a qualitative manner.
So I hear a lot of things, like one of the things you mentioned, common core.
I really don't know what that is because, again, I've stopped looking at the education system over a decade ago.
And this is just to show you how definitively finished that concept is.
I mean, there is no reason to look at it any further.
It's a done deal.
It's just, yeah, it's dead.
So anything they add on to it, I'm not interested.
Well, right.
After all, if the concept of education in and of itself is thoroughly debased, right, at its foundation,
there is no reason to really examine what grows out of the manure if it has already been poisoned, and it is manure.
It's one of these things that are finished.
Now, it's interesting, education, etymologically, other than the rearing of children, means the training of animals as well.
So that's why, you know, it's been, you know, that's why a lot of the things in the, let's say in the States,
are handled by the Department of Agriculture.
If you have a social security number, it's Department of Health and Human Services and Commerce and Agriculture.
It's all locked in.
But, you know, on one of the items that I sent you about topics of discussion, the first item is I just have plainly goats.
Well, yeah.
That's why I brought up as number one, what is a baby goat, a young goat called?
It's a kid.
True.
So the first thing that we need to look at now when we discuss education is perhaps we think of that as the young folks, right,
folks meaning people in German.
Why isn't it interesting?
Why are they, the state promotes this, the corporations promote it, the culture promotes it, the people promote it,
the children themselves promote the concept of the label or labeling them as kids.
A kid is a young goat.
From a spiritual perspective, the goat or the young goat was actually a sacrificial animal.
And it was usually to a malevolent being, malevolent spiritual being, even the term scapegoat.
So the concept of reducing the offspring of men and women into baby goats is just horrifying.
Yeah, this is true, but I'll tell you something.
I want to juxtapose this with something else for a moment.
And that is that the individuals who commonly use the word kid, and I've even been guilty of this,
don't think of it in a negative way at all.
And it's interesting to me because, listen, again, taking that objective step back,
if one were to refer to one's own children as piglets, you know, you might take offense.
If you were to refer to them as puppies, it probably doesn't sound very good.
And meanwhile, these are relatively...
It's what's accepted.
It's the gesture that's important from a mind perspective or spiritual perspective.
You know, the simple discussion is about, let's say, I say this often or used to say it more often,
is if the future of society is dependent upon the young children,
there is no future because all of the children have been turned into goats.
So from a spiritual member, it's the gesture.
How many people enjoy Santa Claus and birthday parties and things like that?
It's very enjoyable and they love it, right?
Christmas, you know.
If they actually knew what the gestures that were involved in partaking in those traditions were,
if you had the tiniest sense of morality, forget about what your religious convictions are.
You'd run the other way.
You would ban it, as those things were banned at one point, you see.
So this is from a mind perspective.
You know, there's a concept of it shall be spoken, it shall be done,
or it shall be spoken, it shall be created, right?
Well, right.
And I've seen in more than one text the concept of, now, please bear with me here,
but the concept of that which you deem to hold true on earth, I shall hold true in another realm.
And that's not exclusively a Christian concept or anything like that.
This is actually buried in a lot of different dogma where you find that your actions have subsequent reactions
and also duplication in the next stage of life in a lot of different dogmatic systems, right?
Well, or even undogmatic.
It's part of an unseen intangible reality that's strictly memorialized literally.
Well, that's the truth of it.
But what I'm saying is that we can see the evidence of it through all of these things, right?
After all, the concept of heaven and hell, you inherit the nature of your deeds on the planet afterwards.
You're either punished or rewarded in the afterlife, right?
The concept of, and I know we don't want to get too far away,
the concept of, say, reincarnation as somebody who has done a bad thing
or has done many bad things or has committed themselves to doing things which are unkind
generally are reincarnated into, well, less than desirable creatures and things like this.
I mean, in other words, the actions that one takes actually have a consequence.
And when you turn around and you do the drill or you do the symbolic action in life,
like you said, Santa Claus, yes, seems like a fun little concept.
But considering the fact that it is the, well, it is the representation, it is the mock action of child sacrifice,
and so are the birthday cakes, not only child sacrifice but of cannibalism as well.
You know, here's the thing.
Yeah, you're not actually cannibalizing a child, but you are, you know, you're not being a cannibal and a child killer,
but you're playing one on TV, you know.
Through gesture, yeah.
Gestures are very important, and there's a formative reality that's intangible to this material reality
where these things actually matter more.
Right.
It's formative, you know, it's of the mind or the spirit, yeah.
Right, so when one turns around and describes children as kids,
you have actually kind of devalued them in a symbolic fashion.
Yeah, and replaced their, the element of communication also is the element of creation of the thought,
and you've also replaced that element with another completely different element.
But, you know, people say, you know, well, you know what I mean.
I said kids, but you know what I mean.
I said, well, yeah, I know what kids mean.
Kids mean baby goats, and well, you know what I mean.
I'm like, okay, so essentially the society is laden with the population that doesn't say what they mean or mean what they say.
Absolutely.
So now would you want that, why would you want to associate,
can you go into business with someone who doesn't say what they mean or mean what they say?
Would you want to go into any relationship with someone who doesn't mean what they say or say what they mean?
Well, no, you wouldn't want to, but sadly.
You have no choice at this point.
Yeah, what are your other options?
Well, you would get off right now and finish, you know, this flying saucer and get off of this place, but either way, yeah.
So, you know, which leads, this leads to another, you know, the next item would be the subculture that's been created,
and the reason I brought up the goats is because to put into the mind that we're going to use the term kid,
not because we want to, but because this is what a lot of things are labeled as,
like there is an entire subculture built around young people now.
It's called kids stuff, kids programs on TV, kids meals in fast food restaurants.
You see, there's a subculture, a juvenile subculture that's been created that never existed prior to the 20th century, by the way.
Isn't that interesting?
Yeah, absolutely.
And there's not only products which are allegedly designed for, again, quotes, kids, but, you know,
even these different gestures of, say, which would seem to be benevolent.
I remember that there was kid care was a state run program in a lot of states,
which was designed to provide health care for children.
You know, it wasn't called children care.
It was called kid care.
It wasn't a veterinarian, right?
Yeah, and it wasn't for the vet.
You know, you weren't taking your children to veterinarians.
But, you know, yeah, see, it gets a little convoluted, doesn't it?
It is, but it's by design and it's the input.
So, yeah, but the culture that's built around these kids, the kid culture, it's pervasive.
And not only do the adults pursue it, the actual, the small people.
Now, children are small people.
They're not mature.
They're small people, small meaning in size, and they're immature and they have not matured.
So the subculture that's been created around it sort of locks them in,
and there are no apologetics for it.
In other words, when, okay, you mentioned the kid care, right?
There's, you know, or the kid's meal or, you know, all these things that they have,
to accommodate this subculture known as the kid's culture, right?
When does, when, where do you delineate when they're no longer a kid?
Isn't there a point where they reach adolescence or prior to adolescence
where they no longer want to partake in that subculture?
And there's a strange, like, removal from one now to the next culture, you know, to being an adolescent?
Commonly pronouncing, I'm not a kid anymore, you know?
You never were a kid, hopefully, yeah.
Well, yeah, but that's the thing.
Meaning to them, yeah.
Yeah, because for one to grow from being a kid, what would you grow into, a goat?
Precisely.
Now, from a spiritual perspective, you know, mankind is compared to a sheep,
and then a goat, and then a dog, and then a pig.
And they each have their qualities when they come to interacting with their environment.
And so when you hear the term sheeple, it's not really, a sheeple is a misnomer.
It's more of a goat people, because a goat will eat anything, you see.
It doesn't roll off the tongue as well, though.
No, it doesn't, yeah.
Now, the sheep, you know, since it's all external input, yes, there's a signal to follow.
But, yeah, so this, going back to the subject matter, the kids' culture is a phenomenon that is twisted
and pretty bizarre and just downright bizarre.
Let's look at the fairy tales, the little kids' nursery rhymes and stories which were penned by,
you know, let's say certain secret societies.
If you look at, I can't even name any off the top of my head, maybe you can.
The kids' nursery rhymes and stories, you know, they're all very macabre.
Yeah, I wasn't treated to too many of them, but I got to tell you that when I started to look at them
as I became a parent, I found, well, these things are actually replete with cannibalism and murder
and, you know, vicious animal attacks and, you know, so on and so forth.
Kind of really no better than, you know, people, sometimes they have the, you know,
the Children's Protection Council on television or whatever it is they call it in your particular locality.
You know, they're very, very worried about, you know, violence on television and what have you.
But it's perfectly okay to have, you know, a crazy old woman stuffing Hansel and Gretel into an oven if she can.
And then the victory in the story is actually that they've burned a human being alive instead.
You know, just for example.
Yeah, no, go ahead.
I mean, because this is the reason I'm glad you gave some examples because all that stuff is,
I've tried to, you know, wipe the hard drive on, so to speak.
It's just another addition to show how sick this kids subculture that's in society is.
Yeah, absolutely.
Across the board.
So if you want to continue on, you know, I asked the question regarding education,
and it's interesting that, you know, the topic is education.
Hopefully the listeners have gotten that by now.
That it's not, it doesn't necessarily have to start with the young.
It could also start with the mature and what they call an adult as well.
But we're grabbing the subject matter from the young because that is the first place one's mind goes
when we discuss the topic of education on a social level.
Well, of course.
And one other thing to consider is that long before you can yourself read a story,
at least when I was growing up, I didn't get very many stories read to me.
But I knew that other children had stories read to them,
and the truth is it was replete with that murder and mayhem just like I was talking about.
You know, consider that what, you know, the big bad wolf.
What does he do to grandma, you know?
Does anybody ever tell you?
I mean, that's a home invasion.
You know what I'm saying?
I mean, that's the popular term for it nowadays.
But, you know, stuff like that going on.
You know, other people are getting injured, broken into pieces, you name it.
And I'm talking about the very basic sort of common, you know, cultural, culturally acceptable,
I should say, fairy tales, so to speak, right?
What does it mean?
You know, somebody in the chat room brings up Ring Around the Rosie,
which has all sorts of interesting little things in it.
But, you know, what I'm talking about here is really that in and of itself is an education, though, isn't it?
And just to remind folks listening is that, in essence, mankind, men, women,
even the small men and women or boys and girls are not animals.
We are not animals in the spiritual sense.
I think we gave the analogy in episode one that if you had adopted a puppy or an adult dog
that had been raised from a puppy by a family of gorillas, you would not know that it was so.
It would still bark and run and do all the things a normal dog would do.
But if you had a very young child raised by a family of gorillas to adulthood
and you invited that adult to your house, guess what they would be acting like?
Gorillas.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So the idea that we are animals is a big misnomer.
This will be discovered in the future, that we require, meaning mankind, requires input,
a form of training to everything from walking to talking.
What else rhymes with ING like that?
All the way across the board.
And the concept of people still regarding that people can do what they want
or what they feel is right is abominable to the core.
This is why the society has reached the height of unlawfulness today.
And just as a reminder, things are a little bit worse today than they were yesterday,
but they're not as bad as they're going to be tomorrow.
What does that mean?
What is he saying?
Have you ever heard of the term the frog being boiled?
You have to do it very gradually, right?
If today was more worse than it is, the frog would jump out of the pot, you see,
and then you have to start all over again.
So tomorrow is going to be worse than today, just slightly, you see.
This is the outcome or this is what one should expect
if one can cast a quick snap judgment on is this a lawful or unlawful society.
And everything is unlawful and debased at this point.
So you can always expect today is a little bit worse than yesterday, just a little,
but not as bad as it's going to be tomorrow.
But it's not going to be so bad where you're going to jump out of the pot, you see.
And this ties in again with the subject matter of education on the input, right?
Because the frog requires heat input, you know,
so the heat is being turned up very gradually.
Right.
And incrementally, you know, this is the word that I choose to use all the time,
is that things are introduced in an incremental fashion.
And that means essentially that it's done, you know,
in a very small way to move things further and further down the road.
I mean, look at it this way.
If you were to place something on your, you know, lawn outside
and someone moved it, you know, a quarter of an inch each day,
you may not notice it for the first few days.
And then after a little while, you tend to see that something is amiss
and not quite sure what it is.
But by the time it gets 10, 20, 30 feet, you know, from its original placement,
you might take notice.
But then again, you might not.
Unless you catch them touching it to move it.
Right.
Unless you actually see the movement.
They're actually walking up and even just moving it a quarter.
This is what we're trying to discuss, how these things have been touched
and moved gradually.
And this is, again, for the seven people on the planet or maybe 500 or 1,000.
I know they're out there.
You know, scripturally, just to go back to that for a moment,
you know that there are 7,000 people for every generation on the planet
that are sort of less censored than others.
Only 7,000 that are kept in every generation.
And I'm being very sober and serious about that as being memorialized in Scripture.
Think about that.
That's still a very small percentage.
You know, you're not going to meet any of them, right,
if you believe that you might be part of that group.
So, okay, just to maybe continue, I have a question.
Okay.
What is one of the most, now I'll say it again,
what is one of the most degrading things one can do to another one,
another person or a man?
I'll say it again.
What is one of the most degrading things one can do to another?
Well, now, this evokes a lot.
Yeah, but this evokes a lot of thoughts.
Is deception the most degrading thing or is –
Well, listen to this then.
Let's carry on.
This is part of the stuff that we do here on Ocelli and the Greek.
And the reason we do the show is because no one else is saying these things
and they have to be said.
Right.
If you're the only one that knows that there's a hole in the dike
and it needs to be addressed and no one's doing it, guess what?
You're going to have to go out there and get wet, so we're getting wet.
Now, again, I'll say it one more time.
What is one of the most degrading things one can do to another?
Simple, grade them.
When you create a situation on the topic of education,
where learning is involved, once the issue of grades come up,
meaning 65 being failing and 100 being perfect or an A, a B, a C, a D,
an E for effort or an F meaning failed, right?
They don't even have an E in the grade, do they?
So what's interesting is when you have a group of people in a situation
where learning is to take place and the concept of grading is created,
what happens then is now you have that group being motivated by penalty.
I think we've mentioned a while back where you and I first started discussing
this on air is this society is motivated by penalty.
The person who is getting an A gets an A because he doesn't want a B, you see?
So when we have this concept of grading,
which we're commonly seen in agricultural items, right?
Double A, triple A, food grade, this or that grade, right?
Yeah, that's just what I was thinking is that generally you would grade
products quality, quality of a product like anything too.
It's not just a matter of agricultural.
I mean you could talk about the grade of any product,
a higher grade piece of furniture even.
But in the education system, when you walk into the room,
before you are educated and you're inspected,
and when you walk out of the room and you're inspected,
you pretty much look the same.
What makes someone different is what comes out of their mouth
or how their behavior has changed, right?
So what's interesting, again, to go back to the grading system,
it paralyzes one's ability to think critically because let's say they're telling you
the sky is purple.
Well, actually, let's not say that because it sometimes does.
Let's say the sky is just – and you can pick any color of the rainbow now
and the sky turns that color.
Let's use another analogy.
Yeah, right.
They tell you that up is down and down is up.
You're going to agree with that because you want the higher grade, right?
So you're going to do what's called regurgitation.
You're going to put in your – you're going to take in what they give you
and spit it back at them, right?
And you get the high grade.
Now what happens if you don't say what they want you to say?
Are you going to get an A?
No.
Are you going to get a B?
Maybe, maybe not.
And if you say enough of what they don't want you to say –
now we're not going on the conspiracy side here where what they're telling you is false.
We're not going to discuss that because that's obvious.
If you don't tell them what they want to hear, do you get a high grade or a low grade?
You get a low grade.
Well, you know, and I've got to tell you that only in one instance –
and, of course, I suffered – one, two, three, let me think about it –
13 years of what they call the education system, right?
Now, during those 13 years, there was only one instance
where I was able to change my grade based on the introduction of something else.
And I actually made a correction to that which had been in place for years before based on new information.
Now, was it your grade or was it a grade that they gave you?
There's a difference, right?
Ah, see, now that's true.
But it was a grade they gave me, and it improved when I brought in and made an argument.
I actually had to, you know, become – I don't want to use the word attorney.
Well, you could have pursued a career in politics then, Chuck.
Listen, let's not curse me that badly, okay?
No, actually, believe it or not, yeah, I agree because, you know,
who would want to lead a group of people as you find on the planet now?
But, yeah, here's the other point about the grading.
It paralyzes critical thinking.
Again, I think we mentioned that.
There is no more critical thinking.
But that was my point here is that actually I had thought critically and presented the new information
and showed them that, generally speaking, their assertion was incorrect,
which they had told me was incorrect, right?
So I was critically thinking, believing that they simply had something wrong.
But that's very rare, very unusual.
I said in 13 years, right, I had only found one instance where this occurred.
So all of the rest of the time, what I was instructed to do as a student, you know,
holding up air quotes again, as a student was to be a regurgitator of whatever input they provided, right?
So you're right.
That's why if you dig a little bit and you look in what's called the Department of Education, it's not that.
It's the Department of Public Instruction, clearly across the board.
Now, I've noticed I did a little bit of looking at this a couple of days ago when I thought about discussing this.
And they're all now changing it simply to Department of Education,
where over a decade ago it was just Department of Public Instruction, like a Simon Says kind of thing, you know,
imposed by force, by the way.
So it's very interesting on how it's very clear on what the agenda is from an institutional perspective.
And I think we've done enough bashing of institutions from a critical point of view
and from an objective point of view as being unlawful, debased,
and just not beneficial for those partaking in them, right, in any institution.
Well, I don't think we've quite reached that quota yet, sir.
But, you know, we can agree to disagree.
But I think more can be done.
It's okay.
More can be done, right.
But in a lot of the things, you know, there's a lot of discussion about how bad these things are
and are why they're so bad, you know, let's say with the education.
There's a lot of conspiratorial elements behind it.
And just to garner a little bit of that, if you go look up here in the States, the Secretary of Education,
you know, they don't go back prior to 1981.
You can't find who was Secretary of Education prior to 1981.
I wonder what they're hiding.
And then you will not find any such department that existed before 1870 or so when the War of the States,
which was the federal versus the states, which a peace treaty was still never signed.
So that war is still going on, by the way.
It was known as the Civil War in the U.S.
This was when they instated this type of public instruction because the last thing you want is anyone being belligerent.
So it's a very interesting, let's say, esoteric political commentary that could be made on the system
that's in place here in the states based on that history.
And I know we said that.
It's a mouthful pretty quickly.
Yes, in 1871, things were reorganized.
And also, if you look, you will not find who is Secretary of Department of Education
or public instruction in the states prior to 1981.
You will not find that anywhere.
So it's very interesting how that's been structured.
This is to satisfy the conspiracy buffs.
There's much work that can be done on that.
But like I said, I would not advise it because I gave up on this.
I tend to keep myself up to date on many topics,
but I really gave up on the education system over a decade ago because it was clearly dead and buried then.
So anything you add on top now is just basically flowers at a grave.
They're not worth discussing.
But discussing the concept of education is something that I believe should be discussed
because we're going to bring and are hopefully bringing points that are not being discussed
that could be included in any other discussion regarding the topic.
So, again, just to cap this one off,
what is one of the most degrading things one can do to another person, let's say, or man or woman, is to grade them.
The whole concept of an IQ test,
how stupid do you have to be to rely on someone else to tell you how smart you are?
Just pause for a second.
Let me say that again.
How stupid do you have to be to rely on someone else to tell you how smart you are or how intelligent you are?
Think about that.
That is just absurd.
You see?
And the IQ test, by the way, is another form of grading, isn't it?
Absolutely.
And the alleged intelligence quotient, I always found that really fascinating anyway
because it is merely a test that they provided that shows what your level of acclimation is to certain levels of communication.
But it doesn't really encompass a lot.
And you can have a savant who can crunch 16 digits of numbers in their mind that wouldn't pass at all.
They would be listed as below room temperature on their score.
Right.
But could crunch, can do 16-digit division in their mind.
So everyone here, meaning the planet, has a particular skill that they are prone to,
naturally, let's use that term in quotes, that needs to be pursued.
Since we just brought up the concept of things being degraded and what is very degrading, which is grading,
is how many times do you hear of job, get a job, or the jobs report?
There shouldn't be any jobs.
No one should ever be encouraged to get a job.
The term job started with the Industrial Revolution when you worked in a factory.
The item you were working on was called the job.
Like a job shopper or that's still used in machining today.
And when the machinists, these factories, whether the technology was unstable or they went out of business or whatever,
you had a lot of people relying on their livelihood working there.
So then when these companies or factories closed, you had a lot of people out of work.
So they were always promised jobs.
Oh, yeah, I like that.
That means I have a job to do, meaning it's a specific task in the industrial situation.
That is one of the worst things that can be promoted as being significant, the concept of jobs.
And you see that in society, right?
How many times do you hear it in the mainstream or alternative media?
Oh, the jobs, the jobs, the jobs.
Forget about the freaking jobs.
There shouldn't be any.
People should not be promoted to have jobs.
They should be promoted to find out what they are good at doing.
What are they naturally inclined to?
And those around them, whether it's institutional, familial, friendly or social,
should support them by providing them all of the skills and knowledge that's been memorialized through time
to help them not reinvent the wheel in that subject matter,
and then pursue that endeavor or that desire or that natural skill.
And you will find that there will be a greater diversity.
You know, I was having a discussion, I think, off air about the, well, what is it called?
The affirmative action, and a lot of people use that.
They said, well, you know, they wanted to give, you know,
if you're a government contract corporation or government, you have to hire a certain amount of minorities,
which, by the way, minority has nothing to do with your ethnicity or color of your skin.
It has to do with whether you're competent or incompetent.
So people, and that's why when you read in the ancient text, people will take the curse upon them.
How many people of color do you hear calling themselves a minority?
It has nothing to do with the color of your skin or your ethnicity.
It has to do with whether you are competent or not.
That's why in law, for example, you cannot really contract with a minor, right?
And if a minor signs a contract, that contract is null and void.
So this is just really a strange reality here.
But the affirmative action idea was that you had a certain almost incestuous relationship in industry
and design in the country with the WASPI sort, the white Anglo-Saxon Protestant,
that they noticed that it was choking off and there wasn't enough of diversity of thought.
And because if people that have been in the military or in corporations,
if you are not, if you are in the States or in the Western world and you are not white,
you are looked down upon.
There's a very strong prejudice against non-whites in the Western world in industry.
I know this sounds kind of like, why is he saying this?
Well, I'm saying it because it's true.
And from a certain sense, it was almost demanded that people that are not WASPI,
white Anglo-Saxon Protestant, you know, that were brought into industry
because of the level of incestuous thinking that was going on.
And just to liven it up, because people from different parts of the world,
different ethnicities have a certain diversity in their tradition and culture
that they can bring to the situation in industry.
And this is why you have affirmative action.
It has nothing to do with helping out black people or Latinos because they're unfortunate or disfortunate.
That is ridiculous.
And this is still being used today, by the way.
And this has never been said before, I think, on air.
That's why we're saying it.
Yeah, I've certainly never heard it.
And, of course, when you talk about not only contracting with a minor is a problem,
but once again, to hit that point home, things which are considered minor are lesser.
That is really a qualitative, you know, a minor incident.
It's not that big of a deal.
It wasn't extremely significant.
So there's nothing that they could do that ever would be.
Yeah, it's kind of a mental branding.
Right, so it becomes a mental form of grading.
You have automatically been decidedly placed in a lesser category.
Yes.
And that's the way it is.
It's actually got nothing to do with the numeric value of the alleged race that you belong to.
Or headcount, because I think what half of the states right now are nonwhite.
Well, how are they a minority?
This is absurd.
And if you read in Scripture, it says that the people will take the curses upon themselves.
How many times, again, have you run into a person who was not white and says, I'm a minority?
I'm like, why are you saying that?
The headcount doesn't show that, number one.
And number two, minor means incompetent.
Stop saying that.
You know, and this is, again, this is not my opinion.
This is objective.
In other words, you ever see the Star Treks where they land on the planet and then, you know,
Captain Kirk feels so sorry for the poor bastards down there.
I'd hate to say it that way, that he wants to make it better for them.
But they have this thing where they, what's the, the Federation cannot interfere with the change of any culture,
the prime directive.
They're called the prime directive, yes.
Right.
Okay.
Well, screw the prime directive, because what needs to be said needs to be said.
Don't expect change, by the way.
You have to know what the future is going to bring.
So, but these things need to be said.
So, you know, the minorities are actually putting a curse on themselves
and saying that they're minorities because they're incompetent and they don't know it.
And it's a curse to actually relate oneself to being incompetent through your entire life,
just as if you're calling young men and women baby goats.
Again, what does it matter?
You know what I mean.
Yeah, well, you know, do I?
Well, that's why we're saying what we're saying.
So, yeah.
Oh, right.
That's why I always appreciated the kind of odd subcultural phenomenon of taking negative words
and turning them into positive words that people did on their own.
They weren't programmed to do so, but they would adapt to it rather quickly.
I mean, how many times have you heard somebody call their good friend, well, you know, a bastard, let's just say,
which is a generally negative term, right?
But actually, you know, if anyone admits to having a birth certificate, they're legally in that title anyway.
But anyway, I'm just going to say that for now.
Right.
But I was just pointing out that the convolution of the meaning of the word is consistent.
It is without any sort of ebb to the flow, it seems, incrementally introduced into the language as a constant.
OK.
So when you look at the grades and somebody commented on the fact that you'd be in first grade, second grade, third grade.
Well, see, to me, that is not degrading the children directly because those labels are applied to the education itself.
And these are levels of the education.
And that is something that one could grade.
You know, you could grade the.
But see, that's different than grading, being attached to individuals.
That's a little different, I think.
I don't know how you feel about it, but somebody did comment about it in the chat room.
So I figured.
Well, I tend to comment on these things without any feeling, because if you know one is to put feelings into it, you know,
you might want to get up on the roof and scream sometimes, you know what I mean?
Every day.
And then you really get in trouble.
You know, again, if you speak to any of the authorities, whether they're in the legal society or what they call law enforcement,
it knows nothing about law or anyone else like that.
They tell you you have to be just like everyone else.
Right. Any any of the institutionalized authorities, because they're institutionalized as well,
is always promoting and almost demanding privately.
They don't say this on in the public media that they provide, because that would that would really rain a shitstorm down on them.
But in privately or one on one, all of these institutionalized authorities want what they do tell you.
If you voice any anything that's different than what is, let's say, presented, they say you have to be like everyone else.
I've heard this several times said to myself and to others that have been in presence of by institutionalized authorities,
whether they are in the medical society, the legal society and so on.
They do insist that the if you are a subject within the social network, that you are just like everyone else.
And and when you ask to find that they can't, you see.
So this is where, you know, the the grading comes in.
If everyone is supposed to be just like everyone else.
Why is there a grading system? Right.
There should be conformity and nonconformity. And that's about it, it seems to me.
Because maybe you're being graded on how well you have been homogenized or just like everyone else.
It's very contrary to what is natural. Right.
Because it's completely debased. You know, this is where the next point comes in.
And it's twelve thousand hours, question mark. Yeah. Yeah.
Folks, twelve thousand hours. Let's see. What can one do in twelve thousand hours?
Let's see. By the wind up toy, there are twenty four hours in the day.
Let's say most people are cognizant about about two thirds of that and are asleep, unconscious for the other third.
Right. Twelve thousand hours. Does that sound like a little bit or a lot of bit of time?
I think it sounds like a lot of bit of time. What do you think, Chuck?
Sounds like a fairly significant chunk of time. Yes.
Why do I why do I bring up the twelve thousand hours?
Because there's a concept of K through 12 or kindergarten, which is the year preschool before first grade, all the way to 12th grade.
And by the way, college is considered 13, 14, 15 and 16 for bachelor and master, 17, 18th grade.
PhD is a 20th grade. They still delineate those as grades, by the way, with numbers.
But people don't discuss that. You'll see it on government forms and things like that.
But K through 12, which would be graduating from high school, you get a thousand hours every year.
Now, I've had people disagree with me on this.
And then they go back and they look at look at it, do the research and like, holy crap, it is twelve thousand hours.
It's a thousand hours, folks. When you send the child to school in the morning and to the afternoon and you have the weekends off,
according to the pope's schedule and you have summertime breaks and all the other holidays.
It's it works out to a thousand hours a year, roughly between eight hundred and fifty to nine hundred and fifty in most places.
But on average, it's about a thousand hours. Well, let's quickly do the math.
Generally speaking, there are one hundred and eighty school days in the American curriculum.
OK, and the average school day is what? Six to seven hours.
Let's go with the smaller number and say six. So we have.
Well, right there, it's more than I see more than a thousand because obviously one hundred and eighty.
You've got one thousand and eighty hours actually right there.
You know, we don't want to you know, we want to be we don't want to exaggerate.
We want to stay as close to the reality here because we're trying to be objective.
But thanks for doing the math. No, I'm just I want to break it down for people so that they don't go.
Well, that just sounds like a lot of time. But no, I've just told you that one thousand and eighty hours is what is prescribed.
Right. For one school year. So do that twelve times.
And guess what? Your number is exactly actually a lowball figure because you could easily add another eight hundred to it.
And we didn't even talk about kindergarten, actually.
Right. So that in the one in the I didn't include it in my twelve.
Yeah, I just went well. There's actually thirteen.
So add another one and you have just now graduated into more than the twelve.
So actually you're you're you're giving a an approximation that's a little low.
Yeah. And then you have the mockery and plunder known as university.
Right. It's a mockery and plunder, meaning they're mocking you because if you you're so dumb to want to continue more,
we're going to plunder you now, as in financially, you're going to add another four years to that.
Right. Minimally, I get a B.S. degree. Right.
It would be yes. Have you heard that? B.A.B.S. I like the B.S. That's my favorite.
The B.S. is great. Yes. If you go to university, all you get is a B.S. degree.
Get it anyway. Absolutely. Yes. Yeah. And it's unfortunate.
Yeah. In other words, the reason I'm saying this on the show is because if I get back up on the starship and
this is what I'm going to be telling them, people. So, yeah, if you've gone to university or college, you have a B.S. degree.
Don't bother with the other prefixes or suffixes. It's all B.S.
But and you're also being mocked. That's why they're making the price so high.
And the P.H.D., the post hole diggers, that's even more bizarre.
I have no comment on that because then we're going to have to get emotional and I'm going to have to take this whole system up on the roof and start screaming.
So, well, but you know what? Not just yet.
Great, because, you know, we're almost out of time on the first hour and we don't want to start screaming so early on in the show.
You know, but the thing is, it is one of those considerations.
We did discuss this kind of before when we talked about the universities and instructional institutions and one being on one side of the street, the other.
But there is more to come on the education system.
I promise you here on Episode 15 of Ocelli in the Greek on American Freedom Radio.
Stick around for the next hour. It's going to go further.
What is American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us with free education.
Well, that's obviously effective. But apart from reversing the dumbing down of America.
All the information they provide is free.
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from?
Exploiting commonplace corruption.
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice.
Bringing light to important information nobody else does.
They never censor, hang up or cut off their guests.
Well, that's no fun, is it?
They created a fantastic alternative media source during an era of bad, manipulative and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shows and scum.
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information, free podium for broadcast activists to speak from,
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable people without a voice,
bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media source in a sea of bad, manipulative mainstream and alternative media shows and scum.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotic.
Freedom.
Oh, yes, I like it very much.
Radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth?
And none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant.
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC.
Is non-GMO.
And is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein, and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand-new detox formulations of micro plant powders.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care.
Anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate.
Invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
Tell the truth, don't be bullshitting people.
Is it enough bullshit as it is?
In fact, there's just enough.
Did you know that?
There's just enough bullshit to hold things together in this country.
Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation.
Where would we be without our safe, familiar, American bullshit?
Land of the free.
Home of the brave.
The American dream.
All men are equal.
Justice is blind.
The press is free.
Your vote counts.
Business is honest.
The good guys win.
The police are on your side.
God is watching you.
Your standard of living will never decline.
And everything is going to be just fine.
The official national bullshit story.
I call it the American Okie Doke.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver
quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views
and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
the only broadcast information.
And so the second hour begins here on Ocelli and the Greek,
episode 15 on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
We were discussing a great many things in a fashion
that you will not hear elsewhere that I promise you,
but, you know, it is one of those subjects that does come up
in a great many other places, often with people hand-wringing,
you know, the lamentation of the speaker about the state of affairs,
let's just say, in the alleged education system.
You know, that which is systematic is questionable to begin with,
but anyway, onward and upward we go.
The interesting thing that we sort of left off with was the concept
that there is more than 12,000 hours invested into what they might call
the primary schooling in, well, in America or what once was America anyway.
You know, and the fact is that we did the math.
We broke it down for you right here and explained to you that
that is not an unrealistic number.
That is the truth of the number that one gives up their time,
according to that wind-up toy or nowadays the digital representation thereof.
You know, it is the way it is.
And, of course, we covered a great many other things,
and you need to go to the archive if you missed it.
Yeah, but hold on, Chuck.
The investment part is interesting because that's – is it really an investment
or are you told that if you don't do it, you won't be able to get a job,
so you're being motivated by penalty?
And on the other side, are the children put through 12,000 hours
because of threats, duress, and coercion,
or are they voluntarily, joyfully running to these institutions?
Well, that is the other thing.
Threats, duress, and coercion.
Well, yeah, threats, duress, and coercion, yes, sir, because I'll tell you what.
If you don't have your children enrolled in schools in most localities in this, again, country,
guess what?
They will not only forcibly come and get the child,
but, hey, they might actually find you in prison,
penalize you personally as the parent of the kid.
And, of course, we covered that term in the first hour and what's wrong with that.
But, yeah.
I think we're going to have to use that term to explain what's going on.
But, yeah, threats, duress, and coercion of 12,000.
That's one hell of a sentence.
Should we say that?
It's a sentencing, isn't it?
Yeah, I've heard it described as the prison rape culture, which is another idea
because what they encourage children to do indirectly or asymmetrically,
the feeling, the groping, the pranks, once they get out and become adults
and they do that in the, let's say, open social order of things,
they get arrested for doing that, right?
And that feeds the prison system because, remember, the prison system is for profit.
And if anyone ever tells you that the prisons require funding or taxpayer dollars,
you've got to laugh when you hear taxpayer dollars.
Anyone who ever says that is a moron with a capital R.
That's your quick label.
I've got to make stickers.
You know how they used to have before bar codes the sticker machine?
Yeah, anyone who says taxpayer dollar gets the moron on the forehead,
and it's got to be indelible.
It's got to stick.
But prisons run off of the account that is issued to everyone through the treasury,
known as the Social Security Number.
That's not a conspiracy theory.
If you go look up the recent labor laws where you have to prove you're eligible for working in the U.S.,
go read the first few paragraphs,
and they do state pretty clearly that the Social Security is an account.
So what they're doing in the prison system is bonding you, holding you a surety,
and they're making, you know, besides, you know,
if you're locked up in a prison or a jail overnight,
that institution gets $300 per night from the feds, you know,
and where do the feds get it?
From the treasury, from the Social Security.
So anyway, yeah, so yeah, I just thought I'd throw it in because you brought up the concept of prison rape culture.
The pranks and the misdemeanor or bad behavior that's promoted asymmetrically
or indirectly in the schoolyards or in the schools now becomes, let's say,
a taxable offense as an adult, does it not?
Well, right, and the other thing is that when you are, well, a little bit too rambunctious,
they send you to a wonderful finishing school.
There are various institutions that are meant to be, you know, for juvenile detention,
and I know this personally.
The fact is that you are still in school there.
The same type of behavior is now, well, let's just say it's more structured
than it is in the other places where there's sort of a loose acquiescence to this type of behavior.
There is a loose encouragement there, but it's actually extremely, well, organized, codified,
when you go into juvenile detention or that system.
That's why they used to have reform schools and things like that.
I don't know if those exist anymore.
Probably, but on the surface they seem very disciplinary,
but there's another subculture that's even more drastic in that case, I guess.
Right.
In other words, the truth about those institutions is that you are encouraged more to not get caught.
That's really what the overall lesson is.
It's not about behaving properly or being educated to be a more productive member of society
or anything like that.
None of those highfalutin aspects are taught to you there.
Really, truthfully, what you're taught is to keep things more undercover
and to conduct your business in a more obsequious sort of fashion
so that you can avoid prosecution in the future.
That's really what juvenile detention is like, and even there you're still schooled.
Exactly.
Whether that adds or takes away from the 12,000 hours within that point of one's life,
you're still going to be coerced into that form of, quote-unquote, education.
We brought up the prison rape culture concept.
Two of the most important things in society that are life and death matters,
whether it's immediate or gradual, is understanding of the laws of the country,
whether they're lawful or unlawful, the codes and statutes,
and then understanding the money system.
Because if you don't have any money and no one engages in commerce
and you're not growing your own sustenance and making your own clothing and your own shelter,
you're probably going to die, right?
So the legal system also, the legal society, is life and death matters as well.
Now, if you ever look into how much information has been memorialized
about the unlawful private credit system and the unlawful legal society,
there are volumes about that society that have been memorialized within their own texts
and they're readily available by anyone, especially to the professionals that work in those fields.
How much out of those 12,000 hours are dedicated to what the credit system is
and what the legal society is?
Zero.
Five minutes, an hour.
And the reason I'm saying this is because it would behoove anyone to go look at –
I'm not going to harp on this one institution even though they deserve it.
Go to one of these Ivy League universities that are promoted as being one of the better law schools
and go to their website and then look up the curriculum for being an attorney.
Remember, an attorney is not a lawyer.
And anyone who can't discern the two is, well, you know what, I won't say it again.
An attorney is not a lawyer, by the way.
A lawyer is someone schooled in the law like a carpenter is schooled with working with wood, let's say.
An attorney would be like a carpenter looking at you saying,
listen, I cut this board three times and I wonder why it's still too short.
Right.
An attorney has nothing to do with law, never did, never will.
And none of them know any law.
And here's another concept.
You've heard of something called a Supreme Court?
Sure.
Now, in order to have a Supreme Court, don't you need a supreme judge?
Oops, oops, oops.
Let's not go down that road.
So let's get away from that mess.
Now, go back to the life and death matters, the money, right, the juice, right, and the legal society.
Those are the main aspects of society that are actually life and death matters, right,
or extreme quality, they have an extreme bearing on one's quality of life.
How much of that, of those two societies, the money bearing society and the legal society,
is actually taught within 12,000 hours to prepare them as being functional members of society
or are you being prepared to be basically prey to that?
Well, that is an interesting thought and I'll tell you something.
Once again, back to the incremental concept we were talking about earlier, the boiling frog,
which you denoted quite well.
Here's the thing about that.
I think that at one time there were minor hints about the legal system
and possibly the monetary system as well.
And truthfully, to observe what is being taught to my older children now,
in contrast to what was taught to me, I got to tell you, they have removed,
they have sanitized every single element that I thought gave me some sort of hint,
although much later I learned exactly how little I really knew about the way these things function.
But there was at least an elemental kind of, you know, it didn't explain to me how to work with wood.
It didn't tell me if I wanted to be a carpenter how to build a shelf or anything like that.
But at the very least, it told me there were trees.
Nowadays, they don't even explain to them that there might be a forest anywhere.
And even the ones with the higher education, by the way,
whenever you hear the term higher, it means you're going lower.
They're the type of carpenters that again have cut the board twice or three times
and they look at you and they're wondering why it's too short because there's nothing there.
It's completely debased.
And again, to go back to any of these Ivy League institutions, go look at their law curriculum.
And is there anything taught about law? None, nothing.
And this can be evidenced very simply.
The same with the medical institutions.
They were horrible at this point.
And this is why the report has to be written in a certain way that when it's returned objectively,
one would have to ask, you know, I thought this was supposed to be an objective commentary.
Well, yes, it is.
But the level of criminality is so high that the language has to change now.
The language has to be more harsh, you see.
And it's still objective, folks.
Now, 12,000 hours.
Now, from the concept of, yes, that's a lot of time to the concept of, well, it's not enough.
I need to do more.
Let's look at it qualitatively.
You know, I think we just mentioned off air.
It's like ask anyone who's gone through the 12,000 hours.
What did you learn in school?
What do they say?
Well, you know, as someone who is actually in possession of what they call a high school diploma, right,
I'll tell you this, and I did not go beyond that.
So, thankfully, I did not receive further injury.
But the thing is, I got to tell you that, honestly, I knew how to read before I went into school.
My father made sure of that so that I was able to read a newspaper before I ever set foot in the kindergarten, right.
Basic math skills were taught to me, and some of those things were elaborated upon just a bit in school.
Outside of that, there was history, which was granted to me, most of which is either fictitious or kind of pointlessly imparted to me.
And when we go beyond that, well, not much until I got into, well, hold on.
Let me be fair.
I did learn how to make a cheesecake in home economics.
And that's what you've got to show for 12,000 hours.
Ask anyone what they have to show for 12,000 hours.
You've got to wonder.
Oh, I know, but I was trying to be as positive about the experience as I could be.
And I'm coming around saying, wait a second, guys.
That's an enormous waste of time in one's formative years.
Although I did learn how to fight some and did also learn how to protect my belongings so that they wouldn't be stolen.
Oh, wait a minute.
Yeah.
Prison rape culture stuff.
That that kind of stuff was imparted to me, not by the curriculum or the alleged teachers.
Right.
But I did learn it.
And I remember this this concept here.
This is we're discussing of education is across the world.
Don't don't think, oh, well, this country, they've got better education.
Look at the system.
Are they grading?
Right.
Do they have their these young children in for thousands of hours and years?
You know, you know, this is not being done properly.
And we're going to further on down the line here, discuss about how much education is really required.
And believe it or not, it's only a few hundred hours to be functional.
You know, and what I mean, a few hundred hours of education would be basically the what's needed to exist in commerce.
You know, mathematics.
Now, you know, and literacy, you know, not just being functionally literate, meaning knowing what the letters and how to sound a word are,
a word out is, but how to comprehend reading with comprehension.
You see, that's it's only a few hundred hours that's required and at different stages of development.
You see, but why is it 12?
Again, the 12000 hours is phenomenal on how let's say the 12000 hours that let's say give that as a given and it's set as such.
There's a lot that can be done in that amount of time.
And when you contrast that with the simple question of someone who's gone through that,
what did you learn in 12000 hours and the blank stare that you get?
And then you have this the Stockholm syndrome thing, you know, where you, you know, I don't have to explain what that is.
Look it up if you don't know where, you know, the person identifies with their captors.
Right. And how necessary it was. Right.
You get this blank stare combined with the Stockholm syndrome combined with people who don't say what they mean, mean what they say.
You know, this is what's happening. This is not, you know, 12000 hours is just a long time.
Now. Now, let's just digress for a second.
How much media, how much, quote unquote, free speech is there and who and whether it's mainstream or alternative.
Now, hold on a second. How come we're not hearing this anywhere else?
How come no one's saying these things? It's just the point of absurdity.
No one has brought up any of the points that we brought up tonight anywhere.
And it's fascinating. Yeah. Yeah. I haven't heard it anywhere. Absolutely not.
Like I said, and like I started to say at the beginning that, you know, yeah, I realize, you know, you'll find this kind of not extremely relevant.
But fact is, people will argue over the common core, over the social training that's being introduced in there.
They'll argue about which is correct to have in there. Should prayer be allowed in the school?
No, no. But I'm just saying, hold on. The reason why the prayer thing, this is this.
Be clear on this, because I'd like to do a show on cliche.
All of your ancient texts state that when you pray, you should do it in private by yourself.
Right. So. So this moral high ground about this, this Judeo-Christian ethic or even Islam, which means to be submissive, by the way, all this stuff is just paganism.
It's not, you know, paganism could go both ways.
You know, but I'm saying in a negative sense here, it's just worthless.
It's and whoever you're praying to is not listening, by the way.
So anyway. And if you're if they are, stop, because the more it seems like these people pray, the worse things are getting.
Maybe they get right. Yeah. So stop that. You know, stop what you're doing, because if what you're doing is making things worse, guess what?
You should maybe stop what you should examine, that the two court, the correlation of those two functions.
But right. And like I said, the other ridiculous arguments about, you know, should there be a pledge of allegiance in the school?
Hold on. A pledge of allegiance is to the flag.
Yes. It's not to the country or the government or any morality or anyone.
It's to a flag. Oh, I know. And it says so right in the first line.
I pledge allegiance to the flag flag, not to the United States, not to the president, not to the culture, not to now a flag, folks.
Now, now get not enough. Figure this out. I'm going to stop for a moment.
A flag is a communication symbol. It's flown on ships and ports to communicate at a distance.
It's just a piece of cloth with a marking on it. In other words, it's a rabbit.
They've turned it in. This is the pagan. They've turned it into put your hand on the Bible.
Oh, that means something or a rabbit's foot or whatever. Folks, you're better than that.
Sorry. You know, there's nothing wrong with pledging an allegiance. Right.
It's a vow, isn't it? Oh, but to a flag. Come on, guys.
That was my point here is that, you know, you're aligning yourself with an inanimate object.
Which is a method it has. It is asinine. It is completely bizarre at this point.
Now, this is not one's opinion. There is no merit in this. It's basically tradition. It's basically culture.
Oh, wait a second. Even though it's the 11th month, weren't there a bunch of traditions and cultures that everyone just suffered?
Suffered meaning to willingly go through. Right. Right. What are those things based on?
Oh, gosh, man. It seems like everything is in line here, isn't it?
Starts to make a lot. The insane becomes quite a bit sensible all of a sudden when one examines the the situation.
Yeah. You know, back to the 12000 hours. Now, I'm just going to say this really short.
And we really cover your ears because look at the poor, how poor the character of those that are administering this education are.
I'm just going to say it once. I'll say it one more time. Why not?
Look at the character of the people that are administering education, all of the teachers and all that.
Look how poor their character is. And, yeah, you might like them, might be joyful or whatever.
But look at their character. Anyway, I'm going to get away from that for a moment because that could be really sticky issue.
They're very nice. Let's just say that. So wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
They're very nice. You don't just say that. Yeah. Look up what it means.
Because remember that we've always we're talking to the 12000 hours on the receiving end now. Right.
But in order for them to receive it, there has to be someone dishing it out. Look at the people that are dishing out your.
I don't think we can get in trouble for this, but the professors, the teachers, all the way from K through 12, all the way.
There's a certain ilk of character there in the person.
That's what I'm going to say. And you can grade the quality of that.
And let's just not look at art and in film how they grade the young school teachers.
There's a there's a good one in a film called Men in Black where they're showing the new inductee into the Institute,
to the MIB organization, who was an alien. He says, I always knew that she was an alien.
And they show like a school teacher, you know. Right. Yeah. You know, she's.
Yeah. So. Yeah. So you folks in the in that. And you got to really rethink.
Just keep doing what you're doing because you're in line with all the other crazy stuff going on this planet.
But we just have to say this because we're being objective, by the way, whenever we're going to report on the system in order.
It's being dished out by certain people. Right. So those people are, you know,
let's just assess that the character of those individuals as well as well.
If you assess the people in the legal society, in the medical society, just assess their character.
These people you really want to be around with outside of what they're saying they're doing as a profession.
You'll notice there's something wrong there as well. And yes, we've just indicted millions of people.
But so what? This is the truth, folks. Sorry. You know, and just the twelve thousand hours.
We're going to cover more about, let's say, what education or what would be if it's all external input and it's training.
And it's very important how things are memorialized and how we learn.
And it affects how we act, how we speak everything about us, because it's all external input versus the animal kingdom.
You know, there's something called public instruction. Right.
Because, you know, public used to be spelled with a K in some older documents and they switch it to a C, I guess.
But I don't know if it changed the meaning much. But you ever heard in private people, especially as very ghetto, like you don't know how to act.
Right. You've heard that the term like someone is rambunctious where if we go here, you have to act a certain way.
Or when you're out in public, act a certain way. That's that's acceptable from a certain social order point of view, which promotes harmony, for example.
Right. But there's a level of public instruction that is put in by the state, meaning whether it's corporate or not, you know, is irrelevant.
By the way, when we mentioned the state, what is relevant is whether it is lawful or unlawful.
Right. You see, that's why just to speak about the state for a second, because, you know, this is all a state function, by the way, education today, today in this present world.
There's absolutely no discussion on, let's say, now in the presidential races.
And I wonder why they're running for a race. You ever think about that? Don't criminals run?
But anyway, so the point is no one is discussing whether what they're doing is lawful or unlawful.
And that's why if you're an inventor or someone who wants to do things to endeavors that would be beneficial for society, you don't do well in a, quote, unquote, communist, socialist or democratic form of state.
You always do better in a monarchy. Why? Because there's too much in all these other types.
By the way, if you think there's any difference between any of those other things, there isn't.
It's just a flavor of a type of state where you have a monarchy.
There is no red tape. In other words, if you have a meeting with a king.
And he says, yes, do this. If anyone gets in the way of you bureaucratically after the king decrees it.
Their head is cut off. Yeah.
Now, if you have any other form of, quote, unquote, government other than a monarchy or a king where you have bureaucracy, red tape and all of this other stuff that we don't need to discuss because everyone else seems to be discussing it, missing the point, even though they're trying to discuss it.
Right. So. So, yeah. Now, the whole thing is, well, people say, well, kings are bad.
Well, because they were bad kings. We're not talking about, you know, whether they're good or bad.
That's subjective. Are they lawful or unlawful? Because if anyone paints in their mind for a second, that unlawful does things that are bad and lawful does things that are good.
You're critically wrong because very much so, because you can have a lawful form of society.
And what is called judgment and sentencing is very swift and harsh.
You see. Right, right. Like the old concept of, you know, cutting the hand off the thief, you know.
Yeah, but that's not lawful because and even when that when you hear about that now in the Middle East, that's that's like after the fifth time, by the way, you know, they do it.
And that's a cultural, traditional thing. But, you know, in law, you don't there's no prison or anything like that either.
Right. So, yeah, if you steal, you give back what you stole plus an amount.
So, right. And I always said and this is something that I used to say before I started having these conversations with you, that so long as there are prisons across this planet, we have a problem here.
Ecological problem. Yeah. You're going to have bad weather and toxicity and has nothing to do with what people think it is.
Yeah, but right. But prisons in and of themselves are counterproductive when it comes to having a better world.
And and people are shocked and stunned by that and think that I'm just, you know, hippie, dippy, liberal kind of idiot.
But prisons in a lawful society. That's how you know a society is unlawful.
Now, jail is different. Jail is where you arrest everyone until you sort out, you know, what has to be done, because sometimes, you know, you just can't let things go on.
You've got to stop a situation like a really bad bar room brawl.
Everyone goes into the wagon and behind bars overnight to sort out what happened.
And then the ones that are culpable or responsible are extracted from that group and the rest are let go.
See, but prison is comes from the ancient Eastern Hindu concept, ancient, where if you murdered someone or raped someone, it's OK.
You really it's fine that you did that because you're appeasing the god of rape or murder.
So now you have to go do penance in the cell. You have a debt to society.
It comes from ancient Hinduism. People are not aware of it. This is another discussion.
Maybe we'll tie that in with when we discuss cliches and things like that, how foolish they people are when they make statements like what came first, the chicken or the egg or biblical cliches.
You've heard there was a lot being brought up and people don't know anything about it and they don't want to know anything about it.
But that's why we're going to tell them on the Ocelli and the Greek shows.
Right. And it all gets back to public instruction, because here's the thing.
Prisons are supposed to be the solution to the criminal activity.
You know, build more prisons. Right. This is the way it's supposed to be.
You're supposed to deal with those who are acting in a unlawful fashion by putting them in a prison.
This is virtually a given. It's unlawful to do so.
And it's actually part of an ancient spiritual revival, the prison aspect.
But the concept of public instruction, there is a level of harmony that one expects when they are out in public, meaning out in the fairways, the streets, the marketplace.
There is something good about having well-behaved people, right, or things that are not offensive.
And things like, for example, if you're walking down a street in China, it's very common for someone to bump into you pretty hard and they don't apologize or say sorry.
They just keep going because everyone has an understanding that they have to get to where they're going.
And it's OK to bump people around or step on their foot.
Where in the Western culture, if someone gives you a hard knock with their shoulder on the sidewalk, you're like, that's like the precursor to a fight here if you don't apologize.
But that's normal in that culture. See, so the concept of public instruction is there are certain accepted traditions and standards in each culture which are almost necessary to learn.
Like, you know, when in Rome do as the Romans is a cliche about that. Right.
And that's that's a whole other story. If you want to talk about immigration, that's what that was based upon.
But the idea of public instruction can go both ways. Now it's gotten to the point where you have the 12000 hours where any victim, right, you are a victim.
If you've gone beyond the eighth grade, you probably have a good chance of being irreparably damaged, by the way.
Irreparably meaning you can't fix it now. You're you're really damaged goods beyond the eighth grade.
But 12000 hours, how much of that 12000 hours is actually dedicated to public instruction, like how to act, you know, in public to be, you know, to maintain harmony and peace?
Again, very little. Yeah, the only the only thing that you're ever taught is to keep your expressions at a certain noise level at certain times.
This promotes public harmony. If you're in, you know, different settings, it is more appropriate to, you know, say, scream and yell in a bar where there's loud things going on.
It's it's appropriate in that atmosphere. But if you're in a library, it's not a good thing to do.
Although there may be just as many people, not nowadays, but there may be just as many people in a place like that as in a bar, theoretically, you know.
So you're supposed to act harmonious with the atmosphere, things like that. So you are taught those concepts.
Yeah. And they give you the exception to freedom of speech, which is don't cry fire in a movie theater.
That is the footnote, right? To freedom of speech is an exception. Right.
Yeah. And a few things like that. But but really, there's not much public instruction.
There is this strange asymmetric mind control of just the blahs, you know, again, the 12000 hours.
Is that really. Well, let's say they call it voluntary.
But is it threat, duress and coercion? And is it motivation by penalty to do that?
Yes, absolutely. This is not subjective. This is an objective report.
We can watch we can put on our invisible suits and watch what happens to those or how they're dealt with that do not want to send their young offspring to 12000 hours.
Right. It's not very pretty. And something else here, just really quickly.
The thing that you brought up off the air was about the the school buses, which is another aspect of schooling.
And I thought it was really fascinating. I wonder if you want to take a minute and explain that real quick, because.
Sure. Tyler, that goes in with the public instruction, which is based on each culture.
You know, like in China, they have a different acceptance of what how people behave, let's say, in the Western world or India or other places, Japan.
What you'll notice in a lot of urban and suburban environments in the Western world is they have this weekly tradition or thing that they do,
where they take a trash bin out to the street to be picked up by a state institution.
Now, if you watch that behavior, they mimic that with their children.
They take their children to the curb just like the trash.
And for someone else to deal with them for those twelve thousand hours divided by how many days, how many hours, six to seven hours a day.
So the children, the children are literally put out to the curb just like the trash to be picked up or sent off for most of the day.
Right. And this is a harsh criticism, it sounds like, to the parental behavior of the people in the Western world and most of the world in the urban and suburban cultures.
But it's not a criticism. It's an objective point of view.
Just as one were to objectify that things that are very bright colored in natural environments that are creatures and sorts tend to be so because they're very toxic,
like a little of the most toxic frogs and insects are also very bright colored.
Right. Like those poison arrow frogs, they have like a bright orange piece on this kind of thing.
Yeah, go ahead.
I'm sorry. Another quick observation, though, just once again, harangue on the transportation aspect.
Some people might be thinking to themselves because they would live in a suburban area.
You know, well, gee, I see a lot of parents that actually carry their children to the school themselves.
But then again, those are generally in areas where there is also some section where people bring their own trash to dump themselves, too.
So realistically, it's the same thing.
It's the same thing. Yeah. And thank you, Chuck, because you can observe that this is not a criticism, but it is very similar.
Excuse me. Almost identical in behavior.
Right. I wasn't criticizing. I was merely, you know.
Yeah, but I meant this whole past few minutes is not a criticism on parents dumping their children in the garbage.
It's just it's just it's frighteningly and horrifically similar.
And the outcome is very similar. But anyway, I just want to mention the bright colored creatures are toxic.
Now, if you go into a grocery store, you'll find that the children, the food that is designed and packaged for children is also the most brightly colored and the most toxic in its ingredients.
So this is the analogy of taking out, you know, treating children as if like garbage is the same thing with what they're doing with food.
It's toxic. It is similar.
Similarly, as how things in the rainforest are toxic when they're multicolored and very brightly colored.
So you see a lot of these patterns from an objective point of view where it's not surprising to see, to see based on the similarities of the behavior,
to see what what the outcome will be.
Yeah, well, one can certainly draw a lot of parallels.
Again, if you take a step back and examine it objectively, you're exactly right.
The packaging on children's food, there's always lots of red.
There's always lots of other bright colors, but red is one of the most common colors.
And, you know, most things that are toxic in some way that are often encountered in nature.
I mean, for millennia, human beings generally thought anything colored red was toxic and poisonous, you know.
But take a look at the red food dyes that are introduced into the food also.
And there you go. I mean, that's it. And that's just one of the colors.
There's many. But yeah, brighter, brighter, you know, more vibrant colors on the packaging in the food, in the in the ingredients even are are prevalent.
And consequently, the most toxic ingredients are always in the foods that are marketed or geared towards children.
All right. Interesting, isn't it?
Contain the least amount of nutrition, tons of, you know, high-fructose corn syrup and all this other crap.
And like I said, again, the coloring, tons and tons of coloring agents used in the food dyes of one type or another.
Yeah, absolutely.
So you tie all these these similarities together and how let's just say and how much of a negative aspect humans are holding their offspring.
Now, this has nothing to do whether they realize it or not or believe it or not or know it or not.
That's the truth. Right.
And then and then once a year, once an alleged year, you also, you know, honor the sacrifice of the children to Molech on, you know, that that season that just passed.
And I've got more. Yep.
The revived Mullick. And then on top of that, hey, what about a birthday?
Yeah, well, let's eat the child. And you ever heard of the term to have your cake and eat it, too?
It's like saying I have my child and I can eat it, too.
Mm hmm. Exactly. Very sick society.
This is this is nothing to do whether you're alternative or mainstream or anything.
This is this goes towards everyone on the planet at this point, bar a very small group where statistically you can say everyone you're safe because in statistics, there's no 100 percent.
You there's always a small exception of, you know, unaccountable unaccountability, I should say.
So, you know, yeah, it's it's very it's pretty sad again.
But but the thing is, I believe that if we stick to the objective side, we're trying to objectify this.
We're giving examples and let's say facts about education that sorry, folks, it's true.
Well, right. And I'm sorry. I know on occasion I introduce I mean, I'm an emotional creature.
I just am. So I get a little emotional about some of this stuff.
I get disgusted and I mock certain things. But you know what?
I'm sorry. I do believe that that it's worthy of mockery and it's worthy of the occasional snide remark and joke.
And I think you can agree with me about that. Right.
Oh, yeah. But, you know, of course, because we're still, you know, we're we're emotional creatures, you know,
but which which I want to bring up the concept of the Elizabethan grammar school, which most people have probably never heard of.
Well, right. I was going to move to that next, because instantaneously when one uses a phrase like the Elizabethan grammar school,
what is evoked in one's mind? Well, to me, I think immediately of the monarchy in the UK, you know,
and I'm thinking must be having something to do with one of those queens named Elizabeth.
And what is grammar? And well, gee, we've already kind of demolished the concept of what people generally refer to as a school,
which more to me sounds like a reeducation camp, very similar to the prison or the military works in very much the same fashion.
But, hey, let's examine this Elizabethan grammar school.
Now, what that that is, is it's laid out very specifically for a reason there.
Why I stated the Elizabethan grammar school, because it's more than that.
It's a concept of what is acceptable for training for a young man or woman or young child.
And the reason I brought it up specifically as the Elizabethan grammar school is that anyone could do a little bit of research on it.
And what they will find that it was a type of schooling reserved for nobility.
Now, what is the difference between someone who is noble or wealthy and not?
You can you can someone who is not. You could just switch places with someone who is.
And now they are that. Right. It's just a matter of how much silver or what you have in your bank account or the bank account or the kind of house you live in.
But people are people. So this applies basically to the human psyche or the spirit of the mind.
What you'll find when you research the Elizabethan grammar school is you'll find that it was a curriculum or a schooling system that involves the young people between the ages of seven and 13.
Basically, six years of education or five plus years of education.
And guess what? When you study the concept of the historical Elizabethan grammar school,
what you will discover is you just heard me say the education was between the ages of seven and 13.
Well, guess what was recommended after 13 years old?
If you wanted more education at 13, you went to university.
So when you did three or four years of university, you had what's called a university or higher education by the age of I don't know, Chuck, what's 13 plus four?
Well, that was 17. So you already now you have had a university education by the age of 17.
Now, if anyone thinks that I'm making this stuff up or dreaming this stuff up,
you go do some research on some of the intellectual greats of the 19th century and look at their bio.
You know, when they were born and when they graduated or got their doctorate or whatever, and you do the math and you're like, holy crap.
This guy was 18. When he got his master's degree.
You know, yes. Yeah. So this was what does this go back to?
Let's go back to the concept of only a few hundred hours are necessary.
It could be as low as 250 hours are necessary to educate someone on how to be functional in mathematics and in language.
Now, you notice we didn't bring up history. Right. Because everything than anything that you hear about history is a lie.
It's a complete lie. Sorry. I know that goes into the realm of cliche.
If you just you know, if you want to look at, for example, let's just dive into this for a moment.
The religious concept. Right. You have the main bearer of religion.
Also that the. Secular historians call this the Christian era.
If you will find anything and everything that's in Christianity or Christendom,
what they tell you is they find no historical references of anything that's done there.
Right. You've heard this many times before. But if.
And also, guess what, folks, if you look at the main pinnacle of modern religion, which is called Christianity,
you will find nothing that they do in the biblical text either.
If you read it in context, nothing, zero, not one thing.
Now, if you take the biblical what's memorialized in the biblical texts.
And you do some historical analysis of it, you will find that it's all in history.
All of it. Interesting. Right.
But no one does any study again. So now that so that would be half.
If you wanted to study that or any other specific thing,
you would have to add that to the few hundred hours of basic training that I'm discussing here. Right.
So. But the beauty of that is that you can become an expert, a pretty regional expert locally in any subject in that you so
called desire to study in about a year or two.
And if you so called desire to study the subject that you are so inclined into,
you can be a world authority type expert in less than five years in any subject.
Anyone can do that, especially now with the advent of electronic media.
But the problem with the Internet or electronic media is it's subject to human input.
If no one inputs it online, it's not going to be there.
And let's sends the robots and all that other stuff. Right.
So you're going to have to go to things that have been memorialized before that.
But what one can be encouraged to consider is that what has been institutionalized in this modern,
as we've defined before, modern is what a society calls themselves right before they take the plunge and plunge.
You can decide what you think that means to you.
Is the institutions right now are all predatory.
And let's just say, how does a predator catch its prey in a trap?
Avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
If you know a trap is set somewhere and you go into it, well, guess what?
Is it still a trap? No, that's called a tragedy.
You know that another thing here.
We spin off a lot. Yeah.
Let's just do the spin off. If you guys can indulge me a little bit longer on my spin off here and rant.
The difference between an accident and a tragedy is an accident is not foreseen, but a tragedy is foreseen.
But you go through it anyway. That's why they call them the ancient Greek tragedies.
If you read any ancient Greek tragedy in the first act, they tell you exactly what's going to happen.
And it's not good. And all of the characters in the Greek tragedy go through with it anyway.
That's why when you hear about something, I think we mentioned how things are codified in the mainstream.
When something is dubbed a tragedy in the mainstream, guess what?
That implies foreknowledge. And they went through it anyway.
So anyway, I just want to throw that in there anyway.
So what else is a tragedy? Western and I guess the worldwide education system.
Because most people, most parents will say, yes, we know it's rubbish, but we went through it.
So we're going to put them through it, too.
That sounds like a Greek tragedy.
You know it's bad and you know nothing good will come of it, but you go with it anyway.
So let's just sum it up. It's a Greek tragedy.
And why the Greek tragedy? Because, you know, if you read like Medea in the first act,
they tell you she's going to kill herself and her children and everyone and they go through it.
It's no surprise. It's not like Alfred Hitchcock or something.
You know, there's no suspense. No need for foreshadowing.
This is what we're going to do. Yeah. So that's why you hear 9-11 tragedy.
This is a tragedy. Oh, boy. And no, this goes right over everyone's head.
That's why we keep saying or I like to say that avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
So so that is the just to harken back to let's wind the whole thing back.
Elizabethan grammar school. The reason we brought that up specifically,
as in Queen Elizabeth, as in grammar, as in school, do a little bit of research
and just gloss over the part where where it says it was for the nobility's children.
Well, what's the difference between a noble's children and your children?
Or if you're a noble, sorry, I mean, to offend you that way, but no offense.
But if you're not noble or noble, children are children. Right.
Just like the puppy being raised by gorillas or the man or the woman.
It doesn't matter if it's a noble's child being raised by gorillas.
If a noble's child is raised by gorillas, it will act like a gorilla as an adult.
So the Elizabethan grammar school is one way to show that education is between the ages of seven and 13 is more than adequate.
And university can be achieved before the age of majority. So there's something going on here.
That's why we we mentioned the education system is, you know, are you a victim of it?
You know, what does a victim mean? So, yeah.
And then the last item, as we've got about 10 minutes or so, is the parents role.
Now, what's interesting is if they're not going to dump, take their children out to the curb.
Right. And have them returned at the end of the day so they can go ahead and do their own job.
The parents role is throughout history was to have the children with them.
Now, remember, once we discussed how mankind is basically agricultural,
you had a lot more people working with the soil or with had dirt under their fingernails in the past.
Yes, they did. And they had the children with them and they still had within the two.
How simple would it be to have children working with you as an adult and still give them 200 hours of education?
So they are very well educated. Not very difficult. 200 hours.
That would be two hours a day for 100 days. Right.
And you want to do that past their formative years.
Really, any kind of formal training that anyone gets prior to, let's say, 10 years old or nine years old is forgotten
and is pretty not really memorialized by the individual.
Especially, for example, if, you know, there's a Rudolf Steiner discussed about,
and this is also goes back to the concept of the semiconductor material.
I'm paraphrasing here. It's not beneficial to teach a young person mathematics
and other things are going to require later on in life before they get their second set of teeth.
And from an ethereal point of view, it's interesting how semiconductors,
which are used in holding memory and computers and things, have this very similar chemical composition to bones and teeth.
Right. So it's interesting to postulate how a certain amount of memory is held in the bones and the teeth.
Very interesting because they're so similar in material.
If you look at the minerals that are in the bones and the minerals and metals that are in the bones and teeth
and that are in semiconductors are almost identical in many ways.
So this is this is a lot of insight by Rudolf Steiner.
And I just bring him up, you know, I'll just say he's a bit of a flake,
but he does say a lot of things that has memorialized a lot of things that are a lot of things that are worth looking into.
But the parents role also has been changed because you had this thing called child labor laws,
which were brought in in the 20th century.
They picked up like one very isolated situation,
which may or may not have existed and how children were not being treated right.
And use that to posture an entire system of policy that removed the children from the parents
accompaniment to be brought to the curb and taken away like T.R.A.S.H. for 12000 hours.
So what's right and you know what else is removed is the concept of what I used to call natural apprenticeship.
You were in the presence of your parents who made a living.
However, they did it. I mean, a lot of people point to the farmer or whatever, but it's kind of irrelevant.
If you were spending time with your parents and you were there at work with them, whatever it was they were doing,
you would generally, regardless of what it is you desired, begin to internalize what it is they're doing.
You know, smaller children mimic their parents if they continuously see them behave a certain way, et cetera, et cetera.
You've got skills and you and you have skills.
Now, you may choose to adopt a different set of skills later and in your further education develop another skill set.
But instantaneously, just by doing this or practicing things in this fashion,
allowing the children to accompany their parents and accommodating them in their place of work,
their place where they and I don't feel bad about using the word work either,
because work to me implies a whole lot more than a job.
You know, one who is an artist creates works as well.
The thing is that if they were there doing that, they would have a sort of skill set incumbent upon them just based on their exposure, right,
to the activities, actions and everything else that comes along with it.
Fundamental skills also.
You know, if there are fundamental things that everyone needs, like you need a haircut, you need food cooked, food prepared, machines fixed.
How many people have you – I've never met anyone who – maybe one person in, let's say, 10 years who knows how to properly sharpen a knife.
Okay, haircutting, cooking.
See, the whole thing about jobs, again, is if people were well-versed in some of these skills coupled with their personal passions,
there would be no end to prosperity really within a society.
Right. That's what I was getting at, is that, you know, all these kids – see, I used the word again –
but all of these kids who supposedly don't have any skills would not be in that condition
had the accompaniment with their parents in their place of labor, wherever that may be, be continued.
Correct.
And there's a level of basic skills.
I remember growing up, a very old man came to me and said – I was like 4, 5, 6 or so –
and he said, learn how to cut hair or cook, basic things that people need.
You'll always be able to take care of yourself if you have basic skills like that.
Yeah, and the old man was very correct.
I mean, that was back in a time when, you know, the elderly were not so damaged as they are today.
Correct.
And education was something that one experienced and was not instructed by.
Anyway, the end of the 15th episode of Ocelli and the Greek is here.
And, Greek, I thank you for all of these insights
and leave you to give a couple of seconds of what you want to say here at the end.
Well, till next time, folks. Thank you again.
Absolutely, guys. And stay tuned to American Freedom Radio.
More interesting stuff to come. See you next week.
American Freedom Radio
I'm telling you, you've got to support American Freedom Radio
because this government is getting out of hand.
Wall Street won't fall on my mummy.
The CIA are cutting into my drug running and my gun running.
Big pharma, psychotropic drugs are making my customers commit suicide
before my hitmen can even whack them.
And then they get depressed and get prescribed psychotropic drugs
and commit suicide too.
They're trying to become the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected.
I get unpaid taxes and if I can't find the money,
the IRS are going to take my jobs.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs
and that's to support American Freedom Radio. Capisce?
So what are you going to do?
You're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom. Freedom. American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat,
improves digestion,
and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana
and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder
is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367.
888-910-4367.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
What is the big deal about swearing to God in the first place?
Why does swearing to God mean you're going to tell the truth?
Wouldn't affect me.
If they said to me,
You swear to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth, so help me God,
I'd say, Yeah!
I'll tell you about as much truth as the people who wrote that Bible.
How do you like that?
Swearing to God is kid stuff.
Swearing to God doesn't mean anything.
Swearing on the Bible doesn't mean anything.
You know why?
Because Bible or no Bible, God or no God,
if it suits their purposes, people are going to lie in court.
The police do it all the time.
All the time.
Yes, they do.
It's part of their job to protect, to serve, and to commit perjury
whenever it supports the state's case.
Swearing on the Bible is just one more way of controlling people and keeping them in line,
and it's one more thing that holds us back as a species.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio
in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccines, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.