The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand, the sonic
entity known as the jelly and the berimic.
Supposedly, that was Halloween.
A lot of different speculation about that.
A lot of different possibilities.
The conglomeration, the composite of the celebration of what?
Well, virtually nothing after hell night.
Of course, you're tuned to the Ocelli and the Greek shoe.
Okay, the sonic entity, as that wonderful announcement tells you at the beginning of the show.
And it is on American freedom radio at American freedom radio dot com.
And I throw in these details just because I feel obligated to.
But now we're going to get into some details that are not necessarily an obligation.
Well, at least not for most of you.
How are you doing tonight, sir?
As good as can be still on this planet.
So I guess that's the best I could say.
You know, sowing Halloween.
Okay.
You know, I spent the day out, you know, when people talked about it and I said, well, how do you know it is that day?
And they all said, we don't.
We just do it.
So, I mean, you know, get me off this planet.
Right.
And, you know, how can you get anything done?
You know, the concept of driving a nail through a piece of wood is highly technical compared to the mentality that it takes to observe time.
It seems or just people are part of the the planet has become a human terrarium.
Well, that's what it is. Terrarium meaning a place in Earth, meaning the place Terra.
And it seems to be bizarre.
Going back to the saying that you need not visit an insane asylum to meet disordered spirits for the Earth is the insane asylum of the universe.
So with that minor rant or tone of a rant, if it's what they call here in the South American Southwest, it's still on the digital effect of a wind up toy.
It says ten thirty one, twenty fifteen. Right.
Nine oh three p.m. by the wind up toy.
And if they're calling today that passed, let's say Halloween being a so-called Saturday.
Well, last year, it's what they call life.
It was that so-called day was on what they call a Friday.
And on what they call 2016, that Halloween day is going to be on what they call a Monday.
So is Halloween a Friday, a Saturday or a Monday?
It's neither. It's none of that. Who makes up the stuff you see?
And no one is questioning it.
And that's what it comes down to. I mean, is it is it just the calendar is the warped yardstick or what?
You know, it's not me.
Yeah. Imagine you showed up at a construction site with last year's tape measure.
And now, you know, you're cutting the board twice and wondering why it's still too short, because they got a new tape measure this year.
You know, it's it's primary, because think about what actions do not involve timekeeping, appointment making, coordination of events.
They all do pretty much. And it's spurious.
It's it's about as fiat as fiat can get. And no one is paying attention.
And when I say no one, I mean, statistically, ninety nine point nine, nine, nine, nine, nine.
You want to throw in about seven or eight nines after the decimal point on this plant.
And that's and this is primary because, well, you know, it's a fine detail, isn't it?
Well, yes, it is. But who's controlling that fine detail?
Well, and see, that's what the problem is here, because, OK, I'll step back a second and I'll try this for a moment.
Here's the thing. If you are changing that yardstick, you're changing the days.
I mean, you would think that there is a mathematical equation that makes it make sense.
Right. It should be based on something if if it is not consistent in itself.
And yes, it is the thing used to govern virtually all activity.
I mean, think about it. What is it that anybody does?
That anybody occupies their lives with? I mean, when you point out that it's a fiat, a lot of people think about, you know,
well, the term is more openly used relating to currency, but currency represents something, right?
It represents something. Yes, it's fictitious. Yes, it's an imaginary marker, but.
Well, actually, then something. So what does the calendar represent?
Well, hold on to the currency. If you pull out a Federal Reserve note, you know what it actually is.
It's a canceled check on a closed account if you look at it.
But anyway, that's another discussion we should have.
You've got the serial numbers on the left, the serial numbers on the right, the president in the middle.
The left is the front of the check. The right is the back of the check.
Two signatures and issuing signature on one side, endorsement signature on the other.
We know the account is closed because the number is repeated.
And then where do those numbers come from? Birth certificates case closed.
It actually does represent something.
But you see, the reason I interjected that is because, well, again, Greek, that's too many details.
Really, it took less than 20 seconds to anyone, you know, pretty much in the Western world and speaking English,
if you say canceled check on a closed account, well, you really can't use that in commerce anymore.
But, you know, that's what you're doing.
So to go back, you know, throwing a quick detail like that to define it and move on to the next subject,
to go back to the previous subject about time, there's a concept where if once it was written, you know,
that, you know, you could look at the largest ship, it's controlled by the smallest rudder.
It's only a very fine element.
So, in other words, what would you need to put in place without anyone noticing to control a society?
And apparently it seems to be the calendar.
You know, it's not the only thing, but it is one thing.
And no one is making a point about it not being based on anything is because of the cosmic censorship we've discussed,
which goes in, you know, really big age chunks.
You know, it started thousands of years ago.
And, I mean, can you imagine, you know, being bred and raised in a society that has this particular system for thousands of years?
You'll never see it if it's been going on for thousands of years.
So, but the calendar...
Yeah, and that's the thing is when you examine the idea of the currency,
I always found it remarkable that the majority of the population never questioned its origin, its meaning,
what it actually represents, its functionality, nothing.
It's simply there as an accepted part of the reality.
But even more so and even more accurately is this idea of how it is we govern the activities in our lives.
You have a birth date, right?
You have a life expectancy.
You have your work, of course, is governed by this.
You make appointments by this alleged yardstick.
What do you not do?
Yeah, you get up in the morning and you go to bed with it.
Right.
With the wind-up toy, which is the mechanical aspect of it, yeah.
Right, which is to give you the incremental pieces of, well, the larger puzzle.
So really the wind-up toy is part of the equation also, isn't it?
It sure is.
And now the wind-up toy, known as the clock, can be divided in many ways.
You know, the 12-hour, 24-hour clock, right?
And, you know, Stalin had a 20-hour clock, 10 and 10.
There have been other variations.
Those 20-hour clocks fetch a premium on eBay from the Soviet era, I believe.
So it's a corporate nomenclature that's set up by a plantation-type environment.
Like, for example, if one studies history, when a property owner or a lord had slaves,
by default the slaves became the religion of the property owner, right?
You know, they followed that religion, right?
So the same thing is going on today.
It goes, you know, how big is the plantation?
You know, it's pretty big, right?
At this point.
So that's why when you look at what all the religions are doing,
none of them are doing anything that is in the books that they allegedly subscribe to,
or even keep time.
You know, you won't find January through December, Monday through Friday,
in the Bible or the Koran or the Rig Vedas or anywhere, right?
It doesn't exist.
But the thing here is that no one is paying any attention to this.
All right, so let's just be blunt for a minute.
How many times have you heard in the alternative media the world is going to end on this date,
or next year, or 2012, or Fukushima radiation, and all this crap?
Even going further back, you know, there was also Y2K, I was just going to say.
Yeah, and, you know, in the mid-19th century they figured the world was going to end,
and it didn't, so they invented the rupture.
I mean the rapture.
So, you know, the hernia rupture.
So here's the thing.
How can you take anything they're saying seriously?
Now remember, we have to be objective here.
There's a couple of ways of being objective, is when you're thrust into a new situation
and you have to see it with clear eyes where you don't have any interest.
That's why very often when I discuss privately things with people, I say,
hey, listen, man, you may not like what I'm saying, but you've got to remember,
you guys are on your own.
Whether you do well as a society or not is irrelevant to me, because you're too crazy.
You know, you're nuts.
You're all crazy.
So, you know, I'm just watching and just trying to reflect back to you what's going on.
And, again, the calendar is high weirdness.
Not that it's fiat.
We just showed Halloween takes place in three different days in three different years
and no one's paying any attention.
That's with everything, people's alleged birthdays and all their holidays, right?
Because it's a work schedule.
See, that shifting around doesn't bother them, but they have what's called
because they're set on the work week and the weekend.
See, they know that every Monday coming around they have to go to work until the weekend, right?
So it's this, yeah, so it's a plantation for sure, you know, that order of a work schedule.
So no one, you know, they're very sure that they get up and go to work on what they call a Monday,
but they're not too sure and don't care if their holidays and their, quote-unquote, other observed days
fall on different days of the week.
It just seems to pass them by like there's some level of insanity or amnesia taking place.
So we can discuss the nature of time and the calendar both ways.
How do you really keep time in accord with nature?
Or look how fiat it is.
Now either one isn't going to help because it would.
Well, see, here's the interesting thing to me is that I've heard you mention this on the air.
I've heard you mention this privately not just to me but to other people, okay?
And I won't bring them into this or anything like that,
but what I always find remarkable when you mention this particular fact
is that nobody ever bothers to even ask you what would be the proper way to keep time.
Exactly. That's my point.
Like I have that thought, and I saved it for now, you know, because we're doing this presentation, obviously.
I want to make it as remarkable as possible,
but I want anybody who has listened to you in the past even to take note of the fact
that I don't think a single one of you has ever asked them,
well, if this is incorrect or if this is crazy, what would be sane?
If you put up one hand and how many fingers you have in one hand,
if you have all five, subtract a few, and that's how many people have done that in the past 12 years,
which is a very, very bad, bad number.
So that's why, yeah, it's insanity, and it's amazing how insane it is.
So if we were to discuss time, I would do it as if you and I were having a private conversation
and everyone else was eavesdropping,
because there's really no way to direct it to the public based on what you just mentioned,
the lack of interest, right?
Right, right.
So from that point of view, we can just say, let's say in the Southwest there's a particular type of tree
that every year on the 22nd day of the seventh month, this is not with the Pope's calendar,
the leaves start to turn brown and it drops a certain berry.
Exactly, it's been doing that for 10 years on the money.
If you record that with the Pope's calendar, you know, January through December or whatever,
it could be as much as two weeks off.
So what I mean by that is today they're reckoning, I don't know, the first of November
or the 31st of what they call October, which is the eighth month.
Well, cosmically, by using, not relying on paper calendars or electronic wind-up toys and things like that,
I would reckon it by observation as being the seventh day of the ninth month.
Okay, so, and look, Septem would mean seven, Octo means eight, Novum means nine, Decim means ten,
but it doesn't mean that either that works, they're just showing you that there are four months
that kind of denote proper timekeeping.
Very simply, the best place to start is by thinking in biological terms.
Have you ever heard of something called the circadian rhythm, which is every seven days the body slows down,
the metabolism on the seventh day kind of slows down?
Yeah, and it's interesting because there's a lot of the quote-unquote holy writs of the world
say that there's a seventh day of rest.
Well, that seventh day is aligned with the moon phases,
and you could actually go to that infinite bastion of wisdom and information, Wikipedia,
look up circadian rhythm and they'll tell you that it lines up with moon phases as well, to some degree.
Yeah, like have you heard, you know, people get a little nutty during the full moon
and a little depressed during the dark moon,
but they don't address the half waning, half waxing moons, which happen on every week, you see,
so it's really, you know, so let's harken back to memory.
How many times within our lifetime have we heard people say we've got to go back to nature?
Right.
Okay, well, yes, you do, and the best place to start is by learning how to keep time,
because the fish, the birds, the plants, the trees, even the bacteria do not go on the Pope's calendar.
Sorry, guys.
No, just we do.
Well, don't use that word, me, count me out.
I'm sorry, when I said we, I was speaking for the listeners and myself, how about that?
So it's very simple.
You know, here, like the full moon, remember we've talked about in the past,
this is a society in full darkness right now, and it's not visible darkness or the color black,
but it does cross over into that.
Their day starts at the middle of the night, the darkest part of the day, right?
Their year starts at the darkest part of the darkest month, the darkest day of the month, the darkest season, right?
And their new moon is actually the dark moon or no moon.
Now, that is so absurd.
It's like we're standing outside in a parking lot, you and I, and do you see my new car?
And you're like, well, Greek, there's no car here.
Yeah, that's why it's a new car.
There's no car here.
Well, you're nuts, man.
That's the new moon.
It's the black moon.
It's not there, right?
So it's the new moon.
Do you see the level of insanity?
Right.
And this gets into another area because, look, let's put the work schedule aside for a moment
and imagine now that based on the more natural calendar, excuse me to use the term, timekeeping,
how are we to account for what year it actually is even?
Yeah, I'd like not to discuss that in public at the moment, but I assure you it's not out there.
Every culture seems to...
Here's the other part of the insanity.
They have Anno Domini, right, 2015, which, by the way, has nothing to do...
It might have to do with the birthday of Jesus, but there is no Jesus in the Bible, guys.
Sorry.
The letter J was invented in the 1500s, and there's no manger.
There's no Christmas.
There's no Easter bunny.
There's no crucifixion.
Just read the book.
You could look at it.
Or historical records.
And just to harp on that side of it, because from a secular point of view, this is considered the Christian era.
There's a lot of stuff going against, quote-unquote, Christmas, right?
And a lot of these megachurches are putting up websites saying, well, we really don't know when he was born,
and we do it our way.
And I'm like, you liars.
You guys suck.
You pagan liars.
Actually, I can't call them pagans because it gives pagans a bad name.
I've met some pretty respectable pagans.
It's very specific, down to the minute, and they're just completely lost.
It's really bad.
It's like a really bad attorney or a really good attorney.
No difference.
So, you know, how do you keep time, you know, with all this stuff?
You've got to knock all this stuff because the Christian era says it's 2015.
The Jewish era says it's the year 5700, whatever,
because they happened to redact about 300 years because they had about 300 years of unrighteous kings.
So we just eliminate the years, which is a normal thing to do in the Middle East, by the way, from the old culture.
Then you have the Mayans.
Oh, man.
Oh, forget it.
That's 20-day months.
Talk about stupidity.
Now, hold on.
Have you ever heard the term birds of a feather flock together, like minds go together?
Yes.
Do you know why the Western world got so unraveled with the 2012 Mayan calendar?
Because birds of a feather flock together.
What do I mean?
The Mayans and that type of culture, they had these pyramids where they would behead several people a day
and pull their live hearts out of their body, and they're into doing all kinds of overt human sacrifice, right?
Right.
As a public spectacle, as a matter of, yeah.
Yeah.
When was the last time you worked in a supermarket and saw a birthday cake?
What do you think the birthday cake symbolizes?
This society is totally into human sacrifice, in parity, just as much as they were.
So, you see, it's the human sacrifice element that they both have in common, because it's absurd.
A 20-day, come on, it's bizarre.
And there's a strange sympathy that's also put on the Western white man about races or people that have been, quote-unquote, eliminated.
You know, you have to go back and sympathize with that.
You know, come on, guys, this is, you know, how about, yes, give the sympathy where it's due,
but also make adjustments in your society, right, so you don't really live that way anymore.
Yeah, that would be nice to do, because white guilt is a continuous problem.
You know, they spend so much time engaged in looking back at something that they absolutely have no effect on
without ever bothering to look forward at changing what is yet to come, which they can do.
Yeah, and that's a cosmic, you know, the white, you know, the native, a lot of the aboriginal, meaning first people,
which is another thing.
They would have, if they were not abandoned by their gods or gave up the control of their gods or elementals that they had,
they would have never lost this land.
They were suckered in by the Jesuits, which is another show for itself.
That's why even still some of the tribes, or tribe people, I should say,
because every Native American group, when you mention their name, you know, Cherokee, Denali,
or they call them Navajo, or all the people that you mention, the aboriginal, their name means the people.
Cherokee means the people. Denali means the people. Tonohodo means the people.
Iroquois means the people. Hopi means the people.
They all call themselves the people. It's a very interesting concept.
They gave up their spiritual power, and that's why they got taken out, so that's another discussion.
But back to the time, very simply, for thousands of years, people settled their debts with the full moon on that schedule.
That's why today you still get a monthly bill. They keep it on that schedule.
And the first day of the month is when you cite the full moon in the east.
Just like the sun rises in the east, the full moon appears to be the same size.
Now, what's interesting, the day starts at noon, high noon, and it would be cited in that evening and prior to dawn.
So you have two sightings. Prior to dawn it would be in the west, and that evening it would be in the east,
because the moon is full for a very short time in the west.
Now, that first day of the month is set apart to itself.
The first day of the month is the first day of the month. It's not part of any week.
So you count seven days after that for your first moon phase.
So the eighth day of the month is the first, what they call, sabbatical rest, or seventh day of rest.
And then it would be the 15th, 22nd, 29th.
Okay.
You see, so when you read in the biblical text when they did their Sabbaths, you always find out it's always on the 8th, 15th, 22nd, or 29th.
And people are confused because those numbers are not divisible by seven.
But they are divisible by seven if you hold one.
Seven plus one, 14 plus one, 21 plus one, 28 plus one, because you've got to carry over the first day of the month.
This might sound confusing, but it's very easy to reckon if it's taught at you at kindergarten.
Well, right. I mean, if that was given to me as the yardstick to begin with to measure time,
that's what I would use, very much like I still utilize this work schedule because that's what was first given to me.
I mean, you know, your first language, as it were, and that is what this is.
It's a language.
And a methodology.
And a methodology, yeah.
Now, that's why when you read in the book of Joshua, they marched around the walls of Jericho, and the walls came down.
They marched around seven days, and they blew the trumpets, and the walls came down.
And no, if you read the text, it wasn't the sound waves that did it.
It's very specific how the walls came down and how that happened.
But you have to read the text, which no one does, being sarcastic here, but true, but very true.
You see a lot of researchers trying to say, oh, some special sound wave.
No, it's very specific in the text how those walls came down, nothing to do with sound.
But they marched around for seven days, and, you know, they're not supposed to work or do war on the Sabbath.
And you run into a lot of biblical scholars, and they'll say, well, if God wanted them to work on the Sabbath, they would.
You know, real dumb stuff like that.
That's not how it happened because they started marching on the first day of the month, and the seventh day was the sixth day of the week, right?
So the Sabbath would have been the next day, the eighth day of the month, right?
And, by the way, this is a lesson about learning how to keep time.
It's a primer, a first grader primer in the biblical text, because you learn how to count your days from the moon,
and your Sabbaths are holding over the one, let's say.
So they marched for seven days, starting on the first day of the month, which was the sixth day of the week.
Then they had the battle, and the next day they rested.
And how do we know this is a little bit of a primer on how to keep time?
Because where did they march around?
Jericho, right?
Well, the term Jericho is Yerico, and Yerico means, guess what it means?
The moon.
So it was the city of the moon.
Which, again, the letter J wasn't invented until much later.
Exactly, yeah.
So this is like when you read the information that is held within a lot of these older texts, and the most hated one is the Bible,
there's no way you're going to understand anything in it.
I assure people that, you know, people, you know, oh, are you a Bible thumper?
No, I'm not, because why would I have you read something you're not going to understand?
You know, watch TV, do something else.
I mean, you're not going to understand it.
Period.
And it doesn't take an intelligent or educated person.
It just takes someone to pull away and share information that is not the information that people think is the information they're using,
because the information they're using, like the calendar, is based on nothing.
These ancient texts are actually based on something.
So, you know, the day starts at noon.
So there's your month, and the day starts at high noon.
And that's why, if you remember before the electronic banking conventions, when you made a deposit at the bank after noon or an hour or so,
they counted it as the next day.
Now, the two timekeeping authorities in the Western world is the, I think, Naval Observatory in Colorado Springs,
and the other one is Greenwich in England.
And I've been harping about this for a while, and they used to prominently have on their website.
They don't anymore, but you can search around on their websites for Julian calendar date.
I think they tucked it in there.
They basically stayed on their, this is your timekeeping authorities now, not mine.
The world's timekeeping authorities.
They say that for scientific and for astronomical purposes, the day starts at solar noon, but for the people, it's civil midnight.
Holy crap.
That's like the original, see, when they first started publishing dictionaries for mass consumption,
they didn't know how to define words because it was not based on etymology.
It was how they socially wanted people to use the words.
So one of the original dictionaries, they defined oats as oats.
What is fed to horses in England, but it is the staple of the people in Scotland.
So it's like the people in Scotland are as good as our horses, right?
It's kind of like a put down.
So this is still going on.
If you read what they're writing and how they're writing it and the intent behind it, you're like, it's shocking.
But again, no one's paying any attention.
Well, that's why in English speaking mosques, they actually instruct you on reading the dictionary and learning what it is,
the meaning of a word is actually and things like that.
That's something that's actually done in their classes.
Yeah.
And it's weird.
And it was adapted even further by the by the black muscle movement in this country.
They wanted, you know, I mean, let me think about this carefully.
I think the most recent representation of that in like Hollywood film might have been the movie Malcolm X,
where he makes him take out a dictionary and, you know, and asked him to look for the definitions of black and white.
Right.
And these are, you know, colors.
These are neutral.
They're not even colors or modes, but they're neutral observations one can make.
And there are characteristics applied to them based on the usage.
And what you're encouraged to think about is why the usage is there.
Now, I know this is a really rudimentary point.
But it colors the reader's mind and the one who's going to use it as a no pun intended.
Yeah.
To a certain direction, positive, negative or vice versa.
Right.
But that's the full intent of these alleged definitions is to thrust upon you the meaning,
not to teach you the meaning, but to give you the meaning.
There's a difference.
Yeah.
It's like the old joke, you know, the black grandfather and the black grandson,
they go into a grocery store and say, it's tough being black.
You see everything in the store here, anything black, like the beans are in the can or this is behind bars.
You know, everything black here is in bad shape.
You know, so there's a there's a meme that's been thrust into the society to taint it,
where if you look, you know, at other societies, they don't see that because it's not in the language.
Right.
Well, precisely because when you take it outside of English,
all of a sudden you have different things going on.
And not to say that there isn't subtle social stereotypes or racism being introduced into other cultures.
I'm just giving you what I can easily observe right here with, you know,
what I supposed to be an English speaking audience to get you to understand from your perspective.
But in all the cultures, you find this where the trajectory of the meaning of words is controlled in this fashion.
And people speculate as to where that comes from.
But I wonder what your viewpoint is.
It's a cat.
It's a it's a it's a well, semi enforced.
It's enforced with the mind or the spirit.
It's a caste system thing.
It's like, you know, how in India, you know, you say caste.
So right away, you think about India, you know, the most populated country in the world now.
They surpassed China recently, by the way.
You know, they have the untouchables.
Right. You know, you can't you can't marry out of it.
And, you know, whatever.
Right. You're limited to your mobility in society, even physically.
Right. You don't have that extreme in the Western culture, but you definitely have a caste system.
And it's spoken about openly.
How many times have you heard of the middle class?
But they don't say, you know, on mainstream and alternative media.
Right. The destruction of the middle class, the middle class, this middle class that.
But they never say upper class or lower class.
So if you start saying, well, the destruction of the middle class, middle class is suffering, they're paying more.
How come they're not using the term upper class and lower classes?
Because if you say there's a middle class, there has to be an upper class and lower class.
And they're not saying that.
So they're trying to infer minimally just by using the term middle class.
You see, you have to infer that there's a lower and upper, even though it's not discussed.
So I find that to be pretty nasty when I hear middle class.
Well, right. That directly speaks to the fact that, you know, if you have a middle of the road,
then you obviously have something on each side of it.
I mean, it's just that simple. Right.
But but they're never discussed. You're correct.
They just infer it. And in fact, the middle class is really a whipping point anyway,
because what what really the middle class is sort of like the the fairy tale, if anything,
because the majority of the people do not dwell within the middle class.
The illusion is that at one time they did or they always do this kind of thing.
But that's not really the truth.
There's quite a bit of different distribution going on as far as numerically who's in the upper class
and who's in the lower class and who's in the middle class. Right.
Well, either way, the deception as well, because it's meant to be strived for by those who know they're in the lower class,
but are not even to be spoken about generally. And those in the upper class.
Well, gee, that would be, I guess, their fear of falling. I don't know.
Either way, you don't want to be poor. That's true.
Don't be poor. Broke is not poor, by the way. Poor is a mentality.
Poor is you're broke. Well, not poor and broke is not the same.
How many times have you heard someone winning the lottery and they lose it all in six months?
Right. Like, you know, a hundred year salary. Right. Right.
OK, that's poor, but has nothing to do with how much wealth or resources you have.
Poor is just not being able to handle it properly.
But how are you going to handle anything right if you don't know how to keep time?
Back to that, you know, very simply. That's the thing.
If you don't know how to keep time, look, you're making payments based on this schedule.
You're you're dispersing your labor based on this schedule.
So, yeah. Well, they're not even here's the thing.
You're not even really making payments because it's fiat.
It's just a joke that the legal society has put on people.
And they took advantage of the credit lines that were put into, let's say, most of the Western world by the late 30s.
They figured, oh, let's bypass and tell people there's still money and they can owe money and we'll just get it all.
You know, but so the labor is real, though. Labor is a real thing.
But you're working for free. I tell people, you know, you know, you've worked your whole life.
You haven't gotten paid. And they're like, what do you mean?
I got a check here. I said, that's not getting paid. That's a pay to the order of that's not getting paid.
And you go to the bank and you get more notes and take those notes to the bank and get something real for it.
Meaning lawful. See, when you start acting unlawfully like that, you're making enemies in the spiritual realm, you know.
So which is another discussion which we broached on many times, even though it works for mankind, for example.
It doesn't work for your polluting. You've heard of the concept of pollution or smog, which is a mixture of smoke and fog.
There's a pollution, that spiritual stench that humanity has right now that is extended beyond the contained realm of the terrarium or the earth.
Even the earth is tired of it. It has nothing to do with nuclear reactors and dumping toxins in the river.
The earth can handle that, no problem, because that nuclear material has come out of the earth.
Don't think, you know, it's just a delusion out there. I mean, here's the thing.
I haven't heard a host or a guest anywhere discuss time like we have just now.
This is actually an Internet, for lack of a better term, digital milestone.
This is probably the second or third time you and I have discussed it on a quote-unquote show.
But this is a milestone that we're pressing the issue on how humanity should be ashamed of themselves for not paying attention to this.
And you think they're going to get... how many times have you heard, we want disclosure from the government on aliens?
Are you kidding? You morons aren't going to get anything like that.
Well, that's the fun part with this disclosure issue.
And this is why, because I used to be one of these people that always clamored for disclosure.
There's nothing to disclose.
Well, here's the fun part. When I see things disclosed quite often, I see them not understood anyway.
Let's go down that route.
Yeah, please.
Something called electricity. Yeah, you hit the switch, light comes on.
Well, that's always been around.
Mankind has always known about that because you could just rub...
The Greeks, they used to sell devices 2,000 years ago.
It was basically wool and glass and you had sparking and arcing, toys, things like that.
So for thousands of years, people had electric devices.
They were just known to make sparks and shock people.
And not until a few hundred years ago, a medical man known as Galvani was dissecting animals
and he noticed that when he touched them with metal, the muscles would twitch.
And I think you might have somewhere on the Facebook posted the demon-possessed fish or something.
That's simply that because you'll notice there's a YouTube about a fish that's got no head and it's gutted.
And when she wraps it with a wet towel on a wooden board over a large stainless steel sink,
which forms a capacitor, by the way, the fish starts to jump around.
And that was what Galvani was witnessing.
Well, right. And here's the amazing thing, just to illustrate this in case you haven't seen it, listener.
Here's the thing. We're talking about a fish that has no innards, essentially.
It's just like the meat of the fish and the scaly outside.
That's the end of it. There's nothing else in the fish.
It would be a third of a fish by weight, half of the fish by looking at it, and fish parts, really.
And it's moving. That's what Galvani experienced.
So it went further on with other people like Volta.
You've heard of the Volt, right? And Voltaic Piles, by the way.
They have something called the Oxford Bell at Oxford University where they teach you
that energy can't be created or all this laws of thermodynamics and all this crap.
And they have something called the Oxford Bell right in the Hall of Physics there in Oxford.
And it's been ringing for 150 years nonstop, electrically.
And it's in a sealed vacuum because they put it in a vacuum so it doesn't make that,
you know, you don't hear the ringing disturbing the university,
which they should be disturbed because they are disturbed anyway.
So in the classroom, they're telling them that you need quote-unquote cells and, you know, energy degrades.
But meanwhile, in their hallway, they have the Oxford Bell, which is a Voltaic Pile,
which has been ringing for conservatively 150 years plus.
And yeah, why don't we have that?
OK, so you're moving on forward from that. You've heard of Tesla.
Now, around that time of Tesla were other people like Heaviside,
Oliver Heaviside, who made telegraphy possible.
And you had a guy named J.J. Thompson.
And then after him, you had a guy named Philo Farnsworth, who was the father of television, who swore.
Well, by the way, they asked him, why are you working on the television?
He came up with it when he was 14 years old, by the way, the electronic one,
because they had a mechanical TV, which was about as big as a house.
But they asked Philo Farnsworth, this is how the legend says,
why are you inventing this thing called the television?
He says, because now everyone will be literate and there will be no more wars.
And by the 1950s, he finally figured out, well, he's pretty smart,
he figured out that that was not going to happen.
He banned, he never watched television after that and banned everyone in his family from watching it.
And he didn't make a dime off of it because it was stolen from him through patent lawsuits and things.
OK, but let's go back. I've mentioned a character named J.J. Thompson.
Now, he can be accredited with what we call the electron, which is not what we,
he had no model as we do today.
But he had postulated a theory of the ether, which Tesla had as well,
that weight and inertia and momentum is not in the mass.
What happens is when you have something that's material, no matter how light or how heavy it is,
these electrical lines of force attach to it.
And once the object goes into motion, more electrical lines of force attach to it.
And it starts to gain weight or momentum.
That's why it takes two miles to stop a locomotive, more electrical lines of force,
not because it's made of all this heavy stuff.
So if you figure out a way to neutralize or depolarize those lines of force,
you can have instant start, instant stop.
So you could be driving down a car at 60 miles an hour with a cup of coffee filled to the brim,
hit the brakes and the car stops instantly and you don't feel a thing and the coffee doesn't spill.
And also you could start it instantly.
Now J.J. Thompson had very strong science behind this and so did Tesla, Tesla's airships.
And there was others that started qualifying this and quantifying it.
And this was back in 1903.
Now the Germans caught on to this because the Germans, why do I say they caught on to this?
Well, because during the Olympics in the 30s, I think it was Westinghouse gave them a big television camera.
It was about eight feet long, took two people to operate.
Well, two years later they gave Westinghouse something the size of a shoebox that did the same thing.
Okay.
Now so the concept of canceling inertia and weight, now let me just repeat this one more time.
Let's say you have a brick that weighs five pounds and you put it on a scale.
When you drop it on the scale or lower it on the scale, you notice the dial moves to five, right?
But if you lift the brick up 20 feet and drop it, the scale will pin it at 30 pounds or 50 pounds because of the increased speed.
And they call that acceleration momentum.
All of that is not in the brick or the lead or the feather.
It's electrical lines of force that attach to all material things.
So these guys like Tesla and J.J. Thompson were very big proponents on advancing the science of neutralizing this,
neutralizing weight, neutralizing momentum and inertia.
So you have instant stop and instant go.
Now the problem when you do this is it's hard to navigate with magnetic north.
So they developed a gyroscopic compass that had a slave unit that ran off of it that worked off of 30-degree increments only.
That's why when people see objects in the sky that move at 9,000 miles per hour and make a right-hand turn, it doesn't really make a right-hand turn.
I mean it could make it.
It has to be in increments of 30.
So 90 degrees is in increments of 30.
All of these flying objects make turns at increments of 30 degrees.
So it would be 30, 60, 90, 120, what have you.
It's because they're using the slave compass.
So have we said enough about UFOs?
What kind of disclosure are you going to get?
Yeah, I'll be willing to bet that nobody even understood that that's what we were saying here.
Yeah.
Now here's the thing.
Here's the funny part.
When these guys started playing around with this, neutralizing the electrical fields that attach themselves to everything to give the illusion of mass has weight,
they said, man, we know if we go up into the atmosphere, that's a pressure problem, right?
You know, how high can we go?
We don't know.
But if you go high enough, you have pressure differential.
That's why, you know, big 747s are pressurized, right?
Right.
So they said, man, you know, we've got to send something that could take pressure really well.
So they said, oh, you've got these little submarines.
You've got submarines.
Why don't we put neutralize the field of a submarine?
Because that's already designed to take pressure.
Right.
And the crew will be safe.
So they started flying these submarines around.
And, you know, they took the props off, obviously.
Right.
So people start saying, oh, I saw a flying cigar shape, man.
It was like 200 feet long, you know.
There's your cigar shapes.
Come on, people.
You know, disclosure.
What are you talking about?
You don't even know what day it is, man.
You're not going to get the kind of disclosure, you know.
Now, J.J. Thompson lived until the 40s.
And let's not talk about Oliver Heaviside.
But Tesla, his career took a dump before, you know, 1910, 1915 or so.
And he lived until the 1940s.
So that's a terrible life to be feeding pigeons on park benches for 30 years.
Could you imagine?
Actually, what did he live on?
Well, the people that he made rich, you know, threw him a bone.
Every so often to go to a hotel, take a shower and sleep.
And J.J. Thompson was a prolific writer, and he stopped.
And he lived until the 40s or so.
So these guys were mute on this for 30 years.
Could you imagine that?
Now, the European end and the Asian end got very activated with this technology.
Now, the reason you're not going to get disclosure on this is because we're talking instant start, instant stop.
It doesn't matter how much something weighs or how fast or how slow it's going.
And we're talking about using a type of electricity that people are not familiar with.
It's longitudinal, not transverse.
In other words, it doesn't move in a wave like a jumping.
Imagine two people holding a jump rope, and one person shakes their arm.
You actually see the wave go through the rope to the next person.
It takes time.
Now, if they pull the rope tight and one person tugs on it, that's a longitudinal wave.
You don't see any wave.
It doesn't take in its time.
It's instant.
Imagine it's a steel cable.
This is working with longitudinal type of electricity that when you use it, you return it back to its source.
So there's no consumption.
There's no heat.
This type of longitudinal electricity can be evidenced when you have a runaway electrical situation.
When you have, let's say, a power switch, and you throw it, and you see sparks come out of it.
Even a 9-volt battery, you can see small sparks coming out of it if you short it.
And remember, it's 10,000 volts for half an inch of that type of electricity to go through air.
So if you see a tiny little spark off of a 9-volt battery, it might be in the 2 to 500 volt.
But wait a second.
That's a 9-volt battery.
Where's that voltage coming from?
It's that longitudinal type of electricity, you see, which no one wants to discuss.
And no, it can't go there just like the calendar.
They're blank.
So what kind of disclosure do you people want?
You're not going to get it.
Sorry.
Even if you got it, you wouldn't get it.
You wouldn't get it.
That's what the problem is.
And it's out there.
It's being used.
And I watch this stuff in a political way.
People demand an answer about something, and they get it.
And it's right there on a piece of paper.
I mean, as related to them as clearly as the English language can possibly relate it to them.
And they continue to ask the question.
I'm dumbfounded by that all the time.
Now, I don't necessarily understand the electricity.
I got your example, but I'm just not mechanically.
Well, let's get away from the mechanical part, because if anyone does a rigorous study on electricity,
no matter how far back you want to go, up until the 1700s and prior, or even 1800s,
electricity was defined as an energy that was contained within living beings.
What's so hard about that to understand?
Even a mainstream doctor who just cuts, burns, and drugs, right?
You know what I mean by that?
Surgery?
You're a general battlefield medic that exists all in quackery today.
All they teach is that, but they still talk about how there are electrical impulses in the body moving the muscles.
But yet they only administer drugs and surgery.
But they're ignoring the electrical part, right?
Any quack doctor will tell you, oh, yeah, the muscles are moved by electrical impulses.
Okay.
Where's your electrical medicine?
Oh, that was tried already.
They threw those guys in prison pretty fast with Reif and Ruth Drown, who went beyond that.
Yeah, and then it's also demonized with stuff like ECT, which is brutal, the way it's applied.
But again...
Well, yeah, that's cooking the piece of meat in the skull.
Yeah, right.
They do it with a hatchet.
It's not biological, and it's AC.
It's a type of electricity that hurts you.
Like the X-rays that Tesla produced were healing.
The X-rays that are used now, in 15 minutes, will kill you.
Or even 15 seconds will be damaging.
So, yeah, it's just beyond...
Why?
Maybe could it be because no one's paying attention to what day it is.
Hmm.
I think it ties back to the small things sometimes.
It's kind of like, you know, for the want of a nail, the battle was lost.
Have you heard that?
There was a messenger, right?
He had to send a message to the general out in the field.
And he was rushing the blacksmith who was shoeing the horse.
And he left a nail out, and the shoe fell off.
He never made to give the message.
Right.
Well, that's the thing, is if you don't...
Here's a funny phrase, but the devil is in the details all the time.
This is where the sabotage comes in, is the very smallest thing has a...
Well, I don't want to borrow that phrase.
Let me skip that.
But an effect that resonates throughout.
It's the smallest thing, right?
You know, you've heard the expression that a butterfly flapping its wings on the other side of the planet,
you know, creates a situation right in front of your eyes.
It's the weather.
We could discuss the weather, which is attached to electricity as well.
It's the same field, but not the AC.
But, yeah, the subtle things.
But, you know, the plus and the minus is very subtle.
And you said earlier, just to be forgiving for the audience as well,
it's fine if you don't understand the mechanical, because it was set up not to be understood.
It's actually quite simple.
The engineers and the university scholars don't understand it either.
And it's very simple what you will glean out of it.
If you go to university to learn about electricity, there are only two places where they teach about electricity.
One is the physics department, and across the street at the electrical engineering department, right?
Now, the physicists, they only focus on the negative part of the circuit.
And they call the positive the source.
So we're going to put a minus one on the physics building, right?
Let's go across the street.
On the electrical engineers, they send the minus to ground.
They just call it ground, and they focus on the source, the positive.
So on the electrical engineering building, we have a positive one.
And the two buildings are facing each other.
The physics building has a minus one.
The electrical engineering building has a positive one.
Chuck, what do you get when you put positive one and minus one together?
Well, I do believe you get nothing.
You get zero.
And that's exactly what you're going to learn about electricity in university.
Right.
See, I don't like the term zero even.
Yeah, which means no number in Arabic, I guess.
Yeah, but that's the thing.
That's the UFOs, and you're not going to get it, I assure you.
You're not going to get any free energy, because all energy is free, by the way.
Your free power is what people need.
When people say free energy, how many times have you heard that?
I was just going to bring you to that.
It's the power thereafter.
The work.
Yeah, the work that's going to come from it.
Because after all, see, this is why I focused on labor when I was talking earlier,
is because the labor is real, the work is real,
but what goes behind it, what goes into it, what actually governs it,
well, that's a whole other story.
See how that all comes together rather nicely?
Yes, the energy, all the devices, okay,
all of the devices people have been using for the past decades or half a century
work on a high-pressure transverse field,
meaning it needs this high-pressure magnetically pulsed AC current.
You've heard that, right?
If you don't think it's high-pressure, go down to a power station,
and it's 140 degrees inside Fahrenheit all year round,
and you've got to wear ear protection, right?
And the thing is roaring, and it's huge,
and it's charging the lines.
By the way, it doesn't travel anywhere.
So we'll go back on this in a minute, I guess.
Four minutes.
Yes, we will.
In a few minutes, when we come back from the break,
of course, you're listening to Ocelli and the Greek
on American Freedom Radio and Americanfreedomradio.com.
And, hey, it does get very simple when you've got a plus one and a minus one.
What do you get? Zero.
Let's go.
Welcome to the institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth,
and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein,
and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces three brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
American Freedom Radio is back.
We're trying to become commercial free,
apart from a few honorable advertisers that we would give ad space to even if they couldn't pay us.
In this quest to deliver quality radio with very few annoying ads,
we are now asking the listeners like you to open up and become partners with American Freedom Radio.
We all know the economy is controlled and a new system called the peer-to-peer economy is now within our grasp.
That means if you'd like this network with its incredible hosts and credible information
to be nothing but the content you want to hear,
then you must realize that you cannot be a part of it if you're just sitting on the sidelines watching.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and pledge your support today.
Donate according to your means.
Some can only afford $1 a month while others can afford $100 a month.
Regardless of the size of your contribution,
it all adds up to keeping the network owners and the radio hosts housed and fed at the end of every month.
Thank you.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape,
various pain-related health care costs, epilepsy and autism,
rising mental disorders and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer and it saves you over one third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information the sonic entity known has.
Well, hour two of this show according to the wind-up toy, of course.
You know, you never know exactly where that's going to go
because it is a breakdown of 24 hours in reality.
Does it exactly go that way or is Stalin's 20-hour clock a little more accurate?
Or is it just incrementally the same thing divided slightly differently?
Well, you got 12 hours at daylight, 6 hours at night.
So you got 18, which is 6 plus 6 plus 6.
Oh, no, there's that number.
Oh, Satan, the devil, Lucifer.
Oh, no. No, the number 6 is the number of man, guys. Sorry.
I was going to say I thought it was three guys getting together.
Yeah, anyway, as in guys meaning the audience.
You know, the thing is it's funny how people use biblical references out of context
and they're wondering what these things mean when they're defined on the next passage over
or in another chapter of another book.
It's fascinating to see how ridiculous.
You know, by the way, just to throw this out there,
how many times have you heard of Lucifer, Luciferianism and all this other stuff, right?
Oh, you know, please get into that in just a minute.
Before we go a little further, though, I do want to hear from you on Luciferianism
because it is one of the most annoying things I have ever heard uttered on alternate.
I don't know why.
We could make it real short.
Just he's dead.
It has nothing to do with a spiritual entity.
It was an unnamed Babylonian king that was very, very conceited, let's say,
and wanted his subjects to have him known as the morning star or the shiny one.
And he's dead.
He's not a spirit.
I mean, this is so ridiculous at this point, you know, that, yeah.
So let's carry on.
We don't have to go back to it.
That's it.
It's just a Babylonian king.
And there is no Easter bunny.
That's all.
You've got to remember.
That's the end of it.
And then when you want to get into Satan, that's a whole other short discussion, too.
You've got, most people have one sitting right there in their neighborhood
and they have a shingle up that says attorney at law.
That's what it means.
So, I mean, yeah.
So that's on the secular side, which I think is all people can handle at the moment.
But we wanted to get in maybe some station.
Well, right.
I wanted to clear a little bit of business here.
First of all, you can join in on this discussion by going to the chat room,
which is on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
If you go there, you can find a nice big old banner that says live chat
and if you enter something of interest there, I will try to bring it up.
I am in the chat room currently.
Also, we have the phone lines open at 218-339-8525.
And as an extra feature, just during this show, because I don't do it during my own,
but just during this show, I can also take Skype calls.
So if you have Charles.Ocelli on your Skype list,
you can just ring on in and I'll add you into the discussion.
If you don't, contact request me.
I'll add you, sight unseen anyway, which sometimes I do regret.
But I will do it during the broadcast of this show, I assure you,
and bring you on into the discussion if you have something to add.
But remember, if you have something to add.
Okay?
That would be nice.
And what else?
Well, gee, we brought up, oh, well, there is also an Ocelli and the Greek website
at ocelliandthegreek.com.
Right?
We have, well, that's evolving too.
That's been changing a bit.
Yeah, and that's primarily there for if anyone is curious about making direct donations.
And there's some videos up there and maybe some other courtesies
which will be put on there in the near future.
Right.
And plenty of stuff over at Americanfreedomradio.com,
which also has a chat button and a donate button on the chat page,
if you're there as well.
Anyway, did I cover everything Greek?
Yeah, I'd say so.
I'm still sick here, you know.
I'm trying real hard to stay on track.
I hope I'm not meandering about too much with my mouth.
No, no, that's fine.
You'll get better if you stick to cross-latitude eating.
Just no tropic, nothing from the south.
Just, yeah, and you'll be fine.
And that's the best thing I tell anyone about when they're feeling,
quote, unquote, seasonal changes.
Absolutely.
And this is a, there we go.
Somebody just dropped into the chat room and said,
I looked for a chat.
There it is.
They say, hi, Greek, by the way.
I'm not going to look at all those comments, but I just wanted to.
Actually, I just turned it on as well, and I see it.
It's in purple with a smiley face as well.
It sure is.
So there you go.
We're both looking at the chat.
Okay, sure.
So we were on the rant about free energy, which it's all free already,
because it's about direction, motion, and pressure,
which is around us constantly.
The free power, you're not going to, well, you do have free power.
When you get a utility bill, that's a public utility.
It's all paid for,
and they're just playing a joke on you to turn it off if you don't send
them a second payment, but that's another discussion.
I'm blue in the face about discussing how the financial system works.
It's just as bad as the calendar,
and it's not the common folk that your everyday meet and greet people.
It's the people with master's degrees from, you know, Ivy League.
They also don't understand it, you know, because, of course,
they leave there with plus one and minus one education, right?
Right.
So, yeah, it's just sad right now.
The terrarium, the human terrarium,
but you're not going to get anything like that where you plug in a device
and everyone's going to get, you know,
unlimited power because your device,
that type of reckoning of electricity will not power any of these unbalanced
things like your toaster, your computer, your TV,
your electric motors are not balanced.
Well, see,
that's the odd thing because I'm sitting here thinking to myself,
if energy is derived from and power is therefore derived from energy and
energy is what, well, what did you say now?
Motion pressure and direction and direction.
Well,
motion pressure and direction can be harnessed from a variety of places.
Water wheel.
A water wheel.
Windmill.
But let's just imagine this.
If you could figure out a way to wirelessly harness the activity in your town,
you could literally power your town hall with the activity of its people
because they introduce all of those elements into the environment.
Hmm.
Or these gyms.
They have these mega gyms now,
like mega churches,
and you look inside and there's all these people in exercise equipment.
Why not hook them up to these things they call generators,
which are not.
They're pressure devices.
And, you know,
because electrical generators don't generate electricity,
just like water pumps don't generate water.
They're just pumps.
I mean,
the last time I cut a live wire,
I was expecting with dustpan and brush in hand to find trillions of electrons
on the floor so I could scoop them up and put them back in the wire.
I didn't, you know,
what's going on?
Hmm.
So, yeah.
So this type of electricity that people are thinking they're going to get,
they will not get,
and they're not going to get disclosure about UFOs,
and they're not,
these, you know,
is it safe to say this?
Yeah.
Is it safe?
You notice we're making predictions without dates?
Because you don't need to put a date when you say you're not going to get it,
you know,
versus when you're going to get this,
this,
you know,
and then it doesn't come.
How about saying you're never going to get it and it never comes?
Because that's the truth,
folks.
Sorry,
I'm not making this up.
Oh,
right.
Right.
I mean,
when people talk to me about the end of the world,
and they,
you know,
quite often want me to speculate as to when it is,
I say to them,
there's really no relevance to bringing that up.
Well,
because they're in it.
They don't end.
But it's going to end.
That's it.
Well,
it doesn't end.
here's the thing,
Chuck,
if we're going to make it,
you know,
if you're watching a film and really paying attention on the film,
even when the film ends,
the film is still running,
it's called the credits,
right?
Right.
So,
you know,
if you're going to do a two-hour film,
do you get exactly two hours worth of film,
or do you get two hours and ten minutes,
because you have to roll credits in the end?
You're in the credits part of the movie now,
of the human epoch.
It ended already,
about less than two decades ago,
and no one's noticing,
because you're not supposed to.
Because,
you know,
it has to do with time.
Oh,
boy,
they're thinking about time again.
Okay.
Yeah.
So,
maybe it's,
right,
the level of apathy,
which is going to lead into maybe other,
various sundries of topics,
but when it,
even when it does end,
which it will come to a physical end,
and in the world,
meaning not the earth,
you know,
all these people talking about pole shifts,
and all this other,
that's absurd,
because,
anyway,
that's,
yeah,
they don't even understand the poles,
again,
plus one,
minus one.
So,
there is going to be a pole shift,
but when it happens,
that'll be the last of your worries,
let's just say that.
So,
it's still ridiculous and absurd on a global level,
no matter where you turn,
but you are in the end,
meaning the end of how the society is structured,
you know,
the deception,
the lack of morality,
the lack of law,
the lack of what's quote-unquote good,
right?
You see,
like,
it's very safe,
especially,
you know,
young children,
today is a little worse than yesterday,
but not as bad as it's going to be tomorrow.
That's the same as saying the frog being boiled in the pot.
Yeah,
it's getting warmer,
but I'm not cooked yet.
Yeah,
so,
if today was,
if today was as bad as it's going to be tomorrow,
then we'd all stop and say,
whoa,
we've got to stop what we're doing.
So,
now the frog jumps out of the pot,
now you've got to go grab the frog,
and you've got to dump all the water that was in there now,
because remember,
you've got to start with a lower temperature,
right?
And then you start raising,
you've got to start the whole process over again.
So,
this is very specific on how people aren't noticing what's going on.
Now,
when I say worse,
worse meaning coming closer to the end of society as you know it.
Look,
the architects and the engineers know it.
All these huge buildings that you see,
billions and billions are spending of credit on these buildings,
they have a 20-year lifespan.
You know,
100 years ago,
they built them to last 100 years,
1,000 years ago,
they built them to last 1,000.
It's almost like written on man's heart,
but they can't define it,
because they've been thoroughly blinded and thoroughly,
you know,
their ears are shut and their eyes are shut.
They don't make anything like they used to.
And there's no reason to.
Right.
There's no reason to,
because,
you know,
there's,
why?
You know,
it's,
yeah.
So,
the free energy part,
forget it.
The term is erroneous.
what I mean about your equipment being imbalanced,
when you have an electrical circuit,
there are aspects,
you know,
you have resistance,
capacitance,
inductance,
those kinds of fancy terms.
You know,
those things have to be balanced.
The inductance has to balance the resistance
and it has to be impedance matched.
The inductance has to match the capacitance
and then it has to be,
the system has to be impedance matched
for this longitudinal type of low pressure,
natural electricity,
the kind that moves in your body and space
and everywhere else,
to have an effect,
to create power.
That's what Tesla was working on.
These devices that everyone is using today
and has been for over almost a century
or half a century at least,
are completely imbalanced
and they require that brute force,
magnetic,
pulsing,
hot,
electrical,
current,
you know,
AC that if you touch it,
kills you.
It requires that type of,
because it's unbalanced.
That's why you're not going to get a,
quote unquote,
free energy device
unless you have it spinning
another type of actuator
that produces this type of stuff.
So that,
you're not getting that.
And put it this way,
people that know how to do it,
ain't sharing.
Sorry.
Just like the guys that know
how to start and stop a submarine
at 20,000 feet up in the air
and make it make a right hand turn
that everybody on the ground
thinks is a flying cigar,
they're not sharing either.
And I can't blame them.
Sorry.
This is to the general people of the planet.
You're not going to get any of that stuff.
So get over it.
Well,
and you wouldn't want to hand lit blow torches
to monkeys anyway.
Yeah.
Let's be honest.
Especially when every time you go to see them,
they're throwing their feces at you.
Right.
You see,
I said that.
Bad monkeys.
Bad monkey.
Chango malo in Spanish.
Okay.
So,
yeah.
Sorry, guys.
So,
you know,
we're sonic entities.
I think we can use this late night hour
that could be rebroadcast
just to make fun of people
because there's nothing else to do.
I mean,
you can go through the entire
mainstream and alternative community
and all the things they're talking about
and all their topics are
wholly irrelevant
because their point of view is shot.
They have no point of view at all,
no reference points,
and nothing to ground themselves
in anything real at all.
And it's shocking to say that,
but it's even shocking to observe,
even more shocking to observe it.
And when things get so insane
or so criminal,
it requires strong language.
You know,
there's no way to pat it and say it,
you know,
oh, it'll get better,
or 2012,
you know,
or my favorite is with these,
the high priests and priestesses
of the New Age movement.
Oh, you see,
these things didn't come
as they were supposed to
because we're in a different timeline now.
I love that,
the different timeline idiocy.
Well, that's the lazy
Star Trek writer solution right there.
Oh, man,
we're talking about high level of,
well, anyway.
Star Trek has a great variety of good stuff,
but I always get really aggravated
when they erase a whole lot of
fallout effects
in a plot line
by just saying,
well, that timeline doesn't exist anymore.
Yeah, right.
There was a lot of insight
and a lot was shown in metaphor as well
with the food replicator
as how the body generally creates its nutrition
within itself
through stimulation.
That's why these guys,
you know,
the breatharians or yogis,
they say this guy hasn't eaten in 30 years
and they put him in a lab
to see if he's going to survive
in his fluorescent lights
and brick walls with metal everywhere.
This man is getting his energy
from the environment externally.
He doesn't have to pass through the tunnel
between the mouth and the anus.
He is getting it externally
and you put him in a room with fluorescent lights.
You know, stupid, you know.
Yeah.
But the other stupidity of it is
how many times have you heard of the Fukushima?
The Fukushima radiation
or Fukushima is going to kill us all,
you know.
Yeah, right.
First of all,
I got a hard time wrapping my mind around that
because some of the things you said about that
and here's like,
okay, first time I'm really going to take an objection
to something that you talk about
because I've never seen...
Well, here's the thing.
I haven't seen evidence
of this one way or another
as far as exactly how destructive
what they call radiation is, right?
But as it's described,
it's pretty horrifying as it's described.
As it's described
and it's intended to do that
simply because the inventory...
What do I mean by the inventory?
The actual physical substances that are transmuted.
Yes, plutonium is a transmuted element.
It doesn't...
It's classified as one.
You have to make it.
Yes.
So if you can make plutonium,
you can make gold and make silver
and I believe in the early 90s
about 40 to 50% of all the platinum
that the Russians were putting on the open market
was made in the laboratory.
Oops, did I just say that?
Let's just forget I said that.
Okay.
So, see, but they can do it
because, you know, the isotopes are...
They'll classify the isotopes
because, see, they have military to back it up.
But if you start making these elements
like gold and platinum in your kitchen,
oh, that's an unrecognizable isotope.
We'll just tell them it's iron
and we'll keep the sample
and if he wants a sample back,
we'll just tell him we lost it.
Hmm, does that sound like
I might have experience with that?
I shouldn't have said that, but anyway.
So let's just say...
Harken back to Tesla.
He showed that he could make radium.
He can take neutral, non-radioactive material
and make it radioactive
and Wilhelm Reich showed that
you can take radioactive material
and neutralize it.
Both of that proves that radioactivity
is not inherent in the material itself,
but those materials that are known
to be radioactive have an inherent quality
that seem to bounce back the field effects
in the natural environment
known as electricity and other things
in a very radical ionizing way.
All radiation does is ionize you.
You want to die of radiation poisoning?
Go in front of an industrial-size ozone machine
in a box for 10 minutes.
You will die.
The same exact death you would have
as if you were subject to Chernokov blue radiation,
you know, that Chernokov blue glow.
Okay?
That's all it is.
It's ionization.
And they've scared everyone.
The reason why, going back to the materials,
is the reason why they've scared everyone
is because they want to protect their inventory.
The stuff goes for 100,000 bucks an ounce.
Now, could you imagine if people found out
that it wouldn't harm you?
See, if you put too much of it together,
it goes critical, right?
It just means it gets really hot.
It doesn't explode.
It's another ridiculous thing.
The point with that is
they want to protect their inventory
because if people knew
that there's $500 million worth of inventory
they could steal by driving their truck
through a nuclear reactor
and loading it in the back of their pickup
with cotton gloves and sell it.
You see what I mean?
So they tell everyone it's toxic and radioactive
and whatever so that people stay.
Because if you drop, you know,
some radioactive material in a room
so it's radioactive, everyone runs out.
And then when no one's looking,
the bankster puts it in his pocket.
You know, we're talking about a 3-inch disc,
half-inch thick.
Uranium, right?
Because, you know, it's worth 100 grand.
So now you don't have to spend any money on security.
You see?
Nobody's going to want to steal it
because it'll kill them.
Now, nuclear power plants do not explode.
Sorry.
They're a billion-dollar tea kettle.
The cores are inside very heavy stainless.
You need another nuke to blow it.
So that's what happened at Chernobyl
and that's what happened at Fukushima.
Fukushima.
They were blown by small nukes.
Now, who wants to discuss that?
I don't.
It's a nasty business.
And if you don't even know what day it is,
what the hell are you doing going,
trying to discuss how radioactivity works
is the general question.
Right.
Meanwhile, the comment in the chat room,
I like this.
So we really aren't running out of silver.
We can make more then.
Yes, silver is an interesting one
because silver is the master metal.
If you were to have a...
Silver would be in the center
and all metals are judged alchemically
either are they on the left or the right of silver.
And by the way, silver is the only metal
that you could use to connect or braze
or solder or weld any other two metals together.
It is the master metal.
It is the most difficult one to make
because it doesn't have a monoatomic form.
No.
So the question is that we're not really running out of silver.
The earth is making plenty of silver.
You know, if you've ever been around
an old-timer gold miner,
you know, when sometimes they lose their land
and the government puts a highway over it,
and they're like,
that's okay, in 30 years we'll come and dig under,
there'll be plenty of gold there.
And you're like, well, there's no gold now.
It's okay, it needs about 30 years to grow
as long as there's enough crystal formation,
you know, quartz, and some copper.
So anyway, these are discussions for maybe another thing.
You know, it's a transmutation alchemy.
Lewis Kervran discussed how the body does that.
Silver, you can make gold, by the way,
in your kitchen using Saccharomyces cerevisiae,
which is a fancy term for yeast,
baker's yeast, and some silver.
Silver is an antibiotic,
is a fungicide, naturally, right?
So this Saccharomyces cerevisiae species
of typical baker's yeast
has an intelligence that if they notice
that the colony is being threatened,
they will actually sacrifice
a certain amount of the colony
in a liquid solution to create gold
in the nucleus of the yeast
and bond itself to the silver,
to plate the silver with gold
to protect the rest of the colony.
Just like a chicken makes calcium
inside of its body,
this yeast can make gold inside of its nucleus
and then it bonds itself to the silver
because the gold would be inert to the colony.
So now you've got these little critters
making gold for you in your kitchen.
And I've discussed how to do this
on several roundtables in the past.
Why bother?
Has anyone ever done it?
Yes, one person did.
Actually, a couple of people have done it.
And an 8th grader science class
got an F on it because she explained how it worked
and they gave her an F because
they said that there's no such thing
even though she had the XRF fluorescence,
which is a fancy way of having it tested
by a metallurgy lab, that it was gold.
So it's like the Wright brothers
would have gotten an F on aerodynamics.
You know that, right?
Because they didn't actually, yeah.
So this is, I mean, come on.
And people think, you know,
they don't even know how to keep time
and they're going to talk about how to make metals.
You've got to harp on them for that, you know?
No, this is true, right?
Just like I find it necessary to mention
in every show that, you know,
just like those who swear that they live their lives
by their practices in a spiritual sense,
because I don't want to use the word religion around you.
Well, mind, religion is fine.
I'm very religious.
I brush my teeth, comb my hair,
and tie my shoelaces whenever I can.
Quite religiously.
Yes.
There you go.
But the thing is that, you know,
those who adhere to the Christian faith,
allegedly, holding up air quotes for you listening,
you know, none of them bother to read the text.
And I love that one.
I love pointing to that one
because we're sitting in this particular part of the world.
But as you like to point out,
supposedly engaged in these faiths,
and not just the parishioners,
but the alleged scholars of those faiths also,
none of them abiding by their text anyway.
At all.
And you could say that very safely, Chuck,
in any religion,
because in any religion,
if anyone studies the text
that they allegedly are supposed to subscribe to,
there's no way they could call themselves
by the name of the corresponding religion.
Right.
Unless they're totally insane or evil.
And evil meaning that they want to go back in
and really shear the sheep, you know,
and for profit.
I mean, the thing is that there is a lot of that going on,
but they're ignorant.
They're just high.
They're on this high, you know.
But, you know,
the worst places about the whole religion thing
is the planet Earth.
You weren't expecting me to say it like that.
No.
The whole Earth is wrought with bad religion,
in that sense.
And spiritual just means the mind.
So that's being used, like,
psyche is the PSY.
Whenever you see PSY prefix,
that means spirit.
So a psychologist is a spiritualist.
You know, a psychotic is spiritually chaotic.
Which makes a hell of a lot of sense, actually.
A psychopath is a spiritually pathological way.
And I'm tired of hearing about the psychopaths
and this and that.
Man, the last thing I want...
I was out to the shops today.
I mean, we're fine.
Humans, you're doing great with your leaders.
Trust me.
They're doing a fine job.
You may not like it,
but it's the best you're going to get.
Well, yeah, I point that out all the time,
is that, you know,
there's a faction in the alternative media
that likes to discuss the overthrow of leadership everywhere.
Oh, boy.
And I'll tell you,
if you're not on board with them,
if you're not part of their, you know, anarcho-ism,
and that's what I call it,
they're not anarchists, not at all.
A true anarchist would be
everyone is the president,
everyone is the judge,
everyone is very highly responsible,
there's no crime,
and everyone acknowledges a deity over their country,
and that's who they go to.
And that happened only in history a few times,
in ancient history.
But that term is not even used properly.
Exactly.
So that's why I said, you know...
These alternative people that want to overthrow or change,
you know what, they remind me of stories
about the old communist meetings,
when they wanted to change into the new, you know,
people's way of doing business
in the turn of the century,
the last century, right?
They had to have these meetings,
and they would tell the people,
yes, when we take power,
everyone will have, you know,
steak dinners and strawberries for dessert.
And someone in the back is like,
well, what if I don't like strawberries for dessert?
Well, you will eat what we tell you!
Right? So there's your sign.
So these people that want government change,
go and start discussing certain things with them,
and you're going to know,
you're going to see very quickly
why the people that are in power are in power,
and they're not.
Right.
And the truth is that if you gave these people
what it is they wanted,
some of these overthrow zealots out there,
if they actually accomplished
what it is that they talk about incessantly,
without doing anything about it, by the way,
but if you actually saw their, well, vision
come to fruition,
if you think things are bad now...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you didn't see nothing.
Here's the thing.
Talk about the end of the world.
You know, in countries that have capital punishment,
when you're on death row,
they give you your last meal, anything you want.
Now, when a society is on death row,
you're going to get whatever you want,
your last wish, before you go out.
And what it will be,
what everyone wants in the current society
is no war, peace.
They want what they call liberty,
prosperity, freedom, things like that.
And they're going to get that for a short time.
And when they do get it,
it's going to be promised to last for a thousand years.
And it's only going to last for a couple of years,
and then glitches will form in the system,
and the world leaders are going to make
some unusual requests,
or it will be very unusual,
to put us back on track.
And the people will do it,
because it will be the real deal for a short while.
That's before the final blows.
So, yeah, these are things we will get into more specifics.
But right now, I hear that,
what do they call them,
think tanks pay like $10,000 to $100,000 per page.
I think I might want to keep it as proprietary information,
because I know what the think tanks are providing governments
about what's coming is absolute rubbish right now.
So if anybody out there is listening,
you can drop us a line somehow
if you want to know what's coming in great detail,
and we could start maybe forming some kind of an organization
that could be well-funded to do so,
because it should be well-funded.
So I figure I'd drop that in.
This is not for now.
This is in a few years maybe,
but right now would be great.
But that's pretty much with the radiation.
And how many times, let's just go back to it, Chuck,
how many times do you hear people say,
oh, look at the wildlife, look at the sea life,
oh, oh, oh, you know, you hear that all the time, you know.
Ridiculous.
What people are not taking into account
is that there is something called a food chain in the ocean, yes.
It's called a food chain.
Yeah.
And how does that food chain work?
So it means you've got big fish eating smaller fish,
which eat smaller fish, which eat smaller things
that are no longer classified as fish,
which eat even smaller things.
And guess what?
Some of the biggest fish are not even fish.
And they don't even eat fish.
Boy, that was not a, was that almost like a limerick?
It could have been.
Tiny.
But anyway, yeah.
So the whales eat plankton.
And if the plankton is disturbed,
the small fish and other creatures that rely on it,
they're not around.
Well, then if they're not around, the small fish,
how are the bigger fish going to eat them?
And if those bigger fish aren't around,
then what's going to happen to the bigger fish that want to eat them?
What's going to happen to the sea,
all the sea lions washing up on shore,
what do you think they eat?
Fish.
Okay, so now what part of the food chain is disturbed?
The plankton.
What do plankton eat?
Hmm.
One thing, it's very important that the plankton get silica in the ocean water.
Where does the silica come from?
The atmosphere.
Where does it get in the atmosphere?
Desert storms.
Not the war that was propagandized to you,
but the desert storm.
Now, if you've actually been watching the occurrence of desert storms,
like places like the Namibian Desert,
where it rains like five inches in 40 years, right,
or Gobi Desert, right,
places that are famous for their very large Sahara,
very large open plains,
and massive dust storms where the dust particulates in a colloidal form
go up to the stratosphere and are deposited into the oceans,
has anybody been discussing the food chain?
Oh, no, it's Fukushima, radiation.
Oh, man.
That's why I tell the young people,
you're screwed,
because years ago the older generation used to be sound wisdom and sound information.
And, I mean, no wonder they're being put in nursing,
they're being stuck in old age homes and pumped up with drugs,
I mean, because they haven't been saying anything worthwhile for a long, long time.
It's really, really bad.
Yes, and chemtrails also.
Now, all you need to do to wipe out the sea life is form a chemtrail.
We lost your audio.
I think I'm still broadcasting.
Maybe you said something that shouldn't have been said.
There you are, okay.
Something, the microphone went out, so we'll try it again.
Oh, my, okay, yeah, you're definitely on a different microphone now.
Oh, yeah, well, the microphone died.
So, yeah, it's a scary night, isn't it?
So that's why we're talking the way we are.
So we're going to try to mitigate that.
Right.
But, yeah, the next thing I wanted to talk about was the Middle East, perhaps,
unless you want to discuss something else about radiation.
But there's something called Nuclear Scare Scam on YouTube, Nuclear Scare Scam,
and that's a two-hour watch by Galen Windsor.
It's a must-watch.
So I'm going to try another one.
There we go.
Okay, you're back again.
Keep us entertained with your voice there for a moment,
and I'll try to rig up another one.
No problem.
Well, you know, it is interesting that we would go into the Middle East
because there have been developments in the past week or so, or alleged developments.
I laugh at them personally because, you know,
this big announcement that came out of the White House earlier in the week
that we're sending ground troops to Syria.
Now, why did this make me laugh?
Not merely because of my association with the Greek and his views on this,
but my own analysis of what I see,
independent analysis of what I have seen
and continue to see evolving in that CENTCOM sector of the world, right?
I use that term intentionally.
What we see, which, by the way, I think your audio is back now, Greg.
Yes.
What we see, though, is this idea that they have introduced troops into Syria, right?
Okay, and it turns out that it's 50 troops that they state they have introduced.
They're 50 special forces troops.
Now, how laughable is that?
Well, first of all, I wouldn't send 50 special forces troops to try and take over Newark.
All right?
I don't know who the hell is going to buy that they've sent 50 special forces troops
to deal with anything of significance in the mass of land they call Syria at this point.
First of all.
And second of all, there's a whole bunch of support personnel that are required to do that.
I know this from a logistical perspective.
I've known many more than one military individual,
definitely many more than one special forces person, military intelligence people of all kinds.
This is a fiction, a nonsensical fiction.
It's been introduced to you to give you the primer, whatever you want to call it,
for what is yet to come.
There is a much larger engagement being, well, kind of put in place.
The table is being set, okay, over there in the Middle East.
And this is their way of saying, well, we told you we sent some troops over there.
So that grand deception continues from our alleged government.
And the truth is none of the real information about what's happening on the ground there is getting out.
However, we can tell you exactly what is going to happen.
Whether you told the truth about it or not is a different story, I think.
But I don't know how you see that because, you know.
Well, how I see it is objectively.
Okay, so there's something called, I don't like to use the word, starts with a P,
about events that are going to come.
And, again, there's the problem with talking about a lot of the ancient texts and they write away the people.
They say, well, that's religious.
And who wrote that anyway?
Who cares?
Well, you know, if you study it, you'll see it has nothing to do with what people have been told.
But I can tell you with great specificity, especially in the future,
well, actually, we're not going to give too many specifics because maybe we can start a think tank
where we can give the proprietary information.
But the cat's already out of the bag.
I've been pushing this for a long time and there is more resurgence of it on the Internet now
that there's a Middle East Union coming to the Middle East.
Let me say it again.
A Middle East Union.
Some might want to call it the Levant, but it's beyond the Levant.
It's going to stretch all the way to Iran.
Now, that's all we have to say.
There's a lot of specifics, enough to, like, choke a mule.
Okay?
But this is all the specifics that one can handle at the moment
because there's a psychological or spiritual problem with listening to this information.
And how the hell are you going to go through specifics?
So I don't, even though I have in the past to some degree.
In order for there to be a union like the European Union,
can you have France at war with Italy
and a very nationalistic government in Germany that doesn't want to talk to England or Spain
and a country, let's say, like Greece, who doesn't know who it wants to ally with?
Can you have that situation and have a European Union?
The answer is no.
No. See, that's the problem here.
There's too many nationalistic governments.
They don't want to work with each other.
Right at the moment.
And what's happening cosmically on this earth is the European Union is one of the precursors
and prerequisites before the final draw in the society is pulled open.
And that will happen no matter what.
And that's why you had the governments being replaced one by one in the Middle East.
You know, Iraq twice.
Now the irony of Iraq being hit twice by the U.S. is, you know,
you ever notice very often when the U.S. gets involved in an engagement,
the country splits north-south or east-west, like east-west Germany,
north-south Korea, north-south Vietnam.
You ever notice when the U.S. gets involved,
this particular spiritual entity that's behind the U.S.,
part of its characteristics is when it goes to fight,
just like a bear when it fights has a characteristic different than a lion, let's say,
or a dog or a wolf.
This particular creature known as the U.S. in battle,
because these battles have to take place in another realm,
it has a characteristic whenever it gets involved, it splits the country,
just like it split Colombia.
Oh, how did it do that?
Were you ever in a company called, a company, yeah, a country called Panama?
I've gotten into the habit of calling countries companies lately.
I mean, that's my strive for precision, I guess.
But anyway.
Well, you know what?
It's not an unfair thing to say, and I'll tell you
that this is not merely a military tactic that comes to fruition
via the alleged United States actions.
This is something that is done strategically in all things.
What is relevant here is that you divide,
and then you pit the existing pieces against each other.
Well, even if they were...
But this is what's done in all things.
Think about it socially.
You're supposed to divide yourselves between two political parties.
You're supposed to divide yourselves between this way and that way.
There's usually two directions to go,
and you're supposed to stand on either side of a line.
This is really the specific strategy.
That's the entity.
The spiritual entity behind the Americans is like that.
That's why they have Democratic and Republican.
That's why it was very easy for people to comprehend the Civil War,
which it was not as North versus South.
It was the Federal versus the States.
It had nothing to do with the North versus the South.
The Federal garnered the support of the North.
So the American entity, the spiritual entity, or the force,
the cosmic force behind what's known as the United States,
is a dividing one, a bipolar, let's say.
And when I mention those other...
Every military, well, most military engagements,
major military engagements that the U.S. gets involved in,
the countries are split.
They may not be directly responsible as such,
but they are within that kind of framework.
Now, they went into Iraq twice.
Now, Iraq is going to be split.
Okay?
And we've said what's going to happen there in previous...
And a new country is going to be formed,
and it's going to be the revival of the country called Assyria.
Not Syria. Assyria.
When I tell people this, they walk away and say,
Well, you're saying Syria is going to come into play.
It's already a country. Ho, ho, ho, ho.
I'm like, you know, you're not listening.
It's Assyria, not Syria. Assyria.
That's funny because Syria is in the news.
But anyway, you're going to see that country coming into fruition
in the next few years or less.
What's going on in Syria is nothing more than the entrance point
of public world opinion acceptance of battles there.
Without getting into specifics, Jordan is next.
Lebanon is already in shambles.
That will be rebuilt.
Iran is going to unify.
I was on a...
Do you remember when Iran had...
When I mean Iran is going to unify, they have two governments.
They have a secular and religious government, right?
They have the president.
Right, you have that Rafsanjani or whatever,
and then you have the supreme leader, which is the Ayatollah Khomeini.
So you have two governments, yeah.
Prior two years ago when they had the elections,
when Ahmadinejad was still there, he was very secular.
He wore, you know, suits from Brooks Brothers, right?
In a tie.
And I said, you're going to see a movement forming in Iran.
It's going to be very silent,
where the governments eventually will unify
and you're going to see the Ayatollahs becoming more secular
and you're going to see the secular government becoming more religious.
And look at the current president.
He's wearing the religious garb, right?
He doesn't wear a Brooks Brothers suit.
And look at the Ayatollah.
He's actually come out and commenting on crisis moments
and things like that, where he never did before.
Right.
Okay, now it's not because I'm psychic or a good predictor or anything,
because these things were written about very specifically,
which we will not discuss the extreme specifics on air,
because we could spend eight hours just discussing the specifics of Iran.
It's not necessary, because what people don't understand is that
in order to form a union of ten nations,
which only nine exist right now, by the way,
the tenth nation is still not on the scene,
how can you have that when you have nationalistic governments?
The governments basically have to have their teeth pulled out,
and have to be willing to work with each other,
with policies very much like you see in the EU.
But it's not going to be like the EU.
They're not going to have a common currency and things like that.
They're not going to be run by Germany.
The EU is not the EU.
The EU is Europe run under Germany,
and that's what the National Socialist Party of the Third Reich wanted to do.
They accomplished their goal.
One of their goals was to unite Europe under Germany, which they did.
The Middle East is going to be very different.
So I'm tired of listening to people about World War III,
and the genocide of the Palestinians.
That's another one that irks me.
Okay, so all the Palestinians are going to be wiped out.
Oh, really?
Okay, so that means if they were all wiped out,
except for one man and one woman,
they can still procreate, right?
I'm not saying that they all should, down to that number.
But they're using terminology here that is highly emotionally charged
and just downright stupid.
You see?
But you don't mean to say that Palestinians are not being mistreated.
Oh, they are, but they're being mistreated.
There are actually just as many Palestinians dying from their own,
I'm going to catch flack for this,
from poverty and crime from their own leadership,
who gets a ton of aid, not as much as Israel,
and they don't share it with the people.
I mean, look at Arafat.
Arafat was not Palestinian, he was Egyptian.
And you've heard of Imelda Marcos and her shoes?
I mean, we shouldn't talk about these things because this is out of date now.
Imelda Marcos looked like a pauper.
So they're embezzling all this international funding,
not giving it to the people.
They go into meetings with countries around them like Egypt and Israel,
and they go into treaties and they don't hold up their end of the bargain.
Because a lot of these treaties are not just a handshake like they show you on TV.
There's a lot of stipulations and things you have to do, and they don't do it.
So their leadership is very, very poor.
But there are specifics that are going to happen.
They're going to be just fine,
but there's going to be a major, major engagement with the modern-day Philistines.
That's what they are, the modern-day Philistines.
That it's going to shock the world.
It's going to shock the world in the near future.
Not near future like tomorrow or next week,
but it will be a level of carnage that has not been seen since,
what was that tsunami that hit in 2004 or 2003?
It was the Sumatra Islands?
Oh, right.
The one that took out, what, part of, oh, my.
Only about six-figure numbers dead.
So anyway, we don't need to discuss that now because the people,
here's the thing, what day is it?
What time is it?
Where are you?
These things, this is way beyond the maturity level of the humans.
Why?
Not because they lack the maturity or they lack the,
they're too stubborn and rebellious.
They want to be into these little groups.
They always, I could see them, they're surfing the Internet.
And this resonates with me.
I'm going to join and support this group.
And if they study what the group is actually talking about,
they'll find that it's completely inaccurate.
So what we're discussing here with the Middle East is,
if one understands the mechanism for ten nations to come together,
and you look at the current status of the Middle East,
and by the way, when you talked about the troops earlier,
it's not only the American troops that are going to be there.
Every country in the world pretty much is going to have troops there in the near future.
Well, my point about it is that we're not being told the reality here.
They tell us 50, it could be 5,000.
And that's not counting the support personnel, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
And the truth is that many nations could have already converged on Syria.
How are you going to tell me that I'm wrong if I told you 12 nations are in there right now?
You know, prove it.
Prove me wrong.
Well, we don't know.
But the thing is, here's the thing, Chuck.
So they're misinforming us because they deliberately want to misinform us.
That's the left hand.
And the right hand is, you know what, they don't even know what's coming next.
Oh, no, I do believe they have no clue what they're initiating.
A lot of times when you see these world leaders and pundits, what you see is what you get when you meet them.
Actually, they're a lot more glorified in public sometimes when you meet some of these, quote, unquote,
robber barons or famous people in person.
You're like, dude, man, you're nothing like you are on air.
You know, what is that?
Are you a puppet or what?
So, yeah, I would say that right now it would be safe to bet that the majority of the world community leaders do not know what's coming next.
And this New World Order talk is another thing.
You know, the New World Order that people are familiar with is going to play second fiddle to another New World Order that hasn't come on the scene yet.
Well, right.
I mean, after all, the really soulless, seemingly soulless corporation.
They are soulless, yes.
That has overtaken a great deal of what is necessary for human life on this planet is one thing.
The one thing that they have not really fully grasped is the spiritual side of it.
They try to control language.
They try to control a lot of things quite unsuccessfully in a lot of cases.
But with that, like, back end success, like we were talking about before, you know, they've controlled the language already.
That work was done for them.
The statements are getting out of hand, but the language was already controlled ahead of time for them.
But what is going to emerge is something else that nobody imagined, who is commenting about these things right now, who is discussing it, who is pontificating about the Middle East and the fallout of it and what it's really going to come down to.
They don't know.
This is, you know, you and I right now, I assure you, are the only ones discussing it on this, I don't know how many billion of sites.
It might sound kind of arrogant to say that, but it's a good assurance.
It's not a guarantee, but it's a good assurance.
And, again, if anyone is interested in more details, just go to the donate button on AFR and drop in about four or five million in lawful money, please.
And you go to the Greek and the Ocelli site and drop in about four or five million through PayPal, and we'll get serious.
We'll get down to specifics, you know, in lawful money, of course.
Absolutely.
Look, four or five million dollars into one of those two places, and I guarantee you...
We'll start doing the write-ups on it.
Yeah, we'll map the whole thing out without delay, in fact.
Thirty grand a page, a hundred grand a page, whatever.
Yeah, the going rate.
Yeah, if you want to know before time.
Otherwise, just sit back, and when it starts, you'll be scratching your head later.
But in the meantime, these things are going to happen very simply because man is always aghast and in horror when man is doing war, right?
I mean, man is at war right now.
The legal society is at war with mankind, and they don't even know it.
And the medical society is at war.
And the religious society is at war with their own people, and they don't even know it.
But they're at horror with the overt war.
The reason this is going to all go back to the Middle East is because when the gods begin to do war, that's where they will start.
And if you want to understand what real horror is, it's when the gods do war with the gods, and the gods do war with man.
And one of the things that is written that will happen is when this starts to happen, man actually tries to do war with the gods.
Which is going to be quite funny to see, but actually it's going to be quite a horror.
So anyway, what was that?
It was a short film about the two angels talking about one guy killed 80,000 Assyrians one night.
And the other guy looks at him and says, do you ever play soccer?
Like, that's really hard, you know?
Yeah, well, that's the truth.
That is funny.
Yeah, yeah.
Some film, I don't know.
Dogma or something.
I think it was dogma.
If it wasn't, it could have been in there very easily.
By the way, that's one of my favorite films.
So all things started, all your folklore, all your religious stuff started in the Middle East, all the origin of man, even in secular history.
It's going to end there, but it's going to be with a really loud bang.
And yeah, that's why the Middle East has to be set up, just like you set up a stage.
Don't take it personal, folks.
So that's what's coming in the Middle East.
So I figure if we can get around $10 million in donation tonight between the station and the Greek and Ocelli website,
we could still do the radio show and still do the consulting because we've got it all pretty much put together.
It just needs to be given out, and it won't be given out in great detail in public first, at least not until the 2018-2020 period.
Well, right, and why give away something so valuable?
OcelliInTheGreek.com, AmericanFreedomRadio.com, and believe it or not, we've run out of both hours tonight.
I hope that you guys have taken something from all of this.
I know I have.
Anyway, thank you once again, sir.
Thank you again.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion, and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years, and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein, is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO, and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367, and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at hempUSA.org.
What kind of person are you?
How do you see yourself?
Are you the kind of person that lets everyone else do all the work,
just hoping that you'll be able to get some of the crumbs that fall from the table?
Or are you the kind of person that rolls up their sleeves and does the dirty jobs that no one else wants to do?
Are you hoping that all the activists giving their blood, sweat, and tears to serve humanity are going to solve all the world's problems?
Or are you just wondering, is there something simple I can do to contribute?
Yes, yes there is.
Help us.
Help us do what we do.
Partner up with American Freedom Radio today by gifting a regular amount to support the network and your favorite hosts,
bringing you less commercials and more information.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and start donating today from between $1 and $100 per month,
according to the kind of person you are.
Thank you very much for your support.
Yo, what's up? Check this out.
The voice of the revolution.
American Freedom Radio.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit, and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape,
various pain-related healthcare costs, epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders, and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer.
And it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD. Come join us.
We all know that they're not telling us the truth,
so stand up for your rights, demand the real medicine, and your right to use it and grow it.
This is Rick Simpson, and you're listening to American Freedom Radio.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.