American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no other media outlet would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
If you're on the Pacific left coast and looking at that very same wind-up toy or digital representation thereof, guess what?
Well, it might be 9 p.m.
So what they call Saturday or what they call Sunday or whatever,
but it doesn't matter because nobody really knows how to tell time anyway.
So good evening, Greg.
How are you today?
Good evening.
Doing okay.
It appears to be around, let's say, the 18th day, perhaps the 19th really, till noon of the 10th month,
which is not hard to figure out that it's the 10th month if you say December with your own mouth.
Everybody with me?
Say it.
You ready?
December.
D-E-C prefix means 10.
Right?
Is that interesting?
Well, like a decimal point generally referred to, you know, something that was divided by 10, right?
Yeah, deca in Greek is 10.
Right?
Decimate.
Decimeter.
Everybody forgets.
You know, they think of millimeter, centimeter.
Well, after centimeter comes decimeter.
That is the meter divided into 10 equal parts, I think.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, and cent means 100.
And, yeah.
So it's quite interesting.
You know, people love to follow, and they're always looking what to follow next.
Not necessarily for a sense of importance or a sense of unity, but just for the sake of following,
because it doesn't make any sense why people follow what they do.
I know.
It sounds like now we're speaking in circular rationale here because people do follow,
but if you look at what they're following, it's very irrational.
And I'm not even sure that people really follow because, after all, if you follow through that logic a bit,
you take a look at the followers and you go up the food chain, eventually you find a leader.
And quite honestly, I don't see too many leaders.
Where are the leaders?
Yeah.
Well, it's external input for sure on one end, and on the other end, you know,
mankind right now has successfully, without a doubt,
eliminated any reality or any conscious reality based on information of the spiritual world.
Okay.
They have succeeded in that.
You know what's interesting?
So having a conversation about, you know, how evolution, you know,
it came from single organisms and so on and so forth.
But in their history, they tell you that civilization started in the Mesopotamian region,
which would now be the modern Middle East.
Man, you know, weren't these single cell organisms everywhere on the planet?
But why did they have to have the ones that evolved into humans in the Middle East?
Interesting, isn't it?
I always found that odd, even when they used to tell us about how all life evolved from the African continent.
But at the same time, you came from what they called the primordial ooze, right?
Isn't that the phrase they used to use?
The primordial ooze.
Yeah, and that came from Egypt, where the pharaoh, there was a time,
one of the later pharaohs that basically got kind of arrogant and said,
I made you as a civilization because you came from slime from the Nile.
Now, if that's not something out of Darwin, you know.
So, and after that point, it was demanded that, from a spirit cosmic level,
that Egypt be reduced to a base society, never to rise again within these ages.
And that was written around that time as well.
And guess what? They haven't.
If you go there, they're still in ruins.
So, yeah, interesting stuff.
You know, the concepts of what people hear of that they don't want to accept or even comprehend,
they call cognitive dissonance, right?
We've heard that before.
It's a psychiatric or psychological term, cognitive dissonance.
What about cognitive resonance?
What about things that people resonate with?
And if you look at what they're resonating with, it seems to be based on,
I don't know, who's got the best showmanship?
Who's got the thing of the week, the du jour of the day?
Yeah, I used to describe it as the land of the carnival barkers
because what happened was, whoever put on the best show,
it didn't matter if there was anything that was substantial to it,
but those who put on the best show seemed to get the most attention,
to garner the most wealth, to be the most valued, etc., etc., right?
I mean, this is one of those things that has been –
well, you can look at recent history and see it, no doubt about that,
but, I mean, it seems to have been going on for quite a long time.
And when you talk about cognitive dissonance, right,
this is one of those terms which has emerged recently,
although it seems like it's a much older sounding term
than most of what you hear tossed around, say, in the alternative or underground media
where there are points of discussion to be had all the time.
But, yeah, you're right.
They don't ever talk about what is resonating with people on a cognitive level.
Now, some might say that's because people are extremely damaged,
and I don't disagree, that's for sure.
I'm sure you wouldn't disagree that people are kind of damaged though, right?
No, I would say – well, again, we've discussed how it's 100% external input.
There's really nothing in the mind.
It's receiving and broadcasting based on external impulses,
and I know that gets a lot of people wiggling around in their chair or wherever they are,
like, you know, I don't think that's true,
but it's going to be quite a shock when they discover it to be true in the future, the first part.
And the second part is, I think we've also discussed this idea,
let's say it's an idea now, that there's cosmic censorship.
People cannot see it because they're not allowed to see it from a higher force.
Well, right, and then somebody might say, well, great, don't you believe in free will?
Yes, the cosmic censorship is what dictates the path of the steam liner
or the ship going from London to New York.
Now, when you're on that ship, you can go on the deck, or you can go mid-level,
or you can go down into your cabin, or you can watch a movie on a big ship.
So you do have a level of free will on the ship,
but everyone on the ship is going from London to New York, let's say.
So the concept of free will is on a micro level,
and the concept of the cosmic censorship and being guided by an external force is the macro level.
And then, of course, it fractals out, because if you kind of look at the ancient soothsayers
and a really good, quote-unquote, medium can actually tell you your future with great accuracy
in almost in a way that is not understood when it's delivered,
but you'll see it come to fruition later.
It has nothing to do with creating your own reality.
It's just a matter of seeing the signs.
Yeah, let's stick to the cruise ship, right?
If the soothsayer is on the cruise ship and you're also on the cruise ship,
you think you have your free will, but the soothsayer is aware that you're on the cruise ship,
then they can tell you that you're certainly not going to sprout wings anytime soon
and go flying off of the deck, and that, hey, eventually you're going to be in New York
because he's aware of the destination, let's just say, of the cruise ship.
Yeah, that would be the macro, and the micro would be what you're going to have for lunch tomorrow.
Right, and honestly, a lot of times you have now just received some external input from the soothsayer,
and therefore they have given you, here we go with the word, predictive programming
to indicate to you that this might be a good idea.
Yeah, well, also you can't forget the dummy load.
No, absolutely not.
Came right up in the chat room right when we were speaking.
Yeah, now here's the thing.
The three things are it's all external, there's a cosmic censorship,
and then there's a dummy load thrown on top.
What is a dummy load?
When you have energy in a system and it needs to be drained off
because using the energy in the system at the moment is not appropriate, let's say,
is one way to say it on a social level.
So what happens is people have a strong desire, let's say, to learn,
to find out about current events, to see what's quote-unquote trending.
We hear that a lot lately.
I was not sure about what that was until I started getting e-mails and messages about it.
So there's a bunch of energy that people want to put towards daily, weekly,
monthly discoveries or about their surroundings.
They have a lot of energy to put into discovering new things or hearing about new things.
So that energy is sent to ground or just wasted with dummy loads,
and the dummy loads are provided by the media, by the religious institutions, by the schools,
and that covers pretty much most places where people go to get information.
Well, right, and that certainly covers the dummy load aspect of it,
but then when you think about it for a moment, now somebody –
see, cosmic censorship is a little more complex than it sounds, I think.
Yeah.
So what do you view that?
I think we should because you say it a lot, and it makes sense.
It certainly explains a lot of why you see the dummy load prevailing
because, after all, if you're being guided into the dummy load,
based on the fact that you're not given the accessibility to search the reality around you
and your limitations on information prevail, well, what happens?
Well, you're going to be sort of directed into the dummy load, right?
Oh, yeah, and it's very difficult to avoid because it's in neon lights.
It's a come here now kind of thing.
Look at me.
It's what makes the most noise and the most attractive flashy colors.
Right, which is why the carnival marker wears red and has a very high hat and carries a stick.
And when we say media, by the way, in previous times we've discussed alternative and mainstream.
It's the same, folks.
Don't think there's a difference.
The only difference is that the level of sponsorship that censors the mainstream media
is what controls the flow of information.
And because there is a very low level of sponsorship on the alternative media,
there is less control of the information.
But the core of the information comes from the same dummy loading education,
whether you have a public education or a private education
or are subscribed to any of the major religions or political systems, it's all mainstream,
and that's what's brought to the alternative media as well.
So when we say media, it's both alternative and mainstream.
Again, the only discernment there would be the agenda for who's procuring the funds to keep the lights on.
That's why very often there's the act of asking for contributions from the listener,
which we don't do often enough, by the way, to keep a supply line of credit going for whether it's the AFR or the Ocelli effect.
Yeah, that's where the participation comes in from who is listening versus the mainstream media
where the participants are the ones selling you something and also control the information.
But the core essence of science, natural world medicine and all that,
and all the knowledge that people can partake in in both mainstream and alternative is the same.
It's just that the mainstream is more mum on mercury and vaccines, for example, right?
Alternative will scream about it, but neither one are talking about why do you need to put a hypodermic needle through the skin.
That's like the point that I make constantly, which is let's dial it back.
Sure, all of these things are poisons, et cetera, et cetera.
But I don't know why no one is considering that the act of injection in and of itself is a violation.
And I do not prefer to have to deal with it in that way.
Even if I did want to be inoculated, why is it that piercing the skin is a good way to go?
I ask that question all the time.
The body is under a vacuum, and whether it's positive or negative pressure,
you don't want to put a hole and breach that boundary layer.
What happens when you have a car tire and you make a small hole in it?
Eventually it will stop to serve its function.
But the body will heal that hole, but why would you do that?
Because nothing ever enters or leaves the body anyway, which we've discussed on the container.
Again, how many times have you heard people in alternative media talk about a virus?
You've got to laugh because that's a medical fiction.
No one has ever seen one or handled one or anything.
The only thing you will see about a virus is a computer rendering or a drawing.
No one has ever seen one in a microscope or dealt with one or anything.
And if you do see something that they categorize in the medical industry as a virus, it's mitochondria.
It's waste cells in the system that are waiting to pass at the liver.
But anyway, to go back to the cosmic censorship, what is it and why we discuss it?
Are you ready?
Yep.
Very simple.
There is a certain timeline that humanity needs to cure.
Just like, let's say, baking a cake 40 minutes or a five-minute epoxy takes five minutes, right?
Or concrete, three days to set and 28 days to cure.
There are certain times that certain things have to pass for certain things to manifest their quality.
Right.
A time of germination in a plant, I mean, it doesn't immediately turn from a seed into a stalk.
Nine months in the womb, right?
Okay, so all these things, this concept of curing or setting.
Okay, so there's a plan.
This has nothing to do with what you believe in.
This has been memorialized in a lawful way that still stands, so it has to be looked at.
Just like if you're conveying on a motorized wagon down a road and it says maximum speed, 65 miles per hour,
and every time you go down that road, that sign is still there.
It hasn't been taken down or contested.
Well, you want to start disregarding that.
There might be consequences, right?
So it doesn't matter if you believe in it or not or who put it there is irrelevant.
It has a standing at that point with your interaction.
So right now, mankind has enough of a story based on questions.
What is the meaning of life?
Why are we here?
What's this?
Everything's been answered, but they do not really want to look at it.
For example, the Kennedy assassination is a difficult one, but the 9-11 one is very simple.
It's very simple.
Not easy, but it's very simple to find out what really happened on 9-11 in a simplistic term
because four-inch-thick steel doesn't turn to dust on its own.
And no, it's not high-energy weapons from outer space and ridiculous crap like that.
It's not difficult to figure out what happened, but if you come out and blatantly talk about it,
people don't want to hear it because the trend is that no one knows, you see.
So this is the trend that you see in many subjects.
So essentially 2,500 years ago, with the advent of the modern religions that you see today,
including Christianity, by the way, because Christianity is based on the ancient Assyrian culture.
People are not aware of it.
And Mithraism, it's not biblical.
Neither is Judaism or anything else.
The major religions short of Islam.
Islam is a tough one because that's, you know, first century or so, first millennium or so.
But if you look at modern Islam, they're still doing basically the same practices that were practiced
around that 500 BC.
They just have a different name for it, you know, Sunni Wahhabis or whatever, different regions, right?
But around the 500 BC time, when most of the major world religions emerged,
there was a big turnover on the civilization of mankind, where up until that point,
man had a pretty good handle on his history prior to that.
So just to recap, around 500 or 600 BC, if you were alive during that time,
it was pretty much common knowledge of what human history was from that time and prior to that time.
But around that time, 500 or 600 BC, and after to our modern day,
all knowledge of that pre-500 BC society has been censored out.
Isn't that interesting?
Now, you know, somebody might say, well, but that can't be true because we know about the Roman Empire.
Which is later.
You know, which is later, right?
Yeah.
But it's been treated as if they knew about it, obviously, preceded the time of what they call the Christ, right?
Yeah, go ahead.
Well, let's just give a little more detail.
Around 500, let's say 600 BC, even, let's say, well, more accurately around that 500, 600 BC,
there was a world government, okay?
It was run out of what might be called the Babylonian system.
There was a common currency, common laws, common systems of weights and measures throughout the entire world.
As a matter of fact, this can be vetted by this archaeologist, I believe, Klaus Donner.
He does some really good work.
He's an Austrian, I believe, and he goes to Colombia in South America,
and he retrieves artifacts that are clearly Babylonian artifacts,
and he walks right through the airport with them.
These are part of ancient history in Colombia that are found in digs.
The government says, take them out of here because they don't agree to the pre-Columbian history that we teach in textbooks.
We're talking about Colombia, South America, let's say.
If you go all through the world, even Asia, you will see there was a Babylonian-type system.
Roughly 100 years after that, it was succeeded by a Medo-Persian-type system out of Persia.
Roughly 100 years after that, it was succeeded by a Greek and then Greco-Roman.
The Greek empire was very short-lived, I'd say about three, four decades, really two decades to expand,
and then three, four decades with the advent of Alexander the Great, but it started before him as well.
His father started it before he came of age, really sort of bringing the Greek city-states together, so we know that.
And expansions and also the philosophies and the sciences and things, yeah.
And then what happened after the Greek paradigm was put in throughout the world,
which spread all the way to the east, by the way, it broke up into four divisions.
You have the eastern-western-European, and then you had the eastern-western-southern part,
which would be, let's say, the middle-eastern in Africa.
And that's how it stands today.
The entire system still branches out from those four sections, still being the Greek paradigm.
Medicine, science, math, all that is still the Greek paradigm.
Democracy.
It was thusly adopted by the Roman Empire, which continued it on.
Which is neither a Roman nor an empire, it was the western part of the Greek aspect.
Yeah, and if you look at everything Roman, it's everything Greek, just Latinized,
and that language was developed around that time as well.
Right, their gods, their system, their idea of what money was, their conduct in warfare.
Right down to the tactics.
Even the phalanx was utilized by both societies.
I mean, it's endless, actually, the transposition.
Yeah, the interesting thing about the story about it,
it's not as simple as black and white as people like to see it.
But around that time again, the 5 or 600 B.C.,
when the switch went from Babylonian to the Persian convention,
and to the Greek convention now,
it was one of the most active axial periods in the history of mankind,
that can be referred to by quote-unquote moderns.
But again, to go back to that time,
people had knowledge of what society was like prior to them,
that we do not have now.
And in the near future, it will be revived again.
And the validation and verification of the information will also emerge.
I think that's why we, on the previous show,
I said, if you want to get in trouble, you agree.
And I said, you know, 4,500 years ago,
there were also 7 billion people on the planet.
We're talking about prior to what they call the Noah's Flood, let's say,
which is also memorialized in tradition in every culture on the planet, pretty much.
There was a big flood around that time.
And we don't need to go down the long list,
because even the most isolated native tribes had a quote-unquote flood legend.
So that could be what people could research on their own.
But now when we've been taught that population has been growing based on time, right,
almost linearly, and then it booms up on the 20th century or so into the billions.
But if you look at the, I guess, turn of the 20th century,
there was roughly 2 billion people on the planet.
And now it doubled in 50 years and then doubled again, right?
We're looking at, you know, four, five, 600% increase within 250 years.
That increase also happened 4,500 years ago, starting about 5,000 years ago.
You had a very small, you know, in the tens of millions, if not hundreds of millions.
And then within a century, it grew to billions.
And then another century, it grew to billions again, right?
Very interesting, because right now there's a polarity of a mirror image of this society
with the pre-flood society.
So it's very easy to sort of look at the correlations
and make a very educated guess at this point on that.
The only difference is now our lifespans are, you know, less than 100 or so.
And back then, their lifespans could have approached 1,000.
And that also has been covered up.
So in that way, actually, you do have an exponential increase.
Simply because you have a lower life expectancy,
then that means that the number's still growing at a very quick rate.
Even with the lower lifespan means that really there's more people.
There's a parallel there, but can you imagine having an average lifespan of 400 to 800 years
and having 7 billion people on the planet?
That is quite a different society.
I mean, like I think we gave the analogy of being able to walk down an open-air market
and someone says, well, I made this rug.
It took me 200 years to make it, and I made it myself.
That's very plausible if you live for 500 years.
That'd be one hell of a level of craftsmanship, right?
And by the way, when this type of craftsmanship is discovered and dated,
it's hidden from the public.
I assure you.
Yeah, I see.
Where in the world could somebody else get a hold of that information, though?
It will be open.
It will be open-sourced in the next few years.
What's interesting, I think we will reserve maybe some of the interesting concepts for the website,
Ocelli.com.
How's that?
In the future.
Okay.
Yeah.
But at this point, we'll just throw these things around.
And it's not BS.
It's maybe lifting the veil slightly.
There's some out there that get it.
Most maybe won't.
But I think it needs to be said.
Human history is far more interesting than anyone can even imagine.
It's sort of like the saying that the truth is much stranger than fiction.
Right.
What's interesting, though, about evidence is this.
And this is what also I would never advise anyone to speak publicly on these matters, even though we are.
You know, I'm not following my own advice.
Would be that you're living in a society where evidence means absolutely nothing anymore.
Okay.
It's a matter of, you know, does it resonate with people at the moment?
Right.
Is it in vogue?
That's very true, even on a very, like, microscopic kind of scale.
I find that even going to a very narrow issue, when I state, look, let's talk about what the legitimacy of the evidence is that backs the claim that, you know, you wish to make in just about any subject to anyone.
And it seems as though they point to people of authority making the same statement that they've made as if it were evidence without ever bothering to present something that is, well, let's just look at the scientific standard, for instance.
Right. If you can do an experiment and it can be independently recreated, utilizing the same materials in another place at another time, that's generally seen as evidence that your conclusion is correct that can be drawn from that action.
Right. So what's happened to that?
Because it seems to me as though that's no longer the case.
It's like the declaration is the evidence, and then you have to sort it out afterwards anymore.
It's the misinformation and the disinformation.
The misinformation is the lie that people believe in because they chat amongst themselves.
And the disinformation is something that's structured by an authority figure, whether it be scientific, medical, legal or governmental, deliberately to mislead the people.
And they know they'll absorb it. Like, you know, bullets aren't magic, right?
Exactly.
Okay. And so the people that put that structure, assembled the structure of that story together, knew that the society was not one based on anything methodological or based on evidence.
And they knew that any evidence didn't matter.
So they said, well, let's just make up a story.
And because we're in an authority figure, people will believe it because they've got better things to do, which worked.
And it also worked for 9-11. It worked for Pearl Harbor.
It worked for, you know, just about everything.
You know, people go and still get blood pressure.
I mean, geez louise, you know.
So anyway, there is absolutely nothing left that has not been corrupted by this laissez-faire attitude towards the truth.
Right.
You see. Yeah.
Well, you know what?
I want to read two things that got placed in the chat room only because, and I don't like to go to the chat room that often during the show.
But but quite honestly, I thought this deserved it.
Here's a statement. We have no proof that any ancient civilization had the tech we have now using telepathy instead of cell phones.
Ellipsis point. Is that what they did to communicate?
Now, that's one part. And then.
The question, do we live shorter lives with more illness because of the tech?
No, no, no. And no is the answer to those two.
People didn't have telepathy any more than you would consider that everything is an external input.
You know, you're constantly sending and receiving, which you could consider telepathy.
In other words, the telepathy that you're hearing about is no different than telepathy you have now.
You have now. It's absolutely the same.
There's nothing in your head.
That's why, you know, part of the dummy load is this Eastern mysticism that is obviously it's very that of Westerners have walked into,
you know, like the Eastern mystic religions and things like that is because it's very attractive and gives people self self-worth.
When they say you have to go inside of yourself or, you know, G.O.D. is inside of you.
All these things are inside of you, which is an absolute lie.
There's nothing inside of you, but it makes you feel good.
You see. Right. So it's the same thing with this tech. Knowledge of this tech has always been around.
Actually, it was more evolved in a rational sense prior to today.
It's just that it's steam engine time now. Right. I think we brought this up before.
The steam engine has always been around. Knowledge of that.
Actually, even in a more evolved sense. Twenty five hundred years ago or twenty two hundred years ago.
If you want to look up heroes engine, but it wasn't popular until the days of Fulton.
Why? Because it was steam engine time. See, right now it's iPad time.
It's geocentric satellite time. It's television time. It's computer time.
Right. It's electricity time. This these things have always been around.
And if you study the precursors to the sciences that people call technology today,
you will find that the precursor information is far more in tune with reality of what is really going on with this technology than we grasp today.
But now we're using it. You see, if you are, let's say, driving a steam locomotive,
you're more concerned about where you're going and what you're going to have for lunch than what it took to make that or what it takes to make that steam locomotive work.
Just like what people call driving a car.
People don't stop and think of, you know, the five thousand parts under the hood and, you know, of an automobile and how they were all put together.
They just want to get in and go. So this is a get in and go technology.
If you don't believe it, I would ask anyone to get inspired to open their computers, open their phones, open their whatever devices and start working on them.
And you will open it and you will see it is completely foreign to you.
Most people, you know, of course, there are techies that can do that. Right.
So, well, you know, and that brings us to another point, which, again, comes from the chat room, but I had it in my mind also.
The concept that we have these increasing influxes of electromagnetic fields, which I you know, it seems to me as though we didn't have these in in such great abundance before.
Of course, some people describe it as radiation. I guess it does radiate from particular points of origin.
So in a very technical way, it could be considered radiation.
But it's these overlapping and really aggressive sorts of electromagnetic fields that are all around us through the Wi-Fi, the cell phones, the electrical devices, et cetera, et cetera.
And I think that I don't think anyway that there could have been a point in history that we saw such a proliferation of them.
OK, those let's think of it another way. Most people think of electromagnetism, electromagnetic.
Let's say that's transverse. Right. It would be like what you see as a wave, like two people holding a rope and one person shakes her arm.
You see the wave move through the rope right to the other side. Right.
You can actually visualize it and the higher and lower you move your arm, the bigger the wave through.
Let's say a jump rope. You could see that. Right. So that's the amplitude. Right.
But then there's another type of wave which you don't see, which you pull on the rope.
You feel the tug instantly versus the wave which you have to wait for traveling down the road. Right.
Or down the rope. Those longitudinal waves were completely immune to.
OK, that's what Tesla used. J.J. Thompson alluded to that for making things weightless.
And I think, you know, this is the transverse.
So you sometimes you wonder if Skype is using it because you could be speaking to someone on the other side of the world and you get instant communication.
But so when you're the what is harmful is the transverse wave when it resonates.
Right. With a particular size of your physical body, meaning the size of a cell or an organ.
Here's an example. We could lay this to rest or let's just make the statement.
Most living creatures are completely immune to these types of waves or electromagnetic radiation.
It's when the electromagnetic radiation amplitude and frequency is so specific that it resonates with a specific part of the body or the cell.
Then it becomes dangerous. Right.
You know, this is the example I wanted to give.
There was communications, let's say cell phone type communications done by certain governments and military back in the 70s, 80s and 90s.
And they found that people that were working this equipment had a lot of what they call disability claims and physical injuries to their bodies from working this equipment.
So the quote unquote governments and military said, well, let's not use these frequencies anymore because it's causing harm to our people.
So they abandoned those frequencies and those are the frequencies that were picked up and became popular with what's known as cell phones today.
Nice.
Anyone can research this. Yeah. So they abandoned the frequencies and they opened them up for commercialism through cell phones.
So, yes, the what is being used by the cell phones predominantly would be in the category of potentially harmful, if not harmful.
Yes. But the majority of the electromagnetic radiation is not directly.
It is indirectly, though, because it changes effects on water, changes effects on air, which are indirect.
But sometimes the indirect effect over a long period of time, you know, it's like death by a thousand cuts kind of thing.
Yes. Yeah. Let's just.
Yeah. And if you could put it another way, if you want to be rational about it and you let's say we're just we came to this planet to visit.
We're going to we're out of here tomorrow. Right. Which is wise.
If you could get on a spaceship or a flying saucer and get off this rock, it's recommended, by the way.
But if anybody has a seat or two, we will definitely accept them on the next ship on off this rock shore.
Unless you're unless you're part of the management here, but who wants to manage an insane asylum in a pig farm?
But there you go. But the part of it is that if you were to be very objective where you're just going to get off here and, you know, have a good record,
you could say that if things continue the way they are now, there will be no life in 50 years.
OK, left on this planet and when I mean life, I'm not talking about human life, I'm talking about whales, birds, bacteria, plants, everything.
It will just be rendered on shutdown mode. But through the indirect disturbance, not the direct disturbance.
Right. Because even with a direct disturbance, like let's say the detonation of the largest thermonuclear devices times a million on the planet,
the planet recovers from it. Right. You could you could go and look at places where these devices have been, you know,
unleashed on the environment and there's they've recovered to a certain degree.
There's still plants and fish and animals there now. Right. It's we're talking about the indirect aspect.
And then in the future, again, there is going to be a revival of planetary.
What do you remember? I think it was Star Wars, the movie where they had the Death Star.
It was a planetary destruction device that could blow up a planet kind of thing.
Yeah. You're going to have that technology revived here.
Shadows of it exist now. And that will also be unleashed on this planet.
Yeah. But it will not be used because the planet will be here.
But those that will have it in their hands to use it will be, unfortunately, taken out before they can.
So I don't know why are we even going down this path. But.
We're not there's nothing to do with doomsday or fear porn or anything like that.
Well, and look, a lot of people could easily agree that if we continue trending in that same direction that it seems as though the cruise ship is going,
you know, eventually we're going to run aground and we've been running quite a while and, you know, the ground is approaching.
I mean, it's just that simple. Anybody will tell you that.
Even those who are telling you that global warming is the biggest threat in the world, which I still can't quite wrap my mind around,
because they keep changing the rules on that one. Greek.
Well, that's why we mentioned if anyone's old enough, remember back in the 70s and 80s,
if you had a motorized wagon, you looked at the speedometer and the 55 was in bright red as opposed to the other numbers,
because that was the most fuel efficient speed for the car.
And the reason why they wanted to impose consciousness on being, let's say, environmentally conscious,
was because we were supposed to be in an ice age by the late 1990s.
You could this is, you know, that was when, you know, then they distracted that with a big hole in the ozone layer, you know,
and then they discovered there really is no ozone layer. It's always moving.
And it's, you know, anyway. Yeah. So.
But besides that, there appeared to have been a hole in it long before there was ever all these things that they claimed were putting a hole in it.
So perhaps it's porous on occasion. That's all.
And it all comes out of academia, which is, by definition, not supposed to be conclusive,
always based on theory and no decision can be made.
Right. I mean, really wrap your minds around that for a moment.
I mean, that which they call academic, that which they call academia.
Right. All of it being rooted in something that is meant to come to no conclusion.
But I think we spoke about in the last show how the adversary is controlling all of the main institutions.
Right. Of this planet, whether it's science, medicine, religion, education, legal society, what have you.
Even the engineers. And let's stop right there, because here's the thing.
Regardless of what you think the adversary is, whom you believe it to be, et cetera, et cetera.
One cannot say that every institution appears to be adversarial in its demeanor, whether it be to the environment, to the people that it's supposed to serve.
I mean, it's literally, without pause, the revelations that come out about every institution, every organization that has some alleged goal is always in opposition to itself.
Right. The doctors make people sicker. Right. The military is supposed to be defensive and it's offensive.
Yeah. Yep. Schools dumb people down. You would figure that the legal society might actually care something about law.
They don't. And they don't. You know, I've never met an attorney or a judge that knew any law.
I even had and I'll share this with the public. A personal acquaintance was the man who penned what you call the Miranda rights.
His name is John Fitzgerald Malloy. He passed around passed away around 2008.
I've had several lunches and breakfasts with him and all these other things.
And I've always asked him about law and he didn't want to talk about it because then eventually I found out he really didn't know anything about law.
He just said that the only thing he was concerned with was whether if anyone was in his courtroom, he had jurisdiction over them.
And he was also concerned about lawyers charging by the hour, because when he was growing up doing that, they didn't charge so much by the hour as they do now.
So and that's all he knew. And I was I was astonished. And and what I mean by the Miranda rights is you have the right to remain silent.
You know that this is the man who penned that he was a Supreme Court justice. And I was shocked and amazed.
And yeah, so so I'm just speaking from experience on that part. Well, right.
But I mean, one doesn't have to even know someone who is that fascinating to observe it anywhere you go.
Your your stores that are supposed to sell you certain things seem to wind up being more occupied in selling you something that has nothing to do with what they advertise.
You know, it's endless, actually. Even your even your dummy box, your TV channels, your TV channels tell you they're one thing.
And, you know, they're actually something else. You know, CNN is running documentaries.
I thought they were the cable news network. MTV doesn't play music. Oh, now I sound like an old man.
But MTV doesn't play music, you know, and so on and so forth. True, true TV does nothing but speculate about things and and give you high drama without very much substance.
And that used to be court TV. So actually, that one kind of makes sense.
But but the everything is never as advertised. And that includes, of course, every religion telling you that they believe in a particular book or doctrine.
And yet they don't read it, reference it, know it or follow any of what's in it.
And yet they are allegedly a religion formed on these bases which are found in these documents.
But which one actually does what they're supposed to do according to their own doctrine?
None. And, you know, I was almost almost stepped on you there when you're talking about the television, because Philo Farnsworth, who allegedly invented the electronic television, was keen on inventing it.
Just he said, I want to invent this television. It has to be given to the public because it will end all wars.
And it will also enable everyone on every man, woman and child on the planet to be literate.
How did that work out? Yeah, not very well. So, you know, the the the thing about that is interesting.
And in the really old book, in one place, there's a there's another realm, something going on with the adversary and the head deity.
And he says, go to him and you can do what you want. Just don't kill him. Right.
And I'm not going to mention any specifics on that. If anyone has seen the movie, they know exactly what I'm talking about.
So it seems like all of these adversarial institutions are doing anything and everything to mankind except direct inflicting direct death.
Even the military, when you think about that, because if the if the military has a superior stance technologically in every aspect of what we call military superiority, why would you drag a war on for weeks, months and years?
You go away. Yeah. You see? Yeah. Yeah. You know that that has been.
And here we go back to my childhood questions. This is a question of mine from childhood.
Is that if you have a military which is so well equipped, you know, so well trained and is there to achieve a particular objective and is so knowledgeable,
then why is it that it takes so long and so many resources, so many lives to achieve said goal?
You would think that just like when if you and I were to sit down and play a game of chess after you beat me a few times, I might begin to learn from some of my losses, maybe, and make the game last a little longer or actually win it.
And if over time I played more than you and understood more than you, I would beat you simply because I have that ability after learning.
And it seems as though none of the militaries ever learn from their alleged mistakes.
And I say alleged mistakes because I think a lot of this has been done exactly on purpose.
At the end of the day, people talk about it being a racket and people talk about it being a tool to achieve particular objectives to bolster one's agenda, et cetera, et cetera.
But at the end of the day, really, war is conducted seemingly for the sake of war itself.
There's a revival.
And whenever you hear someone saying that war is being done for those reasons, by the way, for money, yes, there is a lot of money and all that.
It's a welfare system.
It also has to be tied in with the academics, the physicists and scientists, right?
They're the ones – everyone's looking at the military contractors, but it's also the quote-unquote scientists that are reaping the benefits as the second majority in that game.
And no one's pointing the finger at them.
But whenever you hear someone just harping on that, it's like a little child asking where do babies come from when they say the stork.
They can't really get into it because they're too immature.
Let's just say this once, and we've been passing, and I shouldn't be saying this, but I'll say it quickly even though – let's just say everyone cover their ears.
It's just me and Chuck talking right now.
The high command in most militaries today care not about what the war is about.
They're looking – they have a deity.
It's a very dark deity, and they just care about body count.
It doesn't matter if it's from their people or the other people.
They're looking for body counts to offer to a particular god, and that's it.
Okay, let's go back to the show.
Well, literally, it's the phrase.
It's human sacrifice.
Yeah, well, the phrase was in a lot of ancient texts was that you were meant to appease the god of war, right?
So that's the purpose.
That's the end of it.
Yeah.
Anything else is secondary and incidental apparently, but that doesn't mean that there aren't people who operate purely on that motive.
But what they're really doing is satisfying that particular deity that they –
And there's different gods of war.
You would have the gods of war that are inspiring the social events, right, the minor ones.
And they act in what people call vanity.
You know, how can you be the greatest military in the world, let's say,
and go fight people that are wearing basically sandals in knee-deep snow and take ten years to – right?
You know, go on for ten years.
It has nothing to do with what people consider to be war.
But as you go higher up in the spiritual realm, you also find that the highest deity also considers himself a god of war,
but he does not act in that form of vanity.
The lower gods are death by a thousand cuts, and the higher gods are just one swift blow.
And that is yet to come.
Yeah, and besides that, I mean, let's think about it practically.
If you are the chief deity or if you are the supreme deity, you would have to be a god of war as well as many other things.
So that is not your only concern, and you don't need to be appeased simply by that particular function, let's just say.
Sure, and it was sort of mimicked by the higher –
men were men, women looked like men, and the sheep were scared maybe,
but back in the days where the king would actually put on his armor and be in the front lines with his men.
Have you ever heard of stories like that?
I have.
I sure have.
What happened to those?
That doesn't happen anymore.
Not at all.
And I'll tell you something else.
Being that you're Greek, of course, you might actually make the men scared as well, but the sheep might be even more terrified.
Which is unlawful.
It's a bad joke, but I figured I'd bring it in because people tend to disassociate themselves with how unlawful they are,
and they should be reminded sometimes, which is another thing.
I guess today's show might be random conversations.
We're going into what's called the holiday season by the mainstream.
What holiday is it?
Why is it just holidays?
Why is it so generic?
And it's funny when you bring this up.
Let me just throw in one more thing.
Oh, it's just commercialism.
Well, don't you know that this is based on a revival of the ancient deities that were based on human sacrifice,
and the reason why they sacrificed humans to these deities was for prosperity?
So it's funny when you talk to people about why these holidays are here.
They say, oh, it's just commercialism.
It's amazing how obfuscated they are.
They actually know the truth about it, but they just can't go to the next level.
I just wanted to throw that in there.
Well, right, and of course the concept of awareness comes into play.
Is everyone truly aware that they're appeasing a deity sometimes?
I'd say not, but listen, if you throw the money outside of your door and somebody picks it up and can spend it,
guess what?
The result is still the same even though you're not sure where your money went past your door jam, okay?
But it's actually a wish of prosperity.
It's not even your money.
It's just a blanket wish for prosperity.
If you notice, most of the traditional holidays they ask people to make a wish,
or what would you like to have for this particular occasion?
You ever notice that?
Like what would you like for X, right?
Whether it's a birthday or Christmas or whatever, they ask you what would you like for X, right?
And it's a wish of prosperity, and obviously someone's going to have to go out and get it for you,
and that would be the end that you're discussing.
Someone's going to spend it, right?
Right.
Yeah, it's bizarre how these things work.
And traditionally and lawfully, holidays were reserved to honor your deity, right?
Right.
So anyway, let's just – yeah, because this is a conversation that can go on
and has been going on by certain individuals throughout history about what the hell is going on.
Well, right.
And you know, we may not be able to broadcast around what they call Christmas this year,
but we will continue to broadcast and continue to have these discussions,
just like we have in the first hour here.
So stay tuned for the second hour of Ocelli and the Greek.
We'll be right back.
What has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Provide us with free education?
Well, that's obviously a factor, but apart from reversing the dumbing down of America –
All the information they provide is free?
What about the free podium for broadcast activists to speak from, eh?
Exposing commonplace corruption?
They help vulnerable people who don't have a voice?
Bringing light to important information nobody else does?
Well, they never censor, hang up, or cut off their guests?
Well, that's no fun, is it?
Well, they created a fantastic alternative media sauce during an era of bad, manipulative,
and infiltrated mainstream and alternative media shows and scum?
Okay, well, apart from the free education, free information,
free podium for broadcast activists to speak from,
exposing commonplace corruption, helping vulnerable people without a voice,
bringing light to important information nobody else does,
and creating a fantastic commercial-free alternative media sauce
in a sea of bad, manipulative, mainstream and alternative media shows and scum,
what has American Freedom Radio ever done for us?
Donate to American Freedom Radio today.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
Oh, yes, I like it very much.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth,
and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you Hemp Protein Powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp Protein Powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein,
and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powders.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
Tell the truth, don't be bullshitting people.
There's enough bullshit as it is. In fact, there's just enough.
Did you know that?
There's just enough bullshit to hold things together in this country.
Bullshit is the glue that binds us as a nation.
Where would we be without our safe, familiar, American bullshit?
Land of the free, home of the brave, the American dream.
All men are equal, justice is blind, the press is free.
Your vote counts.
Business is honest, the good guys win.
The police are on your side.
God is watching you.
Your standard of living will never decline.
And everything is going to be just fine.
The official national bullshit story.
I call it the American Okie-Doke.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
The network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty
to deliver quality radio in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio presents
The only broadcast information no one would dare to understand.
The sonic entity known as Ocelli.
So the second hour begins and you may be wondering
what this external input is granting to you at the moment.
It is Ocelli in the Greek here on American Freedom Radio
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and if you missed the first hour
I have no way of describing it
so you may want to go to the archive and listen.
Anyway, you know...
And beyond, Chuck. Beyond the archive, by the way.
And beyond the archive. That's true.
Beyond the archive.
Certainly there is more to be examined
and you can find it.
Well, there's actually two websites
that have something to do with this show.
You have Ocelli in the Greek.com
and you have Ocelli.com.
Both of those websites
contain stuff having to do with this show.
And AFR.
AFR, American Freedom Radio, on their archives page.
Right. Their archive page is what I was referring to.
Yep, exactly.
This is where you can catch up on everything
and go past it too.
There's a lot of other things that can be gotten
and of course all contributions
to all of the websites are appreciated
because after all,
nobody is really being supported
by those entities that are controlling
the information that we were talking about
on the mainstream.
So that's why you have a little more
of something that resembles anarchy
out in the alternative media.
I hate that term, but anyway.
No, it's actually a very fit and proper one.
Anarchy just means there's no one on the top.
It's man goes straight to his deity
and requires every man, woman and child
to live in a very high level of education
and responsibility.
And there's really no misdemeanor,
very little misdemeanor or crime
in an anarchistic society.
It's just that they've taken that word
and turned it into something bad
to serve those that don't want it.
Yeah, anarchy just means no one at the top.
Each man, you know, the king of a castle,
a castle doctrine kicks in with anarchy.
So yeah, that way you literally have no head
is what it is.
I mean, there is no controller, no ruler.
Yeah, you would not be a subject to anyone,
but you would still have judges
and consultants.
Not everyone would have all the fine points
on how to behave and act lawfully,
so they would have to go to someone
whose job that was, which would be a lawyer,
let's say, or a judge, not an attorney.
Attorney and lawyer are not interchangeable.
You know, an attorney is someone
who represents a serf or someone
that's not competent.
And a lawyer is like next to friend
or amicus curiae, let's say in Latin,
which means someone whose job it is
to know the fine points of what is lawful,
to explain it to those who have better things to do.
You know, you might want to do something else
in your life than study what is lawful.
And law comes from your deity.
That's why you have what's called
the Halls of Justice or the Justice Department.
That is the revival of the goddess religion, right?
So that's the patron deity of the Western world
right now is the goddess religion,
and everyone's complaining about it,
and no one realizes it, though.
But anyway.
Right, and I do need to thank you
for making me cringe every single time
somebody uses the word justice now
because, quite honestly, I never considered it.
I always thought of it much in the way
that people use it.
You know, their intent when they use the word justice
is not what it actually does, of course.
But then again, it seems as though
nothing that is termed in a particular way
does what it says it's supposed to.
It's very nice.
It's very nice to think that justice is what you want.
And look up what those words mean.
Yeah, that's the other thing.
This is the dummy load free two hours
where we try to speak about things
the way they should be spoken.
And by the way, the reason why we're doing this show
is not because we're trying to say something
or be different or...
We're basically coming together and doing this show
because these things have to be said
simply because they're not.
And they're true.
I think when you and I got together,
Chuck, I said, well, let's do something
not because I really want to do this,
but because it's not being said.
And it's just fascinating and amazing
how simple these things are.
They're not easy.
You're not going to make friends with the truth,
by the way.
And I assure you, if people say that
they're telling you the truth
and you see them grouping up
and more than two or three people at a time,
it's going to be kind of hard to maintain any truth there
because if you want to destroy it,
start forming organizations around it.
But anyway, since we're jumping all over the place,
I want to just address what someone wrote in the chat
about why the 2300 year curing period,
and maybe it didn't make myself clear
or make the concept clear,
is that there's a 7000 year curing period.
But it seems like at around 2300 years ago,
there was pretty much ran out of things to keep us busy,
so it might as well just shut us down
and put us in the waiting room
where we're sitting around
flipping through magazines backwards.
We're in the waiting phase right now
because there's certain times in history
where a man was not abated this way
and he pretty much was ready to jump out of the pot
a little too soon.
Why do people always have the concept
that there is one particular deity that brings good
and another particular deity
that brings just evil or bad?
That's the schism,
that's the schizophrenic aspect
when people will find out in the future
is that the head deity brings both the good and the bad.
The adversarial deity doesn't do that.
The adversarial deity is the deceiver, the liar, right?
Well, he is meant to be the adversary,
so that's fine.
And the reality is that if you are the creator of all things,
then that means you are the creator of both pain and pleasure.
You are the creator of all things which are light and dark,
all things which are good and bad, etc., etc.
I mean, there is no real definition there.
If you're the creator of all things,
well, all includes the negative and the positive.
A couple of other funny things here.
Somebody said, you know,
no justice for me, mercy, please.
I do want to get into the concept of mercy,
but real quickly I just want to say,
yeah, every once in a while the Greek goes outside
and I hear the cricket too,
and I'm so happy that somebody else heard it
because a lot of times I thought it was just me.
Okay, so thank you.
That's a really good pun, by the way.
The crickets, you know, that's used as a metaphor, isn't it?
I hear the crickets, you know.
Well, certainly, yeah.
It comes from the idea that there were outdoor theaters,
you know, for a very long time
and a very quiet audience that wasn't, you know,
applauding or laughing or participating in the show
would allow one to hear the sound of crickets
because they were dead silent.
You know, they were falling asleep, this kind of thing.
Yeah, I just want to interject something.
Yesterday I was made privy to someone
who's done some work with cricket sounds
and what they did was they took the proportion
of a cricket's life to a human life
and slowed it down so it would be the proportion of a human life
and then played the cricket song
and it sounded like a chorus of people singing,
almost like, you know, the Tabernacle Choir
or, you know, some very well-talented chorus with instruments playing
when you slow down a cricket song.
And it's something about a cricket song slowed down.
You can research it on your own.
I don't have the specifics in front of me.
It's quite fascinating to listen to, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it reminds me of the guy who shows you the reverse language thing
where people are making statements that are relevant
to what they're saying when you play the tape backwards.
Sure.
And I, you know, people say,
oh, well, that's just, you know, crazy stuff
and the guy's manipulating the tape and so on and so forth.
And I say that it really becomes irrelevant
because backwards or forwards you're still not hearing
all of what's being said
and you're not speaking all of what can be spoken.
So it's really an irrelevancy at any rate, you know.
And I say that as an overall kind of thing.
Of course, you've heard it a little differently, but yeah.
Well, that's the wonder of the anthropomorphic form.
Anthropomorphic meaning as we look at mankind
and most of the natural world resembles certain things
that we have, you know, fingers, feet, ears, eyes and all that.
But the pure anthropomorphic form, man and woman,
is so we can interact with the quote-unquote universe,
all of our environment, a certain way.
Yeah.
So, but, you know, everything has a front and a back
and an up and a down
and it's relative to specifically the anthropomorphic form,
which I think we might have covered slightly in the container
that we spoke about, you know, the human body
and how it's structured to a certain degree.
But anywhere else, where do you want to take it, Chuck?
Well, you know, like I said, going further on these types of things,
I mean, we explained the 2300 years.
We've gone through a lot of these different things.
But, you know, it still doesn't really fully explain the cosmic censorship.
Okay.
Do you want to go back to that?
That's fine.
Yeah, I think we should go back to that
because we sort of passed over it and ended up in another direction.
I think that that's really the key here
because no matter what, like I said before,
you know, when people want to argue about the use of language
and what is extremely powerful, you know,
I always have this feeling that I want to speak up and say,
you haven't seen anything yet, you haven't heard anything yet,
and you haven't really said anything yet.
The thing is, well, okay, there's description and explanation.
At this point, we can give, unfortunately,
the best description based on a proper interpretation
of what's been memorialized before us.
What's going on right now is there's a lot of movement,
including bowel movements, that people are making things up all over the globe,
you know, the New Age movement, scientific movement, all this stuff,
I mean, medical, legal, across the board.
It's just this fiction, and what makes it fiction?
And by the way, one of the definitions of insanity
is when you're trying to mix fact and fiction or nonfiction with fiction.
When you mix the two, you end up being in a realm
that creates this unwell condition known as insanity.
But unfortunately, when I say unfortunately,
we're going to have to stay in the realm of description and interpretation
because the explanation is very difficult
because we're going off of what's been memorialized throughout history for mankind.
And what has been memorialized is that there is a human epoch,
a human as we know mankind today,
and still it's very difficult to discuss this
because it's the funniest thing is when you go and look at a scientific article
about this society lived 45,000 years ago or 200,000 years ago or, you know, mankind,
it's like that's just rubbish.
There is really nothing that goes beyond 6,000 years for modern history
or quote-unquote history that we can tangibly access, right?
And it's all this fudge and stuff.
It doesn't mean that there was nothing here before 6,000 plus years ago.
There was plenty here.
But then again, it harkens back to the child asking, where did I come from?
You know, and they lack the maturity.
And what I mean by that is we're being led still by the academics.
And if you don't know about academics, they do lack maturity.
And if you don't think they do, you haven't met one lately.
But anyway, and you're being led by them.
So what we can explain is there is specifically by looking at what's been memorialized
over a 6,000-year period, we see various epochs or ages that mankind goes through,
and they all share there is going to be a time period where there is going to be an axial period,
meaning where nothing will be.
An axial period is a period in history where an event happens,
and everything that succeeds that event has changed because of that event.
Like a recent axial period would be what they call 9-11.
How many times have you heard this is a post-9-11 world, right?
Oh, I say it all the time myself.
Right. That is a small axial period.
Now, the 2300 year ago, or I would say 5-600 B.C., was a major axial period.
That was a time when most knowledge prior to that was cut off.
During that over 100-year period, that's when the censorship came on mankind,
where he no longer had knowledge of the mechanisms that were working beyond the planet
and also the mechanisms that were in place on the planet prior to that time.
It coincides with the advent of modern religions.
It coincides with modern academia.
Modern science emerged also from that time period.
The Greek philosophers, most of what you hear of philosophy,
the Eastern religions also emerged around that time.
So that's why when you start looking at these things objectively now,
the things that have been in place for the past 2,000 or so years,
it's just one big dummy load.
If you don't think that all of science is a big dummy load
and all of medicine and the legal society and religions are a dummy load,
geez louise, you're not paying any attention at all.
It's just a big dummy load.
Right, and all you have to do is look at the doctrine of science
to understand what the problem is there.
Every couple of decades they revise what they told you before was absolute truth.
And it keeps changing and nobody seems to notice that they've decided to augment the program.
It's very funny to me to see that every 20 or so years.
Yeah, they're just taking up time.
And like we said earlier, there is no evidence means nothing, right?
Otherwise, how could they have gotten away with the magic bullet idea?
You see, it doesn't matter.
You see, they could put out who's they.
Well, let's just put that aside who they are.
But anyone of authority of any of these institutions.
When something as ridiculous as that is put out, let's say, as the magic bullet,
it's not that it's important that who believes it or not.
It's that there's a certain level that that question has been satisfied
with something totally ridiculous.
And the most important thing is that no one is doing anything about it.
It's all passive.
How many times have we said that when we've discussed things that are going to be coming on the world,
seen geopolitically, and then very often we say or I say,
by the way, people are going to take it lying down as if it's no big deal.
Right.
You see?
So sure, most people know that there was no magic bullet
or four inches of steel turns to powder from jet fuel.
But what is really interesting about that is both of those events that you're hearkening to,
both of them, the explanation was taken lying down.
Realistically, I mean, there was very little resistance to the idea that, you know,
a guy who had no shooting skills with a poor weapon from a terrible angle,
you know, pulled off an incredible feat.
That was just simply accepted because they also told you that the guy was, well,
a communist sympathizer, had defected from Russia.
They told you that part of the story, not the whole story, but they told you that part of it.
So therefore, look, it makes sense because of some, you know, ancillary supporting idea.
Right.
Why was it that planes would be slammed into the buildings there?
Well, it's because it's an American symbol.
And these people, well, they hate America.
So you can understand why that happened.
You know, like it's like this, the cover story.
And not just with these political or historical events, but I mean, with everything,
it seems like you give them a cover story that has a whiff of logic.
Okay.
Not necessarily logic at its core, but just a whiff of logic.
And there you go.
It's acceptable simply because it was spoken enough times.
And by the loudest element out there, by the most convenient piece of electronic hardware
that was most prolific at the time.
You know, if you go back a couple of decades before the Kennedy assassination,
if the radio said it, it was true.
You don't believe me?
Well, take a look at people tuning in a little too late to Orson Welles' War of the Worlds.
Right.
There were people that thought it was real,
even though if you listen to the whole broadcast and you had actually paid attention to it in its entirety,
you would have known it wasn't real, you know, et cetera, et cetera.
And the same thing prevails for whether it's the War of the Worlds, the Kennedy assassination,
the 9-11 attacks, or, hey, what that preacher man says at that local church or circus
or Circe's house, you know, on a particular what they call Sunday.
Right.
It's just about if we say it loud enough, if we say it long enough,
if we say it through exactly the right mechanism, it becomes truth to the majority of the population.
And it's acceptable to, well, just by overwhelming authority and numbers to push whatever agenda seems to be chosen.
Right.
And sometimes it's just the dummy load, because remember, the dummy load in engineering has a purpose.
It's to drain off the energy before the device is to be put in place to test it, right, or to just drain off excess energy.
Oh, yeah.
It's dummy loading.
Yeah.
So the purpose here when you're talking about all of these weapons of mass distraction, effectively,
which are similarly your churches, your government, your schools, so on and so on and so on, all of them have a purpose.
It's not as though there is just a completely, you know, disconnected purpose to this.
It's not just, okay, this is just a chaotic element and therefore been introduced just for the sake of introducing it.
It actually has a purpose, and that is what, after all?
That is to keep people away from something else, right?
Well, also keep them away from themselves, because people naturally still have the inclination to put out energy into discovering things.
You know, did you hear about this?
No, I didn't.
What happened?
Right.
Just by that attitude alone, you're dedicating energy in that direction.
And here comes the dummy load to soak all your energy away.
Like, you know, if we're going to talk about all these things, you know, JFK is one of the most difficult,
but it's pretty simple to see that it was carried out in a very expert way, right?
It would have been the best of the best of the best and the best of that to have pulled off the actual physical aspect of it,
and then it seemed like it was the worst of the worst of the worst that followed through from the autopsy all the way down to the media.
Isn't that interesting?
Now, Pearl Harbor was very similar.
9-11 was very similar.
And here I want to throw out something about 9-11, which you and I have personally discussed off-air,
is what really happened on 9-11 regarding the buildings and the Pentagon and the airplanes and that can be known, and it is known.
But hell if it's going to be put out publicly.
At this point, the public just can't hear it.
It's far worse than what people imagine.
But to say that and keeping it in context, what I mean by that,
it has nothing to do with these quote-unquote high-energy weapons and things that you hear or nanothermite or anything like that.
There's some good testimony about it.
I believe you had Rebecca Roth on.
She has excellent testimony.
There's some others out there.
There's some people in foreign intelligence that have come out and spoken about things.
You can access it online.
But just like again with the Kennedy investigation, you can't just start investigating from that day.
You have to look at a little bit of the history prior to that day.
And a little bit of that history could be a week, a month, 10 years or 50 years prior to that day.
And the same thing has to be done judiciously to 9-11.
What do you know about tubular steel prefabricated construction buildings?
And you know there's almost no one discussing that.
What do you know what kind of flying object has the ability to do what was done on the Pentagon that day?
And if you research that, you will rule out everything that's being said right now.
But the truth of this, these things are so scary in terms of –
what I mean by scary is that the public doesn't need to be alerted to what is really going on
because how are you going to dummy load that?
You see, once you pass – once you give information that is credible, validatable, verifiable and observable
where you can see with your own eye, you can't go back.
Like there's an old saying, you know, once you have good food, you can't go back to junk food, right?
Once you have a good education, how could you sit at Harvard and listen to the crap that they're saying?
You know, or the top universities.
If you are well-educated and you go into any university on the planet right now, you will laugh.
You will laugh your ass off at what people are sitting there learning or memorizing
because there is no learning in university, by the way.
So this is the interesting part.
So the information about the JFK or 9-11 or Pearl Harbor or a lot of the things that you are seeing in the news today,
once people are exposed to what is really going on and why it's happening and how it's happening,
they can't go back to being dummy loaded with magic bullets and jet fuel and surprise attacks and terrorism.
They can't go back.
And that goes back to the censorship because if mankind wasn't censored,
this curing period of 7,000 years would not be able to take place.
You see, and right now for 2,300 years, mankind has been in the waiting room.
You know, that's why what's interesting is generally as a given rule, there's two things.
The people that know the truth aren't really speaking in specifics because there's no audience for it, right?
Because people are so used to the dummy load.
The second thing is that whenever you'll notice a human agent, a person, let's say a man or a woman,
if you look at the definition of person, it's actually a fictional thing.
But if you have something that is wonderful and beneficial, just do it.
But once you start going out and saying, I'm going to do this to make the world a better place,
now you're in a really bad spot, right?
So if you have anything that's good, just do it anonymously, right?
Like, you know, if Tesla or Victor Schauberger or who was the fellow who did the car that runs on water,
several of them, Myers, if all these people were anonymous, you would have had free electricity now.
You would have had, you know, things and maybe the flying cars, right?
But whenever you go into a society like this and you start pontificating that we're going to do this to make it better,
you're short-lived because you're in the middle of a cosmic war where both right now the good
and the bad forces are against mankind.
And sorry, folks, this is not fear-mongering.
This is just the reality.
So the dummy load is very important until this point, until mankind is liberated from it,
and mankind's not going to do it on his own.
Right, kind of a necessary function of the time in order to keep that energy harnessed without it doing harm, I guess,
just like what a literal physical dummy load would do in an electrical configuration.
Yeah, it's the anesthetic.
You know, a real tough guy, I've seen this before, you know, we're going to pull a tooth and it's like,
I'm okay, I don't need anesthesia.
Pull the tooth, holy crap.
Time comes around again, pull another tooth on this guy, and it's like, no, I want the anesthesia this time.
And that's basically mankind's history.
There were changes that happened without the anesthetic,
and now it's time for the patient to have the anesthetic, right?
There you go.
The operation goes a lot smoother.
I could tell you a funny personal thing about me that you just brought up there,
made me think about why it is that this is such a problem for me.
But, I mean, literally in my lifetime, and I've had discussions with you about some of my past that I wouldn't necessarily discuss publicly,
but the fact is, I mean, my body's been wounded by knives, by guns, and these things just happen, right?
And there's no anesthesia for it, there's no preparation for it that's happened.
But quite honestly, if I sit down in a tattoo chair, and I do have a couple of those, yeah, I almost pass out.
I turn white as a sheet and have trouble handling it.
I kind of think of mankind as suffering from the same sort of thing that I do.
There's going to be a lot of changes coming that are going to be, if you know what's coming and it comes,
you're going to want anesthetic.
But if you don't know what's coming and it comes, you'll just take it as if you are anesthetized.
It's a strange thing.
Well, right, I mean, those that accept their fate seem to take it with a lot more, I don't know how to put it,
poise, I guess would be the word, if you ever notice, if they're well aware that that's what it is.
Hey, you want to use a movie analogy, here you go.
Obi-Wan Kenobi lifted up his lightsaber and knew that he was going to be struck down by Vader,
and he just kind of relaxed and let it happen, didn't he?
But up to that point, he's battling with them, right?
Right, well, also, if you remember the detail, once that happened,
he would be in a state where he'd be in a greater, more powerful state at that point also.
And this goes for everyone.
You see, what's interesting right now is that without a doubt, no matter how dummy loaded people are,
and this is everyone on the planet, it's like when the ship starts to pull into the harbor,
you're no longer thinking, should I go into the cabin or watch the movie or go have a drink?
You know the ship's pulling in.
Maybe you should get ready with your luggage.
You might want to go up on deck and see things.
You know the scenery is changing radically.
It's no more this big open ocean.
You start to see like the skyline of a new place.
This is something in the background of people's minds, and this is not for fear or anything.
This is just going to the next level.
Again, it's like having a tooth pull that's bothering you.
It's not pleasant, but you know it's going to be good later.
I did a survey a while back out by a food court at a mall, and this is almost a decade now plus,
and I asked people, do you believe we're in the end times?
And 90% of the people said yes.
More than that, if not everyone, just a few people didn't, let's say.
But if you ask those 90 plus percent why, none had any explanation why.
I mean one person said, well, maybe because it's in the Bible, you know,
or maybe because of, you know, but no specifics whatsoever.
So that means that the concept of the end times is this very unspecific thing,
and it could be taken any way and propagandized again like it was in the 19th century.
That's where you got the concept of the rupture.
I mean the rapture, right, that does not exist.
That was, you know, because they preached that it would be 1840-something,
the world would end and it didn't come.
So this is, well, because there's a rapture that has to come or a rupture or something.
So this kind of fervor is being taken advantage again,
but it's also being dummy loaded by this revival of mysticism of east meets west
with reincarnation, your intention, you create your own reality, you know.
Yeah, if you're on a big steam liner, you could create your own ship,
your own steam liner while you're on the steam liner.
What a moron.
If you've ever seen a ship being built, it's a major shipyard, right?
I mean you might be able to make a little boat out of a newspaper, you know.
Right.
Yeah, you know, you might make a little model boat or something,
but you're not going to change that steamship, you know, that big, you know.
So we have this level of dummy load right now that is still being applied,
and it's fluctuating, and you see some clarity at some points,
and other points you don't, and it's just, yeah.
But this is the thing that we like to discuss when we come together,
is first of all to give information in a rational way that people at least will
hear it because they're not hearing it anywhere else.
And it's very difficult to give it in a rational form,
especially when people are locked into what we call the Vatican
or the Pope's work schedule.
This Monday through Friday, January through December time reckoning,
like they think it's a new year coming up in a couple of weeks.
I mean, how absurd can that be?
But people are taking it very seriously, and not because, you see,
most people these days, you'll ask them, well, you know, about time.
Well, there's no such thing as time.
Okay.
That's like, you know, one capital moron, and you have another capital moron
that says, well, it's whatever you want it to be, or it doesn't matter.
And it's like, wow, you know, okay, this is really not good.
So how are you going to base any kind of sane, rational, firm information
that requires a reference point when you can't even keep time?
And it's not like I want to harp on that, but if it's so trivial and so minimal
and so unimportant, why is there no consideration to even consider it
in a rational way at this point?
Very simple.
Cosmic censorship.
Because it's not time to consider it.
It's not time to consider it yet.
But, you know, most of the people, again, not to go back to this,
because I really just find it very distasteful to call this the holiday season
because no one can explain anything about it.
It's kind of like the ozone layer or something or the magic bullet,
but everyone goes along with it again, you see.
And even the most rational people that you might consider to be rational,
when you say let's discuss what you call the holiday season or the new year,
well, it doesn't really matter.
Everybody's doing it.
It's a day off or whatever.
It's like, wow, okay, is that all that it takes to suck all your energy into this
just by something trivial like that?
Yes, absolutely.
You see?
Well, yeah, because everybody is playing follow the leader
and not ever examining who the leader is.
Exactly.
Now, lawfully, I mean, we kind of see that there's an even the most unlawful thing
and most askew and obtuse thing.
You'll see there's a little bit of truth in it, right?
I mean, counterfeiters take great time and effort and energy to make sure that
what they're trying to copy looks like the original, right?
So when you have a completely debased system,
right now what I see is that there's no longer an effort being made to,
even though it's debased and counterfeit
and almost pretty much downright fraudulent,
to make it look like the real thing anymore.
Right now what's going on with society across the board is as if you took a
dinner napkin and a crayon and wrote a $100 bill on it and put a quick effigy
or image of Ben Franklin with a crayon and you went and bought something.
So, yeah, that's a $100 bill, right?
I'll take it.
Right.
You know, and this points me to something interesting I was looking at recently
just in general.
I examine a lot of different things,
but one of the most prolific forgers in the history of the art world was creating
things that were so, you know, intensely done that were so, you know,
the craftsmanship that was involved in the etchings and the paintings and stuff
like that was so good that it wasn't even as though it was the original when
they finally discovered it.
Actually, his work now has value simply because of the amount of artistic skill
it took to do these things.
And he did get into a little trouble, I think, also, right?
Yeah, a little bit.
A little bit in a whole bunch of American museums.
You know which one I'm talking about, right?
The Italian that they wound up selling his work all over America to all these
alleged experts in the art world as these, I think they were Impressionist Masters.
I forget really which Masters he was sort of counterfeiting.
But it was really interesting because now his stuff actually has value as if he was
the original artist, which is really fascinating.
It's because of the quality, again.
A lot of the things we like to discuss is from the quality of the nature,
not what people think in quantity of it.
And by the way, just to throw this in there, when you go to these big museums
like the Louvre and the Met and all that, when you see these Masters' works,
all those are replicas.
They don't put the original works out in public.
Those are always held in private collection, always have been and always will be.
There are certain groups, clandestine groups that reproduce these things,
and they're Masters at artificially aging canvases and oils and things like that.
Because think about it.
You might have like the Mona Lisa and someone goes up there with a can of spray paint.
They're not going to risk that.
It's always a replica that you're looking at in public.
So again, but who cares, right?
Yeah, but that's what it comes down to.
Now, here's the problem is that nowadays the counterfeiters don't even honor their craft enough
to really make a good run at it, most of them.
And what you have is it's basically because we live in what is almost a counterfeit society.
It's like a bad photocopy of itself.
Yeah, it's like, you know, the counterfeiters maybe are getting educated
in how the credit system works,
and maybe they're discovering that when you're born with a birth certificate,
you have a credit line to the treasury of each respective nation.
All you need to do is sign your name,
but you have these critters called attorneys that block you from doing it.
Hmm, interesting.
That was a mouthful.
So, yeah, I mean, I sometimes go in public and see people swipe a card and say,
you know, you didn't pay for that, right?
Like, well, you can't just swipe a card and sign your name on a piece of screen or paper
and say you've actually got something.
You know, it means it's already paid for.
You're just showing that your transaction was supposedly taken,
but it really confuses people.
I mean, just as simple as, you know, little children ask where babies come from,
but adults never ask where credit comes from.
It's a credit-based economy.
There's no money.
I know that's news to most people, but, yeah.
I'll tell you the truth.
I still have trouble wrapping my mind around that whole concept because it's just, you know,
Well, that might be something that we should get into in depth on one of the show's upcoming.
We did.
We did on the first time you and I got together on the Ocelli Effect,
but I think there's a cosmic censorship behind that.
Well, that's true, but I think we could do it a little bit different on here.
I really do.
So I think that might be a subject worthy of further discussion.
It's the adversary.
The adversary controls, and the adversary has boots on the ground,
and they're the entitled classes, by the way, just to throw that in there.
Who are the entitled ones?
You know, parents tell their children grow up to be a doctor or a lawyer, right?
Have you heard that many times, you know?
Oh, of course.
But you can't be, if you're a doctor, you're a medical doctor, and there are no more lawyers.
If you wanted to be a true lawyer, you will probably be killed or put in jail.
They're not allowed to be in the society anymore.
You would have to be an attorney, and it's amazing how they interchange those terms, but okay.
Yeah, true enough.
Hey, look, I know everybody can hear your cricket.
Can you hear the vague Frankie singing in the background?
No, I can't.
There's an interesting resonance, again, resonance and dissonance.
What people are resonating with are crickets tonight.
That's true.
But he's actually singing in the other room.
I'm hearing him.
Oh, that's great.
We should bring him forward, maybe.
It's rather late, though.
He shouldn't be out of bed.
And by the way, if anyone donates, I think the seventh person that donates tonight will have you sing maybe some death metal for us.
If seven people.
We had that with Jack Blood, I think.
That's true.
If seven people donated right now, I would probably, I don't know, I would take a request, whatever it is.
You've got to have fun.
Usually we come, this is the 11th time we're meeting, and sometimes I can't stand listening to archives and things for myself.
It's just something very humbling about listening to yourself on a replay.
And we've always tried to deliver a message or a package of information or something, not to make the world a better place.
We're not going to make the mistake of saying that, but just to say things that need to be said because they're just not being said,
and it's just fascinating and amazing.
But I think tonight we're kind of just kicking back, and as if we're having a conversation,
I guess we might want to call it random thoughts, and coming around on these matters as we do, even something about keeping time.
There's a few individuals that are reaching out and making an effort, believe it or not,
so there is a slight effect that they're starting to notice it.
But at large, humanity at large is still quite censored,
and I don't recommend promoting that people change.
You have to just be able to observe and know when the changes come and how you can offer what you can offer when the time is right.
Right, right.
Well, I'll tell you the last thing that I want to bring up just before we do run fully out of time
and I've got to go find out why my son is singing in the next room at almost 2 o'clock in the morning here.
You can do that now if you like, and I can carry on for a moment or two.
No, it's okay. I'll find out in a minute.
He's not sounding upset. He's just kind of singing.
Okay.
Kind of odd, so I'm not going to disturb him, but I may when I'm done here.
But the odd thing is that somebody brought up before, what about universal law?
Now, that's a loaded phrase to me.
Simple.
Your law comes from your God.
What's so hard about that?
Okay, here's the metaphor.
If you buy a computer and you plug it in, it's basically a room heater, isn't it?
You've got everything plugged in the mouse, let's say the monitor, the CPU, the main tower, or whatever.
Let's just say PC, we're in the dinosaur ages now, right?
It just blinks at you, and it needs an operating system, and it really could be unnerving to say,
well, look into the box and you'll see there's a disk there that says operating system.
Go ahead and load that, right?
Now, people don't get upset if you give them that bit of information,
but I'm not saying people are getting upset about this,
but if I or anyone says and discovers that your operating system or your law comes from your God,
how come that's like not even heard?
But if you look at them closely, them meaning humanity, that's exactly how they're operating.
They get their law in the Western societies from the justice department.
Well, what is justice?
It's the revival of the female goddess religion.
There you go.
No matter where you look, your law comes from your deity,
and when you're in your formative years as a child, before, let's say, eight,
your parents are your deity, you see?
So this is very simple, but it's not easy because, like we said before,
you're not going to make friends telling people the truth about things, are you?
No.
Generally, that's exactly how you make less friends really quickly,
is to try and observe what appears to be lawful.
I guess the question then becomes what is lawful?
Simple.
Oh, simple. Okay.
Well, it's real simple.
It has to do with if you are empowered with certain abilities, being an anthropomorphic form,
you can make tools, you can travel, you can think, allegedly, and do things.
You are in a host environment.
How do you interact with that host environment?
For example, use the military as an example.
There is a set of laws for a submarine crew,
which are very different for a set of laws from a surface battleship.
You see, because on a surface battleship, if you have an armor-piercing round go off,
it's not so critical.
But if you have an armor-piercing round go off when the submarine is submerged,
it's very critical.
Why?
They're both ships.
They're both crews.
They're both in the military.
Why do you have different laws?
Because the environments are very different.
So here we have all of humankind or mankind on an earthly environment.
And if you want harmony in your environment, most of the laws that you get from,
let's say, the chief deity is how you deal with each other,
and then you will have harmony in the environment,
because the environment being the earth is also a sentient being.
Like, you know, here's the thing.
You know that you can suffocate a rock.
You know how the scientists say this is organic and inorganic?
Everything is organic.
You can take a rock, a piece of granite, cut it in half, put one in a vacuum jar,
and leave the other one out and examine the one that was in a vacuum jar for about two weeks.
Its color has changed.
Its durometer rating has changed.
You know, its strength.
A lot of its properties have changed.
So, yes, you can suffocate a rock.
So everything is alive.
And Wilhelm Reich showed wonderfully this, I wouldn't say biogenesis,
but he took some quartz sand and he heated it to incandescence, meaning red hot,
until it was bright white hot, sterilized it, put it in a container with water,
and after a few days observed it.
And he also added some, like a reagent grade sucrose or something,
you know, purified, sterilized sugar.
And after a few days looked at it under a microscope
and there was life coming out of the inorganic silica.
There was a guy named Peter Cross who did this back in the 1700s.
So everything is bound with life.
So if you look at the chief deity, for example, it's the way we behave to each other.
So when a lot of times when you hear someone say,
it doesn't matter what you do in private as long as you're not hurting anyone.
If it is a behavior that is viewed as being harmful or transgressing certain laws,
the environment will act against you.
So there's no way of escaping this, you know.
What you do in private will be rewarded for in public.
So it's a very interesting concept.
And this comes from your deity.
And there are many deities, by the way, many gods.
Right, and you have no further to look than the biblical text to understand that,
you know, because allegedly that's supposed to be a monotheistic document.
It's not.
There is no such thing.
Yeah, yeah.
That's an adversarial, like have you ever heard Abrahamic religion?
There's no such thing.
Other than religion meaning something you do regularly, you know.
No, there's no such thing as an Abrahamic religion.
There's no such thing.
Because Abraham was not a deity.
He was a man as memorialized in the text.
So he got his law from his deity.
And the people surrounding him had other deities that got different laws,
which was minimal or very little.
You see, this is a qualitative thing, you know.
Right, but he is a central figure in the Old Testament, obviously.
He's become a central distraction.
And I've also said that it's easier to discover the nuclear launch codes of a country's arsenal
than to discuss any biblical character in public.
Because it seems like no one's ever read any of it.
Nothing that is, I assure you, there is not one book, not one film, not one essay,
or anything written on any biblical character that is even close to being accurate.
Anywhere.
It's astounding.
And all you need to do to see what I just said is true is actually read the text.
It's unimaginable how removed humanity is.
Oh, here's a Skype question from one of the guys that usually listens to me,
but I don't think turns into the two of us talking, usually.
Oh, no, must have listened to, hold on a second here.
Must have listened to some of our stuff before,
because you hadn't mentioned that the text is only in the languages of preservation.
He mentions that in the preface to his question here.
So he must have listened to it before, but I wasn't aware of it.
Okay.
I guess what he's asking is where can one access the text which has not been turned around by the,
oh, King James Version.
Okay, KGV, I wasn't thinking.
KGV is a syndrome, and you don't want to catch it because it's very difficult to cure.
Once you catch KGV syndrome or disease, it's almost incurable.
But if you, just like working with any hazardous bio thing or whatever,
you want to protect yourself before you get into it.
But if you get into it without knowing that you need protection from it, it's got you.
It's important to know that King James, because all biblical texts are based on that, by the way.
Any, what they call version, I mean, you know, people say, what version?
I said, are you kidding?
If the first verse is in the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth, that's all King James.
Sorry, don't be dummy loaded by all these other versions.
That's just a dummy load.
The language of preservation is just that.
It has already, it's held in preservation.
So you would have to go into an interlinear.
Now what's great about the Hebrew and Greek is you don't need a dictionary because each letter has a meaning to it.
So if you memorize 22 meanings in two different languages, you don't need, you can't be fooled by Strongstein.
The Strong's Concordance.
Right, right, okay.
Yeah.
But this is, again, here's the thing.
What's interesting is this document has not been translated outside of Hebrew or Greek.
You have versions of it.
And this is the same with all ancient writs, by the way.
All of your ancient writs are the same.
If every tradition, none of them have been translated at all.
I'll tell you something else.
I'm looking in the chat room and apparently we got one person that has been paying quite a bit of attention
because I see the phrase that Abraham was a Chaldean priest.
Not according to the text, no.
You might want to say that, and you have a quote-unquote right to say that,
but it's not memorialized as being a Chaldean priest directly.
There's a priesthood that came from him later that we merged by appointment.
Oh, there we go, actually.
But he is a very central figure, by the way.
We should discuss at one point, we can do it very quickly.
I think we've brought up maybe half a dozen times that if the central figure, being the Christ,
is for this quote-unquote holiday that's coming up,
isn't that what they say with their mouths at least?
Apparently, yeah.
Yeah.
That was according to the timekeeping that you're using today, meaning you, the world,
that day was September 11th, 3 B.C., and that's very easy to reckon.
Well, there you go, and what a note to end on here tonight on Ocelli and the Greek.
I want to thank you as always for doing this with me because it is always educational,
and these are the things that need to be said that are not being said elsewhere.
So.
Thanks, Chuck, we'll do it again.
Absolutely.
Next week.
See you then.
I'm telling you, you've got to support American Freedom Radio because this government is getting out of hand.
Wall Street won't loan them my money.
The CIA are cutting into my drug running and my gun running.
Big pharma, psychotropic drugs are making my customers commit suicide before my hitmen can even lock them.
And then they get depressed and get prescribed psychotropic drugs and commit suicide too.
The China become the biggest game in town.
When you're paying protection money, you don't even get protected.
I get unpaid taxes, and if I can't find the money, the IRS are going to take my thugs.
I got a mandatory flu vaccine, and now I'm autistic.
I reported a vaccine reaction, and the doctor told me to forget about it.
What have I ever done to have them treat me so disrespectfully?
There's only one way to get the government off our backs, and that's to support American Freedom Radio.
Capisce?
So what are you going to do?
You're going to go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and give them some legal tender they can't refuse.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom.
American.
Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat, improves digestion, and feeds the entire body the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule I drug to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant for over 80 years, and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder is the best-kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein, is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO, and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367.
888-910-4367.
And see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at hempUSA.org.
What is the big deal about swearing to God in the first place?
Why does swearing to God mean you're going to tell the truth?
Wouldn't affect me.
If they said to me, you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth, so help me God,
I'd say, yeah.
I'll tell you about as much truth as the people who wrote that Bible.
How do you like that?
Swearing to God is kid stuff.
Swearing to God doesn't mean anything.
Swearing on the Bible doesn't mean anything.
You know why?
Because Bible or no Bible, God or no God, if it suits their purposes, people are going to lie in court.
The police do it all the time.
All the time.
Yes, they do.
It's part of their job to protect, to serve, and to commit perjury whenever it supports the state's case.
Swearing on the Bible is just one more way of controlling people and keeping them in line,
and it's one more thing that holds us back as a species.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue, with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest, and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom, and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs, and artillery batteries not included.
No rules. No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.