Yeah, I've gotten a bunch of emails that are really proper emails and I want to answer them
So I'm just gonna record the answers to the emails and that's why I'm doing this and it'll be up for everyone else to hear
Cool, and you guys will see why it just won't ring everyone, but it'll show
That there's a call going. I'm trying various devices. You have three machines on different accounts and sure practicing
Yeah, so I'm gonna record soon, so if anybody comes on or whatever we'll wait to see if it populates
And I'll just tell you know people to mute or or not you don't have to
Because I've gotten you know my whole thing of doing this is to put it out there so in case I get hit by a train
Other people know how to build the device
Right back in the 19th century when someone went missing. It's like what happened. This is probably got hit by a train
right
Yeah, yeah, it's old-school talk so I might even read the lease I might even read the lease agreement that I wrote up
Because in case this ever gets really hairy where they knock on your door and say hey, what do you think you're doing?
How many of these have you sold and I'd say I haven't sold any of them and that would be honest because I'd break
These are not first. They're not for sale. They're not a 99 year lease, right?
Mm-hmm
And
Also, I tell people to read it and then and yeah, I'll read I'll read the lease agreement right now
It's written in law not legalese. So many people don't understand it and
I'll read it
It's the title is letting and leaving agreement, that's the old term for lease
It's called on the top. It's in bold letting and leaving agreement for an object
Affectionately known as the scalerator quote and mark one quote a decorative device to be installed held and used in good manner by blank
including their heirs and assigns provided by its creator stellios T on blank and
With mutual understanding until a time of 90 years known as the year 2114
to promise him to hold and to use without tamper or malice and
From time to time its creator may improve replace upgrade Wilson Wilson use and hold held in good manner and
Then here we come to fulfill our agreement for the sum of blank
redeemed in lawful money in accordance with quote 12 USC 411 and
quote quote demand for lawful money clause and quote and
once fulfilled as a one-time settlement of obligation with no further demand and
Further evidence of agreement both have produced their appellations and marks to endorse and seal this agreement
Who the fuck talks or thinks like that these days?
It sounds so poetic, you know and in a lot of ways, you know, and
Yeah, yeah, and that's for me covers all the bases though
Yeah, well, here's the thing if someone says well, it doesn't work. It's not cleaning up my water
Sure, what are their attorney attorney or look at it and says well, it's an object
It's it's it's actually known as a scalerator, which is a decorative device
Doesn't say anywhere here supposed to clean the water. So you're gonna complain that your lampshade doesn't clean the water
And I've asked people to please read it if you don't understand anything give it to your attorney they're all going oh, it's
God yeah, they have no record anyone who gets into an agreement
He has absolutely no recourse because it even says I could go and pull it out any time. I want
Right, right and it doesn't yeah. Yeah, and I had another thing. This is you get all your money back after purchase and
Any for no reason but the right sounds good, right, but it's not a purchase
right
Amazing. Yeah, and no one no one. Yeah, that's oh my goodness
The last person will read it and says letting and leaving agreement
I
Guess is in law. Yeah, this is not legal. This is not legal stuff and
So I'm having fun with it. Yeah, I also like someone says you like messing with people like me. I
Messed with people, you know, but I don't know if I like it
You know, what is there about messing with people, but I'm not gonna mess with people to mess them up
I mess with people that way, you know, they'll be
Yeah, they always try to pinhole you some way or another
But you know in actuality all you're not sharing your point of view on something you learned
Yeah, I don't know yeah, it's it's sad I'm just tired of being here well, of course people yeah, I'm just tired
Of course, it's it's less cowardly to hang around
speaking of which I
found an interesting
video from a retired judge
talking about foreclosure divorce and
Traffic and all that kind of stuff. It was pretty interesting
Yeah, but it's anything after 1938 really doesn't concern me you could use
Don't show anything past 1938
You by the way, you got a real scratchy in a real noisy mic there. I hear you back. Oh, yeah
My it's a fan kind of Mike is that it's that headset, you know
But I can be I can mute yeah, no, it's fine
Recording okay. We'll see if anybody else jumps on if anyone has any questions. Basically the reason I'm doing this is so we have a
Sonic on some important questions that were asked by a thinking man that
Who wants to start building these and obviously you can see whoever asked these questions knows how to think so instead of typing long
I don't like typing. I'd rather record it and then everyone else can get it too because this is an equal sharing thing
Amen
So much easier just to pick up a device and talk
Yeah, it's much better. You can play it back. You could listen to while you're doing something else. Well, sure
This is a really big deal. This is like the early
Yeah, I'll get into I'll answer the questions and I'll get into more discoveries that I had the other day
Okay, it's a really big deal this is what this is in line with like Michael Faraday
1700s with his experiments with wires and iron iron cores and things like that. There was no science about it
there's no math is just users talking about observations and
So this is exactly what this is a completely new field
I've been studying this now for ten months and
There's absolutely nothing that does what this does or the application there's nothing that has the same application
There's a guy in the Netherlands is a patent reviewer. He's been sending me hundreds of patents
Oh my god dozens and dozens
About similar stuff with magnitude. None of these are like this. None of them not one. He's like, yeah, I know I
found your your choice of
copper leaf and was it barium
I
Started with a
Technique. Yeah tightening. Yeah titanium oxide and barium oxide for use that
He's at 2,500 degrees to strong dielectric. I have a whole bunch of it. You can get it's an ingredient in a lot of things
Into it's not necessary. It's just the strongest dielectric
That's that's the whole thing. I found the choices of it because of that property
And does it actually help to attenuate?
The
the fields in the magnet
Yeah, focus some what turns it makes them electric. Yeah. Yeah. No, it doesn't focus
No, it just disperses. It makes them more planar. I'll get into that
It's not necessary to use it. But if you make a device if you're making your first device, absolutely
necessary
Wow
Yeah, but if you if you want to continue it, it's a great device even the most basic
It's crude form as long as you line it up properly
But if you do the copper in the barium tetanate the barium tetanate is diluted
With distilled water and a little bit alcohol and it's added to the glue. There's a binder right gold leaf and the copper leaf
Mm-hmm. It's called gilding. They have gilding glue. You use the wall. Of course
Dilute it with the barium titanate until it becomes a thicker
Material and then you brush it on and then you follow the instructions
And you do three coats of leaf
And what it does and you got a great device when you do the copper barium titanate now
It's like a super great device. It works even better
But I was thinking that does it increase you know the black ball in this instance
The black ball. What's that? Well, I mean the block of the block wall. Oh
The block wall. Yeah, what it does is it back?
It
Mitigates some of the back EMF than when the water is running through it because you're not running on water through it, right?
electrical
impulses build up in the water and
The more mass you have underneath those electrical discharges just like a transformer
Mass it has the better the better. It does its job
And now is pressure water pressure an important factor. Also the flow rate going to the tube. No, no
I'll talk about
If you run the water slower run it fast does the same thing. That's what's amazing about it. This is
Yeah, yeah a lot of devices require a flow rate right this time right I've done
I have trickled water out of it, you know one inch pipe trickling just dripping
It does it sure uses everything in the water just like as it's full bore and full bore
Super high pressure thing going super fast very little. Well, I'm still does the same thing works beyond time. It's longitudinal
Doesn't care
Damn, it's a whole different science. This is how people say is the water business not the water business when the physics business now
There's a whole new physics. I mean you can apply doesn't have to be
Yeah, doesn't have to be water treatment. I mean, there's like an entire opening of applications that
That I think if you started I've experimented with a few. I have another device that I have not introduced yet
that is pretty amazing and
Needs development, but it's not necessary because I mean my I'm old enough now when I was younger I'd get it all done and talk
But now older and I'm more patient right so get one done
It's somebody there's other people replicating it
And whatever whatever and and see how and should move forward quite well
I'll talk about the experiences like for example, the last hookup is for a site I did for a woman. She's a science
Researcher she and also sells medical equipment, whatever whatever, but she's a scientific person
And she asked me to explain, you know, what it does scientifically she said and I got into a little I said
Well, you know the regular common doesn't she goes. Okay. Well, it sounds good. Let's schedule and install we had some
Schedule bleeps who finally got that. I wanted a licensed plumber to do it because it's a
Condo with a HOA and there's something one right, you know, at least it's adjudicated by a licensed plumber, you know, sure
So while we're doing the installation, she's out. I'm getting some containers ready
I'm gonna take a sample and bring it to the lab and find out if it really does anything and like fine
Yeah, let's do that. Please, you know get ready with your sample
Take it to the lab find out what it does, but wait, you know, we're almost done with the install here mark up more confirmation
Well, yeah, we get no. Well, no listen
So we do the install and I said get some water before you we install it and taste it
You know as it tastes like a terrible tap water
You know city water and I said good. Okay, you know get a good amount let it run nice
So it's you're not getting any in the pipes and taste it because I taste like nasty tap water stuff
I wash in all the time. I don't like it
Well, anyway, we installed the device turn on the water and let it run for about five minutes
We did solder flux and all that
Yeah, just go ahead and go inside the sink put some water and take a sample once you taste it
She comes out smiling like a Cheshire cat. Oh my god. Oh my god
I said, do you still want to take it to a lab to be tested? He goes not necessary
Not necessary
I'm like, yeah. Wow Wow Yuri. So she got so convinced the difference is so it's like drinking water out of the tap
And then drinking like coffee on water or Fiji water like really good spring water, right the difference
I mean, I was like, aren't you sure you want to take it to the lab? Like you suggested not necessary
The difference is holy smoke. That's a yeah
This happens every it happens every time every time we do this
There people are retain a healthy amount of skepticism, which I which I'm fine with
And then once we connect the device and they taste the water, they're like, oh my gosh. I didn't know it could get so good
Yeah, yeah, it's better than bottled water better than best water. I ever tasted in my life just straight out of the tap
Yeah, it's amazing
Yeah, but the thing is this is not like a jerk-off device
It's not like those things that you you know, hook up on you under your sink or whatever. This thing is a
It's more of a how would you call it? It's utilitarian. It has to go on the water main and
That that flushes out 90% of the people about 90% of people probably here
And we will not be able to install one on the water main right in the ground right side
That's right outside the building
Yeah, but but there's somebody I know there's all I need is one person to do it
and you know responsible person that is not broke and
Is good with their hands and is artistic creative it can communicate. Well, that's all I'm looking for
Just one person one other person that can do that and all those skills. I just mentioned are very very rare
People if you can communicate clearly
artistic
Are not broke
Make things you can't find people like that anymore. I mean, I haven't been able to so that's the way I'm reaching out, you know, right
So and and then this is a utilitarian device
It's not a jerk-off technology like a a Brita filter or you know, something you hold under your sink or whatever
No, it has to go
into the infrastructure
so, you know most people if you're renting or if you're
Good condo it could be done in a condo if you're you know, renting again or whatever live with your mom or where chances
Are you not going to be able to experience this, right?
But you're not going to convince your mom
I heard this guy on the internet
I want to go dig up the water main and put this in and it cost
5,000 bucks to get one from no mom's gonna laugh at you so go back to the basement turn on the TV
Yeah, they're not gonna go
I'm just passing the fact that you're on to other channels that were on here and seeing if that'll help a little bit, too
Yeah, well, I tried calling
It won't ring the group, but it doesn't matter. I just want to get a recording up soon. I'm gonna start recording
It is ringing people, but you know, you never know. Oh, here we go. It's starting to populate a little bit
One person's having issues
That's fine. It doesn't matter. Yeah, we'll see how it goes
Yes, just get a recording up right up much interruption
Don't forget don't forget to record button
When you're ready, I'm gonna do it on another computer. I've got two laptops and
I'm on the iPhone right now. Ah
What sounds pretty clear
Yeah, yeah, I'm using the Apple headset which is really hard to be
Apple stuff, you know don't buy, you know
It's Apple use Apple, right?
Sure, so let's join. I'm gonna join on here so I can record
Mm-hmm should work
Do you want to record it? Actually, it's better if I have to do business computer. Seems like it's frozen up now. Oh my
Whatever works
Whatever works, there we go. All right, I'm gonna start recording. Okay
I took your advice on these solid-state drives
Okay. All right, so we're recording
alrighty, then and I'm gonna try to get a
try to get a
Little bit of a sonic on some questions that have been asked
regarding the scale rate or construction and I figured it would be more value in
Recording it and so this way everyone here has access to it because that's what this is about
So I'm gonna start off by just saying
These questions are very pertinent to someone who is very very pertinent on building one
And I noticed that and I did have a discussion with this person and they are pretty serious and seemingly capable so far
excuse me, so they
Emails and there's the right kind of email
meaning
If the questions are right and I'm gonna just go down the questions and I'll try to be as complete as possible
Because they're very helpful. So let's see. Let's open up this thing here and see if we can get it going
All right, I finally muted a computer
And we're should have less background noise, okay, so here we go
Person says here they've ordered the magnet. Do you have any guidance or recommendations on buying the following?
All right bullet point. First one is the pipe. What is it made of?
right the pipe
let's call it the spool if you go to industry when you have a
Go to a fab shop and you have a plan a drawing of what looks like the scale reader
And you want that pipe bent around like that. They're gonna call it a spool
so
And it kind of makes sense a spool is just a winding if it's one or you know one time around
Wound around once or a thousand times, which is full
So that's the industrial term for it and from a fabrication shop. So here the question the first bullet point is the pipe
What is it made of?
What we're using and I highly specify and I'll give the reasons why is schedule 80
That's schedule 8 0
PVC
And the reason why we use that is several reasons
First of all, I'll give the caveat. I'm not a fan of PVC
Polyvinyl chloride it has the phthalates and it can pollute the water for phthalates or plasticizers and their estrogen emitters
Blah blah blah all the stuff you hear about that about plastic you'll find in PVC
But the reason why we're using it the main reason is because schedule 80
I'm saying this again
Schedule 80 not schedule 40. It's the dark gray stuff
by the way guys when I've been on Sonics before I've made gave instructions to people and why to use one over the other and
I need to be double triple clear because
When I did the Sonic about the number eight rice I talked about tarot and there's two types of tarot
Don't use the small one use the large one. Someone sent me a box with small tarot
I don't know if that was to piss me off or they just didn't get the detail, but I appreciate the gift anyway
So it's just funny. So let's go back to the pipe
Schedule 80 did I say schedule 80 as an 8-0?
8 times 10 is 80. That's what you want to use now. That's dark gray stuff
Most typically in PVC pipe you'll see the schedule 40
that's a 4-0 and that's a white thin wall the difference is the schedule 80 is a thick wall pipe and
The other one is not and there's also CPVC don't use that either
So why really focus on the schedule 80?
because let's say you're building these devices and
You want to get them out out in the world and you end up
Butting heads with someone in industry if you show them anything other than schedule 80
They're gonna want a certain safety and material test to prove that the device can hold up
But if you show them a device made with schedule 80 that is internationally accepted as a standard in industry
So what it does is it allows you to walk into anyone's door and be respected on what material you're using
the second reason you use it, which is all tied to the first reason is
That it's a thick wall
It's twice almost twice as thick as schedule 40 and that dark gray color
Is such because they have got higher degree of solids built into the plastic or when it's being extruded and
when you're bending the pipe and
Expand putting it under thermal stresses because it's thermally bent
chances of the pipe losing its dimension its wall thickness
And becoming fragile and brittle is very very slim with the schedule 80 where with the schedule 40
The pipe tends to the thinner wall the white stuff is
Gets really brittle and thin doesn't work that well and and when the unit is complete
With the magnetic reactor and it's completely done. It's very robust
I mean you could grab it and beat someone with it and it'll be just fine or it'll fall off the bench
Hit the deck pick it up. It's just fine
Where if you make it out of the other pipe the other PVC any other PVC
If it falls off the bench and hits the deck, it'll crack and break
And that means that if you're giving it to a plumber in there, you know, you guys know why they call them plumbers, but anyway
If he's wrestling on this thing to lock it down tighten it cut it whatever fit it in the field that he steps on it
Drops it from his pickup truck or whatever. It's gonna break
It's not gonna hold up. The only thing the only material that will hold up is the schedule 80
And again when you combine the properties of the schedule 80 verse all other types of PVC
Because of its heavy thick wall it makes it easier to work with and more consistent for bending
Okay
So I'd like to say if there are any questions on that and actually if there are any questions regarding that
Material of the pipe and why we're using schedule 80. That's 8-0. That's the dark gray stuff
And somebody wants to unmute and chime in with a question regarding that. That's totally cool
And otherwise, I'll go on to the next bullet point
Yeah, what size?
length of the pipe
The length of the pipe is ends up being we have a jig which we'll get into
Basically, or if you could just bend it around if you're making one for the first time and you're bending it around a 5 and 1
Quarter inch that's 5 and 1 quarter inch diameter magnet. You're gonna need 34 inches of
Pipe and you and you start off with about a 4 inch tail and by the time she wraps around that magnet
Bends around and you're done. You'll end up with another 3 to 4 inch tail on the opposite end
You need 34 inches to start with now your your pipe comes in 10 or 20 foot sticks
When you buy a piece of pipe, it's a 20. It's called a stick 20 feet long and
Or you get half a stick which is 10 feet long
Lowe's sells it by the way, otherwise, you got to go to a sprinkler an irrigation or professional plumbing supply to get it
so you're gonna have to cut yourself if you're using a 5 and 1 quarter inch diameter pipe and
You could do PI D
Which is circumference then you got to add 28% right because you're bending around
that'll give you your length of pipe and
And
If you're using a smaller magnet you could use less than 34 inches if you're using a bigger magnet you can you're gonna have to use
more
so the 34 inches
You'll get three scalerators out of one 10 foot stick, right?
Because 34 inches just shy of three feet
So you'll get three scalerators out of it and about a little bit over a foot and a half
Left over on 10 foot stick which you then you bend and make those internal spacers that you see in the middle of the magnetic
Reactor have a little scrap left over
If you're making a custom one and you want a longer tail
Especially if you're gonna get into putting flow forms in the pipe
You can cut it at just a 36
Give you a little more length or whatever
But if you gonna wrap it around a five and a quarter inch magnet, you're gonna want it centered around
No 18 or 17 inches, which is a total 34 inch
I also used to the plans that I've drawn up is in radians
I go by degrees instead of length, but that you know people kind of freak out when they see that kind of math
You know radians
You know, that's why when I put up a picture of one that I call the 700 degree
Someone said well, that's a 540 degree bend
I said, yeah
But it's I measured it in radians in other words the part of the scalerator that sticks out the stubby part that's not bent
that's part of the
Circle right there circumference, so I'll give in the future
I'll put up drawings on that and I'll do it in bolts, you know straight measurement radians and all that. So
Yeah, that's a good question
Well, they didn't have it at Home Depot
So no the Home Depot doesn't have it you could special order from them, but they're gonna charge you five times more
You can get it at Lowe's some Lowe's. There's only one Lowe's here to some that has it you get at Ferguson's plumbing supply
You could call around there's industrial plumbing supplies like Harrington is another one that has it
And the any what's called an irrigation supply
Will have it and if you call them and they don't have it in stock, it's embarrassing for them
So they'll say we'll have it tomorrow or in two days for you
right
Shame on you for not having it right because there's a shop here of Ferguson's when I called him
They said oh, we're out of one inch schedule lady. Well, we'll have a stick for you tomorrow
Shame on you call yourself a legitimate plumbing supply. You don't have schedule 81 inch pipe Wow a
Comprehensive hardware store will have it. There's a hardware store here on 22nd Street. That's got everything and they have it
They could sell it if you find a really good hardware store
They will sell it to you by the inch or by the foot so you don't have to get a 10-foot stick
Just get a three-foot piece
There are two hardware stores that I could think of here in town that have it
but do not
Now, well, I shouldn't say do not do not use the white stuff or the CPV state seeded
the schedule 40 4 0 is the white PVC that you see at Home Depot and
There's also this yellow stuff. It's for high temperature same size copper as copper. It's called CPV see
Don't use that either both. That's crap
Now you can if if you want to practice bending pipe, you might say well, I'll use the crap plastic
But you'll have a bad experience bending it because the wall is so thin
When you heat the pipe to bend it the wall will collapse and you won't it won't have a circular profile anymore
The pipe will be real flat
So you won't have any there's no there's no sense. I because how do I know this the first?
Scalarator I put up in the chat nine months ago was made out of schedule 40
And it did come out really well on the bend
But it's the only one that I've ever done that came out really well
The first one every time I try to use a schedule 40 repeat on it. It just deformed too much. I didn't like it
So the schedule 80 is the way to go do not use the schedule 40 or the CPV CEO, whatever
Now just to volunteer there's someone a while back that did something with pecs
The cross-linked polyethylene tubing I like that chemically
because the only thing pecs will release into the water for about a week or two and when it's put in service is a
little bit of ammonia and
Some nitrates and once it cleans that out from the industrial manufacturing
It's a very inert material as a matter of fact
Polyethylene pipe or pecs tubing there's varieties. There's pecs a there's pecs B
Don't confuse it with pot poly butylene which is not pecs or polyethylene
It's a multi-layered stranded kind of like the soda, you know, the two-liter soda bottles I kind of plastic
very difficult to bend it has a high internal resistance and memory and
The only way to make a scale rater out of that is by really hitting it with a lot of heat. We'll talk about that and
When it's complete it needs to fit into a form that has braces that hold it in place
Braces just like you put braces on someone's teeth every few inches
You need to have somehow cinch it down and you always want to use non-ferrous material around it. Someone had put a
picture very industrious individual in chat that did a double one and I saw
You know magnetic hardware around it and that's a no-no, but we'll get into that in the future
You know all is forgiven because I haven't disclosed the important parts, right?
So if you put one together of peanut butter and chewing gum, I'm not gonna laugh at you
Because you don't know but when you know, I still won't laugh at you because you're at least you're making an effort
but in terms of tubing
Schedule 80 is the way to go
for many reasons
And the primary reason would be manufactured you making it so it maintains its shape and secondary reason it will be universally accessible
no questions asked
Schedule 40 is garbage schedule and CPVC is garbage all other forms of
PVC are garbage for this application. It will not even if you successfully bend it with
Without deformation it is not durable enough for the field
Right. And again, the pex is a more high purity plastic. It's used in you know
laboratories and pharmaceutical grade
But it will not hold the shape will not hold the shape. I'm you're gonna have to go through
a process where you're gonna have to make a form that holds it into that position and
Because it's a multi-stranded multi-layered
Plastic I believe separation internal separation might happen in the pipe
So for now, it would be schedule 80. That's schedule
8-0
That would be the way to go
That was a good question and it was drifting away from the length
But 34 inches ought to do it for a 5 and 1 quarter inch magnet. It depends purely on your magnet size and
If you're using a smaller diameter
5 and 1 quarter is a good for a 1 inch or up to 1 and 1 quarter
If you're using a half inch or 3 quarter pipe you go ahead and use a 4 and 1 half inch magnet
The standard for magnets non metric ones
They go basically three three and a half four four and a half five five five and a half
And they kind of dead end around that size
You can get a six inch magnet. They're kind of hard to find. I'll get into the magnets
They get real pricey and they're hard to find. So you're gonna need about three feet of pipe to experiment with
Thanks for that question
So great
We're getting ready to do our first
Magnet reactor in there and we're coming up to the pipe stage for the first one
Do you recommend should we do all like the copper leaves? I'm gonna get into that
That's the next question. Yeah, let's go right into it right now
Not no and not necessary I'll drop an image of the first one that I made and sent out and what that was tested
I'll drop it in right now and
If you're on the chat, which I'm sure you could just look in there, let's see I have it on another account
Let's just uh, this is number one. This is a
scale waiter zero zero zero one
That's made of schedule 80. I'll even and this is it right here. I'm gonna forward it to the group right now
And let me know when it comes up then you sent it said done
If you're in front there, can you see it?
That's the first one ever made the second one ever made first one in schedule 80
This one was made without a jig just bending it around the magnet as you see
You got it, is that a Roger do you see it? Yep, George. Yep. Cool. Okay, you can click on that blow it up zoom in
Yeah, she's she's real ugly. She's so ugly. She's pretty right? Yep, and the the dots you see there
That's the south side. If you flip it over, that's the north side of the magnet. I
Mean, look, I mean it looks brutalist, you know, if you look at it, you know, the brutalist architecture style
I mean, it looks like you could take that into battle
Or it looks like real steampunk, right? Especially with the copper
So, there you go and I'll get into the magnets and why it looks that way and why and those
Support tabs and all that. So this is number two as you can see I could like to brag. I don't build junk
Anything I build always looks good
I
Always did that since I was eight years old
But I used to do
Fifth grade science fair. I walked in it was my science project and all the teachers jumped up
So you can't bring that in here. You got to bring a project that you did not the adults built for you
And I'm like, no I made this. No, you didn't
Had the parents come down and tell him now you made it all on his own and they're all like running around with their mouths
open
So I do brag about my skills
Yeah unions on the end, that's right
Unions are durable
The nice thing about unions is if you're cutting into a is you referring to the photo?
Let's say remember this is a utilitarian project. This is not jerk-off technology
It's not like a Brita filter where you just turn on your spout and pour it in there
You know stuff talk about doing the ghetto style water purification. This is
Utilitarian stuff this is where you know, you're gonna flip freak your parents out if you live with your mom and you say hey mom
I'm gonna go cut the water main and put this thing in there from this guy on the Internet. You ain't gonna work
This is not no, this is not for those situations is how do you do the utilitarian stuff? So George?
I understand you you might know about the trades. So the reason we're using unions here is
That let's say we go to field and we cut out about twelve and a half inches of pipe to drop this in
We fit it with it doesn't matter what the other pipe is iron copper plastic
There's adapters and we adapt with the Union and what's great about the Union is you buy two sets two pairs of four
and
You fix the piece of pipe that you remove to put the scalerator and with another set of unions
So in case you have a hard time or you want to take it out
The piece of pipe you cut out is fitted with the unions also
So you just go back to where you put the scalerator and pull it out and
Slip the original pipe that you cut out with the other set of unions and you're done. You feeling me?
Okay
You don't have to you could type that's fine. That's why we use the unions
Yeah, yeah, I need two spanners
Okay, when you use the unions
Don't use spanner when I say spanner. Thanks for bringing that up that my mind just went there
Even an emergency you should use what's called a strap wrench on the Union
Even if the Union is made of steel or brass not plastic
Because the spanners any spanner you're not going to get a 12-point socket or six-point socket around that
It's going to be a spanner that has a three-point contact jaw maximum and it crushes
You're not be able to grab it with a channel lock or anything or a pipe a spanner
You need what's called a strap wrench and what a strap wrench is. Well, it looks just like it sounds
Usually a piece of rubber around something. It looks like a holding block and it cinches you cinch it down and you turn it
I've seen
People use channel locks and spanners on unions and it's a no-no. There's actually tools for it. There's split tools that are made for them
Get it from the manufacturer. That's the only disadvantage now if you've got a firm handshake and you don't have a weak chin
You could pretty much tighten down a Union by hand
Give it about a minute or two. Let it rest, you know, especially if you use a
O-ring grease come back by hand and lock it down again by hand
The only problem with locking it down by hand
You may not get enough torque that you would when there's thermal expansion and contraction
Even with a spanner with something that has a large flange like a Union
You could lock it down. I think it's 15 to 16 foot-pounds
depending on the size and
Newton meters, they've got the specs written on there for tightening when they're when the temperature changes
You might come back and say hey
It feels a little looser than it did or you know, I might get a little tighter than it did based on temperature
So whenever you lock a Union down you lock it down unless you're in a big hurry
Give it about a minute or two to relax and then go ahead and torque it again with a strap wrench or strap handle
Never use a channel lock or and if you're gonna use a regular spanner on a Union don't tell me that you did
Please I don't want to know good question
Anything else before we move on to the copper I
Knew the picture would throw off the and for more questions, okay
So the next question like George asked about the copper the other question here is
You know, I've ordered the magnet do you have any guidance recommendations on buying the following first one was the pipe what is it made of?
Second is pure copper leaf for magnet coating and I'm gonna combine that with the next question also, which is barium titanate
and
Now the pure copper leaf came about several ways
Not necessary as you see in that first picture
That first one was great and
Everyone after that with all the other improvements was or is great. Also, not necessary. I
Had a vision of people showing this to people and I've had people say it looks like a turbo
It looks like a brake rotor, you know, all the stuff you get. I like that initial
Commentary and just waking up one morning
I got a flash in my head from building loudspeakers on using a Faraday ring on it
Which is a copper band because there's EMF going on
Electromotive force whenever you move water that has conductive minerals in it around a magnet and the way you damp out EMF
Electrical EMF is by using what's called a Faraday ring
copper Faraday ring so I got into the idea of coating the magnets with copper and
Then also when someone looks at it, they don't scream brake rotor, right?
So there's no fault in that it's just kind of annoying most people anyway, by the way have two modes with me
It's annoying and very annoying
So I figured if I could just keep it down to one knowing that'd be good
and I figured I'd coat it with copper and also acts as a Faraday ring and
I asked around for some copper prices custom-made pleat, you know stamped pieces and
Prices were outrageous. So I said well, there's the thickness of the copper matter
Yes, it does, but let's just start off with some copper
And then the other thing was I have some barium titanate laying around
I have it in putty form and powder form you can you're on your own with that folks
eBay sells it you'll find it in common products like tooth filler. They there's a
Temporary tooth filler if you have a tooth filling
Pharmacy has a little thing. They'd be filling falls out. You put this white
Putty in there stuff the hole until you see a dentist
That's made of barium titanate
Putty you could dilute it with water
barium titanate is also used in the
ceramic engine coating
The they have these ceramic additives nano additives, whatever you put in your car engine in your motor oil
Liqui moly makes one that has barium titanate in it, but I don't recommend using that one because it's oil based
on eBay and
Laboratory supply places they sell it in powder or putty form
It's used in the dental industry it's used in as a dielectric it's used as a thermal grease
If you've ever worked on amplifiers and you look at where the transistors are
Mounted to the heat sink. You'll see a white paste. That's a barium titanate also very common material
That's something that your mom has in her cupboard
But it's common nonetheless
Industrially, it is expensive. They'll end up costing anywhere between one to five dollars a gram which in
Regular math, it's a thousand dollars a pound or whatever. You don't need that much. I
Pick barium titanate because it's an extremely dielectric substance
Extremely dielectric. It has some funky electrical properties
Especially when you put it in the mid zone where you have magnetism and electricity mingling with each other
Has some interesting properties also because I went with the copper leaf the gilding process. I
Decided to add the barium titanate paste into
The gilding glue and where do you get that? I get mine from a place called Hobby Lobby
It's real cheap a pack of 25 sheets of pure copper leaf is about $3
You need about six sheets to do a magnet on both sides. Actually more like ten sheets
because I do three coats and
I have a copper leaf paint a water-based. So it also added some of the barium titanate to
Just follow instructions on how to do gilding or applying a gold leaf or a copper leaf
Doesn't matter what metal leaf the gilding process leaf. There's plenty of YouTube YouTube's on it. You need to practice
You know as cautions like, you know, if you're coughing sneezing if there's a fan in the room
It doesn't work gold leaf will end up everywhere where the copper leaf I should say
So I've with the barium titanate copper leaf
Without the barium titanate and copper leaf or without the copper leaf or the barium titanate
You're not going to notice much of a difference between the devices. I initially did that for aesthetic reasons
So when people saw it, you know because magnets have that common color
Most people in the world are familiar with it. It's that you know anthracite that dark gray blackish color and so it's a magnet
But if you flash some copper just like a you know flashing a badgers, I mean, you know, they get mesmerized, right?
Most people look at the coating but I did notice that the ones that have the coating tend to be more robust in their function
so
It's very valid because it's very prominent when you look at the scalerator to see that bright copper
And then when I've mentioned barium titanate, it's like oh my gosh, what's going on here? There's more than meets the eye
Yes, there is
But what basically meets the eye about the scalerator
Which is the pipe spool the pipe wrapped around the magnet and just magnet is really ninety nine point nine percent of the job
done and
I'd say when you add the copper and the barium titanate in the glue for the copper
I'd say it's about two percent more a lot of people say that does not enough to matter
But everything matters because it's cumulative as you improve the process
So these are the major questions so far and I'm gonna pause right here if anybody got anything else to say
We got a question. Yeah
All right
Is there a way to measure or do you have an idea of the the ratio?
Barium titanate you would put in the in the glue and speaking of the glue. I'm surprised. It's water-based. No. Yeah rubber
Yeah, I would okay. The reason why you use water-based is because when you use a metal leaf
You got to put a coating on it and I found the most
Otherwise, it was rub off or oxidized. It's not very durable
I found the best coating bar none is just plain old lacquer spray lacquer not acrylic clear coat. That's junk
But the old-fashioned spray lacquer if it doesn't say lacquer on a spray can or a bottle, you know
You buy it a little half pint of it at the hobby store. It's junk. Don't get acrylic clear coat
So basically the clear coat that I end up finishing it with
Is lacquer and if you have an oil base on the glue the lacquer will release it you'll have a big mess
So the standard right now is water-based as a matter of fact
If you go look at gilding that was done hundreds of years ago was also water-based
Was made out of rabbit hide and egg whites
So the reason I use the water-based
You'd put it on let it get tacky ten to one
Dilution so I dilute my paste my barium titnate paste. So it's a very fine flowing paste
Flows more than ketchup and
I add that to my glue and then a little bit of distilled water and it doesn't really change the viscosity
Until I don't change the viscosity of the glue ten to one. So it's a real small fraction of
Barium titnate there used to be I did some experiments with barium titnate. It's one of these materials that
Put these miracle materials when you when you mix magnetism and electricity, you don't need much
You just need the presence of it to for it to start working
especially if anyone
Remembers 10 years ago 15 years ago 20 years ago. There was a craze
With building crystal cells like batteries that never run out right or the way you recharge them is by shorting the battery out
but David Hutchinson or actually what's the John Hutchinson and
That was there was a John Bedini they were building these crystal cells
Oh just light up an LED light forever kind of thing
And what they didn't tell people is they use all these salts with a tiny amount of barium titnate
So I was always always been enamored with it and I said, let's add some
But we're using a the standard water base. If you go on Hobby Lobby or any hobby shop
art shop that sells
leaf material copper leaf
And you ask them what glue to use
most of the glues available and the most preferred ones on the water base point and
You apply it quickly and it dries to attack. It never dries hard. It always stays tacky and
The barium titnate goes in with that glue just a tiny amount ten to one I'd say
So nine parts of the glue to one part very heavily diluted barium titnate and if you find that it made the glue too thick
you could
You could thin it out with a little bit of alcohol and water just a tiny amount of alcohol not too much because that could
Sometimes coagulate and curdle the glue
so, you know part of me is like it's such early in the game to bring up the barium titnate is
Too fine of a point
But I'm so enamored by its properties that I just want to bring up everything in serial fashion
Everything that I discovered to this point. Is that okay that help?
Yes, it did thank you anything else regarding the pipe and the coatings because we haven't really gotten to the magnets which we will so
Well
The magnets are you using an adhesive to glue them together is making? Yeah. Yep. Yep. I get into now to make that. Yeah
And the next thing is a device to measure TDS not necessary. I'll give a story again that I keep finding the repeated
TDS meter yes or no, you know, it's up to you
And I'll explain why measurements and lab tests are not important with this in minutes
Okay, so what can the mark one be connected to this continuing on this email
What can the mark one be connected to for testing purposes? Is that a garden hose size? Yes now here's the thing about it
I don't know if I've mentioned it enough and I will again
If you send the mark one or a scalerator to a lab for tested they will show that it doesn't do anything
No change to the water whatsoever because their standard with devices are they attach it to a water source and most labs by the way
Do not provide that kind of service most labs that test water just work on samples
They have a standard sample size
500 milliliter that you give them and they just take drops out of the bottle like a bunch of idiots and test it like that
There's very few labs that you'll find at all
That will test the device like the scalerator because you need a running water source and they just don't do that
They just don't do that for private corporations that have labs that do things like that or whatever
but if you find one that does
they will they will show that it has no absolutely no change on the water because they hook it up to the end of a
hose and
They use it like a nozzle, you know
Imagine hooking up the scalerator like a nozzle on the end of a hose and you squirting water through it or whatever
The crazy willie, I don't even getting everything wet it doesn't do anything it needs to have at least
20 30 40 50 feet of pipe in front of it
it's called a
Runner length. You got to have a runner length in front of it and the more runner length the better
Yes, you heard me, right? So how much does more runner length the better? I don't know. I
Don't know but the more runner lengths are better and under pressure the better
Okay, so that's it hopefully we'll answer that how do you test it this is a utilitarian this is not jerk-off technology
You know like Brita filters a jerk-off technology, right?
You just anybody go to Walmart get one pour water in it pour water out. You think you're done
This is not you know for people living in their mom's basement
She'll kick you out if you bring this up
This is utility stuff. This is where you got to go be a man
Trench out a hole
Cut the water main and fasten it in you're gonna have to have skills and you're gonna have that balls and confidence, right?
Okay, so
Basically again reiterate the question. What can the mark one be connected to for testing purposes? Is that a garden hose size?
Yes, but you got to have the garden hose in front of it
So you buy two garden hoses
However, you're gonna connect it with a short length and imagine the longer part of the garden hose 30 40 50 feet is in front
of the device and
you and you block it off with a with a valve or a you know a nozzle so when you pressurize the entire line and
Then let water out and then you'll see what it really does
Okay, I'll acquire material soon as I can't play around little would like to chat soon, okay
All right. Now the next question
Let's see
Keep going down
Well, then I'll get I don't know if the magnet. Okay, first magnets are arriving tomorrow. Okay, here we go
Another another email same individual barium titanate is a little more confusing. Are you making a mixture? How are you applying it?
I think I went over that
Pipe bending techniques the hot sand method. What do you think? Yeah, absolutely
And I think that's it for the questions from this individual and I will continue
Yes, someone just put a comment comment Bruce 90 degree bends in create. Yeah simulated rough increased length
What they do a 90 degree bend simulates runner length. You could find lab reports old reference books on
Water flow through pipe and then how 90 degree bends not sweeps
But sweeps also how they reduce flow. I
Estimate that I'm adding a 90 degree bend
In a runner of plumbing is the same as adding anywhere between 6 to 10 feet of pipe
Is the consequence and I do find that when you add 90 degree bends directly in front and behind it
It does work a little bit better
yes, for some reason it sees this dead end, you know that it has to go around and it seems to improve the
You know improve the
the effect now
I just got to keep interjecting this thing has only been in existence on the surface of the earth as far as I can tell
for ten months
Maybe a little yeah a little less than that
I'm the only one that could pretty much act as the the boss on the subject and I want to change that
That's why I'm doing this Sonics
On other people to get involved in this
So yes, we're still learning
We're gonna keep learning because this is not the water business is the physics business and start playing around with it and seeing what it does
You'll find out what all right. So let's just jump into the magnets in Georgia
You know, if you anyone who's ready to build it, he's got to be chomping off the bit about the magnet
when I first hooked this up I
Turned on the water and I was like, okay, I
Notice the water is kind of fizzy fuzzy and
I'm thinking you know, I want to get away from the front and back of the magnet
Which is the North and South Pole as much as possible
And I know by looking at diagrams even though they're false
If you want a correct diagram of what the magnetic flux lines look like look up Ken Wheeler's book
Thank you guys will be and just put in Ken Wheeler magnetism go to images and
You'll see what the magnetic field lines look like and you'll see where the domain the block wall is
There still is some influence
from the what I call the centrifugal part of the magnet, you know the North and South and
and in my mind intuitively it hit me like how can we minimize and
Bend those fields that are on the North South Poles the faces that everyone is used to
And everyone is thinking about when you mentioned the word magnet
I want to pull them away from the center axis of that domain. How do I do that? How about I stack?
Smaller circumference or and smaller diameter magnets
That will tuck the field in and make it more of a pyramid, right?
It'll bring the field away from the outer part of the magnet
So I grabbed two small max slapped them on real quick as they Wow the water quality changed got more got sweeter
It got lighter that fizziness went away
And I stacked on some more mags not much of a change took them off not much of a change
As soon as I took off the outer two magnets and just had the big one that fizziness came back again, I was like
but the
Three inch magnets as you see in the photo that proportion. That's a five and a quarter outer
Three and a quarter or three and an eighth inner
There's nothing special about the proportions. You could use a smaller magnet, but in the five and a quarter magnet
It's got a two and a half inch hole. So you're not going to put a two and a half inch magnets
I'll fall right in the hole
So I did plenty of experimentation with removing the outer magnets being the smaller magnets left it on either space and
Just having a single magnet and there's a big difference and anyone who's already
Experimented with the scalerator would attest I believe to the same
If you just use a single magnet, you'll notice an effect on the water
But if you add a smaller magnet on each face
Correspondingly, you'll notice an even bigger effect immediately and go ahead and someone does anyone's done it chime in
Give me some feedback. So that's what I've noticed with repeatedly
Okay, how do you connect the magnets? Well, they're magnets when you attach those magnets. Don't do anything funny
You just put them on
Correspondingly how they would go normally like you were sticking something to a fridge on the face of a piece of metal
so the the north side of one of the smaller magnet goes to the south side of the big magnet and
The south side of the small magnet goes to the north side of the big magnet. However, they go and
When you place the magnets over the two smaller outer magnets over the single larger magnet in the center
You'll notice that sometimes if you move them around they want to jump off. Yes, that's right because there are field reversals happening
So just center them and rotate them clockwise or counterclockwise
you'll find they'll settle in and they'll Center up and you go ahead and do a visual Center on them and
You'll notice that if you look through the hole
The smaller magnets cover the larger hole and you have access to the back of the smaller magnet
and what I do is I put a few drops all around once I got them centered of
cyanoacrylic
Acrylate glue which is crazy glue you use the you could use the gel or you could use the flow
You know what? They call minute glue crazy glue cyanoacrylic
cyanoacrylatic whatever the chemical term is crazy glue either it's very cheap and
The gap between the faces of the magnet creates a capillary zone
So the moment you put that glue in there, which it also likes that it will creep in
between the the back face of the smaller outer magnet and the large face of the
the larger magnet and it'll creep in there and immediately harden and dry once you
drop some glue every 120 degrees or every 90 degrees it immediately hardens up and
Another way to make that glue hard enough is water vapor or a water sprayer, by the way
Nothing special and I've had just played around with broken magnets and shit magnets
And I've just put it just placed them together how they normally don't put a little drop of glue in the corner and try to separate
Them they will not separate you could soak them in acetone
And that would do it now you could use five minute epoxy not necessary
In other words
You don't have to add any kind of adhesive between the magnet faces meaning the faces of the smaller
to the larger magnet not not not necessary you may and
You don't even have to use a fast-setting glue
You use a slow again setting glue the if you add the glue if it's a liquid and low enough viscosity
The cavity inside the large magnet you will see the internal faces of the outer small magnets
just put your glue in that inner rim, and it will suck through and and
Grab you don't need to do any special adhesive because remember
Once these magnets settle in and they're not shifting around. They'll just stay in place. Anyway, that's what they do
That's why they're called magnets, right?
So that's what I've been using. It's just basically the crazy glue the
cyanoacrylic glue I get it from Walmart Harbor Freight, whatever the cheap stuff that flows I
use a
Pipe that goes a fitting a shim and once I think my first magnet is centered
I slide my paper shim through to align the other magnets for their line is alignment critical
Yes, and know what's more and critical is the magnetic field lines are aligned again
Because as you place the smaller magnet on the larger magnet, you notice they do attract, you know
You put them on how they normally would attract but they like to bounce around a little bit
So you just count we'll just rotate them like a tuning knob and you'll find the lock into place takes everybody happy
You know like people sitting next to each other on an airplane for a long trip, right? You want them to be comfortable
Is that good enough George? Did you get anything else because you're the only one that brought up the magnet?
Yeah
spot-on
Cool. Now remember don't get crazy with the glue
I mean no pun intended when you put the smaller magnet on the larger magnet face
If you look inside you'll see you see the the faces of the all the magnets
You could just put run a bead of anything in there plenty strong
Yeah, but just recap the smaller of the south side to the larger on the north right and then yeah
Just like they normally would go. Yeah, don't don't try to reverse anything
Yeah, you'll know by the way, if you go north to north, you'll know you're doing that. It'll it will not want to go, right?
You just put the magnets how they want to go now when I work with magnets
I mark them all the big I got a red marker and a white marker
I mark all my faces just to be easy because I get kind of fancy
With the magnets when you buy a magnet
It's it's cut off of a block and all that and then Maggie, you know cured metal and ceramics and all that
It's got some really sharp edges when you order a magnet and you take it out of a container
You could cut yourself on that edge of the magnet. Sometimes it's so sharp. It's not deburred or anything
I put the magnets on a laid spin them and I have a large diamond pad and I round off the edges if you look
At the photo. I think if you could zoom in on the photo that I dropped with the copper
Magnets when they come when the magnetic reactor is done. You could zoom in on that pick right there real close
I'm gonna zoom in use them in real close. You'll see there's about a two millimeter
Millimeter and a half radius on those magnets. They're rounded off on the edges now that I mentioned it
You can see it you could zoom really zoom in on that
You'll see that the edges on those magnets are rounded off
Now it's I've made another discovery doing that when you spin a large and I spit and I round off the edges before I assemble them
So you want to round off the corresponding edges on the smaller magnets if you're going to do it
I don't recommend when building these early ones that you do that, but I just do that
When you by the way when you spin a magnet in the lathe at about 600 rpm and
You start putting friction on it
Wherever you're touching on there's gonna go red-hot right away, and it shouldn't hint hint
Let me repeat that
What we could do with a little bit of fine-tuning is
Get a solar panel and a little battery spinning a large magnet with a flywheel a little bit of friction
You run some fluid through that you'll heat your house with a 12-volt battery
If you know what you're doing
You could superheat anything with a rotating magnetic field and you need a little bit of friction
You'll be making other words you put 100 watts of power in you'll get 150 200 watts of heat out of it
Is it free energy? I don't know you tell me and
when I started
Running because you want to know when I ran my diamond abrasive pads on to round off these magnets
I had to keep them really wet the moment
The moisture and the water of the cutting fluid
Stop, there's just water
It got red-hot anything that touch it right immediately. Just you know, I started doing experiments
I noticed that you can create tremendous amount of powery heat with rotating magnets and a small amount of friction
Anybody wants to go down that route you got to go for it. I just gave you a big hint
Right and for if we get as big as Westinghouse or General Electric one of these big companies
We can open we can have ten different departments doing things with what we've discovered with the scaler eater
But I doubt that's gonna happen
What about the relay?
Okay, the relay what relay last seminar you said that we can relay the reactors
The turbid erator is another device
Yeah
in other words
We could know we can make a new type of relay because we've discovered also a planar magnetic field which I'll get into
I wanted to introduce the turbid erator
Yeah, you know what relay switching relays are right?
They're basically met electromagnets and they have a certain field size and a certain function
And they do have problems when you put them in metal cases next to each other, whatever
but now I know how to make a planar magnetic field meaning when you look at any magnetic field at the face on the
Opposite field is on the backside
Well, I know how to make a magnet where you look at let's say the north end of the magnet
But on the opposite side, it's the north also and the south goes 90 degrees to it every time
Right very power it's amazing when you rotate that sucker you get other phenomenon
We'll share this in due time on a different call
Let's say we'll start a different subject and and that probably will start doing more like video stuff
Shorts, so I'll just take a video of the phenomenon and show you the setup, right?
Because it's more elaborate than this the mark one the scale radar. You couldn't come up with anything simpler than that
There's only two components the magnetic reactor and spool of pipe and the rest of it is embellishing
You couldn't come up with a simpler device. No one can you know, I
Mean there put it this way. It couldn't get any simpler than this
The turbid erator, which is a three-part device that uses this planar magnetic fields is a little more complex
Actually a lot more complicated but still requires the same skill set if you can build this you can build that
It's more elaborate and we'll get into that as time goes on
Right. You see right now. You don't know what the turbid erator is or does so you're not missing anything. Are you?
Well, just what you say
But yeah, yeah. Well, well it leads like someone said you're not in the water business. You're in the physics business
Because no one's using the block wall
No one at all. I had a patent reviewer keeps sending me patents for weeks and weeks
Look at all these patents with magnetic treatment of water. I went through none of them are like this
They're all using the face the north and south. They're all hitting the the fluid
With the they want to all these different ways of how a magnet should face the water. I'm like, I'm not doing that
As a matter of fact, do you want to shut down the scale radar from working?
Go ahead and hook it up and then get yourself a big bar magnet or whatever
Sandwich it put the magnet right on pipe. Just like everybody else does watch what happens. Boom stops working
Yep, this is an amazing amazing amazing. There is no one with a capital W that is
Doing this running the fluids exclusively solely over the block wall only and with purpose with purpose
I've had dozens of patents
Of people send me and not a one is doing it's not a one no one
Everyone's getting creative with because you know, they still they're locked into that eight-year-old nine-year-old. It's a magnet, you know
So you got to use the side that we all know about right north or south, right?
Oh, should we should we put the north and north or south and south or north and south none of it?
None of it avoid that avoid that, right?
So yeah, so that's basically the magnetic reactor and there's the fitting
When you when you wrap your pipe and it cools down and all that around the magnet you'll find sometimes it's too tight
Go ahead and file away some of that material
If it's too loose
You want to put some epoxy a non not JB weld because it has iron in it
Use a clear epoxy
Or use PC 11. I'm a big fan of PC 11 to look it up. That's P Peter Charlie number 11 epoxy
And you just build up some material every 90 degrees on the magnet not you don't have to slop the whole edge of the magnet
You know, in other words if the magnet sloppy doesn't go it's it flops around flops through the pipe
I like to fit the magnetic reactor into the pipe like a nice
Slip fit a tight slip fit even a mild press fit. I
Don't like it slopping around because it has to be centered you do a visual center when you along the pipe
If you center the the magnetic reactor
The large magnet in the center of the pipe visually in three locations opposite each other. She's centered
She's good to go
Must be centered
First one I did I stuck the magnet. I'll drop a photo of the first one
Again when I put it in there
I just pushed the magnet in the pipe and after I installed the magnet went askew and
I noticed the water got crappy
Magnet was still in there, but it was not centered
So I started moving the mess. Let me just visually centered it and I grabbed it with some zip ties
and
The water got really good and then I moved the magnet water got crappy wasn't centered
That's another it's a very critical thing that the block wall
The domain wall is centered along the main path as much as possible
And I'll drop a photo and show you what a ghetto Raider looks like
The first one ever made I'll show you
What it looks like on the install feel ugly because I did it real fast
This is the foundation wall. I
Did it real fast like, you know
Over like a half a pack of cigarettes and five cups of coffee in the morning
So excited to get it in there soon as I've got some daylight, you know
And there it is and that one's dated around April 18th of 2023
So, I don't know if you guys got that picture somebody just chime in if you got it if you can see it
Yes now and if that if that's not ghetto, I don't know what it is
You could see I was in a hurry. There's no unions. It's schedule 40. It's
Magic marker, you know, I did my my lineup where I was gonna cut things and I just bold marker
I just make sure when you stick it in with the glue because it's that hot glue. It's called hot PVC. You got five seconds
Once you slip it in then you can't move it, right? So I said, let me make some bold marks and
It was wet. It was yeah, and and you could see the magnets got this is after I before I buried it
Or closed off the area I can get to it pretty well because it's got sand around it and a hat at cover
access cover now, but
The reason I got the zip ties there there's and I didn't even bother bonding the magnet
Magnetic reactor or anything, but I know she was really off-center
And you can see the bend is not really that great
You know the the upper pipe on the return doesn't bend down and line up with the lower pipe at all like it does later on
And it still works because I've got
majority of the pipe centered and it's just zip ties and that's the first one this is the
The first desperate attempt to get it manifest and boy was it was it worth it
now if you if you scroll up to the gray one that I just dropped in the images you could see a
Big formative difference there
That's the second one that I built a week later by contemplating how it should be done
okay, and
I do apply tabs that are you could go back and see photos of other ones
I do make plastic tabs. If you if you guys recall the ones that if you scroll up
ones that are in the cases
by the way, there's a pic someone put there about a
Lord Kelvin's experimenting Andrew where he splits the water flow. No, I just ignore that. No, it has nothing to do with anything like that
If you scroll up if I have the well drop
What I'm gonna do just for
Finishing purposes. I'm gonna go see the other account here. I will forward another image
Of if you were to order one
From me and the check is in the mail like they say and I know you're gonna pay for it
You will I will get one of these to you and you're gonna settle with me on it
I'll be if you act professional with me. I will be very professional with you
Kind of thing, right?
You will get one
That looks like this this is the shorty I call it
Because the ones below are a little larger. I'm going to drop an image here again. You guys have probably
Seen these before seen this one before
You'll get something that looks like that in a very nice military grade pressurized case
All right. It's got a nice finish to it or you'll get the larger model that has some fittings on it
That will look like this. Let's see. I'll send you a forward this one
Let's see forward or you'll get the the larger still water both one inch pipe
That looks like this. I just drop that one in
so
When you get a device for me, and you don't know me
Let's say boy this guy don't make junk. He makes some good shit when there it is
That one has a gold leaf on it. It's
It looks silver, but it's a gold leaf and it's an imitation gold leaf, which is made of copper and zinc
barium titanate glue
Yeah, I call this the tactical version. It's got the US Army tan colored
2k spray coating on it
Now what you'll see on both of these is once the magnet is fitted
It I have a chinking material or caulk
That goes between the pipe and the magnet and some tabs that are bonded to the pipe and the magnet to hold it in place
You can see that on both of them slightly different
And those tabs are at 36 degrees apart because why because
The heart sits at 36 degrees in the body 36 degrees, right?
It's an important angle
so if you guys see those images those are what the finished products look like if you were to order one from me what you
get
It is impressive. It's not like you're getting something from Amazon or in cheap box
It comes double boxed in a really nice case, and you're also paying five grand for it
So it should look good in the larger version that you've got there great. Yeah to the two
Circles either side of the
Scale orator are they just flanges for the fitting?
The circles you mean left and right on the foreground of the case. Yes. Yeah
Those are the other halves of the unions. You can just put in what a pipe union looks like
Yeah, they just did I didn't want to have them attached
Yeah, are you familiar with a plumbing Union?
Those those two circles on the foreground in the case get attached to the main. Oh
Yeah, gotcha. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Anybody else see that? Yeah, they're not extra parts or anything
Yeah, so the flanges yeah, there's the outer flanges
The flanges that are mounted to the scale orator are the the ones where the o-rings are
These are the outer flanges that get mounted to where you do your cut in
Yeah
And in the center that is that there's a bushing that you added on there
Yeah in the center because it looks or I imagine you got a big magnet and you
Here do smaller magnets and you got this gap you look in there. It's like, you know, so what I did remember
I said when you get stick a pipe you can have some left over about a foot
You cut yourself a three and a quarter inch piece and you have yourself a cone a metal cone or a wooden cone
Heat one end of the piece
Plastic and you flare it out
Until it fills into that gap of the smaller magnet and you turn it around you flare it out again. It's not that easy
I have a
excuse me a jig that I made to do that a
Jig that maybe I could show
Yeah, it's an I haven't done a photo of that but I made a special jig out of wood
that you you just cut a three inch piece of pipe and
As you heat the pipe you basically with a small press you press it down till it stops. There's a stop
Flares the part out, right?
And then you like a mandrel. Yeah. Yeah, like a mandrel. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
The future make but it's not necessary. It just looks good
It's just a well-formed when I send it to a guy as a company he says wow
That's a nice well-formed plastic piece in the center because they form plastics and they're like, how'd you do that?
or he just said
For someone who has a business report makes forms and injects plastics is he called it a well-formed piece
So I take it as a compliment, but I just like plugging it up if you really feel mean
You could get yourself some you know that epoxy that clear epoxy they use
You know when you go to a bar and they have pennies and things in the bar
Put that heavy clear coat material epoxy on it, right?
Go ahead and mix up some silver dust and barium tetanate with that epoxy and just fill in
The gap poured and you know put a block or something on the backside and fill that area up with that
Epoxy is fine, too
But it gets expensive when you put expensive dielectrics in there because remember barium titanate and silver powder is not cheap
You could do that. That'll increase it's a it'll make the water seem a little more
Juicy, let's just say all these little things. We'll get into later with the adding dielectrics to the magnet and things like that
We'll do but it's not that much of a difference. It's just a little bit nicer. It's kind of like years ago
You bought a plain car with a radio and the dealer says for 300 bucks more. We'll put a pinstripe on the car
Does it go faster?
Well, you know, it's a pinstripe, right? It's more than a pinstripe, but you know what?
I mean, it's just options. It does get a little bit better
So basically that's just a fill piece in on the magnet
So, you know a little curious children don't stick their fingers in there and say hey look, it's just two magnets that
It's again I was just inspired as I just didn't like the way it looked just imagine
Bonding two smaller magnets to a larger magnet. Just that's what it looks like and I figured let's fill that hole
Also on installation. It's much cleaner
It won't get filled with dirt and water, you know, because there's a step in there, right?
so again
Now we're that we're on the magnets attaching the magnet what I do when the magnet I have a tight fit
And if it just so happens to be a sloppy fit
Either way too tight grind out some of the pipe use your brain
Don't be don't grind away so much pipe that you compromise it just a little
Or
If it's too big of an opening go ahead and every 90 degrees or 120 degrees on the magnet apply some epoxy
We could do a couple of dabs and when the epoxy hardens file it down as needed to Center
It should be a nice press fit not a press fit
Usually when I say press fit in the fab world, it means you need a tool or press to press it in
No, it's a it's a good slip fit
Like when you slip it in there you can walk it with it
You can walk around with it under your arm and the magnet won't fall out, right?
That's the worst thing too
When you're playing with it when you're putting this together
It's on a table someone tries to pick it up and move it the magnet falls out and hits the deck, right?
Cuz it'll shatter. It's a ceramic magnet. And by the way, let me just add this
Every time I talk about something I got to add various sundry things that sound tangential
I'm using these ceramic magnets in an era where everything is gone with these neodymium little fuckers, right?
Neos don't work. You could try experimenting. It has a slight effect
The real high-powered magnets don't work because the field is so tight and the block wall is so tight
Like the stronger the magnet the tighter the field and you can notice this by the way
Well by handling them if you have a small neo man, I don't want to get in the neo subject
But you know those really strong rare-earth magnets they call them
If you handle that, you know, it's like how strong is this magnet?
You bring it close to a piece of metal nothing. Nothing. Nothing gets real close and then BAM
holy shit, that's strong magnet, but yeah, let's pay attention a
Comparable strength magnet that ceramic of course can be much larger as you bring it closer
Let's say the refrigerator door. You're like, oh, it's sorry. I feel the pull. I feel the pull feel the pull then boom
Because the field is much wider
Okay, so the we're living in an era where the basically these ceramic magnets are in industry and everywhere else being phased out
Unless it's for cost
Because these are big and chunky and they're heavy and they don't have the field intensity
But for this application, they work way better than the Neos if if you tried Neos
It wouldn't work much at all because the field is so tight
So I just needed to bring that up because we're on the magnet subject
But basically when I apply the magnet now you have two situations that go on
You want that magnet magnetic reactor to stay put?
Okay, so you have two things that will affect the device once it's installed
You have the you have a a torque load when let's say a plumber is hooking it up
He's twisting and turning with his spanners, right? Hopefully not if they're using unions, you don't have to use unions
You know the grit in the install you might have to force it, right?
So the overlap where the pipe is also has to be bonded you use PVC glue for that
if you if you shoot in close-up on the
Scale or finish scalerators in the case is real close
You'll see that the where the pipes the spool overlaps is also bonded
You can see the fillet there a fillet of material that use PVC glue or plastic epoxy for that
Now again the magnetic reactor where it fits into the pipe you got two things that will disturb it one is a slow torque load
twisting bending and
The other thing is what I call a shock load shock load would be like you're walking
To where you're gonna install it and from the truck and it falls out of your hand hits the deck. Oh, it's it's the ground
That's shock load shock load would be someone giving it a good whack with a mallet. There's a shock load. Okay
All right. Well, we know from basic fab work
is that
In order to resist torque and twist you need a rigid glue something that is preferably even more rigid
Than the material that's why for example
Young children when they start playing with wood glue
They're always amazed when they glue the two pieces of wood together and they try to break it that it the glue is stronger than the wood
Right. Yeah, I remember that. I don't know if everybody remembers that playing around wood glue when you're
Real young
When you glue the wood together is like shit, right? It's stronger where I glued it stronger than the wood itself
Okay that resists the torque and twist
Okay
So we use that kind of glue every 60 degrees
Every 90 degrees and we leave some areas open then we use a flexible glue
because the flexible glue
Takes the shock load really well
where if the hard glue that's stronger than the plastic or stiffer than the plastic will break with
the shock load
It'll shatter
Let's go back to the popsicle stick children playing with wood glue
they use the regular white or yellow wood glue and
After a few hours, they go ahead and break pull it apart and they say the popsicle stick breaks for where it was glued, right?
now
That that's your shock load
breaking it
but if you had a very flexible glue and
You put the two popsicle sticks together with your well
You're really young nephew or grandson or whatever and you ask him pull the popsicle sticks together. It's real. They won't break
Right, they'll just twist and bend right and you'll see the glue kind of flexing and stretching, right?
You get it
So what would I've considered?
From experience and also projecting my experience on what could happen the two situations one is a heavy shock load and
One is a torque load. So I want two types of glue. So if one fails
So if it takes the shock load and the rigid glue fails
I've got the flex glue still holding the magnetic reactor in place and vice versa
right
if the if the flexible glue fails, I've got the
rigid glue holding it
and once I have those intervals of glue in there, I
Then have a color matched water-based latex high quality that I've matched. I took black caulk and gray caulk and
mixed it
I've heard women in Washington called caulk caulk. That's fine, too. And
They depends on what accent you have
So you take the black caulk and the gray caulk and you mix it till you get the color of the gray plastic
I like that I put whenever I use fillet material like that
Even the epoxies I have a small plastic bag a ziploc bag. Those freezer bags are durable
I put the material in the corner of the bag
I tie it real tight and I have a little pouch with the glue the cornec and a snip a little tiny
One millimeter end of the corner of the bag and then I have like a pastry black bag where I could flow the material out
Really nice and then I have some solvent to smooth it out as needed
And that depends on your skills
If someone ever asked you to like caulk their bathtub or whatever if you're happy with the way you do that
You probably be happy with the way you'll do this if you're not good at that
You probably won't be good at that. It's not necessary to make it look finished at this point
And I believe that the finishing aspects struck and some of the structural aspects will best be done in the future
We might be doing a short video and uploading it somewhere because I think if you do enough videos or whatever on Skype
It'll kill Skype. I'm not sure
So maybe it's best Bruce or someone else Sam might help me with that. Well, we upload a video like on the YouTube
oh my gosh, or
You know some other
whatever free
thing that you sign up for shorts and
You know and the title will be appropriate and I have a description and you can say well
How does the Greek finish this? How does he put that?
Right, but I'm not kidding all this if no one wants to build them. So
Yeah
Good
We could even play the video right over Skype
Yeah, I think it's better to do reference type stuff where it's clean and it's poignant because over Skype
It may not be perfect the first shot around
You know, I could do a video and then have it edited, you know
Just do like we know people do on YouTube right or Vimeo or whatever, right? Mm-hmm Odyssey. There's so many free
Yeah, it was so or you could do the video over Skype. Yeah, turn it on turn it off. Yeah, I
Think it records video also, doesn't it?
Yes, sir
Yeah, but even doing a video over Skype. I got to get lighting, right? You know, you know me I got to do it, right?
I know
Yeah, so I got to get a little studio area together
You know, I don't people won't mind if a cat or two jumps over stuff
But yeah, I just got to do it, right the lighting got to be right
The setting has to be right camera has to be right maybe more than one camera. I don't know
I have all that stuff ready to go
I don't like to do junk, you know, so
Also, it's not necessary to do all that setup if no one's gonna build anything
Right, and I noticed the more interest the more the more interest I see the more interest I will put in and more time
I will put in to help whoever wants to do it. This is something that
Again, it reminds me. I was reading about Michael Faraday's like something came up reasons
Suggest thinking about Michael Faraday other
Look up Michael Faraday a guy with an eighth grade education basically created the foundation of the entire electrical world
They are in the 1700s 1800s, right?
Early 1800s 1830 or whatever
And he had no education or whatever and he basically no mathematics no equations, right?
Just like I've got you know descriptions. Here's some conductive wire. Here's a piece of iron and look what I've observed
When I do this and look what I've observed and I did that and he was not into turning it into a business
He just wanted to document everything. I think he was a Ghanai. I think it's a
Religious sect where it's like they teach you that it's bad to make money. Don't it's bad to be wealthy or whatever
I'm not again
at this point
I'd like to get other people interested in doing see what comes out of it because if it does turn into a business even on
My end more strictly a business and proposal. There's plenty to go around
I mean there's plenty of customers and
And all that, you know
And I'm I'm leading the way on it anyway until someone else wants to lead the way on it because this is very very important
Application and discovery of
Use of the block wall of a magnet again. I want to stress on this
There are magnets involved, but we are not using magnetism
That's why we don't call them magnets when they're assembled to call them a magnetic reactor
kind of gets the mind away from
Sole purpose of a magnet
You bring up a magnet to even someone who's a physicist
The first thing they think of in their mind. I know actually if they have any mind left after
education or university is
magnets sticking to something, you know poles they have no idea that the
Block wall is useful as it's being used here and they never will by the way
When the ever that they have left
So this is an application on many many many levels
And I just want to any if there's any questions about the coatings the pipe bending which we have not gotten into yet
Or whatever. Maybe should I get into the pipe bending a little bit? Yeah type of yes
Hey type of sand sharp sand there's different types of sand all kinds of sand
There's something called sharp sand and they use it. It's a B sand when they make roads
You know, they mix gravel and sand and they put the ass they pack it down and they put their asphalt or cement over it
You can buy it. It's called sharp sand. If you don't have it, it's fine
Any beach sand will do play sand will do collards and anything
the proper temperature I
Found the best temperature is 360
370 degrees I go to a second-hand store and I buy medium-sized pots
liter and a half pot thick wall aluminum anodized pot
Yeah, a lot of you can use cast iron
You want the side of the pot to be thick, you know, how some stainless steel pots just have a thick bottom and thin side
It takes much longer and do it over an electric stovetop cast stovetop doesn't matter get yourself an infrared thermometer
so you can shoot it at a distance when it gets to
340 degrees the sand give it a stir every so often you figure out what that is Celsius. I think
Somebody figure out 340 turns 360 370 degrees is your working point depending on your outdoor temperature
Wintertime if your outdoor temperature, it's fall or winter. You're going to keep it in the 360
370 range if it's a hot summer day
340 350 degrees sand is fine
And you want to plug your pipe and when you plug your pipe
You have a dowel with a stopper wrapped around it
It could be just a piece of rag with masking tape
And your and your dowel is like a push rod
It goes down into the pipe a couple of inches because you don't want to heat up the very ends of the pipe
Where your plumbing fittings go because they're going to deform potentially, right?
so
What you're really doing out of let's say 34 inches of pipe
You only need enough sand
for let's say
30 27 inches
So you I usually I have two
Dowel ends that are four inches long that I stuff into the ends or one end is two and a half inches. Sorry
So you could see you know those barrel cleaners they have on a cannons
It's like a stick with a brush or a ball on the end of it a cloth ball
Basically just make something like that
And attach to the dowel. So when you pull it out, it comes out with the dowel plug
And you you plug in so no hot sand ends up on the last couple of inches of the pipe
That's pretty much it. You got to use a metal funnel
Uh, don't grab your mom's plastic funnel because you know what you pour 350 degree sand fahrenheit
For plastic funnel your mommy's gonna ask you what you do to the funnel
It'll melt and fall into the pipe and make a big mess
So you need a metal funnel or a glass funnel, but I don't like working with glass when I got stuff. I have to work quick
With around or you could just bend yourself, um, whatever piece of
Heavy cardstock will work
Won't burn. I've been using pipe of cups
Paper cups will work. Yeah, because flash point of paper cups over 450 fahrenheit, so you'll find
Yeah
Yep, whatever whatever it takes. I use a funnel because I like to not think about it
And when you fill up the pipes, do you dump it out put your your end piece in your plug in?
Right now I get really fancy you get really fancy. I have very elaborate stoppers with
Valves on them filters and when I put my stoppers on there, I put about two or three psi of air
So there's extra air pressure inside the pipe that keeps the walls from deforming also, but that's
Too technical right now
Yeah, I mean these the the level that i'm making them now I could send it to a space agency
And the engineers would look at it and say this thing is really a really high level tolerance manufacturer
I I don't need to convey all the various things I do
That that don't matter and getting one or two or three of these built and getting them working not necessary
but eventually I will get into how to make a high precision one and show all the jigs and fixtures and
mandrels and all the stuff that I made, uh, and and it'll just it'll yeah, it'll just uh,
Bog you down right now and i'll have to be on for the next six hours to explain all that more than 30 photographs
I'm, not going to do that right now. It's too early in the game, and I think you guys appreciate that
But what you want to do with the hot sand in the pipe
is um
Put plugs very I can't stress how important it is because the hot sand does not go to all the way to the end
Of the pipe you want to keep that
True dimension undisturbed, right? Because that's why you're where your fittings go
And your fittings are dimensionally accurate, I mean they're not that dimensionally accurate plastic fittings
Then you go to a plumbing supply you grab a handful of any fitting of the same size
You'll notice they all feel a little different when you try to put it on the end of a pipe
They don't really make these plumbing fittings of high tolerance. So you don't want to disturb the end of the pipe
Uh, what I do is I have a heat gun. It's called a heat gun. Yes. I use it for paint stripping or whatever
It gets real hot
Uh 600 degrees celsius 1200 degrees fahrenheit kind of thing on high
all right, so
While my sand is cooking usually it takes me 15 to 20 minutes to get the sand up to temperature on a low to medium flame
No reason to hit the pot of sand with a high flame because it'll just it doesn't the heat doesn't transfer to the sand
It's so fast, right? So why burn up your pot and your burner?
Now I have another thing that I do is I mix magnetite if you don't have it. It's fine
About uh 20 percent magnetite in with my sand
Now magnetite's a black iron, you know black sand. It's
iron crystal
And when I started doing this, I noticed that whenever I I put it in there because it holds the heat real good
And uh, I noticed that whenever I heated pipe
with uh
the magnetite mixture
And I rubbed solvent strong solvent and that would normally melt the plastic
Uh, if it had been heated with the magnetite internally or externally the plastic did not want to melt
It changed the plastic
It made it resistant to solvents
And I thought I was just you know, maybe the solvent got aired out lost its potency or whatever
Then I said, hmm
Maybe the magnetite's transmuting the pipe, you know formula changing it making it more resistant to solvents
So I said let's do a couple of experiments
I went back and forth with
Heated non-heated heated with magnetite heated without magnetite and then every time
The pipe that was subject to the hot magnetite mixture
Was extremely solvent resistant
So I just want to I've mentioned this on a regular sonic a while back
right, and I believe that it also affects the water quality because now
If the plastic is less is more resistant to solvents
It's actually resistant to leaching stuff into the water, right? It's more inert
So you're gonna have a better plastic that way again, not necessary
But it is a it is it is a good point and that a lot of people
Are not as far. I have a half a ton of magnetite here on the property thousand pounds of it high grade
That's not fair, right? If I don't have magnetite, where do I get it? Well, you know ebay
They'll send you a little pouch for 10 bucks or something
whatever
Or you could be industrious and how they got talked about i've been talking about magnetite for years, so
So basically that's heating the pipe with the sand but I just don't other than the stops I preheat the pipe with that heat gun
Uh by rolling it back and forth. You don't want to you always want to be very even you could use a blow dryer
But you want to get that pipe
Up upwards of 120 degrees externally
Uh, so you basically you have a room temperature or ambient temperature pipe
When you pour that hot sand in that schedule 80
That hot sand is going to give up all its heat just to get that pipe hot before it makes it flexible
And you're gonna you're working time and the pipe's going to be real stiff
So if you preheat the pipe externally with the heat gun or blow dryer to at least 120
degrees
Uh by rolling it back and forth on the table or on the ground while your sand is being heated
You want to heat the pipe really as much as you can without it getting soft
Because once it gets soft without the sand filler it can deform
And you remember when you're heating preheating the pipe before you put the sand in there you again you avoid the last three inches
On the ends because you don't want to deform them again, right?
So you put markers on there or whatever would just be a good boy to remember where you're pointing the gun
and um
And when I preheat the pipe to about 120 130 degrees by hand
Rolling it around there's many ways to preheat a pipe. You don't have to use the heat gun or whatever
I don't recommend
using hot water because it's dangerous splashing it around and all that but you could if you had a trough with boiling water that would
Work fine, but
How are you going to not heat the ends again? So I use a heat gun
And for the moment, you know while it's hot you could set it aside be quick
Get your uh plugs on one end and start pouring your hot sand in there
And once you got your hot sand in there go ahead and grab your heat gun again
You know, we're talking about like an industrial heat gun. It could be gotten very cheap
Hair dryers can help but they don't work very well. You can
If you just have a hair dryer go ahead and plug up the back of the intake
So the so you can put it on high and the restricted airflow allows the blow dryer to get hotter, right?
And when you put your hot sand in there keep hitting it with a blow dryer on the area where you start bending it again
Because this is schedule 80 now
No fault if you're working with schedule 40
I'm not trying to be an asshole about it
Even though it is junk
Uh, if you're building one out of schedule 40, which is the white plastic pvc go ahead. It's fine
Even though it is junk for me and for you will be if you start using that even though the one I have installed
Here in the house though is schedule 40
uh, it's a very
Big difference between the white pvc schedule 40
And schedule 80 the working experience very big difference
The schedule 40 will will bend very rapidly with the hot sand
Because of its thin wall and it's the type of plastic that it is
So basically as you bend it around you need to find a way to hold it
So you're going to need some kind of a clamping system
As you go
And you don't want to use clamps that have a flat end on it because you're going to put a flat spot on your pipe
So if you're using a one inch pipe get yourself some one and a quarter which slips over
Cut little sections of curved parts. You can make curved parts out of epoxy out of wood
Whatever you get creative pieces of cardboard, whatever
And you're gonna have to figure out how I have a clamping table and a clamping system which I could photograph and
Show you guys what it looks like and all that
But it'll just like over if I start putting pictures of all the fixtures and all the stuff that I built to make these
If you're just starting out, you'll be intimidated. You'll be bogged down. You'll say holy shit
I got to make this this this that and this this and that to make that fuck that
No, I don't want to do that right now because the first one
Even the first schedule 81 that I had no jigs I had nothing it was just done on the ground by hand with some
welding gloves
And yes, I used heavy leather gloves because guess what? It's hot plastic
It won't really burn you
But you you could get a like a real bad, you know, you'll be sore all night
You don't want to be handling hot pipe hot plastic with your bare hands
now
If once you start forming the pipe around the magnet or around a spacer
And you have a way to hold it you might want two people, you know, hold this here push it down there, you know, whatever
Uh, you might want to start incorporating get a spray bottle and the moment you hit
The sections that you've held down and you're happy with
With a spray bottle it immediately cools the plastic enough that it becomes rigid and it will not move
And then once you go around with a spray bottle and saying, you know
Wherever the mist hits the water hits it will freeze the plastic in that position
Um, and then when you're done with it
You're happy go ahead and pull one of the ends or both of the ends on pour that hot sand out of there
And when you're pouring the hot sand out of that round spool, you got to keep turning the spool up and down. So
First time doing it
It'll be funny because you'll be getting sand everywhere
You think you got the sand out and you turn it up pouring hot sand all over the place. Be careful, right?
Remember it's coming out of something. It looks like a french horn
So that's pretty much, uh the quick overview on the bending process at this point at this point
the
Once you build one and you know that this is what you want to do. We want to build more
I do recommend building rudimentary jigs
Uh, there are some youtube videos where people are bending pipe
And their version of rudimentary jig which anybody could do very quickly
Is they have a table or just a sheet of wood that they've drilled holes in on a grid pattern
or selected pattern and then pegs
Right. So as you bend your you could look this up bending pvc pipe on youtube
And I think there's a chick that's doing it and she basically has a bench with holes in it
And as she's bending her pipe, she sticks these pegs in there that holds the pipe from wiggling out, you know out of shape
That's another way to do it
I and remember whenever you're putting something against around
a flat plane against a round plane
That's soft. It's going to put a flat spot and a deformation in it, right? So just consider that
So an easy way to start working on a jig again, just a scrap piece of wood. That's as big as the device
With holes in it and pegs as you go around, you know as you bend it around you slap a peg in there
Keeps it from unbending and unraveling many ways to do it
Very often people ask me show me how to do it and i'm like i'll introduce you to the person who showed me how to
Do it. How's that?
Well, I don't know who i'll introduce you to because i'm on my own
so you guys are not on your own i'm here to help you out as much as possible, but
On an introductory level
Let's just keep it as such and then we'll continue on the more advanced stuff and i'll be glad to share everything that i've done and
Have on how to make these as time goes on based on feedback, of course
Years ago when I was dumber and younger I would have spent a week doing an entire presentation
Uh and powerpoint and show her and you know, so I don't you know, why why it's not necessary right until I see there's an interest
But once I see there's an interest and people are serious
Uh, i'll i'll jump in and tell you everything I know
That said I think we've covered everything unless
I know there's a couple of people are going to hear this and some are on here right now that are ready to go and
Some have already done it
Is anything else that tickles you, you know about asking since i'm here because the purpose of this was to give a more advanced
Uh expose on how to put these together if someone's going to be trying to put one together this week for the first time
So if there's any questions or anything you want to chime in or whatever go ahead right now
Yeah, that was an accident on the
I clicked the wrong button on the heart. But any wishes for the plug
And the dowel around it
So you're putting the dowel inside the pipe, correct with the with the plug
They mean the magnetic reactor around. Oh
You mean plugging for a bit for the uh, the sand yes
Well, just imagine you have a straight
Remember early on we how much pipe 34 inch piece of pipe
So you buy your stick or you have a pre-cut at 34 inches
And you have a straight piece of pipe
right
Uh, go ahead and pour sand in it what happens well sand will come out the other end right gravity
You got to have at least one plug now, if you just have one plug keep the sand from falling on the ground
And if you turn it horizontal start working horizontally what's going to happen on the other end?
And just start pouring out the other end
You got to plug both ends
and and the plugs basically look like three inch long dowels with a
cotton fabric and some tape wrapped around it so
That they when you push it into the pipe, it's got a lot of friction. It will not fall out. It's pretty tight
right
And it's also the ball the cotton
Fabric is connected to the dowel. So when I pull the dowel out the cotton ball, you know, the stopper comes with it
Yeah, I have an image on it right there
Yeah, it just looks you ever watched old movies where they have these cannon cleaners guy comes with a stick
It's got a ball on the end of it and they rubbed it back and forward to clean the barrel gun barrel out
It's just like that but a miniature one
More evolved one is a pipe. It's a tube with a rubber stopper on the end with a schrader valve on the end of the pipe
And the rub and as you twist it
There's a washer on the end of the stopper that expands it into the pipe
And then you put when you have both of your stoppers in and your hot sand you put three pounds of pressure in there
Which is minimal
and the air pressure and the sand keeps the pipe very very round if you look at the
Scalarators in the cases and you zoom in and you look at the profile of the pipe no matter where you look. It's perfect
Right now i've gotten to the point where I don't need to pressurize air anymore
Because i've made enough of these
and i've you know paying attention while i'm working on how to
Avoid that step
And when you have an air valve
to pressurize
To release the air it'll clog it and you'll throw away the valve
So you have to have a very fine brass screen to keep the sand from going into the valve
So the you know, we're talking about stoppers that I made that if you gave them to nasa
They would look at and say this is part of the space shuttle, right?
It's not it's not necessary to build something like that, but I did because I can build things like that very quickly
Here I have the ability to do so
But that would be the optimum optimum
Right. So let's say you were to get a corporate hire to bend pipes for you
You'd want to do the compressed air in there
So in case he had a bad morning didn't have enough coffee or whatever. He argued me out with his wife
He'll be consistent on bending these things. He doesn't have to pay too much attention
right
That's my goal with this is to set up enough systems
Say I call them corporate hires, you know
You put an ad in the paper for someone to make something you interview them. Okay, jack
You think you can do is fine this much an hour pat him on the back
You got to make 10 of these and by the end of the day, okay. Bye. See ya
Unsupervised and when you come back at the end of the day, you don't want to fire him
You want him to come back the next day and keep doing it right because he does good work
right
Yeah, then you're worried about
I just want to ruin the the tails of it, right? You don't want to ruin the tails
Keep the heat away. Yeah. Yeah, it makes total sense that the tails are the ends the stubs
Combs like when plumbing when you have a short piece of pipe, it's called a stub, right?
and uh
you want to keep those, uh
unaffected by the heat because what does the heat do it deforms and you also want to
You don't want them to be deformed or cut or scratched if you're if you're cutting it with a saw you want to make sure
It's a nice clean cut and square it off, right?
Uh, you don't want it to drop on the corner and crack schedule 80 won't crack schedule 40 will
right
And when I say schedule 80, it's the gray stuff, you know very often I think it's all
Like years ago. I would just say use schedule 80 once
And and then i'll go back and listen to people and say I didn't hear that i'm like, oh my gosh
So I have to keep repeating it
The schedule 80 8 0 the gray stuff is very very durable and a pleasure to work with
Once you understand that the heavy wall material requires more heat
And a little bit more labor, but it will retain its shape better stay away from the ends. That makes total sense to you now, right?
You want to keep the hot sand and the preheating away from that, you know
Just for the sake of dimensionality
So I think we might have different terms in australia. Like I haven't heard of schedule 80, but
Is it used as a?
Conduit
Yes
Yes, it can be right. It's a yeah. Yeah electrical conduit. Yeah. Yeah, but it's yeah
It's not for pressure. Yeah
All right. This is for water assignments
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Good one. Good one because I have schedule 80 outside electrical and he brought this up
I'm glad you brought it up because there could be some confusion
So some bloke is going to get I just need some schedule 80 plastic pipe
He could walk out with a fistful of schedule 80 plastic pipe. All right, but it's for electrical conduit
Right, that's that's totally yeah, it's a completely different alloy or a formula of plastic and it's not for water
Yeah, good one, yeah, yeah good one that's saved I think you just saved the entire sonic here with that
No, really because think about it some bloke goes in somewhere greek says I need to schedule 80 plastic pipe
Here's a schedule 80 plastic pipe and get what did he hand him off? What did he just buy?
Fucking electrical conduit, right? You didn't say that greek. Thank you
You saved the sonic. Yeah. Yeah, because I was looking for
To change away from the uh
Plastic that I was using. Um
Which it looks it looks fine, by the way, did you find out more about it the black one the black?
What is it poly poly what polyethylene? Yeah, I think it's polyethylene. But um
Here they have uh, well, they call it upvc which is pressurized pvc like they use around. Um,
Like spa baths, you know that kind of thing
and um, yeah
So I got a bit of that thinking that might be
what you're
Talking to me
No, it could be I don't know
The difference is the schedules is the thickness of the internal wall thickness
Yeah, that's what I was. That's what I was thinking. See if you could uh, you know, what a uh, a catalog cut is
Sheet cut sheet in industry. It's like uh, if you could find a specification
There should be markings on that pipe who makes it go to the fine fine if they have a website
If they're technical technical specs and drop that in you send it
Drop it in here or do it in the chat or somewhere so I could look at it
I I like to communicate that way I can do that with schedule 80 pipe not necessary
Other than bringing up that it is for water, right?
Yep, yeah. Yep. If you're not sure
Material data shape. Yeah
Yeah, yeah cattle, uh, yeah spec cut sheet or cut sheets they call them here
Yeah, it just basically tells you what it's made of and what it's for and what's purpose and pressure and all that other good stuff
Possible
i've been having trouble finding
pvc pipe for pressure because in australia most of it's uh,
it's
I think it's all polyethylene the plastic pipe they use and or they're still on or they're still on copper
um, but
Yeah, they're they do the only pressurized systems that i've seen that use pvc was with like with spa baths
so I got a bit of that because it's
i'm going to try and
I think I want to get a better bend i'm getting spring back
when around me, um
Around me, but i've got a couple of pointers off you today that would probably prevent me spring back anyway
Because I haven't been I haven't been cooling it as I go
As well, sorry, yeah, yeah and make yourself a fixture
You can do a rough one
You can overheat it where it deforms. It's fine
Let's say you get it really hot with the sand and an external heat gun
And you squeeze it a little too much in one section and she flattens out
Uh, if you have the general deep geometry, right? This is how I made the first jig
Uh, I wanted a real tight bend but ended up getting some deformation in the pipe. That's okay
But I had my general shape
Just right the overall geometry and span just right, but I had flat spots
When it cooled down I went and got myself some auto body filler
And I filled the flat spots till they got nice and round. I made myself a profile jig, you know, I didn't eyeball it
So it actually, you know ran like a plane over it that showed me exact what the pipe should be
And I have now I have this model
Uh
That is got auto body filler all over the place, but it's exactly the shape that I want
So when I made my jig, I built my jig around that now, right?
But I use that as a model still
Uh, I could take a picture of it and you'll you'll see just a piece of pipe. It's a scalerator
And it's got auto body filler patches all over it. It's nice and smooth though, right?
And that's my model for my jig
And for my jig model, you know, uh the base of it I basically used um
Hydrocal or we call it rock durham's rock putty here plaster
You just you just pour your plaster
It looks like a mold you push the scalerator make sure you you know
Your model and you cut away so it doesn't get locked into the plaster you pull it out
And you have a negative shape right and plaster
So when you go to bend your pipe, you're bending and fitting it over this plaster mold that is made from your model, right?
That was my first jig and it works. Well, I still use it. It's just ultra modified
Oh, yeah
Yeah, i'll drop i'll drop a couple of pictures of it since i'm talking about it. I don't have the latest
these are pictures from uh
May or june this is like, you know, because I got on this when I started making this I got on it right away
meaning
After the first one that came a few days later came the second one
A few days later came the jig a few days later came that right?
It was I I was on it like, you know big time, you know, I wasn't
Dilly, I wasn't
90 percent of everything i've talked about tonight. I did within the first week
of discovering this
This is not 10. This is not 10 months of uh
Of development at all. It's uh, I basically went over like the first few days of development. That's how excited I was about it, right?
so
Here is a picture of the jig. I don't know if you can get much of it
uh
I'll drop it in right now. This is from may
and uh
See if I can get another one here's another picture of the jig
also for may
This is a week after the first one, right? So this is not recent. It doesn't look like this at all now
You could it's thrown together but you could see
On the second one, especially let me know if you wish when you see them. There's two pictures. I just dropped it
Yep, I can see them on the second one. You see how it's elevated so I get me clamps to go underneath it
Yep. Yeah, right. So if you have it flat on a table, they go we got to get a clamp under it
Right, so you see how it's elevated on three dowels. You only see one dowel in the foreground
And the two wood plates are cut the same you see yeah, that makes sense to you, doesn't it? Yeah, it's elevated
So you can get it
Three axes xyz
Yeah, it does make sense because I started off similar to your book spent my first one around a magnet and then I made a
A jig flat on the table and had that exact trouble with you know, yeah
Now i'm on to about jig number three. Yeah
well, I never I never did it on the table because I what I did was I sat down I had uh,
uh, I just lay down in the afternoon and I said, uh
I'm gonna go build a jig and when I build the jig i'm gonna make my first piece, uh on it and
Before I build it i'm going to imagine the entire thing
and as i'm laying down taking a nap i'm imagining with the jig i'm like
It can't be flat on the table because this clamp has to go under it. So I have to build it like this, right?
you know how like tesla used to design things in his mind and
Check up on them a month later check them for where he hasn't built it yet, right?
Yeah, so in other words it's called thinking it through
As much as possible. Yeah. Yeah, so you could see your workbench
Yeah, you can actually i've got a workbench with lots of overhang so I can get any clamps in there
But it just wasn't quite enough because I had no 360
That's right. You can only get it on one. You can only get about 180 degrees
You can't get the back the other 180 degrees of it
And if you notice on this early jig on the second one, you'll see there's some little black pieces of plastic with tape on them
Other pieces of pipes will meet the flat clamp doesn't flatten out the pipe, right?
Yeah, yeah
And this one obviously is just uh for photograph because this is not an actual bending
Uh, how can you tell if you look at the end of the pipe? It's open. There's no plug in it, right?
It means that's a cold piece. Yeah, I just threw that together for posterity because as I kept developing the jig I said before I
Because in between making the next jig I will just build on this one
So while i'm building on it, I don't have a jig while i'm working on the jig, right?
So I said why don't I just throw it together and take a picture of it?
Right. So at least it's preserved
And so I just went and grabbed a pipe that I had bent
Early on and threw it all back together with the clamps just for the photograph
But this is not live because there's no plug and there's no sand in it. You see
That's your first sherlock holmes giveaway, right?
That this is just this is a staged, uh, a stage. This is staged. This is not actual
Actually when you're actually doing it
It shows everything. Yeah
But it would help if I had the plugs in there because it makes it more realistic because when
When she's hot and you're bending that sounds good when she's hot and bending
Uh, your your adrenaline is rushing right because you don't want to waste the piece, right?
You don't want to reach for a camera
You haven't got a time to you haven't got time to take happy snaps
Yeah, that's right. And if you're not focusing 150 percent on what you're doing, it's not enough, right?
Yeah, you're not focusing enough
Yeah
See like this one here if you look at the first one
If you zoom in real close on the foreground on the right side of the jig
You'll notice there's fiberglass on there, which is high temperature welding blanket, right?
I have well if you zoom in on it on the top picture of the jig
Uh, the the welding has alu alu foil, uh, sticky alu foil
alu tape and fiberglass welding blanket
Because of the heat so because if you just had the wood
And you go there with a 1200 degree fahrenheit heat gun. What do you think your wood's going to do?
It's going to start smoking
right
So I coated the jig with welding blank fiberglass, you know, it's good for 2000 degrees
So I wouldn't get smoking on you notice the plastic fitting which is an industrial plastic fitting in the middle
It's got paper and alu around aluminum around it
Why because if I have to approach it with a heavy duty heat gun what happens to bare plastic, right?
It starts smoking and melting
So the first jig and the second photo it's the same jig
First and second one you'll notice that if you look close at the jig there's precautions taken for heating
To see aluminum aluminum
right and fiberglass
and again that was done before I I
So in other words greek, did you uh, throw a jig together and it started smoking?
No, it never did because I thought of it before I even did it, you see
Because I knew that what what am I doing? I'm making a jig and there's a heat gun involved shit
Well, it better be able to handle a thousand degrees
What do I have to make a piece of particle board that I threw together handle a thousand degrees?
Well, i've got an old welding blanket I could cut up and i've got some heavy duty duct aluminum tape
I could put on there with cardboard, right? There's a shield
Do that before I even started so anyway, that's rudimentary i'll go through
What I need to do
As this progresses and it seems like it will is just go ahead and investigate some other things i'll drop in here
photos of um
Of helps, you know things that I have that will help
Here here's one, um, I don't know if i've ever forwarded something like this
I have access someone who has a
3d computer
real professional
And we have covers and stuff like that 3d printed. I've never got into that. I don't know if you see that image yet
I have um
You see that image, uh, I have someone that works on those
pretty high-end computer program
That has transferred everything into a computer and uh, it's 3d printed a whole bunch of stuff
And I think you guys remember what I think about 3d printing, right? I was pretty clear about it
If you want to piss me off
Tell me you're gonna 3d print, right?
There's someone else that has one
That has a case on it with um
I'll drop in some random photos, uh with copper built around it and that's going to get filled with
They're about a thousand dollars worth of barium titnite and silver powder
It looks like a hummingbird house bird house, but you could see it right it's in their office right there
Did you get that one?
Yes
Yeah, I hope that helps and here's
A
Here's another one of the same person who is building one. They're going to a technical
Show in colorado, which was canceled
Here you'll see the scalerator again. This is in process of building it
You can see there's one on the left
They 3d printed the housing and they have the wood ends that go on it gets filled with the barium titnate and silver powder
Silver powder a bag of silver powder is just like it sounds it's expensive, you know
It does make a difference
Yeah, and i'll get more into the history and more of my experiences and i've got photos of
Labs with it and all this other stuff, you know, like here's um
Send you another
Another this is another company that was doing something else the same guys. Y'all send me another picture
Yeah, so this has already been fully computer modeled
Right
All the physics the mechanics have been done on it
various covers various 3d cover for programs have been created and
printed
There's there's more history than i've led on to there's a lot more that's gone
On to with this right, uh that i'll get into as if necessary, right?
No reason to do a 14 hour sonic on
on this
Did you guys get those last technical ones released? Yeah
Yes
Yeah, okay, so in other words there's more history behind this but yeah, go ahead
Where are they going to install?
In a house for this. Yeah, i've got photos of them installed in the field
Yeah, none of them have been done properly though, but they are installed and they are working
In other words none of them have been installed to my standards properly is not freaking amazing
Think about that. Yeah, there's there's six of them out in the wild right now. Not one is installed properly
But
Uh, two of them in new jersey one in canada one in ohio
The other one is I think another one in new jersey
None are installed properly, but the feedback is very positive
So they're at 30 or 40 percent potential
And they're still amazing
Right, I mean not installed to the alignments that you mentioned previously. That's right
I could I could show you a photo right now
And um, i'll drop a photo in in the first one
and
You guys are pretty sharp
Right. Uh, I know you're sharp
From and you do recall what I recently said
about the installation
So i'm going to scroll through another
file here
I'm going to send you a picture of one that's installed
This is an installation in somewhere in the country
I don't know if it's connecticut or new jersey, but i'll drop this is number one that went out
It wasn't supposed to be installed. It was supposed to be tested only but they installed it
Now this is in a utility room. I just told you if you get that image
Can you tell me where the 50 feet of runner length is on that one
There is none there is no runner length on that one
Uh, the the feedback on that was well the other side of the house has is about 50 feet away
Oh my gosh
It doesn't count
The other side of the house is 50 feet
uh
Yeah, okay
That's not per instructions. Well, at least it got a couple of bends in the pipe
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, but it still works kick-ass so
And I said no it's not working kick-ass. Here's another one. This is one in canada
Uh, I don't want you to show me where the 50 feet is on this one also, where's the 50 feet on this one
This one's working kick-ass also back and forth
Sometimes it works. Sometimes it doesn't because the well has got water. Sometimes it comes up
There's a lake that infiltrates the well and the well gets like really dark tea color water sometimes
But do you see the second picture I put in with the tank in the background, yeah
Yeah, where's the 50 feet on the runner length before it gets to the house on that
It's already in the house and the part of the instructions is it shouldn't even be in the house
It should be outside
Of the house and you can test this
If you uh, I don't know i'll drop in a picture of an umbilical. Are you guys do you guys know what I mean by an umbilical?
Uh, you know what a water main is, uh, have you heard of someone like they have a water main break in their house, right?
And they shut off they shut off the water and guess what the children can't brush their teeth
They can't flush the toilets. There's no water going in the house, but what is what you do
You go to what usually the water main breaks before the main shut off to the house
So you go to the main shut off to the house and you shut it off
And you go to the street and you shut off the water main to stop the leak. There's no reason to
Pay for water like you're filling swimming pools just going into the ground now. The house doesn't have any water
You go next door to the house next door
You go to the next door's hose bib and you attach a hose
And you bring that hose bib to the house that the water is shut off to and you attach it to their hose bib
And you turn on that water valve both water now
One house's hose bib
Energizes the other house with the shut off water through its hose bib and you all have water happily ever after until well until the
Water main is repaired. You see you see how the umbilical works
It's almost like two cars when someone's battery dies you get a boost right from another car. It's almost the same principle
I call it an umbilical line
Do you follow how that works?
Now here let's say
You got someone with a healthy amount of skepticism
And they're like, well, I don't know if I want to install this right now and they're like, well, why don't we give it a try?
Why don't we give it a try?
So you go to their house and you shut off the water main
Right at the street or wherever and you go to their neighbor and you knock say hey look
I'll give you 20 bucks
If you let me borrow an hour's worth of your water or like if they're really friendly
Or if your mom lives next door, right i'll give you a real head case their mom lives next door
She's not going to say no
So I go next door
And I hook up a hose with a short length of six foot length of hose to the scalerator and then the 50 foot
Goes to the house that I just shut the water off and we turn the water on and now they're getting
The entire house energized with scalerator water from the house next door
I can show you a picture of an umbilical set up like that
But then we're going to populate the entire if anybody comes to this
I might delete these just to clean up the
Uh the chat here or not
Up to you guys
Grab the pictures if you want
But do you see what I mean by the umbilical?
That that is very helpful
If you want to just someone to try it or if you just want to if you don't want to cut into your own water main
And you're friendly with a neighbor it's good to be friendly with the neighbor adjacent to you
If you're friendly with the not friendly with the neighbors adjacent, but you're friendly with the neighbors down the block
You're going to need a long hose, right?
so
If you are friendly with a neighbor or an adjacent property and you before you cut into your water main do the umbilical and it's the same
thing
Now, let me tell you what happens. Uh, go ahead any more any questions on the fab on the fabrication
greek, I had a question the
Inner magnet, I thought I heard you say that it was two and a half inches
But when I look at the inner hole diameter on the other one, it's three. It's three and one eighth outer
Yeah, two and a half inches is the inner hole of the uh of the large magnet and three
The law okay. The large magnet is five and a quarter
outer
The inner magnet is three and an eighth outer
The inner of the larger magnet is two and a half and the inner of the smaller magnet is one and three eighths
Still there
Yeah, I was expecting the
Smaller magnet diameter to match the hole diameter of the larger magnet. No, you don't uh, no, no, no, no avoid that
Because what will happen it'll fall right. It'll fall right into it, right and then you'll have a big problem
They actually as a matter of fact, you know fields reverse when you do that, right
You know what a rail gun is you ever heard of a rail gun instead of using gunpowder?
You use magnets pulse magnetic fields to propel an object
Okay, yeah
Yeah, you just go out and buy yourself about 30 or 40 of the big magnets
And then you get a magnet that's about the size of the inner hole and just let it go and watch what happens
If you know how to do it
The inner magnet will shoot out at about twice the speed of sound and go right through your neighbor's window and house
Yeah, you may just make a rail gun if you do that
We're not in the rail gun business yet. So hold on
Okay
Yeah
No, you want your magnets to stack with overlap
Lucky I didn't know that one. I was just saying
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, so
Yeah, you want your magnets to stack and overlap
Okay, that must know what I missed. Yeah, I missed that they were. Oh, yeah, you missed
Yeah, you want to stack them and you want room for stacking
Now how much room for stacking if even if it just stacked for a 16th of an inch
As long as it doesn't fall through it's fine
As long as she doesn't fall through it's fine
But I like to have I like to have an overlap for structural reasons
Also, the more magnets you use what would be optimum for a device would be a spherical magnet imagine stacking
Enough magnets that you make a cone
So it looks like two cones
That would be optimum, but you would also increase the diameter
Right or you know, you make a very abrupt it's a hyperbolic cone
So as they as you so the next magnet you stack much would be much smaller in proportion
Because I have kept stacking extra magnets and it doesn't make that much of a difference
but I believe that if you
Do them hyperbolically?
Where they almost come to a point like a pyramid a cone a very sharp cone, but hyperbolic
It will improve it again because it's not about the magnets. It's about what?
Kind of a block wall quality are you creating right?
And the more you focus the centrifugal part of the magnet
Away from the block wall the better the block wall works
This is still all theoretical remember
I'm, the only i've got I get no i'm the only one that's been doing this for 10 months now
This is a new thing. So one of the things
One of the purposes of me reaching out to others is to increase the study, right?
And also i'm never gonna I don't want the rights or patent someone so whatever yes, I am the daddy or whatever so what um
And the more people that do it and put it out in public
I'm, not afraid of anybody copying it by just looking at it
or
Getting a patent or claiming it or whatever because
Even at this point it's almost too late for someone to quote unquote steal the idea and go unchallenged
Because it's already been put out into the public domain as such you know what I mean
But what's beautiful about it is if you really know how to work the business and you could go that route
And keep everything proprietary and hidden just like those technical drawings that I show covers and stuff built on it
Uh, and you know be you know, the standard, you know, greedy fucker, you know
If you have a patent and you want to get wealthy off of it, you're not necessarily a greedy fucker
But you know you can take that typical route, you know, it's my idea my patent you can't use it
You know, you can go that route with this by the way
I don't think it should go that way because this is something that is so unintuitive to most people
Because you mentioned that there's a magnet there
Of course, you got you use you're not using the right part of the magnet if you're everybody knows, right?
Greek
Yeah
um
Did you ever try, uh the same test when you're putting the hot sand and the magnet tech together
on uh that other kind of uh, white pvc
And see if it had the same problem or the same. Yeah results. Uh, no, no, I didn't know white pvc to me is junk
Yeah, I would never you know, I I get that. I'm just curious if it would have improved it or something
But it is on the house. No, I wouldn't improve it enough. No, it's just junk
It's junk plastic and it's the wall thickness is too thin
No, just curious from for me for me to do in other words
I can't sign my name on it, even though the first one that I did is like that because that's what I had
When I first got the idea because of the discovery
I I have plenty of pvc pipe laying around. I got plenty of magnets laying around
So I got up one morning and said let's put this together
Right, let's put this together before lunch and get it installed because I was already doing an underpinning
On the foundation wall there
Anyway, the timing worked out fine. It was already trenched that area was dug out already as you can see
It looks like a new concrete step built there. So that goes on another foot and a half
Yeah, it goes a foot and a half down and a foot and a half under the house. There's a huge amount of cement there
right
So I was already open and fit for and said hey i'm ready to put all the dirt back. Hey
make yourself another pot of coffee get some other pack of cigarettes make yourself a
You know, I didn't know what to call it back then
Scalarator stick it in there cut the pipe put it in there real quick
Still there, but then I was like, this is junk
Pvc is junk
Anybody that works with this stuff knows that it is, you know, if you were gonna it's okay for outdoor use
It's not allowed to use that white stuff indoors
Uh, it's too fragile
Uh, but you you get a pallet of this stuff or a bundle of this delivered and they they drop it off the pickup truck
The bottom two pieces will crack
Like just handling it
Yeah, i'm i'm against uh, i'm against using it
for for something up an object like
Right. It's like the 3d printed stuff to me. It's junk
Anything printed is junk if it's worth anything. You're not going to 3d print it
so
You know, I I really like to I like to show respect to other people
You're dropping five grand on a scalerator that I make i'm not going to insult you by sending you schedule 40 plastic. Oh, yeah
Right
Yeah
so, uh, if anything else I want to get just relay what a typical scalerator install does for
For someone what what you should expect
If someone finds out about you have something like this
and uh
They're they're not broke. You know, they make a pretty good living. They have a you know, almost half a million three
quarter million dollar house
And they're like, oh I hate the water my hair my skin's dry
Water doesn't taste good even through a filter. My dad says I should get a water salt water softener
Barro, and i'm like no I heard about what you got
It's kind of expensive but what tell me about it scientifically
Can you tell me about it scientifically especially because this is a person who works in the science background?
And I said well, yeah, there's no such thing as this there's no such thing as that they're in agreement with me and to a degree
And they're kind of healthy healthy dose of skepticism
And they're like, yeah, okay, let's let's do it. Let's do it and i'm like, okay go so we got a plumber
It's a place with an hoa and one of these home associations. I get a licensed plumber
Uh to so the installation is adjudicated. So some of these nosy bastards come around. Oh, what are you doing?
That's a licensed plumber. Oh, it's fine if he's licensed
So while the installation is going on they're like I tell the person go inside before we cut the main
And let the water run so you don't get water sitting in the pipes and get fresh water that you normally get
Fill up a jug with it and I want you to taste it. This is before we put this in, you know
Your your control water. This is the water before
And the plumber start, you know, we do that plumber starts cutting away whatever and i'm, you know, okay
So how's the water? How's the tap water? Oh, it tastes like shit. It's crappy tap tap, you know, tucson tap water as usual
Okay
And while the scalerator is going it doesn't take about half an hour 45 minutes to get it in there
um
They're like, oh, you know, I I want to also when when this gets connected and ready
I want to also i'm getting a sample ready to take to a lab so they could tell me the difference, right?
And i'm like, are you sure? Okay. All right, you go ahead get your lab sample whatever ready, you know
Measure it and all that. That's fine
So anyway, we get the scalerator in
Turn the water on because there's some copper solder and all get the flux out of the water let it run for a few minutes
Get all the pipes, you know run all the fixtures in the house. Get it on water clean water in there
By the way, go get a water sample inside. Let it run get a water sample gets the water comes out
Oh my gosh, did you still want to take it to the lab? Not necessary
It's not necessary at all. The difference is huge
Like you sure you don't want to have it tested not necessary
Right
So here you have someone who's scientific works in the professional field
Is very skeptical
Is still skeptical and wants to have the post scalerator water tested so they can quantify
Scalerator goes in
And immediately they're like the lab testing is not necessary. The difference is so big
It even tastes better than the best bottled water. We have coming straight out of the tap
And then I keep getting consecutive messages
Day after day after day after day after day. I can't believe how easy it is to clean. Everything is sparkling
No water stain. My hair is smooth. My skin is not dry anymore
The water coming through the berkey filter is delicious where it tasted like crap before every day every other day messages
The water is amazing. I just came back from a trip. I missed the water in my house
The water is amazing and a few days later another message the water is incredible. Thank you
This is from someone who had a healthy amount of skepticism
Who wanted to take it to a lab to see what it really does and they're like absolutely not necessary
Imagine that this is how big the difference is
when you with
municipal water municipal tap water
Which is predominates. I think it's 85 percent of most urban and suburban populations use, you know
City water what they or state water, right? Not a well water
So this is a repeated reaction that I get
And this is what you would expect also
So with that said if there's any other questions we'll finish up and stop the recording, uh, I agree
Yep
Yeah, I just had a question about uh, the two install examples you showed in the last two pictures. Um
If you added 50 foot of runner length to the supply side of that, uh,
Yep, magnetic reactor. Would that be appropriate for that install?
Absolutely, but and and not in the building
if you
You know do not put it in the building and
The way you discover this is if you do an umbilical setup where you got the scalerator hooked up
Between two houses where one of the water mains are shut off
you remember you got a
50 foot of hose on one end and a shorter end on the other
You got that scalerator in your hand. You can walk around with it, right?
Just like you walk around with a garden hose, right?
And what you do is tell someone open the window open window here on the short end here
I'm gonna hand you a scaler put it on the floor. It's not leaking right now. It's not leaking
Okay, put it on the floor close the window
Go taste the water
On the on the house what happened?
Water tastes fizzy went flat
Okay, come back. All right still running. Yeah still running. Okay, open the window hand me the scalerator put it outside
How's the water now, oh my gosh, it just changed again it's light and sweet
Amazing, you know, you got an answer for me on that
I don't
All I could tell you is I know
Don't put it inside
It's the frost line, uh in the northern part of illinois is a little tough for that. Uh, because yeah down
Yeah, you got a backhoe. It's a backhoe job. Yeah. Sorry. Yeah
Yep, well another way to do it another way to look let's be smart about it. We're engineers right now, okay
Let's be smart about it. So you got your utility room your laundry room your basement
Where you could you see your water main coming into the house, right?
All right, uh, you just pick a spot. It doesn't matter where it is. Forget about your running line
Forget about all that right now. Where do you want to cut in?
What's the most convenient spot to cut into your water water main?
I think that spot was just past the supply into the house basically. Okay, great. Great right there put your fitting there
now, uh
You make a penetration you make that fitting and you have that fitting return and it aims outside goes outside. Yeah
Penetrate through your foundation wall basement wall window
Go outside
Dig down a little bit put it in a frost box styrofoam cube
Whatever near the house against the house
right
insulated, uh, you know if you if you have
Uh against the house and one side is is the interior wall. It'll never freeze right if it's closed all around it, right?
Yeah. Yeah, and it's outside the building now not under roof but against the building is fine
Okay, right and and you'll be fine and then you penetrate you come, you know
As you went out the penetration comes back in insulate that pipe
Uh, look this thing has been in existence for 10 months. I mean, I don't know what to say
All I could tell you is I know it works
I know it works. I know what works. I know it doesn't I know if you want to get one going
This is how you should do it
right
Yeah, I agree
The pictures that I showed that are inside that are none of them correct to show you more. They're none of them are correct
Uh or correct enough you still there's still one of them is there's another one that
Water softener was replaced. The guy says I hate this water softener stuff slimy water. It sucks can't drink it
You know, it destroys ro and you can't filter it. Gotta get everybody hates it
They have one indoors in the utility room and it works. They don't need the are the waters
They got rid of the water softener and they're not getting any hard water problems
But it's not optimum by by 50
I don't know 70. It's only 70. You know
I haven't been able to quantify that again. I'm the only one that's you know going into the testing side
The experimental side right now still, you know
The only even though there's some other I showed you the guys with the 3d model computers and the building expensive cases
You know, it's like they're they're not advancing this
So adding the runner length one, uh one change if it was inside the house basically no it's not much
as far as I could tell if you want to do a
If you substitute a runner length do yourself like a rube goldberg get yourself a a bag of fittings 90 degree fittings
Right and start making a maze, you know, you know, it looks like a maze, right?
Yeah, well, that's what I was 90 degree spirals going around every time it sees a 90. It's equivalent to five feet, you know
Okay
Not a sweep a 90. There's a difference between a 90 and a sweep, right?
Yeah
So it looks like you could do that with the shark bites, uh
In that picture pretty easy. Yeah. Yeah could make yourself a rube goldberg maze, you know, maybe at least four or six
I think an odd number would be better
Will you use a t if you use an odd number you should use a couple of t's in there, right?
Just so the water gets jumbled up
Yeah, this is an experiment I can't assure it but keep it outside
In the frost line areas. Yeah, you I would do penetration out and a return back in with the device outside
Okay, it's not hard. I mean
If you're going through a basement most basements have penetrations for uh laundry room dryers vents windows, right?
Yeah. Yeah, not hard to do. It might you just have to make it look pretty
If you you know, I think going through even a bluestone foundation wall is less work than backhoe
Right six feet. What's your frost line six feet there five feet?
42 inches
Uh, don't be a girl
You could do 40 and wait till springtime or you could do four junior
Don't be a girl 42 inches isn't that bad? There's play in canada. I think it's uh, seven feet six and a half feet
You know two and a half two meters
Okay
Don't be a girl 42 inches we could dig that out
We could dig that out over a pastrami sandwich
Uh for sure. I don't know if the wife would appreciate that right away. Yeah. Well get one for her too then
Yeah, but so anyway, that's the skinny so far remember this is all new
and uh
You know the more as time goes on
Right. Um now there's more to it. I turned off the recording
But what hit me yesterday I did a sonic with ocelli and um
Every moon every month. I get a new revelation about this an install likely the copper came
A month after and then the other thing came a month after right and all these other the runner length
Well every month I get a new thing what this is if you look up faraday. I mentioned earlier. I was looking up faraday
that was the precursor to the transformer which is
If you have a given amount of conductive wire around a steel bar
And you loop it around that steel bar and continue the circuit backwards
You create a whole other circuit on the other end another loop of a different length
Of wire on the steel bar you energize one circuit
It sends energy to the other circuit via and it changes the voltage depending on my new windings, right?
That's your basic transformer idea, right?
Step up step down
Well, guess what we're doing the same thing, but with water. This is a hydraulic transformer or a hydro transformer
Real interesting and i've been looking up for different latin terms
Uh to name things sometimes like the company I wanted to do was called aqua borealis
Meaning I borealis meaning north northern water because the northern waters are tend to be famous
So
What I uh looked up
real strange the word
Energy in english guess what that word is in latin
It's not energy or something
The word for energy in latin is industria
That's kind of cool. I think I didn't I wouldn't have ever imagined that energy in latin is industria
So we get industrial from right? Well, so industrial comes from the word meaning energy
But anyway, i've been doing some research on how a transformer a basic transformer works with primary and secondary windings
Right now we just have a primary winding
And that's all i'm going to say so the under and over is not a ridiculous idea no
No, it's not no
But we have a it's still a primary winding two primary windings. We don't have a secondary winding yet
I don't know what's going to happen with that. But the turbinator
Is the next level to this right now and the secondary winding
On the hydro transformer is in between the two. So now it opens in a whole other field of experimentation
This we're we're in the same boat as faraday was somebody with an eighth grade education like me
Uh, basically, I I don't know what he did. I think he was a hat maker or something or doing something like that
And he took interest in electricity
By reading some papers that ben franklin and some other people wrote. It was very primitive at the time
And he came up with rules and sets of rules and laws, you know observed observations that are still held today
Right, you hear faraday cage faraday ring right faraday is still very
relevant
Right and we're talking about someone with an eighth grade education
nothing, but uh glass pieces of wood pieces of iron and some copper bare copper wire
Is still the foundation of electricity today?
And this is we're embarking exactly on the same thing
Parallel but with water and it's never none of this has ever been done before as far as I could see on the surface
And um, yeah, it's exciting it's fucking exciting. I I mean I call it my magnum opus which means the good my great work
This is the greatest thing i've ever done
You know that could be you know scaled up so anyone can enjoy
I feel good about it. You know, it's my magnum opus
And like faraday
They asked him you could turn this into a business you can do, you know, make yourself wealthy. He wasn't into it
You know
I'm sharing it with everyone. All he did was write essays after essay after essay
And distributed them and other people of interest
You've heard of james clark maxwell and other people after that came along discovered his stuff
And many many others hem holtz
So, let's see who else discovers, you know, this is what we're doing here or i'm start I started
And take so where it goes, but i'm every moon I get a new
revelation
point of view
application
so far
It's exciting
What came the other day with the new moon?
Full moon was that it is a transformer
Just like a transformer
Using the block wall with uh, hydro hydraulic when we say hydraulic, you know, people think of hydraulic machines, but it is hydraulics
It's a hydraulic transformer
You could coin an entire new field of study on this. It's wide open
When I say every field is still wide open. It is also and this is completely
This is every field in science is still wide open because they fed us so much bullshit. They they now they're believing their own bullshit
That's why they're not doing anything anymore
This is wide open and it's virgin territory
It hasn't been trodden on yet
So it's open for the exploratory mind, right pretty exciting like I said, it's my magnum opus
The greatest thing i've ever done
Do you think the uh reason for putting it outside has also to do with the earth energies intermixing with this
Absolutely. Yep, there's something that happens even with the michelson-morley experiments when they were looking for ether wind they
Didn't measure much when they had it inside of a brick building
that had you know steel reinforcement and
Metal fixtures and doorknobs and things but when they went up to a wooden shack near a mountaintop
Oh boy, did they measure the ether wind like crazy?
right
Right, right
Yeah, but that that part of that redo of the experiment's hidden you could look for it maybe you could find it
Yeah, they make it comes from the southwest
Bending the mirror the light going through the mirrors changing the refraction and everything like man
Going when they went back down to a regular lab. It didn't show anything because the building is filtering out. Absolutely. This is an ether-based device
Because nothing goes to the block wall at all. You can't
You can't put only another block wall will go to the block wall when you flip it when you flip a magnet only an
Iron will not go to the block wall. Go ahead get a magnet find the block wall. Go put a piece of
Iron or steel or something will not go there
It doesn't exist
Right, but if you take another magnets block wall, it will go to that block wall
very interesting
There's a lot going on here, I mean we can do a four-hour call every day
Discussing the possibilities and things that I keep discovering. It's not necessary
because the purpose of me reaching out with these
with the
inertial domain
Skype group is to get other to see who else is is
Capable and ready to to knock these things together
Because that's the only way we're going to find out more about it and do something if I get hit by a train
It dies and dies on the vine. That's crazy, you know
You gotta have other other people building it
Making it and talking about it
so
If you want to be successful with this you have to be a good communicator
You have to be good working with your hands. You have to be creative
You have to be meticulous when you make things. It doesn't look like junk
You have to be a good perceiver
Right perceive perceive the finest details
right, you need if you lack any of those you're not going to succeed with this if you want to pursue it as more of a
More than just a hobby you have to have all those things in place
So and those kind of people are hard to find
But I don't think that they're impossible to find. I think they're they're hard to find
But it doesn't mean you don't stop trying right?
Oh, no, did I mention you shouldn't be broke either if you're broke you won't be able to do it
So you need
community a small community that's uh has all those qualities
Because if you can't communicate and how are you going to communicate, you know?
How are you going to tell someone else what fine points you've discovered, you know all these things
And it has to be built. Well, because if you if you build it each one is so different than the other
We don't have consistency
It's okay to make mistakes
also
So because this entire thing about using the block wall wasn't the discovery by mistake
so
Anything else? We've stopped the recording by the way, so
Well, i've got
I've got one little question for you. Greg. Yeah when you were talking earlier about um
Your hot pvc glue you got five minutes and then it's set and you can't get it apart
Um, no, no, no, no, no five seconds
Oh five seconds. Yeah, it's called red hot red hot blue. Yeah. Yeah, I don't I don't like using that. Yeah
No, I don't like using I think it's mutagenic as well, but I was going to say you can actually get it apart
If you get your zippo out and set fire to it
Oh my gosh
Yeah, then you can get your fittings apart if you ever get stuck
When you've got one of the you know, a good good fitting in a slab
Yeah
No, I got you. Yeah. Yeah with the unions though. It's not so bad
I use the medium gray or I use a plastic epoxy
aircraft quality epoxy made by permatex
um
Yeah, but when you're fitting
When you when you you base it on unions, I also use a lot of flex connects now
right, so, you know, I can have you know, uh
When I like to use a flex connection on one end
So you're not stuck in this rigid piece. Yeah
Uh, there's many ways, uh, the flex connectors
Make a very easy install the unions make a very easy install, especially when you show up with two sets
So whatever you cut out
Of the main section you fit your unions to that also so if you want to ever remove the scalerator
You have the original piece you could drop it
Exactly back in and it's as if right
Yeah, yeah i've had to sort of retool and that because i'm set up for copper work. I do a lot of
Heritage rain eyes and everything. Oh
Everything is old is copper. So i've got a lot of old
Tools for working with copper, but i'm not I don't have the
I don't have the library in my head of uh of poly fittings, but i'm getting there
Yeah, there's a transition fittings from copper to plastic, you know, as long as you get a thread on one end, you're good, right?
The copper you want to finish?
Yeah, you got to get a thread on either end the copper as if you're cutting into copper
You're going to have to get a thread on it or a shark bite
They have a lot of new fittings now with o-rings and you know jaws that grab things and whatever
And there are also transition fittings that go from plastic to copper
Yeah, a good plumbing supply. I mean you're you're on you're in tasmania, right? I don't know how
Yeah, it seems like it seems like you've got a lot but I don't know enough but maybe you don't have a lot. I don't know
Yeah
It's it's yeah, you can get most things but sometimes
It might take a little while to get them
They don't have a lot of stock
In tasmania, but the plumbing supplies for stores if you if you know what you want with just a couple of days
Yeah, but if you keep it up you'll you'll make enough to move to sydney or melbourne and get a big company with 30 employees
And you'll be supplying scalerators for that entire half of the world
Right. It doesn't sound bad. Right? That's all possible if you want to do that
Well, i'd prefer to subby that out, but you know, yeah, you know what? I mean anyone anyone who's real industrial in a year or two years
It could be should be doing very very very well with this if they understand marketing especially
South australia and western australia have real hard water problems, you know, oh, yeah
Yeah
Be kick-ass. Yeah, you just need to find you couldn't you can't do it alone
You have to find someone to partner with that can handle the admin work
uh and some backing a little financial backing and the backing
Is for a little bit of marketing and you have it grow the business grow naturally you don't get an investor
That starts you off big you start making, you know, one a day and then two a day and then five a day
and then ten a day
And when you get to making um 100 a month then you have enough money to uh
Expand the operation, right?
But because right now I could make one a day which right
Comfortably and it doesn't cut into my schedule at all. You know, like I said I can
Make myself a pot of coffee and three three or four cigarettes have a scalerator ready to go in case right a few hours
Yeah
Yeah, and if I get if I sell one a day at five grand a pop
Right, that's 150k a month or a hundred thousand a month
And you know what the profit margin or the earnings margin is because you know how much the magnets cost
And how much a three-foot piece of pipe costs, right?
And right and because they're not buying them. They're buying the idea
And the application they can replace a five thousand dollar water system with it
That needs maintenance and this doesn't right
You can build up enough capital in a year I could I could sock a million aside
right
Almost like not even feeling like I have a job
part-time
Yeah, this is the reality of it
Oh, yeah, yeah and the
Applications are huge. Like I said in south australia. They they have
they have terrible water and um
Yeah, and that's and they also have quite a lot of breweries as well, you know, it's like oh, yeah the water quality
Yeah, the of the brewery. I mean, it's all well the bakeries
I know for sure breweries and bakeries rely heavily on what their water quality
In other words, the outcome of their product is only as good as the quality of the water they use
Bakeries and breweries they both use yeast also, right?
Yeah, yeah, exactly. But like I said like water quality is not
Something that's given consideration but
Yeah, they have no choice they have shit technology from shit science
It's shit all around really
And the thing is every time you do one of these and you want some healthy skepticism
Someone doesn't know you they find out about it. They want to give it a try. They're going to be very skeptical
And you accommodate that skepticism because you know the moment it gets installed immediately
The water flowing through it is superior and you should see the looks on their faces
Like you sure I thought you wanted to have it lab tested. Oh, that won't be necessary
That's how drastic the water quality changes and anybody that's done this knows right? I think there's some
You run if you haven't run shit tap water through I think you're using rainwater and I think in illinois
The install that was done there may not have been optimum
But i've noticed I think they've noticed a difference in the water quality. I haven't gotten feedback on that
Some feedback from you vandy
But it's not just about dropping the hard water. It's about the actual
Water quality everyone can taste what and the more athletic you are the more fit you are the more you notice the water quality
too, by the way, the way water tastes and feels
All right, if there's nothing else i'm just gonna hop off
Uh, thanks very much. Great
Yeah, you're welcome. Yeah, this was uh what I call a sonic email response
Again, just based on
Someone who's very serious about it an enterprising individual, uh sent me those questions earlier that I started with
And i'd rather uh, instead of typing it out do one of these so everyone else has a fair shot fair shot at the information
and more
Okay, everyone we'll build those scalerators then right and let's stay communicating and we'll do another one soon
Thanks, great, you're welcome. Take care everyone
Thank you