Her hair and skin the same day started improving.
Now it's been less than a week and it's way better.
She's like, this is magic.
This is not a sclerator, this is magical.
Because this is Tucson, hard water.
Now, Vandy, he's been doing stuff,
he's been putting pictures and all that,
and it's rainwater tanks.
If you're still on, you could chime in.
That water is not hard water.
If you want to just tell us a little bit of
the improvements of quality or maybe not noticeable,
because your water is pretty clean other
than some algae in the tank, right?
Yes, but I have been using the sclerator
on the mains in my house,
because I don't have,
well, I've got pretty good rainwater
and like my TDS on the rainwater was about 59.
And I made a single,
a single magnet set up, you know,
with the three magnets,
like in the pictures that you posted.
And I've got a 16 millimetre feed line.
It's a high pressure poly line.
And I have, it's approximately,
I'm trying to think in feet,
it's about five metres from my mains tap.
And then I've got another
or 10 or 15 metres to my house.
And I haven't, I haven't tasted it
because I don't drink tap water,
but I've noticed that it, it makes it,
it makes the water feel very slippery.
Like,
Like it washes better?
Yes, it washes better.
But also like I do,
I do biodynamic gardening.
Ah, okay.
And you stir your water,
you vortex your water.
Yeah, yeah, like, yeah, yeah.
And you could put little droppings
from a horn that you store in a horn
and all of this, that and the other too, yeah.
Exactly.
But when you stir your water,
you'll notice that after a couple of minutes,
the texture of the water becomes silky on your skin.
Yeah?
Yeah, it's more friendly
as opposed to angry water.
Yeah, and so the water out of my tap
feels very much silky like the vortex water.
And then that's the one thing that I noticed
as well as the TDS dropped from,
before I put the, before I put the,
on the mains line,
it was coming out of my tap between like 79 and 95.
And now it comes out pretty much consistently
at about between 60 and 70.
But I did notice, I noted down how you said
it needs runner length.
Yeah, after the unit.
More after, more after.
But you're going, but look,
you don't have to consider that much before the unit
because the water is coming from somewhere,
either a container or another line
and the container will suffice.
But after the unit is important.
The more runner length after the unit,
even a kilometre would make it even more effective.
I found, I'm not taking it to that limit though, so.
Well, I noticed I've got a garden tap that is,
it's only about two feet from the scalerator.
And the water comes out of that at a higher TDS
than it does in my house, which is, you know.
How much is that?
How much reduction?
It's about 74 out of the tap
that's close to the scalerator.
And it's usually between 60 and 70 out of my kitchen sink.
Okay, yeah, so it is considerable.
Because what I've noticed with the TDS,
now there's a question here from Andrew.
I heard the Hunza have lived,
have longer, healthier lives to use glacier meltwater,
which minerals also deteriorate and depleted.
Does this affect the block wall change?
Okay, let me get some material stuff here.
Mineral infused.
Is there general health?
Yes, there are.
What this is, before we get into the material aspects.
Thank you, Vandy.
The material aspects of it or anything like that.
This is not, right now we're gonna be talking
about the inertial domain, the energetic parts.
What we've done here is discovered,
I say we, right, in the collective,
that if we go back to the first photo
and below the second photo, that's mark number two,
I show that's a typical scientific or promotional picture
of how you should impose the center part of a magnet
on a water flow.
Whether you alternate them,
it doesn't matter if it's the same North Pole, North Pole,
or alternating or South Pole, South Pole.
That convection is wrong.
It will not yield, it yields mixed results.
I've had good results with just facing a magnet to the water.
If it's constantly recirculating in a tank,
it will reduce the scale,
but it will not improve the water quality or anything.
The point that I'm making here and have been making
for almost a year now, since April of last year,
is that I'm the first one to wrap the pipe
or the fluid flow around the part of the magnet
that everyone is ignoring.
It's like, I'm the first guy
to date the ugly chick in the class, right?
Nobody wants to date her, so I ask her out for the prom.
What balls the Greek has, right?
So the best looking guy in the class
asks out the worst looking girl.
Go figure, right?
This is exactly what's going on with the scalarator.
There is nothing written about the block wall,
the domain wall, the Neal wall.
As a matter of fact, it is a stepchild
kind of part of science.
It is completely ignored.
There is this poor bastard Felix Bloch in 1946
wrote a paper about nuclear.
I could post it here.
It's a PDF.
Nuclear resonance, basically.
Here, I won't post it.
1946, nuclear induction.
F. Bloch, Felix Bloch.
So the block wall, the section of a magnet
where one field stops and the other one ends,
which is the equilibrium part of the magnet.
You wanna know more about that, by the way,
Ken Wheeler, the Fat Ugly Monkey guy,
you call it, I think he says,
so the Ugly Monkey podcast or livestream he does.
There's a video on there that he put in Ken Wheeler,
Theoria Apophysis, block wall.
He has a video and he makes fun
of how dumb humans are and all that.
And he mentions what the block wall is
according to his findings.
But there is a paper by Felix Bloch,
it's called Nuclear Induction.
You can look it up, July 19th, 1946.
Very pedantic, whatever.
Talks about, you know,
because they named that part of the magnet after him.
Now, there's also the Neil Wall,
but neither one is true because it's not a wall.
The block domain, the center part of the magnet,
you could look it up on your own,
folks, whoever wants to.
What is the block wall on a magnet?
It's not a wall because if you put two magnets together,
that shifts between the two magnets.
If you break a magnet, it shifts.
So it's not a wall in any way at all.
It's a domain that shifts.
It's a neutral point, right?
So this poor bastard, Felix Bloch,
they used his name on this thing
and they tend to ignore it completely in industry.
And the uses are immense.
Now, we're talking about just the water here.
The reason why we're talking about the water
is because it's unprecedented,
the change in water quality that it does.
And you're not using the part of the magnet
that everyone is focused on.
And if you put in magnetic water treatment
and go to images, magnetic water treatment devices,
go to images on your browser,
you will see these poor bastards,
thousands of companies, hundreds and thousands
have invested in selling these things to people
that do nothing, almost nothing.
When I say nothing, they're not consistent
and I've tried them, right?
So when we go around the Bloch wall,
the water quality changes intensely, intense changes, right?
The TDS measurements that you're measuring
are actually false.
It is a way for the, when I say false,
is there a TDS drop?
Well, the water behaves as if there are.
It is.
And right here, I could drop in photos of my shower,
which hasn't been cleaned in six months.
And you could see it's totally sparkly.
It's acting better as if I was using RO water,
no mineral distilled water, but it's not.
What's happening is the water is being charged so much
by the Bloch wall, not discriminant charging
by the North or South only,
which we can get into the North or South.
The North or South pole of a magnet
has a black hole in the middle of it.
You can see it.
And that flips the pole.
That's the counter space part.
We can get into that when we talk more about magnets.
Again, today is just to introduce the concepts here
and to give a little bit of history
of where I've been for the past six months with it
and how happy I am that we have some,
at least 40 participants here I see in the group
that would listen to this.
But yeah, so can the scalerator be attached under the sink?
I live in a condo and I can't modify the water main.
Yes, it can.
But what I would say under the sink
is put it as far away from the mixing valve,
you know, where it actually connects to the sink
with a, get yourself what would be practical
if the sink, whether it has a cabinet underneath it or not,
at least a 10 or 15 foot piece of tubing,
coiled up, not a small coil,
but a wide coil go around the cabinet several times.
Doesn't matter which direction
before it goes into the sink faucet.
Yeah, I would do a minimum of six feet
and it will work quite well.
Yeah, not as well as if it's on the main.
This is the part where the R&D,
more research and development,
remember this is only, thank you, Michael, in the text.
This has only been in existence since April of last year
and I'm the only poor sap that's talking about it.
This could be in existence for thousands of years,
but I'll tell you, it's not on the surface
as far as we know and it's not on the internet
as far as we can tell.
And this is one thing also.
I don't think anyone's gonna figure this out
unless you have direct experience and direct knowledge
of what will, in this group
or what I've been talking about,
because it's counterintuitive.
What I mean by that is if someone wants to copy this
and they go to a computer like COMSOL
and they type in what the scalarator looks like
or recreate it and they hit the button
to show me what influences the magnetic fields have
on the water, it will show nothing.
It will show, it doesn't even show a block wall.
And I have engineers say,
yeah, the computer does show a block wall.
No, it doesn't, it doesn't show anything.
What are you seeing?
Are you that hopelessly brainwashed?
It doesn't show anything,
any effect of the block wall at all.
There is no way that anyone working in an engineering firm
that wants to imitate this will be given any funding
if the supercomputer shows that such an arrangement
does absolutely nothing.
So the chances of this being copied by industry
or whatever is next to nothing to zero to nil, right?
And you won't get a patent on this either.
They'll look at you and laugh.
But they'll put you through the saw once you know,
I know someone who's gotten patents, several people.
And one thing they do allow is when you meet them,
the patent reviewer,
you can bring in and do a demonstration.
You bring in the device, if it's a water device,
bring in some water tanks,
they give you a room to set it up and all that.
You demonstrate it, right?
The moment you demonstrate it and it works,
they're gonna put you through the saw.
I don't know if you guys are familiar
about the SAW system in the patent.
Yeah, just like it sounds, S-A-W.
It stands for Special Application Withdrawal System.
They withdraw your application.
They withdraw.
When they withdraw your application,
they send you a letter.
We found that what you are applying for
is a matter of national security.
So they call it the SAW.
So how do I know that?
USC 35.
In accordance with, yeah, one of them.
And yeah, that's one of them.
Yeah, but they call it the internal.
They have an internal mechanism to flag them.
So this is a very rare opportunity for anyone here
or whatever that is ingenious,
is good with building things.
Don't say you're gonna 3D print.
If you wanna 3D print anything, just don't tell me, please.
I don't wanna know.
That's like saying you like to cook,
but you reheat frozen dinners.
That's your version of cooking.
By the way, they have said on Sonics,
most people that say, tell me they like to cook,
I watch them and they don't know how to cook.
They're reheating stuff.
They don't know.
It's a big difference again.
So, yeah, this is very, very exciting
in terms of the water quality.
Now, this is so early.
I'm the only one that's really been pressing forward
in working with this since April of last year.
So let's say nine months or so.
And I've had at the same time in paralleling experiences
with both conventional industry and the airy ferries.
You know, the airy ferries, meaning the structured water.
By the way, there's no such thing as structured water.
It's a gimmick.
You know, if anyone tells you there's such a thing
as a water molecule, even Ken Wheeler
with hydrogen up here and oxygen, prove it.
If it's so prominent and dominant, show me a picture.
Show me how that imposes itself or fractals itself
even in crystal formation.
Show me.
You know what?
It doesn't, because there is no molecular structure to water.
Water is one molecule.
All the water on the planet
represents one molecule of water.
I've been trying to give this analogy for 20 years,
even with Ocelli, when we talk about water.
I say, we have a Olympic-sized swimming pool between us.
You're on one end, which is 660,000 gallons.
Might even be Olympic-sized swimming pool
might be 666,000 gallons, those bastards, right?
But so, okay, I tell Chuck, you know,
you're on one end of the swimming pool and I'm on the other.
When you drop a glass of water or one drop of water
on your end of the swimming pool,
and I take simultaneously one drop of water out on my end
or an hour later, it doesn't matter.
Is it the same drop of water or a different drop of water?
Now, some people think they're slick and they'll say,
well, I put red dye in it and I could see the water.
No, you see the red dye.
You don't see the water when you drop it in.
Ah, gotcha.
You see?
That's the first irrational logic person say,
well, I'll put dye in the water so he could see it.
So when you drop the water in,
you see the dye, not the water.
Get it?
So I'm telling you it's the same exact drop of water.
The same water that was used to fill that pool,
wherever it came from is still the same water.
And I've backed this up many times
with people that I've talked to in neurosurgery.
Oh my gosh, what does neurosurgery have to do with it?
So there is a miracle going on here
that's been going on under our noses for thousands of years
that we tend to lean on the subject matter
as being miraculous, water.
But no one's talking about it this way at all.
I hate seeing like the presumption
there's a whole bunch of people out there.
You'll find them on YouTube.
They got, I don't know, the easy water, this water,
that water, the water molecule, fourth stage of water.
Prove it, show me.
Their rationale and their logic
falls very, very quickly, falls apart.
Even Vita Austin, who I revere as doing with the hydroglyphs,
you know, she freezes water next to photographs and thoughts
and the water frost patterns reveal,
you know, hydroglyph what the photo or the thought was.
When she starts a conversation, she says,
we all know that water came from outer space,
from meteorites and all that.
I'm like, oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
Does that mean that her rest of her work is invalid?
No.
Is she allowed to say really stupid things?
I mean, like really stupid things
and still be right about the hydroglyphs?
Of course, aren't we all, right?
So this approach on the scalarator
of running the water line or the fluid, by the way,
you know, sometimes I'll interchange water with fluid
because guess what?
Have you tried fuel in that?
By the way, when I mentioned look up
magnetic water treatment devices, when you're doing that,
there's some rascals in there
that want to sell you devices to run your fuel, right?
Your gas line with magnets also,
and they start telling you to get better MPG.
You know that bullshit, you're not
because they're doing the same exact thing
that the water people are.
And in the water people, the airy fairies,
they use cone, we use a cone magnet,
very expensive cone magnet and this, doesn't matter.
If you're facing either the North or the South or both
or in parallel or opposing, doesn't matter.
It doesn't work.
Well, what do you mean Greek, it doesn't work?
Of course it works.
The Department of Energy wrote a paper on there
that if you're an industry
and don't use magnets in water, you're an idiot.
Yeah, but it doesn't work like this
and you're still gonna get scale, right?
So what is this?
Running any fluid along that part of the magnet.
Now, unfortunately so far, not with much experimentation
but more like thought experiments,
the best way to do this is by looping,
it's called a spool by the way,
in industry.
If you wanted to go make that pipe made out of titanium,
which I like, titanium is a wonderful material
for water treatment by the way.
It's extremely paramagnetic.
It's not magnetic.
It has some properties that are very unique as a metal.
Otherwise they wouldn't say,
their stargates are made out of pure titanium.
Remember the Stargate series?
It was, again, people are taking advantage
of the ignorance for the people.
They closed the Stargate and the general was like,
no one could go through that, it's pure titanium.
Like, oh my gosh, pure titanium is soft.
You could cut it with regular steel hacksaw
or dollar store hacksaw cut plate.
That's again, taking advantage of the ignorant people.
You tell people this impervious is pure titanium,
most people think it is, right?
It has to be alloyed.
So if I go to a fab shop to make me a titanium two inch spool
a real mean ass scale or a mark two
and they want $20,000 to just bend the pipe
and weld it and polish it internally
or externally for titanium.
When you refer to that bend, it's called a spool, right?
And the magnet, we're not gonna call a magnet,
we're gonna call it a magnetic reactor.
And the reason we call it a magnetic reactor
is because I don't care at all
about the magnetism of that magnet.
Basically you care about magnetism of a magnet
when you wanna stick something to your refrigerator
or you pick up a junk car or whatever,
or use it in a relay.
By the way, not necessarily true
because this can also be used in relays
in a way that will blow your mind.
But we're not interested in the magnetism
of the magnet at all.
What the North and South Pole are doing,
we just give them their pay for the day
and tell the North and South Pole go home, leave.
We don't need you at all.
We just want the block wall.
As a matter of fact,
all of the magnetic flux line diagrams
that you see online are incorrect,
except for the ones that Ken Wheeler has drawn up
and people that have studied it with him.
Now I'll also put up some photographs
of what I've discovered with magnetic felines.
Vandy put one up the other day,
the South Pole and the North Pole.
There's a North Pole and a South Pole.
There's a variation between the North Pole
and the South Pole.
They're not identical.
One is not the opposite of the other.
They're very different.
And that needs to be explored and worked.
I have done some mild experimentation with success,
but I'm not going to go down the road
and get a knock on my door one day,
and they're going to say,
Greek, if this works, you're a dead man.
You know, I don't need another call like that.
I've had those before.
So this is something for someone else
or when we get to a point where we can hide a little better,
I can discuss more on what's going on with that.
But Vandy did post a picture in the chat
of the magnetic field.
And I will post that again.
We are not interested in water treatment.
Well, I am not.
The scelerator has nothing to do with magnetism,
but it does employ a magnetic reactor
in a way that like, for example,
in a nuclear reactor,
the nuclear reactor's purpose is to heat water,
not to put radiation into the water.
Thus, it's called a nuclear reactor.
A reactor, it means its initial purpose
is being used in a secondary form.
So you do need magnets.
You can even use an electromagnet, by the way.
But why?
Why would you be pumping electricity
into something, you know, voltage and current,
where you can, unless light,
being very lightweight is an issue,
but then you have the weight
of what's providing the electricity.
So we're using the magnets just to capture
and create that block wall.
And you could look up a block wall,
Neil Wall, ridiculous.
This is like, this is the stuff
they're putting out to the children.
By the way, when you look at science books,
physics and all that,
keep in mind that no matter how complex it looks,
the goal and the intent behind all that
is to fool ignorant children, right?
To not show what's going on,
but to satisfy their curiosity with gibberish.
I'm one of those people that whenever they show a movie
like Good Will Hunting or something,
even like Felix the Cat,
where they have all the equations on the blackboard,
I would pause it and tell everyone in the room,
those are Hollywood bullshit equations.
They don't make any sense
and why they don't make any sense.
And no one cares.
No one in the room is like,
oh, shut up and play the movie.
You're ruining it for me.
Shut up.
Right?
It's like, I don't care about the equations.
And look, they're fooling you even here,
just like they do in whatever, you know?
So I just wanted to bring that up.
So yeah, I think maybe we've been on,
we've been kicking this now for an hour and a half.
So if anyone comes on for the first time,
they're gonna be how long is Greek
with another 14 hour thing or whatever.
Let's see if there's any other questions.
Yeah, can it be done at Berkey?
Yes, as a matter of fact,
what I will do,
how about I post,
I'll try to sanitize the name
because I have to ask the person
if they wanna be public or not.
Someone asked about the Berkey,
if that was Bruce, right?
Yes, sir.
Yeah, I got a surprise for you then
because here you go.
I will sanitize this and I will send it to right now.
I want you to read this comment here.
I just sent, this is from last week.
Thank you so much for selling me
on the Scalarator, it's magic.
This is not sent to me,
this was sent to the person
who recommended the Scalarator
and then forwarded the message to me.
So this is a third party, right?
I can't stop cleaning everywhere sparkles
and the water tastes amazing out of my Berkey.
I saved some of the old and yuck,
meaning the old water out of a Berkey filtered,
right, it tasted like yuck.
So.
All right.
Yeah, so yeah, it does.
And Berkeys, by the way, are great on paper.
They're wonderful filters on paper.
They do what they say they do,
but I've never tasted water come out of a Berkey
that tasted good and there's one reason for it.
It's because of that stainless steel.
The stainless steel holds the memory.
Yeah, you have to know how to clean the stainless steel,
not physically, electrically.
And I could get into that in the future.
It's very simple, actually.
If you just get an AC power cord,
interrupt the power cord,
and where the power cord is interrupted,
you put your stainless steel there for five minutes,
let AC run through it, right?
Just take one of those cheap lamp cords
and take one leg off the lamp cord.
Yeah, and so you expose the wire, right?
Let me make sure it's unplugged first
and then attach it with magnets or whatever to the stainless.
I think it's non-magnetic with some tape
and make sure there's a light bulb on the end.
There's a load.
So when you plug it in,
it doesn't matter positive or negative, it's AC.
When you plug in the cord with the lamp on the end of it,
one of the legs that are broken on the extension cord
goes through the Berkey.
The Berkey's making the stainless steel
becomes the conductor.
Don't touch it.
Make sure you don't have any pets or children around
while this is going on.
Some people say 10 seconds is enough.
I like to do more than five minutes.
But even 10 seconds will help.
And then once you do that, do it dry, dump it out
and then clean it with baking soda.
Never use anything to clean a Berkey
that you wouldn't ingest.
So you don't use like CLR, lime and scale.
Some people say, can I use CLR, lime and scale?
Even though I finished saying that.
Say, all right, would you drink CLR?
Would you add CLR, lime and scale remover to your food?
No, I just mentioned,
do not use anything that you wouldn't eat.
So you would use vinegar?
Yes.
You would use lemon juice?
Baking soda?
Yes.
Right, you see?
Right.
So stop using industrial chemicals
and you'll notice how things will taste better.
Look, there's someone's house that uses, yeah.
So how does, yeah, go ahead.
So how does a runner length,
size of magnet length afterwards,
how would that work in on the Berkey
when you're scaling it down?
Is my curiosity here.
Oh no, no, the Berkey, no, no, no, no.
The issue, the comments that I just put here
is a Scalarator, a 700 degree one,
a custom one was put on the water main outside
with a plumber because it was an HOA,
got a licensed plumber to install it, all right?
It was put in outside the house.
Okay, okay.
The pipe goes through the garage first
and then it goes through back around the kitchen
and it's got plenty of elbows.
Every 90 degree elbow represents about 20 feet
of runner length, by the way.
Anywhere between 10 and 20 feet.
So let's say you have 10 feet of runner length
with two 90 degree elbows,
you count it as 30 feet, 40 feet.
Each time you put a 90 degree elbow
in a plumbing situation,
it's like adding 10 feet of pipe.
Energetically and mechanically.
Yeah, it's terrible.
They shouldn't be, it's not friendly to flow.
They should always be using sweeps,
but I found that they work to my advantage.
As a matter of fact, if I build a Scalarator
with an extra wrap, like a 540 degree one
instead of a 380, right?
If I make it a 700 degree and I put two 90s on the end
where it just blocks the flow,
it almost as if water is in the Scalarator,
it sees those 90 degrees and it doesn't,
it's like looking down an alley.
You don't see the way out,
but when you get down the alley,
you can see you go right, you know what I mean?
Right.
That's how those 90 degrees work.
When the water sees down to that fitting,
it doesn't see a way out,
but it knows that if it turns right or left,
it'll get out, right?
Terrible.
But it seems to work really well.
It's kind of like, you know,
all right, so you want to run down an alley,
you're like, there's no way I can get out of here.
You're trusting that there's an opening
on the right or the left, right?
You don't want to get caught in a fight in here.
So the water gets a little antsy
when it sees these 90 degree bends
and it tends to work better.
A little excitement in your life once in a while, right?
You know, Schauberger said, yeah, for the water.
In other words, Schauberger says
that the water has a consciousness, by the way.
His consciousness was overtaken
by the water consciousness several times
when he was by a very lively, healthy river
during moonlight.
So, you know, you can allow,
it's better than having the TV
take over your consciousness.
Absolutely.
Yeah, so the Berkey here is just a Berkey.
It's just a poor man's canister filter, you know?
It's basically whatever water source you got.
Like, if you go camping,
you take a Berkey with you, right?
You should.
You just put it, you know,
you go camping with enough people,
why are we bringing him, honey?
Oh, because he's going to carry the water filter.
That's why we're bringing him, right?
Right.
So, yeah.
And what I appreciate,
I appreciate the heads up on that, though.
That's good information on that.
Yeah, we'll be going into a lot of other water stuff
that I've discovered,
but generally, just to recap,
and we will end it soon here,
the Ocelli is a classic Ocelli.
I think it was only for the Ocelli subs,
not the rated Y subs,
that I did about four years ago,
five years ago with him on how to treat water.
It was basically pre-chilling the water
using $10 pitcher filters and buying some magnetite.
And if you can't get that zeolite,
adding it to it, whatever,
pre-chilling certain techniques
and what to do and how to handle water.
And whoever listened to it and did it
found the water quality was exceptional,
better than Fiji, better than anything bottled,
whatever, whatever, whatever.
That was a classic call.
We'll recap on some of those things again,
in case people here have not heard that,
but basically keep it cool,
keep it out of the light, contrary.
By the way, all these airy,
fairy structured water people,
you go to their websites,
nowhere does it say,
keep your water cooler out of the dark at all.
No one does that service.
And I don't even feel like I'm giving a service
by saying that, but anyone who does that
will find an increase in water quality.
But we'll get into a lot of little tips and tricks
because I have developed quite a few things
because again, years ago,
I said, I'm no longer working with water.
I found it to be a dead end thing
just because it's the wrong planet for improving things.
This planet has a course.
So if you see any technological improvement,
it's not out of happenstance.
It was planned a long time ago
and it's part of the course you're supposed to go down.
This is not the right place
to start finding things that need to be improved
and start improving them.
If you think you can do that,
you're making a big mistake.
And I discovered that a long time ago.
So I said, no more water work for me.
And I had to do something about the scale.
I came up with the scale rate or nine months ago.
And that's pretty much my focus has been because,
and again, I had not been talking about it
for a while on the Sonics
because I had started intermingling
with some of the groups that I mentioned here,
both mainstream and non-mainstream water people.
And they get scared.
They're afraid.
They also do what's called delay tactics.
They capture, they kind of like get your attention.
Oh, we're gonna be really wealthy with this,
but you gotta wait like three months, okay?
Don't tell me, how many people have you told about this?
Can you wait another two months?
And then three months go by.
Can you give it a few more months, maybe till July?
You know what?
Why don't you go like fuck yourself?
Did I say that politely enough?
So, because delay tactics is a psychological thing.
They did that to OJ Simpson.
By the way, if you guys don't know the truth behind that,
it's very well known amongst many circles.
OJ Simpson, his wife and Mark, whatever,
they were involved in a very big human trafficking
and drug trafficking network
that was put together by judges in California,
attorneys generals, ex-military, ex-police.
One of the guys went a little crazy,
killed OJ's wife and whatever.
And OJ was like, I can't stand this anymore.
I couldn't stand it while it was going on.
This is too much.
I gotta talk about it.
And they're like, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, you might get into a little trouble,
but you gotta, well, you talk about it
in about three months or so.
I know you're really upset.
Can you just hold it?
Can you promise us you won't say anything between,
three months later, come again.
Oh, three months is over.
Oh, OJ, you can't.
You know how many people's lives are at stake?
Don't talk about it.
I've seen these delay tactics over and over
and over and over and over in many, many aspects of life.
And it really messes people up.
Look at how OJ Simpson is now, right?
I'm not OJ, but I'm just saying,
I like to give that story.
I like to throw in these pieces of information.
It's kind of like kicking the powers that be
in the shins a little bit.
If you ever listen to me talk,
I always try to bring up how 9-11
was a textbook nuclear event.
Not because I know better.
Yeah, I do know better,
but it's kicking the authorities a little bit in the shin.
Don't you wanna kick them in the shins
at least once before you go?
Maybe kick them 1,000 little ways.
So yeah, delay tactics.
So anyway, this I'll be opening up more and more
as we go on and I hope you guys find it of benefit.
And like I mentioned, the end from the beginning,
what I would like to see,
I'm gonna be dedicating as much as I can to it.
But at the same time, if my noodle, my brain breaks
and I say, I'm not doing this anymore,
please excuse me.
But what I would like to see is everybody on this call say,
we're gonna mortgage everything we own
and we're gonna convince our grandmother
to give her her life savings
so we can get at least a million dollars together
and open a factory and all of us will be shareholders.
That would, then we wouldn't have to keep talking, right?
And then we'll say, okay,
why didn't you say that in the beginning?
And why we don't need to continue these calls
in this Skype group?
Well, let's get to work, right?
So I just wanna put that out there too, so.
So with that said, we'll end the recording right here
and we'll schedule another one real soon.
Thank you, Greek.
You're welcome.
I guess I just ended the recording,
so that should pop up momentarily in the chat.
That's fine, you're super hot, dude.
Your mic is really, oh my gosh.
Yeah, turn it down, please, thanks.
Sorry about that.
I had my mic off completely, so.
But yeah, there it is, it's already popped up.
By the way, did you guys hear any cats meowing
in the background?
Because Ivan is trying to get my attention.
There's these.
No, you didn't hear any cats in the background.
Not once, nope, not once, Greek.
Good, yeah, because I,
the thing about the Apple noise cancellation
is it records a graph of your voice
and it rejects anything that doesn't fit those parameters,
so I didn't think a cat would have to imitate my voice.
Right, that's the digital side.
No, it's real rare I hear Ivan anytime.
Yeah, yeah, because it's Apple.
It does both digital and analog.
Okay, you know, just throwing this a little bit
for people with the silly phones like our dollars,
stupid rectangles, like I say,
those little, by the way,
if anyone knows anything about photography,
we'll look at a smartphone and laugh
and what a shit camera it is,
but boy, you'll say, how can it be a shit camera?
Because it's not really a phone,
it's really built to be a camera
that you could use as a phone, really,
because it takes such good pictures.
I don't think it takes such good pictures
and I'm gonna show you why.
See, Greek's really overdoing it now.
What is he talking about?
I love the pictures on my phone,
but I'm gonna share something with you.
Because I know about optics,
I looked at these tiny little cameras and lenses
and I'm like, that is called a fast lens.
Not only is it a fast lens, it's a super fast lens.
What is another term that's more common
for people who don't know about optics
when you say that is like a super duper fast lens?
Someone who knows about optics will say,
well, people don't know what you're talking about.
Why don't you just call it a fisheye lens?
Then they'll know.
Okay, all of your cameras have fisheye lenses on them
and all of your pictures look like fisheye pictures,
every single one.
But wait a second, Greek, that sounds outrageous
because when I take a picture,
it doesn't look taken by a fisheye.
That's right, because your phone
has about 10 different chips in there
that has more processing power
than all the ships that ever went to the moon, supposedly,
to take that image that looks just like a fisheye image
and flatten it out.
So you, stupid human, think that it takes good pictures.
But some humans that know about optics
and what the trickery that they're doing say,
ah, I don't like the pictures on this stupid phone
because look how distorted they are.
And most people don't notice that,
that these algorithms that take
all of your fisheye pictures,
yes, every picture you've ever taken on a smartphone
is an extremely distorted fisheye lens picture.
Every one, every phone does this.
And they straighten it out
using digital software algorithms.
Now, I can see that because I know that
and I could prove it and I show it to people all the time.
One easy way to see that
is when you take a smartphone picture
of a room that has square walls,
you know they didn't build them crooked.
You'll see that the walls never meet at an apex.
They're always curving and bending
and angled this way or did at, always.
You'll never get a photo.
Now, there are architectural modes in some cameras
that pay specific attention to lines and angles,
but you will be easily revealed
if you use regular photo mode or portrait modes
and you start taking pictures in angular situations
where you know as a builder
that the walls are plumb and the floors are level
and you look at the picture and you're like,
oh my gosh, look how convergent,
look how distorted that is, right?
We take pictures of food and we're like,
oh my gosh, look how distorted that is.
It looks huge compared to the plate.
It's not like that in real life.
She's like, oh yeah, oh yeah, I noticed that now, thanks.
Right?
Well, not only that,
but it literally contains less information
than the old chemical prints did.
Oh yeah.
You could, you know, microscopic examinations, right?
You take a microscope to the old physical,
you know, chemical prints.
You can determine a lot of different information
out of those things.
People don't realize the stuff you can figure out.
Sure, because each grain has a shadow to it.
Yeah, exactly.
But when you take a look at these digital images,
it's crap.
It's so, it's got-
Yeah, but it's gotten,
people are stupid and they're easy to fool.
Yeah, but it's got like 20% of the information
contained in a chemical print
is what you get out of any of these digital prints.
Any of these digital photographs that are taken now,
it's got about 20% of the information,
true information for measurements, for textures,
for shadows.
Well, but even from,
that's more of a forensic point of view,
but I'm speaking from just a casual observer.
They look distorted to me.
Most people have been told they look good
and they're amazed by the contrast clarity.
They think they're good pictures.
And I pointed out to the wife, Linda, all the time.
I said, look at this.
Is that thing really that big in real life?
Just look at it in the room and look at the picture.
That's totally distorted.
Most people don't see that.
But that's what I'm trying to tell you
is that even when you try to scale things
from the digital, it's impossible.
It doesn't, I mean, they show you these computer analysis,
shows them, it's garbage because-
Well, from a camera,
because the lens cannot take a flat picture.
It's always gonna take a fish eye.
There's a little tiny lens, it's called a fast lens.
It cannot, it's impossible.
No, I got it.
To take a flat picture, yeah.
I'm just trying to say,
just knowing how to work with those things.
I'm not an expert exactly, but I had to become-
I don't wanna be an expert in that.
Oh my gosh, that would be a nightmare
to be an expert in that stuff.
Well, you know that was one of the JFK things
I worked on was photographs, right?
Yeah, but they didn't have smartphones back then.
I'm talking about the smartphones only.
Right, but that's my point
is that I could take a black and white photo
that people think, oh, that's a crap picture.
It's an old, it's got information in it that is real.
Oh yeah, well, I used to have a medium format,
which is a film is each frame of the negative
is two inches by two inches,
not the little 110 that people grew up with
or 35 millimeter, medium format film.
When you take medium format film,
you can blow it up, black and white,
especially the 100 ISO.
You can make a 20 foot by 20 foot picture billboard
and it would still have clarity and resolution, right?
Yeah, I can scale a person back to original size.
I can put them in there,
like if you're six foot tall,
I can print you six feet tall on a photograph.
Full resolution.
Yeah, and full resolution, exactly.
Yeah, that's a medium format.
Yeah, but Sonny, where the world is going,
and this is a perfect, the call maybe now
is that the Scalarator is representative
exactly what's going on with the photographs
that no one is noticing because right now
there are millions and millions of people
looking at magnetic water treatment devices, right?
And the structured water devices
and all these other things.
When I'm telling you they don't,
and people will get into, I've gotten into my face
when I say those things don't do anything.
And they get in my face, well, yes, they do.
I'm like, not consistently, not consistently.
And you know why?
I know because being a water person,
if they worked, I would be the first one to say so.
And I've run them all through their toes.
They don't do anything.
They do so little that you can actually have 10 people
arguing after using them for a month.
Did it do anything?
I don't know.
I think it did.
It's like, oh my gosh,
it depends on which way the wind is blowing, you know?
That's why I said these companies
that you'll find in the alternative structured water,
they have to sell water filters.
They have to.
Because obviously the devices they're selling
don't do anything or much.
They get upset also when I say
your devices don't do anything.
Because you know, I'm a bull in a China shop
sometimes too, right?
I say your devices don't do anything
compared to the scale rater.
And one of them, Jonathan, was like, yeah, it's true.
If I would have known about this 10 years ago,
I wouldn't be doing any of this.
He was honest, you know?
So, but anyway, yeah.
This is amazing.
So we'll see where it goes.
And I think it'll go somewhere.
And at least I'm putting out what I can.
Right.
With that said, yeah.
All right, great.
End it right now.
And we'll just keep this,
I'll keep populating this with images
and things like that to keep the interest going.
And we'll maybe do an outline.
I'll take questions during the week
and we'll do one next week.
I'd suggest you put the pictures in
when you do the calls though,
because that'll get everybody quicker, easier.
They might have restored now
because we had the call joined.
You might be able to roll them back
because now I can roll it back.
But at first I couldn't roll it back.
And I think a couple other people couldn't see it either,
the pictures at first.
So just-
We'll figure it out, yeah.
Okay, great.
All right, guys, thanks very much.
Until the next time.
Thanks, Greg.
Good night.