Hey Bruce, see you joined
I'm gonna
Kill the screen
Hey, George is here. Okay
Hello gonna join with this other one. I made it great. I just I
Think we're gonna wrap it up today. I'm gonna go out right in the office right now
I'm gonna go out get a box that I have all the stuff that I build
With turn on some lights and just take some final pictures and and I might want to just kill the group
You know in a couple of days. We'll start a recording soon when it gets pertinent
okay, and you know just to you know, see where everybody is because remember this is a
Proprietary stuff. This is like, you know, no one, you know people that come up with stuff like this. Don't do this kind of stuff
They don't share
Run and hide, you know and keep it a secret and all that. So I want to get it out there
And so we could do like another phase in the future. I figured we'll just
Make this the last call record. I didn't really go and photograph all the stuff I wanted to I want to sit back and see
what other people do with it first if
they do anything, you know and
Because remember someone showed me will you show me how to make the scale or eight or I said I'll introduce you to the guy
Who showed me?
So right
No one showed me any of this and I want to just see what kind of
How we can muster up and people, you know
Find being people in when they're in adversarial, you know positions like, you know, the soccer mom who lifts the minivan to save her children
Not that much but you know, push people a little see what they come up with. Also
It breeds creativity, you know, we have a problem, you know, you might know how to fix it, but how would you fix it?
you might add something that's
New to the mix that no one else could come up with because you know, everyone comes up with their own stuff
So yeah, that's what I'm trying to do with this again
No matter how good you try to do. You should always have some selfish reasons in there
Why are you doing it? And what I'd like to do is garner extra input
So we'll see
Did I mute everybody no, okay, I just know another
That's fine. I turned on another computer so we could do on their recording. If there's any pertinent questions or anything, I
Don't think it's gonna photograph. I think I could photograph some on the iPhone 7
Walking around. I think I can take pictures with it. So, you know
But I don't think it would be necessary
What I was thinking of doing is bringing the scaler box in the office here and shooting some pictures of the jig
Mm-hmm, you know and some
some of the brackets very simple idea if you're going to
clamp a
pipe and
Your clamp is sourced at a hardware store or what-have-you. I get most of my stuff from Harbor Freight
Do I pay double for the same thing?
So the clamp on the end of the all woodworking clamps and all clamps even specialty clamps are flat
So if you have a round profile dimensional object, that's soft
And you clamp it with a flat plane. Guess what? It'll leave a flat impression
So you're gonna have to outfit your clamps with a corresponding
piece that's round
Make sense, right? I don't think I have to show that. I think it'll be a big plus if I do though
Maybe I'll hear the washing machine in the kitchen because getting dark now outside. I think has it better
Probably rig something up. This is like an impromptu thing
The reason I wanted to do the call also is because I've been some pretty interesting interesting parties are coming up
Here and there about
About
Taking interest in the project, you know
so
I'd like to keep things moving along constantly or
And see what one thing leads to another because ultimately I'd like to just do this get it started walk away and see it
In the world, right? I
Don't know if anyone here has actually built one yet
Implemented in one and actually experienced
What other people say about it who have been introduced to it, you know like
What I usually like a typical install goes like like this. We have a
conversation
With a prospect of person who was interested in better water quality. Let's say
They're at the bottom end like they using a water softener, right?
Which is like the worst thing you could probably do and by the way
A lot of states are banning them because for environmental reasons, which I agree. I mean, why would you add?
salt
To your tap water or well water to get the scale out and then what do you do with the salt?
You know, it feels terrible. It's slimy, whatever whatever
Typical conversation and these are all like what you call professional people
you know, they're they work in let's say some scientific field or or
Where you know, whatever
They have a healthy degree of skepticism usually they say
Can you please explain to me scientifically what it does?
Right away you have to discern, you know
How do you tell them there's no electrons or protons in the lazy neutron that it doesn't exist
So you have to do it the best you can
They somehow feel to the point
that
If they usually the price comes up, I like to bring the price up immediately
within the first 10 minutes that it's 5,000 bucks and
If I notice that they're serious and water quality is important to him. I said well
How about we do a wholesale and that's half of that and then they're fine, right?
Because your typical water softener is going to be in the 2000 range installed to 5,000 depending how big it is
All that other stuff so the typical conversation goes like that, you know, most of them have been a wholesale price
At the 2500 in my shed right now. I'm grabbing the boxes
So they agree
2500 but you know what the cost on these things is, you know, the pipe is about a dollar a foot. It's to be
$2 a foot three feet of pipe and the magnets are under 50 bucks
And it take usually about two or three hours depending on how fancy you want to make them look
So we schedule if it's an HOA one of these homeowner associations I advise
Getting a licensed plumber to adjudicate the install. So in case somebody really nosy
It's on the board comes over like oh, you should have a licensed plumber, you know, okay, so you get a licensed plumber
I was surprised. I have a real good one Vasquez plumbing
The parts were about a hundred dollars in copper and it would take about an hour and a half and he said give me a
price of
$225 I was like what?
That's like wages. You're working for like 1980s. It would have been too much money if some fortunate
So anyway, the conversation usually goes on to the next level
let's
Let's do an install. So well, however long it takes to get out there meet them get a plumber
Okay, so what happens plumber shows up, you know the person that you know, whose scale orator is four is usually there and
While it's being installed. They almost in a lightly threatening way. They say like
You know, I'm going to take a sample over to lab to see what it does
That way and I'm like, oh that sounds is that a threat? You know, I'm thinking I'll say no, it's alright. That's fine
That's great. Actually would like to see what it does here
So as the installation winds up and
Everything sealed do a leak test pressure test
Okay, go inside run all the fixtures because you want to get what do you do a copper especially or glue in the pipe?
You want to run all the fixtures inside the house get it flushed out
After about five minutes or running. I'm like, okay get yourself at least a 64 ounce sample
Set aside. We have a 64 ounce sample your two quarts from the previous water and
Then it's like get a cup and I want you to taste it come out here. Let's taste it. Let's taste it outside
It's tasting inside
Right away. They're like, wow
And I'm like, all right, do you have the lab sample that won't be necessary
I'm like, well, don't you want to send it to the lab? No, that won't be necessary at all. So what changed their mind?
so drastically
That they were almost threatening to have it taken to the lab and now it's not necessary whatsoever
Right. Think about that the impression that it makes
Is so big so huge
And also we get a chance to taste the tap water from an hour before to what it's like coming out now
They're like here here. Here's some Fiji water tasted this tastes better than the Fiji water right out of the tap. I'm like, yeah, it does
So it's a reason I brought this up again
I have mentioned this again before over and over because it seems to repeat
almost the exact scenario and
The impression that it makes is so big and positive
You know that it's it's not like
Something you typically in life we experience various things, you know that things are supposed to make things better
I don't know you get a bigger TV screen or whatever
Everyone's a new computer or whatever a new girlfriend boyfriend upgrade to a better spouse. I don't know whatever
I've never seen anything that was so dramatic and left such an immediate impact
And of course, it's water quality. If you're most people are not interested in good water quality
So I just want to bring this up again to see if anyone has had that experience yet would not just themselves but with anyone else
using the scale reader
Because that seems to be the typical paraphrase, you know account
Alright, so let's grab this other box
Make our way inside. I
Think I've finally gotten over the circus flu, which is great almost one month
Think I might have mentioned I don't know if I would died at one point because I woke found myself awake in the hallway at
2 30 in the morning and
I'm standing there. I'm like, how do you get in the hallway and I look into the room where I sleep and I see
Myself in bed sleeping and I'm like, how could I be standing in the hallway and see myself in bed sleeping in the other room?
That doesn't make any sense
So that I opened the door where the wife was sleeping and I said Linda, can you hear me?
And she goes, yeah, I can hear you. So, okay. I'm not a ghost
right
So it's quite interesting
Don't agree can't pick home in right and not at all
All right, so
The scalarator boxes
So I'm gonna be back into this. I'm gonna just take a picture
jig
And I'll get the
Could have been it out. I
Should have done it outdoors outdoors where you don't have shadows as much
And I have a magnet temporarily fixed to this
How many people so many people are on?
I'm just a second here. I was making a coffee
Right now you have
Six nine right now. Oh good including myself of course
So we could start getting the business that
I'm gonna remove the magnet from this one. I
Have of several what do they call them in the appliance industry scratching dents?
Or bent and dent or scratching? Yes. I think they're called scratching dent
Yeah, please hold
Yeah, yeah, I got a couple of those. I'm gonna be using those samples
I need to start making some more other ones now soon this week. I have two more that have to go out
So we'll place this one in here
Let's take a photo. Let's see how that comes out
believe I
think Skype allows
To take a picture
It's very complicated, all right, let's do this
Let's do this, okay
Alright, so we'll take the pipe out. I even did a sonic where I talked about
When you were gonna take a picture of something you're in the room with it
You know what?
It looks like so the picture should give that feeling to whoever is looking at the picture
So, let's see if we can do that. That's what the jig looks like and that would be the back
so
And that should show the contours let's do it right
And take a picture of the jig
All right, let's upload that see how well that goes
It's just the rod jig
All right, somebody let me know when the picture shows up should show up now
Yep, we got her
Yep, that's what the jig looks like and you see that would be for the back part of the scalerator
I'll place it in there now
This is a reject piece
And always maybe I'll show the one
Where I think I have another one then there's another jig
There's another jig also when you're done done done
with it
Kill two birds with one stone with this I'll show the other piece
Maybe I'll put the other piece in there instead of the reject and take a picture so you get orientation
Yeah
Let's do that and it's killed two birds with one stone that will also show you the fill that I talked about last time
this
okay, so
Should start recording soon. Okay. This is the orientation of the jig upload that
So here you get the
Orientation
With the piece in there, so, you know like the flat parts on the bottom what you'll notice about I
Think it should be up. Okay guys got it
Yes notice
Thank you, you'll notice there's a pink spot on the left of the scalerator that's sitting in the jig so you get the orientation
This is what I call a model
So that pink spot is Bondo auto body filler
Because when I bent it originally it had a kink in it. I wasn't happy
So I filled it using a guide
To how I like the curve to be the reason why I did that is because I need a model
so the model
Then once I had this smooth and where I want it. I made a clamp
That fits
That is the negative of that and I'll take a picture of that right now
It'll make sense when you see it and the clamp is specific to that location
You'll see because it actually is labeled top bend
And I'll take another photo of it
With on the inside of the clamp so you see the significance of it
You see that clamp it looks kind of messy on the top, but you see it says top bend and it goes over that curve
Yeah
Yeah, okay. So now I'm gonna take I'm gonna take the clamp and I'm going to put a piece on it
Actually, I'll just photograph it like this and you'll see what I'm talking about
when it's
it's when when I
Put
Put the putty on that clamp. I put a piece of plastic saran wrap on the pipe
So it wouldn't stick and that's what the inside of the top of where it says top bend
It's the negative relief of that curve and it should have come up right now. You can see it. It's a putty
It's basically the steel stick, you know, it's an epoxy putty comes in a tube. It looks like a big tootsie roll
Usually get it from Lowe's because it's twice the size for half the money
I wish I could get you know
There's a 3m distributor here. I can get it wholesale, but that means you got to buy a case of this stuff
I don't really feel like investing $1,000 or $500 in epoxies
So it's a little expensive when you make trips to the hardware store. It's like buying popcorn in the movie theater
But anyway, you see the inside of the clamp how it's a negative relief of that curve. Yeah
I'm just gonna ask
Could
Could a person also use just a scrap piece of pipe and then heating it so that it expands to that form
Yes, exactly. You could mold it on there. Yeah, but you don't have a lot of that much control and accuracy though because
If you feel like you have the control and accuracy, yes do anything will work as long as it's firm
And I'll show you the there's another clamp. I've also made specialty
Fixtures to make the centerpiece and then I'll show the
Final clamp when you're done done done to make sure that the other outer pieces are aligned
Now what I'm going to do is instead of installing
I have another clamp
Similar to that. I'll just I'll just fasten it and I'll leave it there and you can imagine
The backside also has that putty
How would you call it it's just putty relief
This also has the same
It's not the greatest background, but let's just get it up there. So you always see it
And you see how that clamp is a I'll take another shot of it
Further away should have that one, too
See that one goes like that
And that one so you see these clamps go all the way around I have one clamp every let's say
30 about 60 degrees
minimum
That's how that one goes it's different it's not a squeeze clamp it's a bar clamp
And it goes around and around what I'll do, right?
what I'll do right now, which I haven't done before I'm going to go ahead and put my stoppers in and
All the clamps the way I have them oriented
makes sense
So you'll see what a production unit looks like and it'll leave the model in there as well
And I'll put my stoppers my sand stoppers. I call them
in place
So if I were just making this unit right now
This is what you would see if you were here and the unit was just let's say
Completed because the clamps are applied as you go around and round, right?
And some of the clamps have curves some are straight because this the pieces on the ends are straight
There's no curve on them. You know the tails, right?
But the as you go around and round
They're curved. And so the putty each clamp each clamp has putty on it
Where it's straight on the ends just the last two inches I make a straight curve
accommodation
But where it goes around the curved section where the radians
You know progress at the loop the spool what makes the spool?
I have a curved section like you said you Bruce you could cut a one and a quarter inch pipe
by the way is
pretty close
To you could slide a one and a quarter over the one inch
But you can't slide a one inch over the one and well over the three quarter
So I'll show you what it looks like in
Progress. This is pretty much
What it looks like if I were casting doing my sand bend right now
with everything in place and you'll notice the top of the
Squeeze clamps have either a straight three straight lines or three arc curved lines. So that is when I'm
Doing it. I know which clamp to grab
The clamps on the ends you'll notice
Let's stop talking and take a picture so you can see
You'll notice
Go back
This is on my washing machines
So go further back enough, okay, let's see like that
Let's do that. It's very complex picture
So but you'll you'll get the idea
Against would have been best if I did it outside in the daytime on the work table
Okay, so you should have the photograph now you see my sticks in there it says hot sand and there's a line on the blue
tape
It's like a plug
Wow, you'll see what the one that you see the one that says top bend earlier and the clamp is still there
But you see the the clamp on next to the hot sand one. There are four silver lines that are straight
But if you see the top end clamp towards the back you notice the lines there are arched or curved, right
They're not straight lines. That means that when you grab the clamp
you know where it goes and all around where the curve of the pipe is there's a mark on each clamp that shows that the
Fixture is curved and on on the straight ends of the pipe. You can't see the far one to seem is it's straight
So you want to mark your clamps?
Where they go?
Okay
So if I were doing a hot sand filled bend right now, that's what it would look like when I'm done
So at this point what I do is I remove one of the plug-in hot which is hot sand and I pick up the entire
jig and I dump the hot sand out on one end and then remember you got to do it on the other and rotate it and
then I
Use a leaf blower to or compressed air to go inside the pipe blow any hot sand that also cools the pipe
And then you want to remove the clamps
If the pipe is too soft, which it won't be
Because they could now compress the pipe, right? So you know you as you're going the thing is cooling down
So I don't think anyone will have these clamps by the way, the springs are really strong
So what I did is a retempered the springs
With a blowtorch to you know, when you temper a spring with a bloat with heat it loses its springiness. It's it's tension
So there's a lot that goes on into this. In other words, you have to have knowledge of many many things
To get it to this point and I'll take another picture
Right now what the assembly looks like from a distance. Maybe that will help actually Bruce
I think or anyone here that it looks kind of crazy, right? It looks like a crazy octopus, whatever
You can't really see what's going on unless you know what's going on. I think right because I just I think it's I think it's
pretty clever
Yeah, and you see the jig is floating right right you see the jig is not flying so you can get underneath
Yeah, this is my first try. This is my first jig
My first thing the spacer in the middle ends up being exactly the same as a magnet
I had to put some aluminum on it to build it up
So I this is the first jig on and I knew it had to be elevated because I've worked with
Woodworking before I know you can't you have to have
Be able to get underneath it right anytime you work with a clamp
It's a two-sided deal, right?
You got to get to the top and underneath and I know that having a fly on a table doesn't work has to be elevated
Okay, so let's just jump since this is about jigs
I'm gonna go out and get a finished scale orator when you're done done done and you fit your magnet and
Everything together and it's done like it's ready to ship. Let's say right
What you need to do is make sure that especially in life for quality sake
If you look at the regular scale orator, you notice that the two ends are straight going out, right?
Those two straight ends need to be true. What I mean by true is
When you
Measure the length of the scale orator as it's going to be fitted. It's usually 12 and a quarter
You approach the main and you cut the 12 and a quarter out of the main
That main pipe is straight in line, right?
It was a straight piece dead straight that you cut a section out of and most likely it's still going to be in that position
You want the ends of your scale orator to be perfectly in line with each other?
Just like a bicycle wheel is true or a wheel would be true or flat
So while you're manipulating and building this thing and fitting the magnet
There's tension and gluing and there's thermal stresses that might occur whatever whatever whatever
You'll notice that when you're done done done
That the two ends even though your jig was true. It are not so true anymore
There's slightly off enough that when you go to how do I know this when you cut the section of main off and you go?
To fit it's like oh, it's not really lining up and you have to put tension into it to bend
You know one inch pipe is pretty stiff even plastic when it's fixed, you know
And the scale orator is pretty stiff because it's scheduled 80. It's not gonna budge, right?
So you're like fuck, you know, I got just a little bit
It's got a lot of tension like you try to tighten the Union down. Oh, it's really tight
You know, you know, it's not you know, not true, right?
So what I did is I made a hollow I'm gonna go out and get I have I got the ones that are in the cases
Because they're done sitting there
one without a fitting I
Made a jig that accommodates, you know, the magnet has extra depth
when you stack the magnets, so
You can't use this jig at all for the final for the final
Truing at all it won't work whatsoever because the magnets are bolted on and you know, and they're sticking up
You know if you see this jig, you see there's a center spacer that you know, once you fit a magnet
You're not going to be able to use this jig anymore, you know, because it's at the bottom is the center is solid
So this other jig is just a very plain jig just to align the outer ends
And I'm going to demonstrate that right now by fitting in a finished scale orator
I'll take a picture of the blank of what the jig looks like and then the finished scale orator and you'll see how it works and
Once you put the finished scale orator in your final jig
This is after the scale orator is done done done ready ready for
Shipping right shipping means delivery
You fit it you drop it in there and if there's any
The ends are very tight if there's any misalignment
At all, it will show it will not fit in exact you'll put it in and it'll be a little off
right
So
I'm gonna take a photo of that right now. This is a little shorty scale orator. Oh, they're so good-looking
So I'll take a picture of this one this one's really short because it has a medium case but this is what the
The final one looks like and I'll pick it up and show you what it looks first
I'll tell you I'll send send a picture first of the scale orator in it
Now what happens when you drop it in this jig, let me just put it up it's easier to
It's those those end blocks are really tight
So when you put the scale orator in there and you'll notice there's play or it doesn't drop in squared
You come back with either a very good blow dryer or the heat gun and you start gently
Heating the ends to line them up. So they fit in the jig and you use your clamps the straight clamps
You got that picture, right?
So now I'm going to remove the scale orator and I'll show you what the jig looks like it's very plain and
The purpose again and is to accommodate the magnet
This is just a very simple plain
jig
And it's got a hollow spot in the middle. This is what it looks like
Very simple. It's double layers one inch thick
Just two half-inch pieces of plywood particle board glued together
And that's what the jig looks like and its purpose again is to just show stability and the way you make it
Is you cut your profile and your end pieces? You just put a straight piece of pipe through that's your alignment
Right. So when you make the jig
The way you start out with it is to just I
Think I only have really long pieces of schedule 80. Oh get a schedule lady to do it justice
You guys said a lot see the last picture of it. Yeah
Yes
You see you see how it's just open. It's very it couldn't be any simpler or easier to make that because the purpose is just
Its purpose is just to make sure that the ends that are going to contact where it's going to fit are true in line
and when you try to drop it in and the way you make the jig is you just outline a scale orator or something and
You cut it and then you fit the outer pieces and right and
When you do that
The way you make the jig the way you figure out where to put your outer pieces
Is very simple and I'm going to show you right now. This is exactly once I cut the piece
With the jigsaw. All I did was this what I'm going to show you right here to make the jig
I just took a piece of pipe and
laid it in there and
made sure
That the four blocks of wood that are sandwiching the pipe are
Really tight glued in screwed in whatever glued and screwed
And I'll show send that up and that's how you make that
It's the easiest thing in the world
to make and you should make that because it's the hardest thing in the world if you're going to go install a scale orator with
Schedule lady and the ends are not true
Especially with the Union they do require amount of a sixteenth of an inch never seemed so big, right?
So if you're off by a thirty second or a sixteenth of an inch you try to squeeze in and you're like man
This is a huge amount, but you didn't notice it, right?
So that's very important. You see how you make it once you do your cut out
You just lay a piece of pipe and then glue your four blocks really tight against the pipe because it's going to be straight
That's what you're trying to replicate
Right at the end of the day no matter what the crazy straw madness this scale orator looks like
The system the domestic system in the house just wants to see it see a straight pipe, right?
So you that's how that's how you make that and that's your final jig
So and you notice what you you only use this when you're done done done done done right before shipping
And shipping means delivery to whoever gets it
That's is there a is there a glue that you're using on that bend that goes up comes up on top of the other pipe
where they cross
Yes, there's a glue in their schedule a I'm using a medium gray and the way you do that
It comes in a dab one of these cans with a little brush. It looks like a cotton ball on the end of a stick
Okay, you can't use that yeah, what you do is you pour the glue into a small ziplock bag I
Went over this and you yes. Yes the corner of it's a look up what a pastry bag works
Never seen even in Hollywood a pastry chef right before they shoot in between the eyes
He has a pastry bag it's called a grout bag in construction
You know, and it's just a you get the snack bags the freezer ones not the regular ones are too thin
And you put your glue in the corner you tie it off with a twist tie or string or tape
And then you just cut a tiny amount of usually
Whatever hole you're gonna cut off whatever edge you're gonna cut off the corner of the bag
It's gonna be too big even if you think it's a small hole still too big. So start off really small
You'll be surprised how much flows out of it
Okay, then you have a lot of control yeah, and you always practice, you know, you always practice
I have a little one right here a grout bag with white caulk in it. It's actually clear caulk. I'll photograph that
Should I photograph that show you how it's done
Might as well. No, it's not great. It's yeah. Yeah, it's not gray
It's
Just a ziplock bag and you can see I just squeezed it a little bit
This is clear caulk because I use it when I put labels on boxes. I use
clear caulk
Because it works better than glue and also removes this kind of rubbery
Right, you could pull it off. It's really sure in other words it releases
So that's so instead of it being a white material. It would be gray material
You should definitely
Glue the pipe to itself
With the PVC glue. Absolutely. The reason why is
Let's say the pressure limit is
670 pounds
Which it is for schedule 80 if you were to put a tremendous amount of pressure in this even though it's heat bent
What does it want to do? It wants to straighten out
It's the last thing you want is this thing flexing and under pressure and wanting to open it actually does I have pressurized them
Unglued and you see them they want to straighten out right everything not that it has memory
It's just that the forces there there's calculations
in hydraulics in high
Of when you bet make a bend the extra forces that the plumbing experiences at that section, right?
Because everything wants to be straight. It doesn't want to be curved
So you should definitely glue it. Yes
Bonded and I should do a should I do a close-up of what the bonding looks like
Or you guys see it, right if you wish
Yeah
And it's the same color it's it's called medium gray
It's medium gray
And and so the bonding looks like it's very neat
And if you if you go over or whatever use some acetone
That's a close-up of that one
There you go, that's just on there that goes all around and around the magnet and everything
It's kind of it. Yeah, it's it's kind of a requirement structural
requirement
Somebody just posted
Somebody just posted can we record this call even though we missed the first 12 minutes
That's all right. I can go over the photos
If
Yes, why don't we stop and I'll stop yammering run in my mouth and I'll record and I'll go over the photos for the recording
That's good
Let me just put this back in the case
And you know, I have you guys are familiar that when these are presented you should there are works of art
these things are qualified as
To peep to go to people some people who are very interested in water quality and are interested in handcrafted devices
All right, so what I'm going to do is
Start recording and I'll go in the office and
Just go over the photographs for the sake of the recording, okay
Okay
Okay. So this is our third installment of sonics regarding the scale orator build
And what we're going to do I've posted several photographs regarding the jig and
construction
So we'll go to the top photograph if and will which photograph are we referring to?
It would be
Today is the February 5th 2024
And it's the photograph dropped in at 6 13 p.m. My time. So your your your Skype will show something different
what you'll see is
A cloth background and a jig it's a wooden platform slightly elevated with a round circle in the center
plaster contours on a frame work
Sort of very uneventful. What is that? It's not even really good to the eye and
Centerpiece shows up, you know some designations pretty rough
As you go down the second photo shows what I call a model scale orator sitting in the jig and the orientation
So you see the orientation from left to right, you know, it goes flat and then
the as it rotates
Counterclockwise the piece goes over so you have the under and over
Situation and this is the position. I have it and usually when I'm
working it and
I also want to go you have a scale orator in the back, right?
And the one that's sitting in the jig right now on the second photo down
From the start of this call, you'll notice on the left curve there. There's a pink material
That is Bondo auto body filler and the purpose of that
Was to redefine that curve
Because the initial curve it was very every time you bend this they're slightly inconsistent, right?
Whether you use your thumbs your big toe your dog's paw, you know
Whatever you use it's going to be different every time so I needed to make something that would fit in that curve
Molded to be consistent and if you scroll down again
Not to be confused that pink there is just this is just for the photograph it's a model
This right so what I did was I molded you'll see a clamp there on the left and this is the third photo now
You'll see inscribed on it is top bend and there's like a putty material on the end you scroll down again
You'll see that that putty is the negative of that model curve
Right now when you work with putty on an object to form model to curve or whatever
You need what's called a bond breaker. Don't work with the putty on the device
And try to remove it. It'll stick. So you need a bond breaker. I use saran wrap cling wrap
You could use wax or grease oil, but that's messy
right
So you could see the inside of that clamps very smooth and the putty is one of these putty sticks putty epoxy sticks
You get them at hardware stores. It's not a paint. It's not a paste. It's a putty
right, so it looks like a tootsie roll kind of thing and
You mold it get creative you could use plaster or any other material but I like material that sets quickly so I can get back to
work
the next photos
Subsequent to that is another clamp
Now that one is more of a bar clamp and the photo below that shows more in perspective what it looks like
Same thing. There's a hell of a lot of putty on that
And you could see that the that bar clamp if we go back to the previous image of it on the close-up
There's two different color putties one of them grabs the center mold piece of the center hub
To keep it from rotating back like a hook
And if you go down to the next photograph below that one where it shows the full square bar clamp
That's the full complement that if I were bending the pipe right now, that's what it would look like including with my sand plugs
and you'll notice that there's quite a bit of clamps here 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 clamps and
They're all molded now the bottoms are flat from the factory, but the tops are
Molded that's why if you look closely at the clamps or designations like the one next to this plug that says hot sand
You'll notice four straight lines. That means that it's for the straight section of pipe
But if you go, let's say
Clockwise, then you see the one that says top bend that is very specialized. We showed it earlier in a detail and
The one behind that
Clockwise again, you'll notice that there's two arc shapes on the top of the clamp
The other one has three lines silver lines
and they all the rest around the curve have silver lines because that clamp is meant to be on the radius portion on the
Bent portion not on the straight part of pipe. It's important because if you just have a straight
Molded negative. Let's say it will leave an impression a flat spot
Right, so if you notice the scale raters that are done
They don't have any impressions because now the earlier ones that I did I could put a photo if you look very closely
They do have square
impressions on them
Kind of like a sloppy carpenter who leaves waffle hammer waffle head marks on a piece of wood after he nails it
So I decided to mold put this putty on each clamp
to conform to the shape
Right, so this is the fourth photograph I reckon let's go back and count
One two, three, four five six seventh photograph. We just talked about
So that's pretty much the construction
So the first seven photos are regarding the base jig
The first this is this jig was made from my mind
Basically pot of coffee and a pack of cigar half a pack of cigarettes in the morning. What how should I make this?
I already had the model scale orator bent
Before I did the molding the molded sections out of plaster
So one two, three, four five six seven first seven photos of tonight's
install are
of the construction and bending clamping molding of
the scale orator
All right. So up to there any questions because so far that's strictly the the molding and making though
As we go into successive pictures, it's when the scale orator is complete
Any questions about the making of the jig or or molding
Center piece is a four inch hub transition piece for four inch PVC. I had that laying around. I used to work with the mind and
You know four inch pipe is like, you know angel hair pasta right on a mine because everything's big
So I had PVC pieces left over but that conforms to a five and a quarter inch magnet
So that's centerpiece. You mean the big center round piece. Let's just make sure we're speaking on the same thing, right? Correct
Yeah
Yeah, if you don't have something like that
What you do is you probably I presume that you have your magnet before you get started
Go ahead and trace your magnet on a piece of whatever wood or foam
I would hardwood or particle board or plywood
Trace it very accurately and cut it very accurately with your jigsaw and two of them
so you have a stackable unit a filler spacer piece doesn't have to be that it's just like
Again, this is like ghettos ghetto rigged, you know with stuff laying around. I
Walked around the shed and wherever I said, what do I have? That's about the same size as this magnet, right?
And that's what I had and it was much taller actually cut it
That that fitting was twice as high as that were much higher so you could see that
I don't see so I cut it down didn't need to be so tall
So let's say whatever magnet dimension you're working with
You're going to need a spacer to mimic the position of the magnet in the center many ways to do it
Many ways to do it you can see that it's cut because there's so few threads on the top there and I and when I cut
it I
It was just a little bit smaller than the magnet. So I built up some cardboard, you know, like the shirt cardboard, you know a
Thin chipboard and then I put aluminum on it. Everything has aluminum and a plaster and
Any surface that's facing upward or sideways has aluminum
Fiberglass welding blanket or aluminum because remember you're using a heat gun as you go around right that heat guns
1200 degrees supposedly and
If you just have bare wood or plastic
It doesn't really like you end up you start smoking your jig literally. Let's start smoking, right?
It doesn't really burn it and damage it it could if you use it enough, but it starts it's it's here
It stinks, you know, it's like you want to heat up the pipe
Why is the is the wood starting to smoke right? It's like, oh that sucks, you know, but remember I put this jig together
Purely from my mind. I imagined
The steps that I would go through that it needed to be fireproof. It needed fire resistant
Heat resistant it needed to be elevated because I know my clamps are gonna grab underneath right? I know right?
I know this I know you see even the bottom platform of the jig corresponds to the top platform, right?
So when I go to pick it up and grab it, it's balanced
Because you know when I dump the sand out everything is still connected if you don't want to undo your clamps and then dump the sand
out
Because it'll it'll lose its shape, right?
So you want it to cool down considerably in the hundred and fifty degree range like below 175 degrees. It's pretty solid
It's not bending. So you have your thermometer around
And it doesn't really get above that outside. Anyway, that's why you need to work it with the heat gun
But when I when I'm done, I pull one of the hot sand plugs out dump the sand out
Then I remove the other plug dump the sand out rotate it
That's why the top and bottom of the jig base are is the same
So when I grab the bottom or grab the top, it's balanced right most people
Someone asked me. Why don't you make a square base on the bottom?
That wouldn't work too. Well when you have to pick the thing up and rotate it right get it
So again, I have an unfair advantage, I'm in my sixth decade
I've been doing this stuff since I was in the third grade. So, you know
many people that I
encounter in life
When it comes to building and making things don't have that kind of let's say gumption drive experience or whatever. So
In a way listen to what I'm saying, but don't be intimidated because I have an unfair advantage
I've been doing this since I was eight years old this type of stuff
Forming and inventing and building things that don't exist
So what I'm trying to do here is explain that yeah, I did it all from my mind
without trial and error because I
Try to forward
You should do this, you know, what is my day gonna be like what you know, where am I going today?
What do I need? Do I need an umbrella? Which shoes do I wear right? Where am I going right? Just be thoughtful of
You know imagine I call it running the program imagine you are making a film of your of
What you're going to be doing and encounter it that way before in this way you come before you prepared
So that's the long answer because one thing ties into the next right?
Yeah, well I got that
Good yeah
Yes, it was too cold it was your sand wasn't packed enough and it was too cold
Well, once you get to that point, it's exactly the same point as where you put the pink putty on
That wants a kink right there, but you have to like counter rotate it and then it wants to go back
Yeah
Almost like a saddle
Do the first time and then you have to rotate it 180 degrees and then do the second band
Because it resists it resists the direction you want to go
So you fool it into going into the direction you want it to go by rotating it right like counter-steering
Mm-hmm. Yeah, you have to be also when you start forming those long beds
You have to maintain even pressure as much as possible. I hope you're wearing thick leather gloves
Right. Yeah, I got some welding gloves. Yep. Yeah, they could just be the cheap construction ones, too
Sometimes the welding gloves are a little too thick
Yeah
You want a thick welding glove that still gives you some feel because this is fine work believe it or not at the end of the
day
Someone was going to chime in go ahead. Someone was going to ask something. They're just partially there's yeah
Curious what temperature sand people have found works the best with the schedule 80
I found that usually in the 370 range
369 works best for me at my altitude in Tucson in the summer and fall in the winter
I'm sorry in the winter in the summer. It's a little cooler. So
370 is a good working anything above 350 but less than 375
Now you'll never be if you pour the sand some people say use 400 degrees that will distort the pipe
It'll make it too soft and it'll make it'll leave it'll get to the point where if you dump the sand out
You stuck a bore scope, you know when those little micro cameras inside you'll see little pieces burned into the plastic inside
too hot
So the way you're going to perform your bend is with your hot sand inside holding the dimensionality, right?
So the pipe doesn't crush when you're bending it. It offers the softening
That's not absolutely necessary to make the pipe mobile
But you must progress as you start bending it along with a heat gun externally
you could use if you know how to how to
Jerry rig a blow dryer to remove the I
Wouldn't suggest it to make a blow dryer way hotter than it should be and your girlfriend burns her scalp, right?
Well, whatever don't don't do that. If you if you know how to like what would you call it hot wire a blow dryer?
No pun intended. So it gets really really hot. Go ahead or just you can get it. Heatguns are cheap
I mean like the one I have is at the top of the line Harbor Freight when it was $8 with a coupon
I think they're $20 now
High and low settings do help
Now I think what would be the ultimate help and almost too much
Spoon feeding would beat a short video
Set up two cameras and edit it, you know left and right
And actually film myself doing it from start to finish
You know pouring the sand in
Working the pipe heating it bending it around putting the clamps on dumping the sand out and running it at one and a half speed
I've timed myself the entire bend and all that process about 12 to 15 minutes tops
You know the entire process and you imagine that because if it took longer than 12 to 15 minutes, what happens to hot sand?
Right. It's not hot sand anymore. Is it you have to shake around the sand too when you're
Using the thermometer one spot might be hotter than the other. Oh, you should be stirring it. Yeah, absolutely
And the sand remember I have magnetite in it, which is just an unfair advantage. It stays much hotter, you know
And also I like what the magnetite does to the plastic I have
You should add it yeah, you'll you could play around with the plastic get some strong solvent like acetone rub it on PVC
What happens it gets real sticky. It starts dissolving the PVC, right?
Go ahead and heat the PVC for 15 minutes in magnetite and then go back with the a stone watch what happens doesn't affect it
That comes in handy when you're using the glue to right
That's really works against you when you're using the glue because you want it to soften for the glue
That's why when you're using the glue you do want to prime it
You do want to prime the pipe I use just use acetone nail polish
Nothing nail polish remover that they sell for nails because that has oils and conditioners in it not dry out the ladies hands
You want you know industrial strength acetone from a hardware store or whatever? I got I use
Yeah or Sally's Beauty Supply
Um, they sell pure acetone, but you always want to
precondition
When you're using the glue
Preconditioned with a q-tip or a brush never asked for a stones flash point 70 degrees, right? It's boiling point
Sorry, it's like 60 45 degrees boiling point something ridiculously low
So you need to keep a soft cut, you know, don't leave the lid off of it
You know have a small rag or something that fits off
Don't don't rely on putting that threaded lid on and off make a simple plug for it while you're working with it
Pour it into a smaller container. You could also pour it into one of these little squeeze bottles, you know the ketchup
You know the yellow and red
Mustard and ketchup bottles they have in fast-food stores years ago
You just buy those at the dollar store get ones that are not cut at the top you cut it yourself
You'll find and you pour that on a rag constantly or a q-tip
Whenever you're going to use the
bonding cement the PVC bonding cement
You want to prime it with acetone first why?
It's less the but you'll get a much better bond because the bonding cement has acetone in it to eat away at the plastic a
little so it bonds and fuses
when the
You'd go direct with the bonding cement with no primer
There's something called primer. It's purple. It's really nasty. It's gonna look real ugly if you use that stuff, but use the acetone
It allows the bonding cement to retain more of its
Acetone, you know that the formula won't be compromised
It will you won't get fast drying
So if okay, there's another way to say it when you're ready to bond the PVC the schedule 80 pipe to itself or to a fitting
if you
Don't use any primer or acetone before you apply the gray cement
It dries too fast against the plastic and it does not bond as well
Pre-softening it with a little acetone is the way to go
Always and I've noticed this very much. I've I've broken the scalerator, you know
I've basically stuck a pipe inside the pipe and twisted and twisted with you know on the ground and I popped one and
I noticed that the side the ones that did not prime
We're able to break at the glue joint where the ones that were primed broke at the pipe
Right, so you always want to have that kind of integrity if you can the aluminum is a good like insulator
It's not gonna because I have a plastic piece
For the center that found and it's a five and an eighth. So I'm just gonna wrap aluminum around it
Is it but it's still melt that
wrap hard car
Wrap hard cardboard chipboard, you know, like shirt cardboard they call it. Yeah. Yeah around not the corrugated
Yeah until you get the size you want. Yeah
When you say aluminum, I mean
What aluminum what foil tape? No, that's not doesn't haven't it tears. It doesn't have integrity
Okay, you can't get enough tent if imagine no matter what you wrap with aluminum foil imagine
going around 200 times around a baked potato or a
Take a brick and go around a brick until you build up a quarter inch of foil and push on it with your finger
It's cushioning. It's still like a cushion. It's going to need some glue behind it and all that
So the thing chipboard is
Plenty dense enough. It's also shock absorbent. So if something gets tight you need to pull it off. It'll give a little
You know oak tag, you know, you know the illustration board you can get it at the dollar store, you know, that's the heavy
Illustration board comes it that's that's a cheap form of chipboard
That's the thickness that I recommend
You know the illustration board that they sell for children's crafts
Yeah, if you get too thick of a chipboard, it won't bend it won't bend even like there's some chipboards there, you know
Sixteenth of an inch eighth of an inch thick that will not bend around that radius that it's too too too stiff
Yeah
So you got to mind all these things again. I did all that right off the bat just thinking about it based on my experience
Well, I try to get out this strong hand around the magnet
You could it's very tricky because the magnets not tall enough remember the pipe is much taller than the magnet when it's laying down
You could get away strong hand here on the magnet, but remember to build a spacer underneath the magnet, right?
Just yeah. Yes Ivan put the magnet next to the pipe and you'll notice that your pipe is much higher
So build some spacers up. So where your magnet sits
With the spacer should be about the center of your pipe right next to it. You just measure everything, right?
What could happen if you're really strong arm it
Because the pipe is wider than the magnet and it's soft and you flex it around the magnet
Your magnet will not pop out. It'll get stuck in there
Because some of the plastic will form itself around the magnet. That's this has happened with a smaller one that I made and
It was straight enough. So now fuck it. I'm not gonna get in there where the Dremel will try to cut this thing out
I'm just gonna leave it. I'm not gonna reheat it either. It's good enough
Okay, so
Fortunately, I have not had any screw-ups at all because I've pre pre meditated and and is you know
Imagine you have an idea for a film, you know
You you think of the story and then you do a storyboard the first scene second scene third scene
So when you do this, it's like act 1 act 2 act 3 and then in act 1 you have scene 1 scene 2 scene 3
Run your mind through this when you build stuff no matter what it is
You know, that's what makes like someone who's a seasoned construction worker
Versus a DIY guy who hasn't built a shed or an extension to his house for the first time
He doesn't know what to expect because he doesn't experience the movie
Right the experienced guy. You'll see him show up at a job site. He starts doing these things are real quick
He's like, what's he doing that for and then you watch him and like two hours later go
Oh, I see why I put that there now
Right because he's seen that movie before so try to look at it as a movie
You're gonna film a movie of someone building. This is something that's never been built before
How's it gonna go down and then you get your stuff ready that way I call it running the program
What I've been in various
Ventures with people before I used to go is called the program
This is step one step two and then when they wouldn't follow us
They remember run the program run the book where you discussed it. This is follow your list
This is you know, remember didn't make any sense
Is it but it didn't make any sense when you talked about it and gave me the list
But now it makes so much more sense. So actually it's not I said, yes, I get it
But if you actually just sat down with the list and listen to what was said and actually just relaxed and went and saw it
Like a movie it would make more sense, right?
You don't have to physically experience something to experience
Everything that's necessary that needs to be done, right?
It's called virtual right do a virtual bend in a virtual build get everything ready
Because ultimately what you're doing here. This is what I'm doing. Let's say it this way from a self-centered point of view
I'm making these for people who are interested in exceptional water quality and also
Interested in acquiring a piece that is artfully made very well handcrafted
Right, that's that that's so this is not for everyone this but it's definitely for some people. So
if you find someone who's interested in superior water quality and getting a very something that is just made with care and
Artistic even if it's gonna be buried in the ground
You know put a viewing window on it, you know with an LED so you have your party
You can press or just actually have it, you know with a return so it's on display or whatever
When you have people interested in both those things you've got someone you know
You have a client for a lease and I also recommend leasing these by the way, I think I went over it
So if when these things develop to the point where they'd start doing amazing things
You might get approached and someone, you know, like a black SUV, you know men in black kind of thing
Might say George or Matt or Greek or whatever if this thing works like you say it's a you're dead man
How many of you sold you can honestly say I've never sold one because you never have
There are 90-year leases, right?
That's what I recommend by the way, you don't have to do that, but I'm suggesting that right anything else on the build jig
Not right now
Mm-hmm following photo. I'm gonna go. I'm outside here. I'm gonna go back into the office. So if we follow down to the next photo
I have the scalerator. I believe sitting in a flat jig
And if you follow down to the photo below that I believe it's the scalerator out off of the jig to see
It's a very very simple almost you'd call it like a flat template
What's important is that you have the hole in the center to accommodate the girth of the magnet the depth of the magnet?
Protruding right because it has a profile projection
That you cannot use
the previous jig for the purpose of this
next jig is
so that
The ends of the scalerator when it's done are true and in line
So when you cut into a section of pipe it will fit into that section true and in line
And I've learned this the hard way and you use this
When you're done done done done done with it, you know, whatever it when you're ready to when it's ready for
shipping or delivery right before install
you do this and the way you make that jig is you just cut a very simple profile as such and
You just put a straight piece of pipe
Just like you see on the very last picture
across and you glue four blocks of wood that will clear, you know the curves and all that and
That represents that straight piece of pipe represents what is in the field right now that you're going to cut into right?
That it's straight
So when you put your scalerator in there
It should fit very snug between those four blocks two on the left two on the right and if it doesn't which usually it won't
You start gently warming at least two inches away from the ends
Very remember there's no sand here. There's nothing
Gently warming and pushing with your clamps that you have in the four aforementioned pictures. Just take your time
Don't overheat it
To get the ends of the scaler to squeeze in between those four blocks and once they do
Remember, it's you have very high tolerances there
That when you're done and it's cooled you remove it when you do cut into your section of pipe in the field of wherever
It's going to do it. It will fit really nicely
That's the purpose of this final jig
What I showed here tonight is just the most helpful that I've
Had you know to produce so far other than the concept, you know in terms of like, okay
This is how this is what I'm using
right, this is what I'm using and
The final jig is going to make the install much easier and it's you could see these things are
Basically ghetto level construction, you know
These things are the first things that I've made and I have not had a need to rebuild them or remake them
These things were done like where I
Got up in the morning and I was like, you know, it's beautiful out today
I'm gonna make a scale orator jig because bending it by freehand is a bitch
So, let's see. What kind of scrap do I have and I don't know how to even have the right jigsaw blade
I'm gonna do it anyway, you know, and that's that's what you guys are seeing here, you know
While I'm still having my coffee and it's like hey Linda. I think I'm out of smokes. Can you give me a pack of smokes?
Yeah, okay, cool
This is like that kind of day, you know morning. Just throw it together
I know what I need done and I know how to make what I need
You know for it to have to satisfy that need and that's what these are
Very simple very coarse very rough, but they work
But the bottom line as you can even see I love bragging about how good the scale orator looks at least the aesthetic to me
That when you look at the finished scale orator, whoever does cannot imagine that this thing was made with some scrap wood
On a dirt floor and you know what? I mean
With cats jumping all over him, you know wanting his attention or whatever. So we're able to produce a
really high level of finish
That's something that is exceptionally performs exceptionally. Well, it's just some really really basic rudimentary stuff
Again I can't underscore how important the final jig is there because you do that again
after you've done your magnet fitting after you've done your all of your gluing and
supporting and
Right before shipping is when you do this
And if it's out, it doesn't if your scaler doesn't drop in nice and firm
You're gonna have to go back and heat never heat the very ends of the pipe of the scale orator that are going to accept
the finished
Couplings, however, whatever couplings
You use now in the future. We'll get into various couplings
I've invented a coupling a compression coupling that makes installation very easy
this is a segue now because the unions you have to you also when you cut in with unions you have to
employ quite a bit of precision because you're not going to be able to stretch the pipe if it's too far apart and if it's
And if it's if the unions are too close together, it's going to push the o-ring off. So
Unions look easy, but they're actually quite complex
So I've invented a compression fitting that fits over the pipe with a rubber
Gasket that grabs and works
I have one that I've been testing now for 11 years not a scale or a better compression fitting that I've come up with and that
Will be for future
Sonics if we continue down this road with you know developments and things like that
But for now, I feel like very satisfied that I've put out enough
To get enough whoever's listening to this
a starting position
and making these
Based on of course, whatever you want to invest in it, and I think I've shown to this point. It's absolutely minimum. I mean
Give you an example some of the scrap wood
It's like I'm driving down the street and I someone put out like a kitchen cabinet or a desk
You know and I'm like, oh that's a nice amount of wood
It's just particle board, but I'll probably use it for something and I just load it up and you know
This is like made from found wood
even you know
so
Nothing
Special to make it but once it's done you let you'll end up with something
That's a very very very very special and exclusive in the world
Anyway, I think that's all the wind I have for now unless someone else has any questions or anything they want to bring up or
Doesn't have to be a long one. The other audios have been over three hours or so. So
What say you guys and gals
Yeah
Great. Yeah
Yeah, so when you're installing it, I got what about the minimum my death like 36 inches like working space
Left and right whatever. What would I do? What I would I do a trench you mean like trenching?
Yeah, if you're gonna go into the ground
Yeah, let's run a movie on that. We've never trenched before. Let's say there's half the people here. I've never trenched before
Okay, might be might be like 90% never in trenched before
Think about it. It's what does it sound like you're basically digging a corridor or trench a ditch?
Yeah, you don't want to hit the pipe already
Yeah
You what you want to use is water you want to use plastic implements you want to go left and right that up and down
Water and a shop back to get down to your pipe. But once you perform the trench
It's loose dirt
So as you try to work on the pipe to any movement anytime you touch any side of the trench
Dirt's gonna fall and start filling your hole. You might have nice clean ends ready to go
You're cutting the pipe and dirt falls in again
What you're going to need is a bunch of drop cloths I use cardboard and cover the surrounding dirt
The ground and drop the cloths down the sidewall
Into the trench so you're not contacting
As much to it, but I'm noticed I'm making this my first comment first point
You don't want to be in contact with the dirt at all because it's loose. It's dirty
That's why we call it dirt, right? It falls around makes a mess
So once you make your trench you want to cover the areas with what well, whatever old sheets blankets
I like to use corrugated cardboard
Just some big sheets of corrugated cardboard. I just bend it like a 90-degree
Horizontal across the top of the ground and then a vertical piece that drops down
So I have a nice firm area if I bump it with a tool or my arm
I'm not making a more of a mess or having a collapse
Right, I like the cardboard better than a blanket now when you're going to trench
That's where you should have it professionally done
If you haven't done it before you're gonna do it and you don't want to break a pipe now
Here's the thing if you happen to break the pipe while you're trenching
Break it at least where you're gonna cut it off cut it out. I
mean
Add some humor, right?
Yeah, so yeah, so hopefully if you if you're fixing on breaking stuff, especially pipes that day
Just break it where you're gonna fit the scalerator in now. I see someone by the way
Yeah, that's a whole other discussion on trenching. That would be like, you know, how do you know?
You know, it's major and get into that. I don't have any special tips other than covering the area that's been uncovered
Uh
Yeah, well, I've trenched before but I was saying like at least get it deep enough to fit the scalerator in right?
Oh, of course. Yeah, and you have your the scalerator here
The typical one one inch is 8 by 12 8 on the short side 12 on the long side
Now
Can you comment on the marks in red on the screenshot what they are? Yeah, those are tabs
Those I call them tiger claws. Those are just tabs to hold the magnet in place a little extra support
And I just made them decorative. They're at 36 degrees apart
Albert
Just something to help the magnet because if there's any
stress
You'll notice that there's four of them on each side
If the magnet gets pushed or stressed thermal stress expansion, I want something else holding it in place
And
I just came up with that that there should be triangular and 36 degrees apart 36 degrees is an important number an important angle
It's in your tabs are out. It's in the body. The tabs are also glued
Yes, they're glued on the back. Yes, you can glue them on with cryo
Acrylic glue which is crazy glue. I use both crazy glue ends and the solvent gray glue
Yeah, and they're pretty tough whenever you start making these by the way, let's say just the tabs
go ahead and cut a tab and get a scrap piece of pipe and glue it on and
The next day come back and break it off. So you have a feeling of how strong it is comes off really easy
You say oh, that's not really doing anything, right?
But if you try to break it off and the tab itself breaks, they go. Oh, that's pretty strong
Right. So guess what?
Whenever you build stuff you want to test it, especially at this, you know juncture
You know, this is something new
You want to know how strong it is, right? So to build confidence because I one of the first ones I made
Without I think I posted a picture. I didn't like it was the improperly installed the tabs fell off
Person had it in their back. You said they I said all the tabs are not there
I send it back put the tabs in center and as the magnet hasn't moved
I said how the tabs fall so I had in the back of my pickup truck for about a month and 30 degree weather. Oh
I didn't ask if the pickup truck was as empty as his head or
Was the pickup truck full of stuff and wedged in between something but you know what? I mean? I just left that alone. So
But yeah, I'm glad you asked about the tabs. You're looking
Those tabs could be anything if you look at the tabs, for example on the what I'll do here
I'll do a screenshot of another one where the tabs are slightly different if that would help Albert
Let's bring up another pick
Here
This is a different one, let's just do a copy. I'll do a quick
close-up screenshot of some different tabs
Okay, it's pretty close, okay
Let's do this I'll do a screenshot of some different tabs
And while I'm doing that anything else guys or gals
about
About this deal we're talking about tonight. This is basically formative forming the
Forming the unit jig process
here is a close-up of
Another scalerator with a different shape on the tabs
Copy that drop it in right now
Close-up. There we go
You know, you think you guys got that yeah, no, it's got a little speck of dust on there
But it's a close-up of that unit. Okay. See that the tabs are a little different there. You got a bit more of a close-up
Yeah
And you can see the the work on it. It doesn't look like you made it in your backyard with scrap wood jigs and
You know what? I mean?
So
Six tabs could be anything they could go all around, you know, you can have one tab every 60 degrees
They don't have to have a fancy cut
I've made a fancy
PVC cutter that it cuts at different angles and all that stuff
I mean, you know we could do I can do ten eight-hour calls on all the various
Things that we can do all the various ways we can make this all the little nuances when bending tabs
Finishing gilding the spacer the box, you know, I mean, it's a tremendous amount
But it only helps those that are doing it or at that stage. So
Let's say you guys haven't even bent a piece yet, you know talking anything beyond making the jig or having a jig is
It's relevant, but it's going to be way down in the history list later
It's best to talk about things that are relevant
Right. So the finishing is a big deal
There's nothing like walking into let's say a pool supply place and saying hey, would you guys be interested in something?
That is flow through no consumables that eliminates hard water problems
Do you have clients complaining about hard water? And would they be interested in something that eliminates that? No, I
Yeah, absolutely bring it in. So I bring in the two cases
Oh put them on the counter and when I open the cases like you don't know what you know
What's this guy these good cases look pretty serious, right?
Soon as I open open the cases and you see they have customers in the store
The work is what do you what are they? What do you hear when the case opens?
Right
Not cool, how does that make you feel you make something you present it to someone for the first time and their reaction is Wow
Right now, where do you start? What kind of footing does that start you off on?
right
you see
That's why I've made them on such a level of finish because that part is over with the impression
You know, they say you never have a second chance to a first impression the first impression is Wow
How do you think the rest of it's going to go right no matter how skeptical they are
That whoo. Ha Wow
Is gonna be you know stuck?
that's what they remember it's gonna leave a certain taste in their mouth, but you can then continue to feed and
The only way you can create that is with integrity and stuff that really not just looks good
But it's good because if it just if it's just lipsticks and mascara
Guess what that comes off easy. So he has to have integrity
That's why I use the you know, the Pelican case knock, you know, the the Harbor Freight Pelican case knockoffs
Pelican cases are the standard, you know, they're 130 140 dollars and up Harbor Freight hasn't for a 30 or 40 bucks
Sometimes they're on sale for 20
so
And if I didn't have the heart, you know, if I had to get a Pelican and get a Pelican
But these things don't cost that much to make
But they command a very high cost think about a Patek Philippe
You know even with the movements, you know, the expensive watches. It's about five dollars worth of stainless steel, but they're 30 grand
Right. It's all about the labor. This is very well understood
In society
If you took a
1988 Toyota Corolla to the crusher and melted it and he took a brand new Rolls-Royce Phantom and crushed it. What would be the difference?
Maybe 2,000 pounds, right? So
So again, this is
You can see this is not just the idea
It's there's a mindset about
Doing things that are finer and better, right?
again
When you present this to someone in the case and it has that level of finish and you open it in a room of strangers
Stranger to you and they're strangers to each other and they all
in
Synchronous synchronously go. Wow. I think you're on a good foot. You're in a good start
and that's ultimately
Where this begins when it showed how it begins when it's shown in public any other notes or any other questions?
anything else
Otherwise, we'll just end it here
And the recording shortly. I hope this is helpful. And I think we'll call this the last installment of phase one of the scalerator and
I think we're gonna nuke this group and give it 72 hours in three days. So it'll be
You'll have Tuesday night Wednesday night. So Thursday morning. We're gonna nuke this
So get whatever you can off of it, you know, I mean by nuking it
I think Bruce you got another term for it deletion
Take it off. Yes, take it off the internet. Yeah, just for posterity's sake. This is just for whoever showed up here and
Not as a historical, you know archive if that makes sense, but feel free to archive whatever you like. Yeah. Yeah, this is a
once-in-a-lifetime thing, right so
And if we have to go over anything here, I have all the photographs if there's any questions regarding anything
you know, I
have it memorized and
Otherwise, yeah build scalerators man. Make a make a ruckus make some noise
Clean up some water get some get some people smiling. They'll be your friends for a long time
I saw people messaging me every week. Thank you
Who's this? Oh, thank you for the amazing water. It's like oh, oh you oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Welcome. I'm glad you're still enjoying it. Thanks for the feedback, right? It's great
wonderful feeling
So with that said I'm gonna stop the recording and the
All and all that good stuff, but just the final questions or anything
You're welcome, thank you for for coming and doing all that stuff so
Let's stop recording. All right
Thank you, welcome everyone, bye-bye. Thank you