[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening. This is the Greek Speak
live stream and podcast featuring the Archon in the Greek. I'm the Archon creator of
greekspeak.com, my co-host and originator of the name of the website. The Greek will be joining
me shortly but prior to that I want to thank everyone for tuning into this introductory
episode where the Greek and I will be laying out our intentions for the stream and the scope of
our discussions during the first season. We're going to be tackling a range of subjects,
some of which have already been broached in articles on the website and we're aiming to complement
those writings with some exposition of similar things and I hope that we succeed in making
these talks as thought-provoking and insightful as possible and hopefully we'll be able to
arrive at some conclusions rather than conjecture or open-ended interpretations. So I hope you find
it to be an enjoyable listen. GreekSpeak.com has no political religious or commercial affiliations and
is completely funded and managed by myself at this point in time. The podcasts will be available
to download in the Greek Speak Media tab menu on the website's homepage so thank you once again
for tuning in and I hope that you enjoy this introductory episode.
So Greek, are you there? Greetings yes, hello. Hi, I'll go things.
Okay, going well. This is the first time around and we're going to give it a go and see how things
work out and hopefully we'll have an audience that will grasp what we're saying and be able to use
it as well. You have done a few of these in the past which are quite spread out across different
lesser-known media outlets and I don't think that I'm remiss to say that none of them more particularly
structured from mass consumption, would you say? I would say no, not at all. Like I said,
in the past, if anyone's heard any Greek Speak, I've always introduced the Greek as someone who's
just visiting here taking notes. So the aspect of Greek Speak is, you know, why aren't these things
being said, why aren't they being considered? Because guess what, they're extremely obvious and I
leave out the extreme part and then I should say there are most things are quite obvious to anyone
that has any form of perception, you know, topically. And again, these are obvious points. I never
like to make references to things that are hard to access. It's good to bring up reference materials,
it's good to bring up, you know, things that have been memorialized, I like to bring up, you know,
the memorialized information as a reference. Memorialized just means that it's been in the record
or official or unofficial either way. And having people just look at things and, you know,
there's a lot of complaining and there's a lot of bickering and there's a lot of wondering and that's
completely unnecessary. So again, bringing up a topic and then bringing up the points
supporting the topic regarding the obvious. And I think as we go along with more sonic events,
I like to call them sonic events, what have you, there could be podcasts and streams, but I would say,
again, whoever is listening will notice that many of the underpinning notions and supporting
information is going to be pretty clear. Okay, yeah, as far as things that are obvious, I do think
that as we progress, we'll be defining exactly what the scope of that is because people find that,
you know, what's obvious should be self-evident, but because certain things are not self-evident to
them, then therefore they're not obvious, so we must be talking about something else. But I think
we'll get to that in time. Well, if there's a sober mindset and in quotations, you know, if you're not,
if you don't have a sober mindset or a sane mindset, I don't think there's a hammer big enough to
drive at home, so. Okay, yes, and we'll also get to the topic of mindset, which is a subject in and
of itself, but this is going to be episode zero of what will be a series of streams, which will
collectively be called the Greekspeak podcasts when they're made available for download. So I think
it's a good idea to start with some general introduction of who we are and what the purview of our
talks will be so that people aren't taken aback by the content or the tone and have a fair idea
of what to expect. So I'm going under the name, the Archon and the creator of the website and
originator of the streaming project, which is named after a term first thrown out by the Greeks
some years ago when he was making appearances elsewhere. I had become a listener by chance and was
prompted to take up my own line of study after hearing what the Greek had to say on various matters,
and one of the fruitions of that is now greekspeak.com. I run the site at my leisure and my hopes
for this podcast and stream is to see whether there are segments of the public that are responsive
to not only the kind of subject matter we're going to discuss, but the mindset that it imparts also.
I think the concept of having a proper mindset or mentality is a central theme within Greekspeak,
more so than examining any single piece of information about a subject because frankly much of
what we're going to discuss can be found online already, but it's not uncommon for people to be
selective about the information that they accept. So I accept that the content on greekspeak.com will
have varying degrees of interest from the public based on whatever mindset a person has, which is
fine, but regardless of whatever topics are presented on the site, my hope is that it will not only
impart the information, but also a new way of looking at things. So that's it for me. How about you,
greek? Oh, basically a surface dwelling earth inhabitant that's just taking notes and doing a lot of
telling it seems. That's pretty much the end of it. I think again, like I always say, I'm just
happy to be here with everyone else, whoever everyone is, and just like to bring up some points that
might, I don't like to use the words help anyone or make anyone better or whatever because that's
really up to them, but bring up things that you notice, that things that can be noticed that are
in contrast to again, we'll bring up the term that the current mindset to be contrasting and
complementary, which actually might ultimately end up with the eviction of the thoughts that most
people have about things. I would garner from that and from our past talks that you're more in
the habit of talking at people than with them per se. Why does that end up being more common
than the other? Well, the thing is, when you're reading an introduction or when an introduction is
being made, it's basically a one-sided projection. And the introduction could be to let's say something
called a dialogue, just like we had an introduction here, and I believe that everything that is being
discussed under the purview of Greek speak is an introduction because to really get into anything,
all of its ultimate details is requires almost most people might consider an infinite amount of time
on any subject. So basically almost everything that I discuss publicly that we're using that term
in quotes is an introduction, even if it's an hour long. Because the ultimately then the dialogue,
I think, will begin when certain things are established. And it doesn't seem like there has been much,
should we use the term progress? What is progress? Within the human mindset or the human condition,
and there won't be, which we probably cover in other sonic events or extremes, and give the reasons
why as well. Yeah, so speaking at people is interesting because I think I've also brought up, there's
a social element that if anyone does public speaking, and you're looking into the eyes of the audience,
you very often they're wondering, you know, when is he going to shut up so I can say what I want to
say, right? Yes, that is common. A second thing we could do is to delineate how the term Greek speak
should be understood. It's a term that you used to loosely dub a certain kind of talk some years back,
and I've run with it to create this website as my own enterprise. My take is that it's a catch all
term for a kind of rhetoric encompassing anything from critical theory to natural philosophy or
scientific exposition and even common sense, which in parts are more objective understanding of
reality. What is your take on that term as the originator of it? Well, here's the interesting thing.
I like to say that I haven't originated anything. I merely packaging it in a sonic form and throwing
it at people and not necessarily see what sticks, but just tossing it out there so no one can say that
it's never been done. It sounds like an interesting endeavor. It's sort of like, if you look at even the
term Greek speak, that was originated by others. For example, I would have either private or public
conversations on the internet and people would say, "Here's the Greek, he goes by the Greek, and we're
going to have some Greek speak and a kind of stock." It just goes around, it's an organic thing.
I think most of the terms that I'll bring up people will, like a sonic event, for example,
well, what is a podcast? What is a stream? Well, it's an event and it's audible, so making it sonic.
So basically, just putting stuff together and having other people's input form the thing,
there's no convention or anything to Greek speak. There is no such thing. It is without a thing.
Right, so I think that by me running with it, it might end up becoming a thing, but I think the
contours of it will be fleshed out for everybody as the podcast progresses nonetheless.
There has been a reoccurring aspect to it, I would say, one which is central to its thrust, and
that is the idea that it's the kind of talk that is antagonistic to many prevailing conventions or
mainstream world views. The idea is that there exists this kind of communication that many people
don't want to hear or engage with because of how it sets them at odds with the world that they live in
and their understanding of that world in themselves. So, I mean, that's nothing new because there's always
been some kind of alternative media or independent journalism or even secret societies that operate
alongside the mainstream with their own view of things, but Greek speak, I think, you might say,
does not place itself alongside the fringe movements of the world, correct?
Sure, not at all. Yeah. Well, what are the fringe movements? I think they're just fringe movements
because they're labeled as such. I think we in the future, we might discuss more of the core reality
of the quote-unquote communities. You know, you have the mainstream, you have the alternative,
the fringe, right? They're called communities in some sense or groups. It's not really as
we're being told because ultimately there's an underlying culture that has to be considered,
you know, for example, I think it's been brought up in the past if you visited a culture of
or a society of headhunters, they would have a different worldview than, for example, a technocratic
or technological society that sort of forbids cannibalism and headhunting, right? Which one is right?
Which one is wrong? You know, for example, on aquatic society versus a desert society, you know,
which one is right? Which one is wrong? So I think transcending the culture is the aspect of
having a successful, I don't know, what would you say? Again, communication of the purpose of
communicating, of speaking. Otherwise, why critique something if it's not going to be objective?
See, the objective reality of various societies is the reality that you're a surface dwelling
earth inhabitant and you're in an anthropomorphic figure that interacts with your environment.
And that's the basic starting point. The reason I bring it up is because when people see things
as unconventional, they do tend to sideline it. So there if you have the mainstream that people
generally accept as being legitimate and the alternative stuff and the fringe stuff around it,
which unfortunately comes with also a sense of it being not worthy of your attention. Once it gets
into that alternative label and I wouldn't say that Greeks speak necessarily, strives to be that
or that this podcast strives to be that. I think the alternative media is, you know, a discrete
thing unto itself that I don't think that we're trying to necessarily stand next to.
Well, how about instead of saying alternative, mainstream, view it from a qualitative point of view.
It's easy to understand the qualitative, qualitative nature of things. Let's say regarding food,
is it of high quality or is it of low quality, right? You'd have like hot cuisine,
well-prepared food, well-sourced ingredients and then you have what's called junk food,
right, which is not well-prepared and not well-sourced ingredients. Which one do you think is more
popular on the outset and on the onset, the junk food, right? So I view things as being,
are they quality, you know, how are they judged? I use that word, judge, yes, I mean discern from a
qualitative point of view. So you can study anything, whether it's academic, theocratic, political,
physiological, you know, regarding natural philosophy, which is basically science. Any aspect that
humans can be involved in or people can be involved in from a qualitative point of view.
So let's just take a point that you've been bringing up the alternative or fringe or mainstream
for the contrast, perhaps someone who has more of a mainstream outlook,
outlook meaning to accept information and sources versus the sources from the alternative
or the fringe. The thing is, let's just put that aside and look at the quality. It doesn't matter
what it's considered, I think, I think at the end of the day, you're going to settle,
always people will always settle better. This is again altruistic with a higher quality input.
And it just doesn't seem to be the way things are. I mean, just look at the, you know, again,
the food aspect, right? So, you know, so again, when you're looking at mainstream, whether it's on
the receiving end or the projecting end, you know, mainstream, let's say, would be the mainstream media,
academia, religions, whatever institutions, or you're looking at the alternative or fringe,
what is the quality of what they're serving? Their patrons or listeners or whatever. And look at
it strictly from that point of view, first. Well, to that, I guess if you're going to make a qualitative
assessment, you do need a reference because if you, for example, to go with the food thing,
if you've only eaten junk food your whole life and you don't know what anything else tastes like,
then it becomes hard to evaluate the quality of it. You know, I've met children who will tell me
that McDonald's is good for you because they're 12 years old and they don't know anything else,
and I ran into them when they were coming out of the store with their lunch. So, if somebody,
you know, lacks the discernment to make a qualitative assessment because the subject matter is so
unfamiliar, then they're caught in a bit of a weird place. At best, for some people, Greek speak is a
kind of pondrable entertainment by a, you know, well-spoken character in the form of the Greek.
So it might be interesting, but it's soon forgotten among the more pressing actualities of life, no?
Yeah, again, that could be qualitative in a sense, like, let's just go a little further from the,
with the junk food aspect, and let's say you were considering the culture of these children.
The reason they consider it such is because of their culture, if you were to go to, let's say,
a rural place in Asia, they would not consider that to be, you know, the food that they should have,
and if you want to even contrast it more, if you were to visit a society that was cannibalistic,
they wouldn't view it as such again either, right? And then you have, for example,
theocratic societies that have certain food laws and restrictions, and they would view things
differently again. Like, for example, in India, I think you mentioned McDonald's, they're
predominantly based on beef patties, right? Hamburgers, where somewhere parts of India would not be
accepted due to the Hindu culture. So again, it's best to focus on the qualitative aspect of
transcends those cultures because whether you're a cannibal or a Hindu or a westerner that eats,
you know, junk food, your liver is your kidneys and most of the things in your bodies based on
type or interchangeable. So there is an inherent aspect of quality affecting you, right? So we try
to transcend that. And of course, in the future, when we do more of these sonic events, when we
go cross subjects, let's say regarding what the people call science or what their theocratic
leanings are, religion or other cultural aspects, it might sound critical, like you said, to the mainstream
year, you know, one that's culture towards that, but it will be undeniable that it actually is part
of the undercurrent of what they like or don't like and it's sort of irrefutable. Like, you know,
for example, if you tell anyone, let's say, Santa Claus doesn't exist, no one will refuse that. I
mean, Sans, the children that are deceived into thinking that, right? No one will deny that Santa
Claus doesn't exist or what's Santa, what size, if you see a serious debate over Santa Claus's shoe
size, it'll be dismissed as not being can't be serious, right? But yet people celebrate them as they're
in the most Western societies as their chief deity, right? So, I don't know, that sounds harsh and
critical, but it's actually true because you look at what they say, what they do, not what they say.
So again, when we bring up the different subjects, we're going to go into the qualitative aspect,
like, for example, factor fiction, one can say that something that is factual takes president over
something that is fiction. And again, to be sort of on the outset critical, you'll look at any culture
and you'll see that many aspects of what they believe in or function with is fictional, whether it's a
legal fiction, you know, regarding matters of law, whether it's religious fiction, medical fiction,
science fiction, and I don't mean science fiction as the entertainment venue, but actually what they're
being told is science is actually mostly based on fiction, not because it's an outside criticism,
but it's actually recorded and memorialized in their own official documents as such.
So, then eventually you'll see that we're going to be basically speaking about the earth-based
society with its different cultures that is basically insane. And that's basically the moral of the story.
You're surrounded with crazy people, and of course, anyone that has just the mainstream mindset
right now might say, well, that's crazy, that's not for me. Well, you know, that's again, that's an
interesting part of what I might call filtering, right? You know, there's an ancient saying, a friend
to all as a friend to none, right? So, are you trying to please everyone or look for approval for
everyone or you just have to say what has to be said? And I think the latter part, it ends up with
unfavorable results in the mass mindset. Well, in terms of society, let's take a look at that,
because to lay out some key themes that will underlie future discussions, I think,
would be helpful. So, the basis for a lot of Greek speak is a kind of diagnosis of a universal
condition that has been fallen human societies all over the world, which no one is exempt from,
except that each person is affected to it by a different degree. So, we want, in some way,
to sum up that state. And the question I put to you is, by way of an analogy that you've used in
the past and kind of touched on here, which is that if you were a dispassionate outside observer of
this world, say an alien from another planet on a reconnaissance mission, what is the report that
could be given about how human society is currently constituted and operated? Well, that's a,
is that a question or a statement? I think it's more of a statement because that can only be followed
through by hours and hours and hours of discussion or presentation, or quote-unquote talking at people.
But I think one thing which might have been the theme of today's stream, in some respect, is
what I call cosmic censorship, right? Is that something we might want to get into or?
Yeah, I don't mind a section of that briefly. Well, I think is one thing if you were visiting this
planet and making a report back, the report back would probably go thusfully, you'd say that no one
is paying any attention as a group, as a whole, with very little, very little exception to that.
And in that sense, paying attention to what's specifically because clearly things function in the
sense that there is, you know, a forward movement of some kind and activity going on all over the place.
I'd call it their activities or wrote at this point, meaning that they just just have a habit and
they do what they do because they've become accustomed to it. How many times have you heard, like,
most of cliche, "Well, I don't know, I just work here." Or, "I was just following orders."
Or, that's the way it's always been done. Well, that's what I believe, and I'm entitled to it, right?
The worst thing I've ever heard is, "I will defend to the death, you're right to say it." And I'm like,
"Well, be careful of saying things like that because someone might accommodate you."
So, I mean, how many times have you heard all of these things that are borderline cliche? I mean,
actually, they are clichés. And that is the norm, right? This is the way we do things. This is the
way it's always been done. I've only work here. I was only following orders. All right? And then you have
the spectrum, that's the central spectrum, then you have left or right of that or up and down of that,
the more extremist vocalization, which is, "How dare you insult, my belief? How dare
you insult, right? Who are you, you know, to say that, right?" And on the other, more mild,
here, let's say, still respect it to the same framework, the apathetic. Well, I don't care. It really
does it matter what you believe, you see? Perhaps we can look at some concrete examples, even though I'm
sure things come to people's minds because it's quite common what you're talking about.
Well, a concrete example is even setting things in concrete. Once concrete is poured, by the way,
and set, it's not easily moved. So it is, in a sense, everything we just mentioned is part of the
concrete pour, you know? You know, concrete is very malleable. It's actually a fluid while it's
being worked. And once it's cast and set, it's very difficult to remove or change. So in a sense,
this is a good concrete analogy, even though there's not much there. When people say all those things
that we just, I just brought up, there's really not much there. It's just fluff, let's say, right? Again,
I would suggest that there are people, maybe not part of the multitude, that have had knowing
questions or knowing thoughts regarding what we just brought up. Why are things the way they are
in the apathy? Let's just say on one end, there's the apathy on the other end, there's the
aggressive aspect of it. And then there's the central aspect of it, which is, well, this is the way
it's always been done. I just work here. I'm just following orders. And this is the way we do things.
And then you have the more passive, I don't care. And then the more aggressive, how dare you?
Aspect of that. And that is pretty much any subject. For example, in the medical society,
there's a lot of discussion regarding how the human body should be treated or dealt with from
a medical perspective. And anyone and everyone always encounters, if you're pursuing what's
called alternative healing methods, which actually if you understand the concept of the way the
standard medical industry works, that is an alternative. It's not the way it should be done. But
nonetheless, they always ask, well, who are you to discuss medical methodologies? Are you a
doctor? Where did you get your degree? So there's the of the plausibility. If you're going to discuss,
let's say, theological or religious concepts, where did you get your degree in theology? Are you a
priest? Are you a rabbi? So you have all of these other systems around the systems. Actually,
things that people say again, that support, that mindset that no one is paying any attention,
and they're just doing things because they're on autopilot or they're wrote, you see. And this, of
course, is the norm of the planet. So you can actually progress forward if we're going to do more
of these streams and say, well, then the Greek speak is actually hopeless then. Well, not really,
because again, there are people that have annoying questions and thoughts regarding why things are
the way they are. And then I guess is the benefit of understanding what's being said here.
In all of this, I would like to acknowledge that there will be some or could be some skepticism
that some people will receive, you know, these kinds of claims and assertions with because for
a person to accept what you're saying right now on face value means that they have to redefine
their understanding of the world at a level that involves some discomfort to, you know, the way
that they live their lives. So how does somebody reconcile the lifelong mainstream perception that
they've had with the claims of Greek speak when the mainstream perceptions have the force of
society or world governments or mass media and plausible deniability on their side?
They don't have to redefine it. They just have to define it because right now they lack definition.
They have no definition. It's like the blob, right? The culture itself is the container
and everything and everyone within it takes the shape of its container. So they can't define the
shape of the container. I think just again, go back and see what's been memorialized about the subject,
any subject and you'll see it's a very deep contrast to what people believe about that subject
and how they function in it. And then here's the ultra, the ultra esoteric, mysterious aspect is
that when you see the contrast of how people function and think versus the real reality of what
these things really are, one has to wonder it's a mystery how anything is getting done.
In other words, if you see what the medical industry is doing or the food industry or the political
industry or the religious industry or any aspect of human involvement, based on what the reality of
those things are, there shouldn't be anyone here. There should be complete chaos. But there isn't.
So there's another underpinning a reality to it. One might call it the non-physical side, I believe,
has a strong influence on it. Also Tesla, by the way, Nikola Tesla, which is not mainstream, but
if you like using things that are electrical and electronic, he's one of the main people to credit.
He said that when man starts researching the non-physical aspects of reality, that's when he will
make more progress in a year than he has ever before in any scientific field. So again, when you talk
about things that are not physical, like thoughts and let's say many things that are not that do
influence the physical world, are seem to be infinite because they can't be quantified.
And I think that scares a lot of people. But again, just to go back to what you had asked, I think just
what one can walk away with after listening to Greek speak is that is based on definition. One of the
earlier things that I used to do years ago, and Greek speak when I was being interviewed or speaking
publicly or even privately is bring up the notion of words, what words mean. Like, etymology is very
different than a dictionary. Dictionary just is how to pronounce the words or all the subjects can sound
uniform. That's why when you look up a word in a dictionary, it shows you the phonetic spelling first.
Where etymology would be the root meaning of the word. So I used to bring up word concepts,
and a lot of people actually discovered the word nice, for example, is not a very quote-unquote
nice word, right, for the word academic or on and on and on. So again, bringing up definitions,
for example, you go to back, I brought up medicine a few times, like people are always concerned
about viruses, right? Where years ago was about hygiene. Well, if you actually look up the history
and what's been what is really known about viruses, it's part of the field of known as toxicology,
and it has to do with the liver. It's not something that you get when someone sneezes.
So, you know, and again, I brought up the Santa Claus aspect, you know, how can he be a chief deity
when everyone admits that he's a fiction? Right, and we go on and on and on and on.
So basically just define the thing and then hold it up, and some people might feel like a victim when
you do that, right? When you criticize any aspect of society, just by they view it as a criticism
because you're defining it, they might consider themselves a victim, like you're gesticulating
something towards them to offend them. And then you have the other ones that are like, well, thank
you for that because now it makes sense. You'll hear that often once definitions are brought up,
what things are, and it's more than just a consensus reality because we agree on it. It's that,
no, there's a level beyond that, which is very simple. But once you bring that up, then a lot of
people that do appreciate the definition of things, they will say, well, thank you. That makes things
more clearly, and now things make more sense is a very common. So again, as this
Greek speak, I believe is geared towards more of the quote unquote sensible person.
There is, of course, a very popular strain of thought that is currently circulating where
they say the definitions do not matter because that is to put a constraint on an understanding of
things, whereas to go with a purely subjective outlook where your feelings are going to determine
which direction you're going to take is more reliable. Well, they say that until things
break down completely, and then they say we have to go back to look at the definitions we shouldn't
have taken that route. Again, with the medical, a very simple way to look at that is pharmaceuticals.
I think it's over 80% of commercial pharmaceuticals are banned after about a decade because they're
deemed dangerous, but when they're introduced into society, they don't look at the definition or what
the composition of these things are. They just look at the advertised benefit, and then after a decade
of suffering, maladies, and side effects, they say we should ban it. Because why? Because it just
pharmaceutical morph into something dangerous, or is it always dangerous by definition?
During the course of Greek speak, people will arrive at a number of crossroads, I think. A person could
on one hand take the left fork in the road and reject what we're putting forth here and take it as
somewhat curious talk, but ultimately benign and purely subjective. Or on the other hand, they could
take the right fork in the road and acknowledge that what's being said is an indication of things
that they've already suspected on their own, and so they could continue to listen in hopes of
working those things out. And we know what happens if a person takes the left fork and discards,
the subject matter, their life continues on as it was before. But my question is what happens if
they take the right fork and alter their convictions? How is Greek speak ultimately useful to someone
who recognizes it as something important, even though they're still bound by the constraints of
their circumstances? Well, I think you just answered it there. Are you seeking something that's
going to add clarity or do you just want to go on with how you've been? That's fine. And when I say,
go on, how you've been because the great majority are pretty much within that category.
You know, they don't know why they're doing what they're doing, but you dropped out there for
about five or six seconds. I think you're asking, is there a benefit or how do those that accept it
or understand it or use it? You know, what is the outcome? Well, you know, again, it's not going to
change much, but it'll add clarity to whoever is seeking it. That is a thing in itself, too,
of known. Is it better to have known or better to have not known? And again, these are not these
thoughts, these things that you'll hear in future streams as well as today are not based on conjecture,
opinion, or desire. And again, one thing I was thinking about while you were asking that is,
I personally am not seeking approval. So that's another, you know, in air quotes, a category.
You know, if you, for example, both if you look at mainstream and alternative, they're, guess what?
They're both seeking approval. And when you do that, you have to accommodate who you're
audiences and then nothing changes, you're stuck in a vicious cycle. Because if you've made an
objective determination that no one is paying any attention and what I mean by that specifically is
by the definition of things and what things really are as best you can define them. Right?
If you're, if you're going to accommodate people that are living in a fictional or, or, or plausible
reality, you can only accommodate them with more fiction and more plausibility. Right?
You see? So I, again, to go back earlier, like you were saying, the mainstream and alternative,
the purveyors of that kind of stuff are always accommodating their audience.
So in that, they're, and they're stuck in a dog chasing its tail scenario. And that's pretty obvious.
I mean, you can go, there's so many venues on what's called the internet or even in print. And
they're all accommodating the audience. Even if you look at, for example, classical texts that are
supposed to inform that's reader, let's say the biblical texts or other things like that, if you
look at an under-bridge version, they'll tell you in the introduction, they're accommodating
a certain mindset. It's not, it's not really how it is, you know, regarding the, the subject matter.
Again, again, with science, medicine, religion, politics, it's, it's very, very different.
You know, in other words, it, meaning what it is memorialized about those subjects is in high
contrast to what people think it is. And I think I've brought up in the past the concept of someone
called Gustav Leban, who wrote about the crowd, who was analyzing the phenomenon and how crowds
form. And I've distilled it down basically his work to say that in order to gather a large group
or a crowd with approval, any concept has to be simplified so they do accept the concept. But the
problem with that is that it becomes so oversimplified that it no longer represents its original form.
You know, it's the same thing like, for example, you could look at any political system,
what is shouted by the pundits or the politicians themselves or even in print is very different
than the political reality that is documented and memorialized in their codes and laws
and got in, in reference materials. Very, very different, right? The same thing with every religion.
Like I, I always say there's not a religion on the planet that knows anything that's in the text
that they let you subscribe to. Or they don't even do anything in it because it's again, you know,
with medicine, same thing, right? They definitely have everyone believing it's one thing,
but if you actually spend some time studying quote unquote medical documents, you'll see it's very
different. So there's a contrast between what's been memorialized again. If you bring up the concept
of visiting this planet taking notes and now we go into their records department first before I've
used society, I would view society. It would be very easy to view society as being insane
because everything they're doing is contrary to what's memorialized. Now if you were to view the way
they were doing things and then go look at what's been memorialized, you might question what's
being memorialized as not being true because everyone is almost acting in the opposite way
regarding these subjects. You see? So it depends on which approach you have first. If you're well
versed within the reference materials of any subject on human society, it's very easy to view them
as being clinically insane or just insane or not well on the onset very quickly. But again, if you're
well adapted to the way they do things and then look at their definitive material or what's been
memorialized, you might question that and say it doesn't matter because obviously everyone
also is doing the opposite. And the reason I repeated that is because that is a typical resultant
comment that you get from people. You know, if you were to not even... you must remain fundamental by
the way but not even in a conservative way, fundamental, it just means staying true to it, right? But in
conservative means that you're rigid and dogmatic. Regarding any subject, if you were to run into anyone
in any society on the planet right now and present them with the reference materials of what they're
engaged in, they will almost immediately dismiss it as not being true or not mattering. You see? Not
matter. They're not having a matter on what they're doing. And that seems to be the classic resultant
with what I call the surface dwelling, earth and habitant. We're maybe doing the opposite here. We're
going to bring up the notion of what the reference materials first and then putting it out, you see,
without looking for approval. Yes, I think that as time goes on, we'll definitely get into some
some details that are tangible that people can reference. For now though, since we're still in
the introductory episode, I think we'll look at one of the more central themes to Greek speak,
particularly on the website. One of the first things that people see when they visit
Greekspeak.com in the menu option is cosmic censorship. It's a central concept within Greek speak,
though by no means a new one, to human history. I think it's been spoken of in everything from ancient
Vedic writings of godism and Hinduism where it's sometimes called the Maya to modern portrayals,
perhaps most famously the matrix movies, but in countless others of course. So it's this idea that
there exists primarily two realities, one which is secondary and home to most human beings and
rules their perception and the other which is primary yet concealed and exerts a shaping
influence on the secondary one. So unless I'm wrong, cosmic censorship is an epithet that the
Greek is used quite often to describe a state of affairs and the force which maintains the separation
between these realities. Correct? Oh I'd say so. Only because it's easy to communicate that once
the listener understands what is being communicated regarding the term cosmic censorship.
I've had in the past some people message me and say, "Are you talking about this cosmic
censorship?" Meaning if you do a search on a browser they bring up some Einsteinian
quackery and relativism and things like that regarding singularities. That's not what I'm
talking about. I actually was not aware of that term until I had a fully functional way of expressing
it as cosmic censorship and later on finding out it was used by academia regarding the existence
of black holes or something like that. And the reason I put that term together is because censorship is
the act of censoring and cosmic meaning broadly placed and cosmos believe it or not is the Greek word
regarding the world. But it's been applied to mean beyond the world even if they're discussing
universal things, meaning physical or conceptual. So I figured putting the two words together
would be a good way of expressing how people just don't see things and how it's because of
another force that is implying that. And again I just want to restate that it has nothing to do
with the cosmic censorship that you find in academia which is regarding their whole
again science fiction. It's might sound critical at this point but in the future I might explain
away what people consider to be science is actually fictional. For those people that are curious
there's an article on the website you can read about that that would be introductory body of work.
How did you come to be made aware of cosmic censorship? Do you remember that or was it something that
came to you at a relatively early stage? Well in short I was seeking ancient texts regarding
matters of law. It's a big subject people tend to go away from it and I figured well why not start
from a historical point of view when was the concept of law first brought up. And for example if you
study something known as the biblical text you'll find a mosaic laws in there but then if you move
ahead and study what's called the prophet the prophets you'll find that there's a decree made
by the gods to close the eyes and shut the ears so they don't see and don't hear meaning they
meaning the people. Right so I started then again looking and looking and looking at ancient texts
and like you said the maya in certain traditions and there are many traditions that speak of the man
being blinded or shortsighted and I started seeing that is part of the reality of which people
how people function and it's a reality and it's part of their culture believe it or not.
So I saw that it is part of the reality and again it's a form of censorship and it's cosmic
and again cosmic again if one studies that it means just the world but it's also extended beyond that
and that's why I chose that term. And this you found evidence of this looking at various texts this
is something that you found in say eastern texts western texts esoteric things. Let's just say east
west north and south. And what's interesting about since we brought up ancient texts you don't know
where ancient texts are there dumb people or stupid people or I'd people with low IQ the people's
perception and ability is judged by how well they can see in here. It's an interesting western
phenomenon how certain people are called ignorant well ignorant means ignorant or just of lower
mental capacity. All right that's a psychological fiction I think. I mean these are things that can
be discussed in great depth later but I found that from a more neutral and objective
perspective it's a perception not what they call intelligence. Ultimately everyone has the same
as long as you're functionally there just like having a warehouse of computers with given
specifications on memory and function they're all with equal. It's the ones that have a better power
supply or a better operator that tend to see it perform better. So again I just want to bring up
the point that the the the concept of people being more intelligent than others again which we might
discuss if we ever go into the education system which the critique on that would be how well can
you repeat what you've been told. It's called a grading system how many times have you heard of
you know a valedictorian or this guy you know what makes this guy or gal smarter than everyone
else well they got a better score than everyone else. All right so that just means they could repeat
things back. So it's very what you know the interesting part about intelligence the definition I found
objective objectifying the definition of intelligence is how well can you perceive
eyes and ears again lack of cosmic censorship. It doesn't mean you'll be in a better place because
again in this given your culture if you don't adhere to the plausible normality you'll be ousted right.
Perception certainly matters we're going to get to that in later episodes there's an article on that
on the website for anyone that wants to take a look also but concerning cosmic censorship if it is
indeed a universal condition then it implies that the primary distinction between people who wish
to gain a better understanding or perception of reality is to what extent are you censored. So on
one hand you have people who are so censored that they don't know that the censorship exists and
then moving on from that you have varying degrees of clarity at different stages so what differentiates
the cluelessly censored person from someone who has gained enough realization to acknowledge the
censorship in the first place. That's really up to them because that gets really sticky let's say
you're the latter someone who bully you know who not let's not use the word bully but has
noticed that there is a censoring factor to human participation in reality right use that term
when you approach someone who is let's say doesn't acknowledge that they're being limited and
is quite happy with where they are there is going to be a violent opposition eventually and violent
doesn't mean physical violence either right it could be verbal or intentional violence which you
know is emotional so many times I've said if you notice someone is censored to the point where they
can't even acknowledge the censorship or can't even see anything evidentiary put in front of them
just walk away because it's not going to end up well right so this is part of the reality that's
why it's you know when people are confronted on a social point of view regarding why is there so
much war misery and starvation they just say well that's the way it is they don't want to address and
look at look at it deeper and then of course you'll have the alternative side well it's the
bankers doing it well not really right you know as there was war before there were bankers right true
so so you can say you know one thing or another but are you objectifying it in the answer to what I
see out in the world is no there is no objectification but again going back to the question
it's a very well it's self-answering in other words as again going back to the ancient history
the less censored the individual the sage is the wise men so off forth and so on you know
what did they do in regard to their culture and society and the masses did they
they interact openly and look for approval did they separate themselves go out and live in the
mountains or the wilderness and some secluded place they usually separated themselves they set
themselves apart and minimize contact and I know that doesn't sound like something I know this is
we're just starting the stream and this is the beginning I mean are we laying down the idea that
if you listen to Greek speak and try to put into effect in your life that you'll have to separate
yourself and not and not garner approval from others can I say yes right I would say be careful
yeah you'd have to be careful and also you're and this is both mainstream and alternative and you know
it does because they're this to me that again they're they're all the same everything out there is
the same until it's delineated from a qualitative perspective right so yeah but it doesn't mean
that it shouldn't be said and it doesn't mean that it can't be said so hence you know the Greek speak
mm-hmm I would say people recognize this understanding of the wise men that isolate themselves you know
I think for me the most tangible references Obi-Wan Kenobi and Star Wars you know he's living on
Tatooine somewhere not really interested in what's happening the rest of the the world so to speak
until it's this time to do something and you see that over and over again in various fictional
depictions but that is not to say necessarily that you should go live into Himalayas because you
might find that what you're trying to escape from is there also and it's it's it's it's by the way
is it misanthropic I'd say it is to a degree but is it only misanthropic meaning Greeks speak no
because ultimately you know people say all you need is love or God is loving you hear that
bantied around I dare them to define it and they can't but ultimately leads to that point because
you know ultimately and I'll just put it out there in any culture the true word or the word that
can be defined as love actually just means doing the right thing even if you don't feel like doing
it at the time mm-hmm so we'll define again the these it's about definition yeah I think some people
will intuitively recognize that definition of love and for some other people it's completely
foreign time will tell whether that bears out to be something reliable and I think we'll get into it
in later episodes but as far as the misanthropic stuff there is there's something that has to be
said for the fact that the world is not constituted the way that we're told that it is and whether you
want to see it as a hatred for the ways of the world or hatred of institutions or hatred of people
that's going to vary from my point I do have a certain disdain towards the way that things are done
and towards the forces that drive things I don't have any personal beef with people per se because
they're gonna do what they're gonna do anyway but you have to understand the way that things are
constituted otherwise you're just you're not being vigilant at all well the thing about having a
personal beef is difficult put the judgment of that aside and say objectify it because most
persons are the same yes they're told that they're all different and unique and wonderful but if you
delve down deeply they want everyone to be the same they meaning if you've ever dealt with anyone
in the legal society or the medical society or the religious society they tell people that openly
that they're free but when you deal with them on a personal basis they say well what are you
why are you coming to me with this you have to be just like everyone else right they always say
that in private so there's an dichotomy or schizophrenia there but to personally hate someone or
personally whatever is is in a sense foolish when you start objectifying things you'll see within
a culture high everyone is pretty much the same right not let's just use the word similar
not exactly the same they're not carbon copies even clones are not carbon copies by the way but
you can you can see that again you've heard of the term mass as we've used it right or the general
group right are they that implies a similarity or oneness all right again what would the obi
one can obi seclude himself or sequester himself if there was that much variety no it's them and me
right now it doesn't mean it has to be antagonistic or polemic it's just the reality we you know
is objectifying something in his reality something to be liked well that's to be determined later
determine what the reality is first determine if you want to personally hate someone
after you determine what an objectified why they are the way they are
let's wrap up this episode by talking about the idea of mindset i think you've touched on it once or twice
and i may have mentioned it also which is of course interchangeable with mentality that word
what has become trendy i think in the past 20 years or so is that when people
realize that the mainstream channels are perpetuating nonsense those people then turn to alternative
media and conspiracy theories as a source of information and they go down a rabbit hole of equally
fallacious nonsense we see that with youtube it's very easy to get caught in the youtube
recommendations sidebar for different things and you're on there for hours watching videos by people
who really you know may or may not be making sense so people overload on this new information but
ultimately they aren't much better off than they were before because they haven't switched out their
old mindset for a new one can you give a bit more exposition on that and what exactly is the
proper mindset would you say again you're going to need a reference something to stand on firm
footing good foundation how do you get that well what's the easiest way that anyone can access a firm
foundation on any subject or any matter is by defining it and again to go back and you brought up
the youtube venue i would say that you have university then you have alternative universities same
junk and it sounds like an overt criticism of it being low quality it is right you have met a
conventional medicine and then alternative medicine same junk right so and and what the reason
that might sound a little over critical at the moment you're just going to have to hold on
your hat and wait and we'll explain that and i will say that if you have discernment and there's
a level of discernment that you can bring to bear on how you interact with various fields of
knowledge then there isn't this sort of one-size-fits-all criticism of junk that you would
necessarily apply to that because of course you can get something profitable out of alternative medicine
or mainstream medicine but not if you don't have any discernment then you're just going to have to do
what you're told you know a lot of cherry picking uh i wouldn't say that there's anything worth
throwing out in in in wholesale also you know how i brought up qualitative and quantitative
earlier uh the numbers don't mean anything when you're looking at quality like for example
uh when i go out to the shops and for example i was looking for some kind of a anti-bug lotion right
a lot of mosquitoes around especially for children and uh the clerk at the shop said well this is
the one that everyone gets everyone buys and i'm like oh that's the one i don't want because
and she goes well why and i said well because have you met everyone do you see how people act on this
planet and she didn't quite understand it a rejection of what is commonly accepted is a healthy way
to objectifying reality by the way you know the patent office does that by the way when you apply
for a patent it's commonly rejected and then you have to go in and do what's called a defense
for it right you have to uh expound on why you deserve a patent if you patently reject what's been
commonly accepted wholesale again and then go back in with scrutiny and uh a diverse discernment
and diverse discernment meaning you have to know why it got that way too not just that it is that way
you'll be better off always understood and i think that as time goes on um that will prove itself out
as we continue to do these episodes okay i think that um we've covered the full gamut of
introductory topics that we need to that should do it for this episode unless there's something else
you want to touch on in conclusion no and not at all again in conclusion i would just say no one on
the planet is paying any attention with very few exception and uh paying attention was just uh
basically be defined as you do you understand what something is based on what's been memorialized as
it being defined as and then applying it properly because there is a proper way to do it um
i mean it doesn't mean like for example if you're working on a car engine you can't use kitchen
utensils to pry off a valve cover because you don't have a right tool but that is not the right tool
for it you see so in essence uh i think uh time will tell if we come back and do more of these which
i think we will will be more topical in nature and we'll expand on it and show how simple it is to
do what we've proposed yes that is correct anyone who listens to this should have
a good idea of what to expect moving forward the Greek speak podcast will continue to tackle this
kind of subject matter and um the articles will give an indication of the kinds of things will be
looking at so thank you to everyone on the live stream for tuning in there is no set date or day of
the week so to speak for when we're going to be doing these but to those who have subscribed to
receive information which can be done on the homepage you'll get emails about that about the time
in the day um with enough margin in advance and once the streams are done the podcast will be put up
on soundcloud where you can download them for free or you can download them through the website will
there'll be soundcloud widgets so um thank you greek for this episode i think it went well
okay you're welcome and uh they'll probably be more to come yes there will be so until next time
everybody and uh thank you for listening
[Music]
You
[BLANK_AUDIO]