[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening.
This is the Greek Speak live stream and podcast featuring the arcan in the Greek.
I'm the arcan, creativegreakspeak.com, joining me for episode one of this streaming series
is my co-host of the Greek, who will be with me in a minute.
Episode zero has been posted to the Greekspeak.com homepage beneath the subscription box where
it will remain indefinitely as a fixed feature.
The subsequent episodes will be posted in the newly created podcast page, which is accessible
through the media tab in the top right corner of the homepage.
GreekSpeak.com has no political, religious or commercial affiliation and is completely
funded and managed by myself at this point in time.
So that does it for my introduction.
I hope you enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
[Music]
Hi Greek, are you there?
Yes greetings, I'm here.
How are you doing?
All right, yeah, I think we have quite a bit to talk about today or speak on.
Yeah, since the introductory episode, since we did shed some light on the direction of the
series, I'd like to move forward with some in-depth discussions on the various subjects that
are covered on GreekSpeak.com.
I think we were quite spread out across various subjects last time, but if we could allocate
this one to the issue of cosmic censorship, I think that would be a good start.
I started off one of my articles on the website with the sentence that what is oddly absent
from most people's perception of life is the suspicion that there is something problematic
afoot with the general existence.
So we do know that at some level, everybody can detect the presence of malevolence in the
world around them, particularly of the painful kind.
What is less remarked about though is how people's perceptions essentially fall off a
cliff when it comes to contending with the more ambiguous yet more sophisticated forms
of malevolence that chip away at them in part because of what they subscribe to willingly.
What can be said about that reality, Greek?
Wow, okay, that's like a merry go round and it's like, what horse do you want to jump on,
right?
But essentially the two things that I picked out are the malevolent evil, let's say, and
the way that people exist with it, let's say, right?
I would say that would pretty much gather that thought into a very simple way to present it.
Just to start off, again, since we're discussing cosmic censorship, what is it and why do we say
it that way?
Well, I would suggest the word cosmic is originally a Greek origin, meaning the world, meaning
society, but through time it's taken on a meaning to mean pretty much all-encompassing.
So I would just define that almost like a personal definition, it's anything and everything
mankind perceives.
So I just wanted to define that from the sense that I think about it, but now we tend to
relax and just say cosmic just means, well, you know, the cosmos is space and cosmic meaning
something far out or esoteric, just all-encompassing based on our perception, because basically
if you lost your perception, nothing would exist in essence.
So just to make the definition, I think, more clear, and the definition of the word censorship
means to obfuscate block or prevent from being viewed or even seen.
I think the cosmic censorship, the term takes it a little bit further by implying not only
things that are obfuscated, blocked or not seen, but also things that are not comprehended
or acknowledged.
Now on the question of evil or malevolence, what's interesting again, let's define the word
evil, you go to etymology, etymological reference or what they call etymological dictionary, and
you'll see there's a pretty, you know, showing the origin, pretty elaborate sense of how the
word can be defined or what it means, but what took hold of my interest, as you go down
on the definition, you'll find that it also includes being subject to disease, which brings
it home for more people, because when you understand the word evil, well, it's basically
based on the cultural norm.
Society of headhunters would find it evil if another group came in and prevented them
from harvesting human heads.
So then there's the relative morality there, but this, I think, transcends that when you
look at the aspect of being subject to disease as being one of the definitions of evil, which
is actually what we find in a lot of the ancient rites when a society or group of people were
deemed evil, they were subject to disease and war and famine and pestilence and maladies.
So this is also one of the attributes in discussing cosmic censorship, because, for example,
I think I've brought up the medical system several times recently, because it's hand-in-hand
with the agricultural and food also intake.
What's interesting is if you look at what's put out is terms of pharmaceuticals, which
mean poison, by the way, look up the word pharma, and what's called medicine, most of those
drugs within, or medicines within a decade are deemed unsafe, right?
And the people do suffer what is considered the side effects or that makes them unsafe
while they're aspiring to acquire them and use them.
So nothing changes.
So is that evil?
And, yes, very simply by definition.
But then again, what drives people towards that, you see, is the cosmic censorship.
In other words, yes, you can say that the people are drawn to it through means of propaganda
and marketing, meaning advertising, which essentially is the foremost breeder of covetedness in the
world, which basically makes people aware of things that they were not aware of before.
And then not only that makes them want those things, right, at cost or whatever.
So this aspect can also be explored, but the aspect of cosmic censorship kicks in with
something with the harmful remedies and medications that are put out in modern society,
when you present all of the facts and the truth of the matter, historically and present
to the willing victim.
Willing victim would be easy to encounter at a line at a pharmacy, which are pretty common
in the Western civilizations.
And you say, hey, by the way, I see you're online here to acquire some of these drugs,
whatever you're for.
Do you know statistically this or the facts are this or even more informally that have
you ever considered the side effects?
And most of the time, if not all of the time, it's disregarded.
Now if we're supposed to be rational, logical creatures, how can we we meaning they, the
person that you just addressed, deny what you had just said as the potential of causing
harm, but yet they still desire it.
So, and again, let's for go for now, the aspect of propaganda advertising and marketing,
then there's the aspect of personal gain or the person is suffering some illness and
this has been put in front of them as relief.
But yet the truth of the matter is outside of, let's say, something that's a pain killer
that would dull the senses, the none of them really work.
And this is pretty much well known as overall beneficial to the body, right?
You know, of course, there's the compromise.
So I use this as a metaphor because this model of presenting what is real or truthful to
someone is often negated in an unreasonable way.
And there can't be any explanation other than there is a force or a condition called
cosmic censorship that prevents them too.
And I think the cosmic censorship can be considered to transcend cultural norms, personal
desires and things like that.
So again, bringing this through as an idea is just a metaphor.
You will see goes across many fields of study, many aspects of human society.
So the malady and the evil and the, that that, that, that, that, that befall the people
because of their negation of reality or the truth of a certain matter, can be considered
to be a testament to their, to their robustness.
So you know, the way that the humans are made or people are made, but also unnecessary
suffering if you view the whole situation on what's going on because the, the access
to the information to avoid it is there, but it's negated and constantly negated.
So that's the, the essence of the cosmic censorship.
Now that, that has to tie into where does the cosmic censorship come from and, and more
of what it is and how it's done.
It's quite a sophisticated interlocking web of, of deceptions then that would power the whole
thing I'm thinking because when you make a statement like pharmaceuticals generally don't
work other than for pain relief.
I mean, that's a big statement, but clearly they do work enough for people to feel compelled
to use them beyond just the relief, right?
The, the reason why I say that is because if you, overall it sounds, it sounds to most
of being absurd statement and then to some they would, they would be highly speculative.
And then a very few know that and what, so let's just bypass the first two and the ones
why do they know that?
Because first of all, those that know the pharmaceuticals don't work and this goes also
with many techniques and methodologies that the medical systems use is because look at
the outcome, whether you want to look at a very short outcome, which would be the, while
the person is being treated with these, the results are not, let's say as, as conclusive
and as complete as, as predicted or promised, right?
Then you have the long term effects and within the, between the initial taking of these things
to the long term effects you have what's called side effects.
So it all boils down to the operation was a success and the patient died.
You see?
So you can do your own study on this.
It's not really popular because you have to also understand how the money system works
when there is no money.
That sounds kind of crazy to say that.
But again, to go back to the cosmic censorship aspect, where is it coming from?
Why?
What and how is it being caused is beyond like you mentioned deception because in order
to provide a deceptive condition, the condition has to appear truthful and correct to the victim.
And most of you couldn't, if someone wanted to deceive someone else, they wouldn't wear
a t-shirt.
I'm here to deceive you and hold up a sign.
I'm here to deceive you and say I'm here to deceive you.
They wouldn't, you see, that's an extreme.
But so it's, it goes more in the realm of counterfeit and it has to interlock with what the
person believes is correct.
Notice I didn't say right or good.
Right?
Because again, in a society of headhunters, if another group came in and persuaded,
attempted to persuade them or prevented them from harvesting human heads, that group would
be viewed as evil by the headhunters who want to harvest human heads, you see.
This is not relative moralism or anything like that.
This is just, is the being going to survive in the condition or thrive in the conditions
that it's in or not.
That's why I brought up the term of, one of the definitions, one of the terms included
in the definition of the word evil is being subject to disease.
Because that is not a matter of opinion anymore or moral relativism.
Right?
Remember, you know, back in the medieval ages, people would go through the streets and
carts and say, you know, bring out your dead, bring out your dead.
You know, it was quite normal.
But as it, even though it was normal during the plague times, was it evil?
Of course.
You see, and that's how you can contrast what you think is evil and what is good by just
basically looking at what is it actually being performed by this description?
Right?
Or what is the condition that is prevalent, but that can be described with the term evil?
Usually until it, that term evil is brought down to pestilence, destruction, war, disease,
it's, it's just argued or negated.
Good is thriving promotes life, pleasantry, pleasantness.
And evil promotes death, promotes struggle, promotes disease, which is sometimes worse than death.
Right?
And, say, and, and malady, right?
Unpleasantness.
And because here, people are more interested in quantified support.
They, most people have lost the ability to understand qualitative support.
The quantity of evil in a society can easily be measured by how many people are dropping
like flies or sick or are killing each other or bickering with each other or warring with
each other.
You see, in essence, mankind is still in a place where you're going to have to quantify
in a material sense.
But if people's conceptualization of good and evil have largely been limited to the material
terms of their well-being, what are you implying are the alternatives to that if we want to
use quality as the measure instead?
In other words, how else would we conceptualize good and evil when we live in a material reality
anyway?
Well, I wouldn't say that the reality is, is material, actually, a very small aspect of
it is, especially if you understand electrical engineering, how the weather works, what, what
scientists are wrestling with the real microcosms of things looking under their telescopes as
well, the microscopes and how small can they see, what is everything made of and any material
scientist, even with their, I would say, training because their technicians, in essence, will
tell you that the closer they look at matter, they find that there's nothing there.
And if you look at the fulacious model of the atom, right, they have a planetary model of
an electron spinning around a central body known as a proton or neutron, the size of that
atom is mostly undefined or defined as space.
So I would suggest that in the future people will start to discount that we are just in a
material world over the reality that we're, most of reality is immaterial.
They'll find that the actual significance of their reality is intangible by their five
senses or six senses.
So to address the question specifically though, the good and evil thing, how do we move away
from the quantitative assessment to the qualitative assessment if that is to be had?
Well again, this is a subject that people find as a category that's something that they
want to just slip over to the side or make it, make it something that is optional to think
about and it's a category again based on if we go back to what is morality, what is
law, what is good or bad and these are things that if one were to study history from any point
of you, we'll see that references were constantly made to a group called the gods or an essence
something that people might say intuition.
Oh, it doesn't feel right in all this, right?
So again, it's something intangible but the dictates are accessible, you know.
If you look at, for example, moral teachings, all of the dictates whether it's Eastern or
Western religion or Eastern or Western philosophy, people can access the dictates of what
more good morality is or good and evil is but when they start examining just like the
atom, the closer you get, the less you find is tangible.
Meaning if you're looking for a source, you know, if if I were to come into your, your
presence and drop a heavy object on the table and say, this is a rock, you'll say, yes, it
is a rock.
Well, what is it?
Is it a sedimentary limestone or is it a granite?
Right?
You know, we can examine it and materially.
And you're not going to find that kind of direct examination with morality and good and
evil because there are so many different societies on the planet now.
Here's a simple analogy.
You have someone who lives in a dwelling that has a quote unquote, roach infestation, right?
And they have to stay in that dwelling so they go out and either hire an exterminator or
try to exterminate these roaches or create a condition where the roaches are no longer infiltrating
their living space, right?
They're considered vermin or pests.
Okay, take that person, put them on a planet where the predominant species and inhabitants
are roaches.
What are they going to do now?
You see?
They'll be out of a job to say the least.
Yeah, they'll be very uncomfortable in misplace.
Now, that's an extreme example.
So what some people view as being beneficial, other people view as being not beneficial.
One man's junk is another man's treasure.
One man's floor is another man's ceiling, you know, on a two story building.
Yeah.
And the other things, I think that this is, this might sound dogmatic to most people, but
no one, I believe, and I say I believe because I don't want to argue with anyone over this,
either past, present or future.
I'm going to say it this way.
You don't have license or a right to redefine these things if they've been memorialized through
history in a way where they are so clear and so potent that if you find yourself in a
society where your history regarding morals, what's good and evil to be ignored, I would
say that is a sign that you're not living in a, let's say, intellectually harmonious state.
In other words, when you have everything laid out for you in the past, the reason you keep
records, for example, is so you can procure it to the progeny.
People come after you because it's important.
So people, once they begin to examine prior records of what's been said about this and have
distilled it down to a way where the commoner can also, not only the commoner can only examine
it, but also comprehend it, you'll see that there's not much of a question about defining
these things.
I mean, one of the red flags I should say about society is when they seem to complain or
ask questions about things that have already been answered, regardless of their materially
direct, you know, like dropping a stoner or rock on someone's table or just a concept like
what's good or evil.
These things have been defined for thousands of years.
Now if you live in a society that is arrogant enough and ignorant enough to believe that
they can redefine it as they go along, I would suggest that you learn to set yourself apart
from that kind of a society if you're stuck in living with them.
It's a harsh commentary on the current society, but I would suggest that it's about as
true of a statement that anyone can make.
During episode zero and even during this stream, you've brought up the analogy of the headhunter
society as a means to make a juxtaposition between different moral systems or to illustrate
how morality differs from culture to culture.
And I don't think most people are averse to the idea that morality is not a set and stone
thing, but someone hearing your headhunter reference for the first time may very well think, well
wait a minute, why is he using such a gory analogy?
Like, do we need analogies of a murder-approving society to illustrate moral concepts?
And maybe the guy giving the analogies when we need to consider for examination and not
what he's saying.
So can you explain a bit why you use that analogy and why do you say that it's not moral
relativism, even though for most people it does sound like that?
Well, I wouldn't say it's moral relativism as much as it's a moral contrast to perhaps
have someone look over towards the headhunter and then turn around while they're looking
at the headhunter from a vantage point and create that same vantage point looking at
their society or their concept of what's associated or characterized as the right behavior,
which is probably a definition of what is moral.
And that'll mean right and left, but I mean what would be correct or even in a sense
of altruism, right?
Or you've heard, do no harm or help your neighbor and do unto others as you want done
into you.
Every culture has some moral, I call it a dogma because there's hypocrisy that underlines
all of that, of course.
And when you talk about morality, I think that in the future we might have to define a
little bit more of the mechanisms behind it because if you say something is right or
wrong, there's a much more.
Much deeper structure associated with morality that goes into what's been communicated to
people regarding other sources and forces.
So again, that's a big term.
But I think that examination based on what people have translated as being right and wrong
is a good place to start.
Sure.
It does feel a little bit like you're talking around the answer, but well, it's not really
because simply like for example in the Western society, more a moral would be something that
is not approved by their quote unquote legal or justice system where moral is something
that would be approved by their legal or justice system.
And you notice I didn't say law.
So we'll eventually will have to get into showing whoever's listening that there's this
concept of deification, heavenly God's spirits, something that mankind has engaged in as a
society.
And it can be also be posed as a secular argument because even though the most secular quote
unquote atheistic people is not about whether you believe it or not, it's whether it exists
or not is that you'll see in the most secular situations as well references to deities.
All the way through science as well.
You know, what's that thing that looks like a mountain that spews molten rock?
What do they call that?
In English it's called a volcano.
Well, guess what?
There's a god called Vulcan, you know, justice.
Who's justice?
Why is it always a woman holding scales blindfolded?
Well, could that be a revived goddess religion?
So in essence, people consider when they hear someone is very religious, they immediately
associate them with being moral.
Well, what if your religion is to sacrifice children for breakfast?
Right?
Well, then that group that would be considered moral and this is not relative because when
you're in that society, the morality is the underpinning structure of what you're allowed
to do without, let's say, a quote unquote punishment and what you're not allowed to do with punishment.
I know you say that is defined by the legal system in a sense.
Of course, people understand that when you commit a crime and you get put on trial, there's
this aspect of almost shaming that you broke a law or whatever, but people have their own
or what they believe to be their own personal outlook and their own personal morality.
So when you ask somebody what's the right or wrong thing, they don't make reference to
a law, they make reference to their own convictions or what they think are their own convictions
and what feelings good.
So that goes beyond the legal system.
Right, and I think eventually you might even show that most people don't have original
and authentic thoughts.
Okay.
Yeah, that can be approached or broached.
Yeah, there've been an essence if you were to state the reality, you're on a planet called
Earth at this particular time in history.
However, again, you want to state that history.
And the status of most of the people on the planet currently are subjects.
They call them citizens, but they're subject to some form of authority and that authority dictates
whether it's overt or subliminally what the morality will be.
That's pretty obvious.
It's not considered and it's not discussed even in minor or major podcasts or sonic events.
These are subjects that people don't want to broach because they even have their own view
upon the subject as being relatively unstable and find safety with what the masses or the
numbers of people find to be correct as their point of view as well.
When we look at the known timeline of human history with civilization going back around
five to six thousand years ago with the Sumerians, at what point is one thing?
Is it possible to detect the emergence of some kind of censorship that is clearly acting
on people's ability to decipher the reality in front of them?
And do we include natural disasters and wars in the censorship classification?
Yes and no.
I would say generally if you understand that, like something like the Art of War, SunZoo,
that the Art of Negotiation to win without fighting is probably the most optimistic way
to resolve a feud or something that leads to war.
I would say yes, that cosmic sense.
The brutal, in other words, to jump to brutality and violence without a formative understanding
that negotiation and compromise leads to a better situation, I would say so.
And he said five or six thousand years ago could go back further than that, but I would
suggest that what we see at that point is not by studying, let's say, secular stuff, but
non-secular stuff, which would be let's say the ancient rites, because most of the ancient
rites or ancient writings, whether they're biblical or otherwise, tend to lean on a spiritual
side.
You know, they always evoke the presence of a God or a demon or an angel.
And in essence, you know, if you say the gods that should encompass all of that as well,
all spiritual beings.
And we will see that or anyone can see by studying the ancient rites that there is an involvement
there.
And in a modern society, you can consider depending on what fashion, what's in fashion
for the day or the decade or the year is the now there's the question that people speak
about ETs, you know, malevolent ETs perhaps, you know, but the cognitive mind can easily
encompass all of it.
If you going to bring up how the effect of cosmic censorship started, you can easily say
it's the gods, which would be gods, angels, demons, and so forth, spiritual beings that you
see evoked in ancient texts, you could also consider that there are other civilizations
that are doing it.
Let's say, you know, this is a psychological, you know, and unperceptable condition that
they project that mankind is basically blinded to many things and develop certain attitudes.
You can also view it as there is a group of humans or people, let's say, that have technology
that is far advanced to others, meaning it doesn't have to be the technology that we speak
on today, it could be technology where that is integrated with them that they've developed
like what they call "ciability", you know, a spiritual ability or psychic ability.
That is another possibility.
And you just or it could also be purely mechanical.
You can have a little box that you turn a knob and everyone in the room or within an area
can't see, you know, their head from all on the ground anymore.
So you see, the reason I'm bringing these up is because you need to entertain the possibility
of all of these things.
And ultimately, is there something that is preventing people historically and presently from seeing
things that are quite obvious and can be presented to them in an obvious fashion that they can
understand?
Yes, there is.
And hence the term again, cosmic censorship and it does go back in history.
Anyone who is even slightly familiar with the biblical text is aware of things like the
Tower of Babel and the writings and prophets where the prophets are told that they are to
close the eyes and ears of the people.
You see?
And you'll also see it in many other ancient rites.
It's brought up here and there, but essentially the lean heavily on what we call the gods.
Again, angels, demons and gods, God heads, Demi, God.
But I would suggest also to fully encompass the study that it can be done, you know, by
beings that are not gods as well.
I'm just throwing it out as a speculative, speculative condition, but the condition does
exist in ancient times all the way through.
And how it's, again, just back to the question, it started very early on and seems to prevail.
And one way to, to, let's say, do a quick judgment on that is the concept of war, a provocation
where the parties are not aware that there is a third party provoking them is a form of cosmic
censorship.
Yeah, you did mention at one point, I don't know if it was in the last week's episode
or privately that there have been, you know, wars around longer than they've been other
things like banks.
So therefore you can't just blame war on bankers.
Obviously it has to be something that goes a bit further than what we can perceive the presence
of longstanding issues of tension.
Sure.
Then again, one day we'll probably touch on it in short, but even the concept of what people
call the bankers, how can there you have bankers when there's no money?
The entire world's on a credit-based economy.
So again, it's very Alice in Wonderlandish, you know, very, it's almost in a, it's like a
sec, if you start studying the bankers, for example, it's like a psychedelic acid trip.
And all of the information, by the way, can be corroborated and supported with their own
writings and laws.
So the question, I guess, harking back to how early the cosmic censorship started, I would
say as far back as anything recorded, not only about human society, but by human society,
meaning, well, you could take that however you want.
You will see that there is a force interfering not for the best possible outcome, which
not necessarily means to bring pestilence and disease, but to just carry mankind along
over a duration, kind of like the metaphor that I've used before, the waiting room.
It seems like a human society throughout history has been in a waiting room of some kind,
and I mean, the term waiting room, as I would, like you were waiting at a dentist or a doctor's
office, were waiting in an administrative setting where you're told to sit down and wait
and take up time.
Yeah, I think that there's going to be more space to explore that theme a bit later.
But one thing that you talked about in a previous episode was the idea of the blob, describing
how mass society is currently akin to like a formless sludge that simply takes the shape
of its container because of how thoughtless it is.
So, I want to get back to that a little bit.
So Western society is essentially upheld by two pillars.
One of them is the Judeo-Christian tradition, which was the state-sponsored religion of
the Roman Empire.
The second pillar is the Greco-Roman, which generated the enlightenment and the Renaissance, and
shaped Western culture around its philosophies and traditions.
However, what is curious to me is how, despite the heritage and the legacy of the enlightenment
and Renaissance period, it seems ironically that the typical 21st century Western person
is not the cultured intellectual that those periods revere.
It's rather become the disinterested and almost proudly ignorant every man or plebeian,
the aggregate of which is this blob that you mentioned.
Can you lay out what some of the key developments in modern history have been that have led
to this current state of mass uniformity of which I think cosmic censorship plays a role?
Well, I would say, even if you laid out an elaborate scheme that is prevalent today about
the cosmic censorship in modern society, I would suggest that the same scheme was overlaid
in mass in past societies, it's just that we may not know about it.
And with research on how people have been guided as you would see their cultures permit is
very similar.
So in essence, when we just bring it up in a modern context, it's also the overall outcome
is the same in older contexts.
Except for now, people are walking around with what I call the stupid rectangles in their
pocket, a little touchscreen, or at home or wherever.
They do it using light and sound versus just hearing or reading.
It's a technological, let's say, evolution where people are more connected, where people
are more connected, where time seems to be shortened for the message.
So in modern times, the only difference again, because you'll see the control that goes
back all throughout humankind, is that what would probably took weeks, months, or years
to accomplish in the past, can be accomplished now in a matter of minutes or hours, or maximum
days.
And the reason I say maximum days is because you'll notice how the interest changes over
a few days sometimes.
So the danger of, let me just retract that term, danger.
The condition that the quote unquote "modern" is in right now is far more extreme than any
other time in history because of the almost instantaneous exchange of information with
the stupid rectangle.
And for people who just to clarify a stupid rectangle is, if you have a smart device in your
pocket, just take it out and just hold it about three feet away from you, what does it look
like?
So I would suggest that the main element of modern society and cosmic censorship is almost
instantaneous censorship, right?
And just to go back to the blob aspect, that has to tie in if anyone wants to study the
crowd by Gustav Leban.
Now I'm not endorsing that piece of work or Gustav Leban, but it's something that sticks
out notably if you just want to study the subject of how people form groups and why the groups
are formed and just a study on group think.
And the reason I call them a blob and such is because the individual is consumed and consumed
by the group.
In other words, his individuality or the interest of the single person no longer is of any
avail to the group.
This is a group actually, there's so many single people are eliminated that there is no more
group other than that.
That's why I referenced it as a blob.
And essentially if you're going to promote through this new way of instantaneous communication
to the group, you in essence view them as a blob, you see, or taking the shape of the
container.
But we are living in an era where the idea of individuality is sort of at the apex of
human striving and there's a lot of effort in a lot of media and a lot of marketing that
goes into pushing that idea.
So if you have people that are partaking in the crafting of their individuality through
the means that they know or that they've been shown, how do you reconcile that with
the idea that also they are more blob than they are person?
That is part of the Alice in Wonderland or Wellian or just plain out deception.
What I mean by that is the extremeness of the current reality is just that.
It's so extreme that it's become almost esoteric, meaning the point that you just brought
up about the accentuation of individuality, the reality of it is quite the opposite.
Someone who is ever, let's say, if you're older than 30 or 40 and you've been through various
administrative authorities through your personal experiences or even education system
or religious system, what I mean by that is if you've ever had a sit down with a priest
or a rabbi or an imam regarding, critical questions regarding one place in society, if you've
ever had a similar conversation with, let's say, what they call a legal judge in the
legal administration system or the political system or the education system from a point
to point or person to person conversation with an authority in one of these administrative
institutions, they will always tell you you have to be just like everyone else and the
entire thing just falls apart.
I've actually even recently in passing had overheard a conversation with what they call
police officers and someone bringing up points in the law and the police, so-called police
officer said, "I'm not interested in that you have to do what everyone else does."
I personally have had conversation several lunches with Supreme Court Justice bringing up
five points of the law and they say you have to do what everyone else does because no one
knows what you're talking about.
I've had conversations with people in clergy and they say the same thing of many different
religions.
You have to do, we go by tradition and if you're interested in what we do, you have to do
what everyone else does.
So again, I just want to bring up the point of the individual being accentuated or emphasized
as a complete farce.
But even if you say that the premises of a period like the Renaissance are farce, there
are still events or agendas that were put in place to specifically create today's
world of homogenized reactive consumers.
And the Renaissance could perhaps be said to be one of those events.
What I'm curious to hear is what other events would you point to within the last 400 years
of modern history that contribute equally to that?
Because I mean, surely we can talk about industrial developments or timekeeping or population
changes or the rise of contemporary art or things like this.
Well, I think those are secondary to what one can examine regarding what's called a
authority because at the end of the day people sleep better if they feel like they're in
line with what the authority wants them to do, quote unquote, the authority, right?
So if you look back at something called the concept of the nation state, Westphalia,
agreements, 1600s or so and all the way forward to the post-Napoleonic upheavals to what
they call the early world wars, you'll notice that there is a vacuum of information
regarding on how these authorities are being set up.
So I would suggest that the quest for power over societies, known as nations and countries
and just societies in general, whether they're subdivisions of the main country or whatever
has not gone away, but the information about how it has been done has, you see.
So for example, you have a society that's led by a king in an ancient times and you have
some even today, but I would suggest that that notion of a type of political system or
authority set up as a monarchy or what they call a democracy or parliamentary administration
or whatever is all part of, let's say, a charade now or it's just theater, it's just theater
that if one were to examine why does he say that it's theater and come up with a clear answer
that you're basically the entire world has been subjugated by a very small group of people
that do not want to be known.
You'll see there is a vacuum of information in the past 400 years on how this has been
achieved as it is today.
And evidence of why you live as a subject basically as property of a very small group of
people is just by looking at quote unquote how the legal system is set up.
Everyone is registered as property.
You're given a number.
All of your actions are recorded and categorized not only by gender, you know, whether you're
male or female or man or woman or also by your race and your creed.
You'll notice that the entire set up as it is as it's landed today is all based on commerce.
Basically there is no concern for people other than in a commercial sense.
So if you again understand the early ways of authoritarianism and you understand the current
ways of authoritarianism, this is also based on what's good and evil and morality and how
society is being run.
You'll see there is a vacuum in the past 400 years of how things have gotten the way that
they are today.
Most people don't make any quam that they're registered and they're given a serial number
like a toaster or washing machine or a car.
You know, most people don't worry and are concerned that they're living under a credit
based economy with no lawful money and circulation.
Most people don't understand how there is a hierarchy being set up through academia and
political systems, how it got this way.
They don't see it.
And that's where I would consider there's been a vacuum of information in the past 400
years because in order for it to succeed into the stable, or semi-stable environment, it
is today.
That would suggest it's more stable than semi-stable because when you hear of instability, that is
also manufactured to a degree.
There is no question really about how in the past 400 years you've gotten from one way of
society living with a certain mindset and then the current mindset that there is today.
So I would suggest that there is more of a vacuum than anything that I could point out and say,
"Hey, look, this is an interesting notable thing in the past 400 years."
Okay, that gives a lot of food for thought.
For people that are unused to hearing polemics against the canon of modern history, I still
think you could better buttress your claims that what is touted as the most defining period
of modern history, namely the 17th and 18th century, are farce.
Like why was the Renaissance, for example, a farce?
And can that be shown objectively aside from your view of things?
Well, look at what it's led you to, not you, but specifically the society at large.
You're essentially now reduced to a piece of property.
And most people don't see that and they never will.
And when I say never, I mean in a very general sense, no, they won't see it.
And then one would go back and maybe ask a philosophical question, "Is mankind supposed
to be this way?"
You know, that's the question.
Is mankind supposed to be numbered and labeled and registered as it is today?
And how did it get to that point?
And I'm not asking that.
I know how it got there.
Most people do.
Most people don't.
So I would suggest that any kind of a renaissance that leads a society on a planet known as Earth
into abject slavery, which is in a sense what it is.
And this is not a comment.
This is an actual fact.
You can call the slaves whatever you want.
You want to call them citizens or subjects or Americans, Iraqis, Russians, Colombians, whatever.
I would suggest that if you look at the past 400 years and the post renaissance period,
having a vacuous body, in other words, the situation just didn't happen by chance.
And to see the vacuum and the lack of body of work to explain how you've gone from being
even surfs on a field, harvesting wheat to being registered with numbers and living in a
credit-based economy, with everything being in a pseudo state is quite the achievement.
So in essence, when you say it was a renaissance, who would you say it was a renaissance for?
I wouldn't say it's for the mass population on the planet at large.
It was actually their defeat, the cosmic from a cosmic point of view.
If you traveled anywhere in the universe and said, "We're going to take this planet here
and turn everyone into our property," you wouldn't be viewed as a hero.
Well, would you?
Depends on who you're talking to.
How's on the topic of the aspects of the Greco-Roman legacy like the renaissance?
You've mentioned to me in the past privately that the Romans were not that interested in truth
despite the lofty facade of what could be seen in their writings about virtue and honor
and so forth.
Can you expand on that because I think it has implications for the age that we're living
in in terms of how to contend with truth in light of cosmic censorship?
The Western society has adopted a lot of the, not only cultural, but most social aspects
of authoritarianism from the Roman civil aspect.
The Roman society that I would say started around 200 to 300 BC from that time, the later
Roman Emperor, where the first god Emperor Augustus Caesar around the first century or BC
or so at the end of that time, they kind of solidified what we now define as a Roman system.
And the Romans have never been interested in the truth.
They are an authoritarian group that has assimilated other cultures, especially the Greek culture,
for example.
You will find in history that the artisans, philosophers, scientists, what have you,
of ancient Rome were not Roman at all.
They were essentially adopted from other cultures, I would say, mostly the Greek culture.
And there were a, might makes right, which, you know, where is there, you know, is there
a truth and might makes right?
Yes, if you stated as such, you know, but they are not interested in truth, for example.
One example, politically, the political system of the, of Rome at the time was very corrupt
in terms of being, you know, hypocrisy, waste, theft, immorality.
And there was an apparatus, a very strong apparatus to cover that up and always painted white
wash it as, you know, as being honorable and dignified, right?
And you can notice that this is through all the modern political systems as well.
The Roman system of quote unquote justice or law or legal system, again, was not based
on truth.
It was based on authoritarianism, right?
Again, you can almost view it as, as one would view their timekeeping, for example, no one
is questioning the Gregorian calendar, you know, the current timekeeping, the year, date,
and months for the, the, the, the commercial, in a commercial sense and social norm is to
adopt the Gregorian calendar.
People never address it as such.
They just ask, you know, what day is it?
And they spout off something off of that.
And if you look at the history of it, they'll even in today's modern timekeeping authority, they'll
tell you that it's an arbitrary system.
Well, this is solar calendar.
Well, the sun's movement is an arbitrary.
Sure they are.
You ever heard of a leap year?
Yeah.
So, I would suggest that, you know, looking at anything from a lawful perspective, you will
find it to be again, shown in a very authoritative way when it's under the Roman system and then when
it's to, you try to define it, you know, what's being put in front, forward from a Roman system
and you will see there's no truth in it or it has no lawful base.
But I don't make great, a lot of, you know, people who hear this who perhaps are versed in
classical studies or ancient studies would say or claim that the Romans had all these philosophers
like the Greeks did and they, they had an output that clearly showed what their intentions
and culture was and that is not an accord to what you're talking about.
Well, if you look at their, name some Roman philosophers that don't have Greek backgrounds,
you can't.
They do exist, but they're not, they're very minor.
Name, name architects that are a Roman that don't have a Greek background or Greeks themselves.
And this goes all the way to the Renaissance time.
And also when you, when you bring up the, the aspect of the Romans, I'm not interested in any
truth, this is actually, you will find this as a criticism throughout history about
Rome.
I've been moralized in people's writings.
That is.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And I'm saying this because I'm fair.
I'm not a, a, a, a, a, a, or against it.
I'm just objectifying it.
And fair would mean, you know, bring up something and present something that anyone can access,
not just your opinion or your belief because eventually those are unsubstantiated and because
I think as we've discussed and maybe we will in the future that the, the individual is a
very little import.
And it, it sounds contrary to what people are being told, but, you know, once you start
to do some study, you will find that the, the quote unquote society has been groomed a
certain way, not individual by individual, but a group at a time.
Would you say that there is a, I mean, obviously if you go back in time, you end up with different
circumstances where perhaps you could say that people were more at the mercies of nature
or certain forces or circumstances that we perhaps have alleviated somewhat today with
technology.
But would you say that there is a dividing line somewhere as far as perhaps ancient era
versus modern era or medieval period where this sort of homogenization started to become
very adamant because at some point you did have some kind of a flourishing of individual
sensibilities, which, you know, would have been notable at that point, which perhaps don't
exist anymore today.
The only thing that doesn't exist anymore is the, the amount of time that it takes to
communicate.
That's been shortened.
Everything else is still, you know, I would say prevalent because, for example, if you take
what's called the education system, if you look at the standards that were held as a
good education, a hundred years ago, in any country, by the way, or any culture to 300
to 500 to a thousand years ago, you'll notice that diminished, that has diminished drastically.
So again, that is more of the macrocosmic censorship versus the microcosmic censorship.
People are being, I call it, dumbed up.
They like, most like to refer to it as being dumbed down, but when something is increasing,
it's going up.
So that's why I call it being dumbed up.
I think a lot of the history that we've been given is merely a farce, and that needs to
be revisited.
I think we were all walking around with this glorified romanticism about things like the
Renaissance or certain societies.
I think right now, ultimately, without putting, without regret, I could say, we're in the best
condition, potential condition, currently, than ever any other time in history.
By looking at the modern era, particularly since the arrival of mass media, it does seem
like the 20th century has introduced to sort of hitherto unseen social state.
So as a result, we're confronted with this sort of widespread existence of a type of person
who acts less like his own autonomous agent of his life and is more of a reactionary subject
with a flavorless identity that sort of melts into this blob.
This has happened in spite of the Renaissance and light knew, and as you mentioned, perhaps
they're overrated.
But from these movements, we've both this idea of the individual, where a person who is
removed from a group control can be his own sovereign.
So this quandary of having really nothing to choose from other than the unintellectual
individual on one side or the impressionable masses on the other side has been a source
of frustration, I think, for a long time.
And one of the statements that has been birthed of that, that I think we hear now in the
last two or three, maybe even four decades is that people are stupid.
You see this a lot of movies and cartoons, and it's sort of taken in jest, even as we
see it in articles and memes and books that sort of decry how unbearable or unreasonable
mankind can be.
It's taken as a sort of satire so people have an excuse not to really address it.
Why is it that a statement like people are stupid or some variation of that is still popular
despite all of the outcry and the polemics against humanity that we've seen over the thousands
of years in the form of literature and media?
Okay, let's replace the word stupid with the word broken because I think when you say
the word stupid, it evokes a little bit of humor, well, you know, just like half ingest
all in earnest, right?
Let's replace it with the word broken where people made to be broken.
No.
Are they broken?
Yes.
You can even see in a poetic way, you know, when something or a living is broken, it means
that they lose their will, they lose their capacity to act as to any potential that they
would have had before or do have.
So I would suggest that one way to view people are stupid as people are broken because then
you can answer the question very simply.
And again, you sort of skimmed by the concept of individuality again.
And while you were saying that, I thought of a very simple notion that the propagandists
like to use is that when the propagandists are or any control mechanism, social control mechanism,
promotes individuality, they're simply doing that because they know that once the individual
is promoted, the individual tends to feel more alone and they're easier to control that
way.
You see, albeit if one studies Gustav Leban, let's say, or the crowd or group mentality,
inside the individual has to abandon the self to become so adherent to a group.
So again, just tying it in, again, these are complex matters that can be simplified easily,
believe it or not, but they don't appear to be as simple as they are because of all the
various overlays on it.
Again, there's a romanticized history.
There is a constant changes in culture and what's fashionable.
And then of course, again, to lead back to the overall cosmic censorship that is our humans
being censored.
In other words, are we being blocked?
And the answer to that is clearly yes.
And it can be supported more qualitatively than quantitatively because, for example, recently
I read an article about someone remote viewing moon bases and it was a quite esteemed remote
viewer in the past.
And the critique on the book was that, well, there is no supporting evidence on what he's
saying.
Well, that's just quantitative, not qualitative, you see.
So what people are looking for and what exists when it coincides, then the coincidence of
those two things is the direction of society.
So for example, if you have people that are being manipulated or blocked and their expectations
are limited to the resulting of that blocking, then the society will remain in harmony.
But if the individuals will say blocked or cut off or censored and their expectations
are not met, then you have uneasiness and then the formula has to be redone because you
won't be able to control them.
I do agree that broken is functionally a more suitable word than stupid to address this
condition.
But I will return to the word stupid for a second because it does have a meaning, right?
So it's not just this pejorative, nothing that we treat it as.
But if we were to take the word seriously for a second and we could replace that with
something like folly instead.
But this is still something that has been talked about for a very long time throughout
human history in more than just a pejorative way.
So the curious thing about stupidity or folly for me is that society doesn't seem to
know much about it.
I don't know of any center for the study of willful ignorance or any serious academic investigation
into the subject.
And you will find a lot of people bloating nowadays about gratitude and happiness and
things that are very much in line with the new age movement.
So it's not out of the question to make a foray into various mental conditions or mental
states.
But when it comes to stupidity, we don't really see that.
And when we broached the subject of mental capacity or intelligence, people would defer
to the idea of IQ scores as being the only way to measure that.
If we can't really define what people refuse to define what stupidity or foolishness is,
how can we then claim to know what knowledge or wisdom is?
Yes.
Well, just while you were saying that.
I looked at the etymological definition of stupid, mentally slow lacking ordinary activity
of mind, dolly, name, or stupid person here.
It has an insensibility, numbness, dullness.
You hear that very much in society.
People are not sensible in terms of common sense.
They're numb, right?
Apathetic and dullness.
Where's the creativity?
So I would say that in terms of the other terms being used, they can be defined.
Iran can be defined, idiot can be defined.
But I think what overshadows all of it is the prevalent use in the, especially in the English
language, the use of the word nice misused, all right?
And I think that without getting into just, we can do just do one hour podcast and just
the word nice and the implications of using it the way it's being used versus what it really
means.
So if you were to say people are nice, isn't it the same as saying people are stupid?
Well, then we have to define nice.
Right, we have to define nice.
It's in essence, we use foolish, stupid and senseless.
The interesting thing, depending on, again, this to turn away from you and I speaking and
turn to the audience is, are you a fool?
You know, whoever is listening.
Well, one way to judge a fool is if you bring them competent, sensible and objective,
objectively good information and it's rejected, without being considered, you're a fool.
Right?
I think there's an ancient RIT that talks about don't suffer fools, you know, or if you
you mess around with fools, it's your fault.
And that's to the audience, by the way.
So, you know, are you a fool?
You know, how many times have you come across in your own personal life information that
you didn't want to consider?
Now, that goes beyond, for example, something where you'll hear people say, well, I just
did something stupid.
How many times do you hear that?
Well, let's go back and look at that very closely or not.
Actually, let's not look at it very closely.
Just came over it because it's just the same as looking at it closely.
It means that you knew better, but you didn't implement that knowledge.
Right?
Because if you never knew that or you never knew better, you would never in, in, in, after
thought say I did something stupid.
Now what if you didn't have the, this basic knowledge?
Well, it's, I wouldn't say wisdom is basic, but let's just call it the knowledge, let's
say a wise mindset.
Would you, is it possible, either a group or an individual to continuously do things that
are, quote, unquote, stupid and never know it?
The answer to that is yes.
Right?
And if you want an example of that, if you're probably sitting in a room with a door, just
open the door and go outside.
So in connection with that as far as wisdom, it does sound like you're saying that wisdom
is something that is in, in scar supply.
So we can say that there is a current, a widespread proliferation of stupidity or foolishness
or folly.
That to me doesn't seem to be insignificant in terms of analyzing cosmic censorship.
Well, analyzing cosmic censorship is interesting in itself.
And I think it's going to be ongoing until, you know, you, you run into the quandary where
you have, let's say here in quotes, the, the next few sentences here, an individual that
is so evolved beyond the current norm.
And it's so perceptive and knowing that they view more of reality than the others.
And they notice that the others that don't view and don't have those abilities can't be
changed because of an external force.
Then you can have it defined.
But the, the catch there is who you're going to define it to.
Because there's only, let's say, a select group, whether it's by divine implication or
random numbers or whatever you want to call it, a percentage, a very small group of people
that could see beyond others that can perceive beyond others.
Let's say comprehend beyond others and perform beyond others.
They, themselves, will contain this knowledge within their group.
Because they'll view the other group.
It wants it to establish that the rest are not capable of going down that path or even
comprehending the condition that they're in.
You see?
It's going to be the true understanding of cosmic censorship will never be public or you can,
but it wouldn't matter.
It would be speaking Chinese to an all-inglish audience.
That's why many, many conversations can be held regarding, look how many secrets are
hidden in plain sight, right?
Look at how all of this was shown to you, but it didn't really matter until this happened,
yeah?
One can say then what's the importance of discussing cosmic censorship or defining it
now?
Very simply.
And again, if anyone's heard Greek speak before, the motto of Greek speak is, be set apart.
You have to set yourself apart from it first.
And anyone that's taken basic survival training, let's say a ship goes down and you're on a
lifeboat.
The training, the one that is trained for that situation to prevail or help others or
to have a special team in high survivability or survivalist would be that you have to set
yourself apart from the panic.
You have to set yourself apart of the ignorance of what to do.
You have to set yourself apart of the potential, the being disabled by the potential danger.
And you have to think clearly and you have to be calm.
How many times have you heard that people in harsh situations remain calm?
Think clearly.
Just remember what you're training taught you, right?
So quote unquote, special forces, people that are highly trained with very highly specialized
abilities to prevail in risky situations or harsh situations have to set themselves
apart even from these surrounding conditions.
You see?
So ultimately, what one can consider with the cosmic censorship is you're on your own
with this meaning it doesn't mean that you can't converse with other people.
And there ultimately can't be a group, quote unquote, very loose group of people that study
and ponder this, but it ain't going to change anything because it's part of the prevailing
condition.
But hold on now, it's not going to change anything, but we can see in the world that there is
this universal disacoolerbrum which refuses to write itself.
And in response to that, we have had people over the past two or three decades that have
begun protesting very noticeably.
It's obviously older than two or three decades, but as far as the most recent modern period
that most people remember, we have the alternative media having come to the sort of forefront where
the likes of a David Ike who becomes famous in the mid to late early to mid 90s for his
political talks is on the scene in Alex Jones follows soon after with his radio show in
the late 90s to early mid 2000s and his documentaries.
But from what I see, it really is in until 2007 with the zeitgeist movie that we do get a distinct
tipping point for what is generally called the consciousness movement, which has now become
a permanent fixture at the edges of the mainstream society.
And it does occasionally penetrate that mainstream when groups like anonymous become popular.
So now over the past ten, fifteen years it's become invoked to be questionable of society.
Why is it Greek that despite the efforts of various alternative media personalities to wake
up the masses that we don't see this large scale awakening taking place?
Okay, let's backtrack the names that you mentioned.
And let's just not limit it to the names, but just for the sake of the next few minutes,
let's just bring evoke the names that you brought up and consider that.
These people that you just mentioned are popular.
Yes, yes, they are.
Many people have heard of them, not everyone, but I would say most even people on the street
would have heard of them.
Now, in order for them to be that popular, they would have to accommodate the current audience.
And one would summarize that before they started speaking the way they did, the audience
was in one condition.
And when the people started hearing these people that you mentioned speak, the people
now in this other condition, that's the presumption.
You know, quote unquote, these people are more conscious awake or whatever.
And they're not because in order to be popular, you have to accommodate the prevailing condition
and maintain it.
So the people that are attracted, generally, now I would say that I wouldn't say I'm directly
attracted to.
I look at, try to look at everything broadly, but the people that are generally attracted
to this consciousness, consciousness, conspiratorial, alternative, whatever, even the peacenix
are, they're, you know, they used to call them in the 60s and 70s, are not any different
inherently than the rest.
In other words, they have a limited perception while they're engaging in their alternative
means as well, because the people that brought them in on this, meaning the names that you
brought, had to initially start their campaign by accommodating the current mindset.
So it's, again, if you go to the zoo and you want to feed the animals, well, you have one
bag for the lions with a certain type of food, a different one for the monkeys, a different
one for the birds, and that does not change as long as there are monkeys, lions and birds
and fish or whatever, different types.
So the type that all of the alternative campaigns, let's call them, and individuals, of people
that they attract, they have to take them out or present it to what's called mainstream
or the common consensus.
And what they do is they lead them around and it'll be one specific subject, isolated
and sequestured from all the other pertinent ones and nothing changes.
But is that to say that that sphere of knowledge should be ignored completely?
I mean, there are things that come out of it that do contrast to the mainstream know
that do seem to offset that.
Well, as I said earlier, not ignored, but considered.
For example, personally, I'm not attracted to the alternative stuff anymore than the mainstream.
I consider it though, meaning consider it like when you're presented with something,
whether it's mainstream or alternative, accepted or unaccepted, when you consider it,
well, you look at what's being presented in the various ways you would look at any other
piece of information.
And then once you're depending on if it peaks interest or how significant it is to the
individual, how much time they want to invest in it.
For example, I'll go on the stupid rectangle and if it's a particular news item that's
brought up what's called the news, you know, you will see whether it's limited to the mainstream
or limited to the alternative.
Right?
For example, again, using medical stuff, the mainstream will never bring up negative points
of vaccines, but the alternative seems to just do that.
But you look at both sides, consider them equally, and then you're going to say, but wait
a second, what is the concept of vaccination?
And then you'll see the whole premise is a farce.
So either way, the premise and the underpinning or the foundation of the subject is never
considered in both sides.
Or I would say the alternative appears to be doing it, but even they are off the mark.
And I think in previous Greek speaks over the years, I have brought up how simple it is,
not always easy, but how simple it is to get to the root of the matter.
In other words, go in reverse of what you're being told as far back as you can go with a
certain level of efficiency, find what it's based on, and then bring yourself back to
what's being discussed and see if the two are pertinent, and you'll find that in almost
it.
99% of the things that people consider to be serious topics or matters are false, or based
on a farce anyway.
But then I have to wonder, what is the end of all the commotion that is created by things
like social unrest or protest or criticism of the mainstream if the condition of cosmic
censorship is unchangeable?
Certainly, people have over the past decade, two decades begun to use a different vocabulary
or to redirect their interests or their focus, and yet the implication of what you're saying
is that it's all futile.
It's futile in an altruistic sense, but it's not futile in the way that things have to be
until they're not.
That's not quite frantic.
Well, okay.
It's, all right.
Let's just say, it's futile when you say that we have to go out and form this political
party to make the country better.
You've heard that before.
Or, it's futile to say, let's put these people in jail because they're causing harm, right?
It's futile to say, let's make the world a better place.
Well all those things happen and the world will be better, humankind will be better overall,
yes, but not within the realm of what people consider to be their reality or reality as such.
Are there examples of people throughout history that you would point to and say that person
did a pretty good job of escaping as much censorship as you'll ever see?
No, no, I believe they do exist, but they were not public.
Again, the problem with being a historical figure is that it has to accommodate the masses
to be historical.
Even when you look at, let's say, ancient Greek philosophy or other things like that,
as they're presented to the public, it's not at all as it was memorialized.
In other words, you're not given proper translations.
Meanings are twisted, you know, the actual, the essence of the story or what the philosopher
or scientist whatever said is changed.
So I would say no, there isn't, that I'm aware of, but those people not exist that were
set apart or let's say not a subject to cosmic censorship, of course they existed, but they're
not public figures that we know of.
In allegory we do, in metaphor we do, I think in the last episode zero, you brought up,
you know, let's say in the Star Wars story, the concept of the Jedi, right?
You know, they were, they extracted themselves or set themselves apart from the rest.
Right.
Well, I think we've been able to say a lot about the subject of cosmic censorship, though
by no means having exhausted the subject.
Is there anything else you want to highlight about the theme before we wrap up?
Yes, ultimately I would put a very heavy leaning and let's say define the meaning ultimately
that it is put upon mankind by the gods.
Now if you want to take what I just said and define a term by term that would be most advisable.
There's not such thing as the gods, Greek, don't you know that?
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
Well, the thing is, in order to say that there is a thing, you have to define that thing.
So because there is a problem in definition, it's easy to hold that statement up, isn't it?
Yes, that's true.
I do remember, and weeks ago I met somebody who was like, we don't even know what the word
God means.
And then he proceeded to try to find a definition and wasn't really successful.
Well, they're immature.
You see, in past events, I've always spoken about how most people stop developing it about
between nine and twelve years old.
And your most esteemed academic intellectuals, I could prove to you through questioning and
dialogue that they're really not beyond an adolescent.
They just, the thing about academia and university and the intellectual elite in their circles
is not to really have knowledge and wisdom, but it's to present things that they sound
that they do.
It's the way that they speak and how they speak and to spend a lot of time formulating presentations.
It's just a different language.
I haven't found any academic suitable that I would call wise at all because if they were,
they wouldn't be considered academics, by the way.
They would be ousted by their own group.
I know that sounds like a tall statement, but if you, initially, if you look at, I'd say
Greek, that sounds ridiculous because, yeah, I could see generally what you're saying is
true because they're basically prostituting themselves to the academic society, but here's
a guy he's pretty good.
Yeah, but the closer you look, you'll see he's still selling out.
You see?
Yeah, there's the concept of the road less traveled, but I don't think what I'm talking about is
even a road.
You're on a hovercraft and you basically float over all kinds of things regardless of how
it's paved.
That's the thing.
People are on most people are on a wagon.
I'm not talking about now throughout history also.
And now that the road isn't paved well enough for the wagon that they're driving, they don't
go down it.
I'm saying that there is no road.
Can you navigate the entire terrain and the best way to do that is not by touching it.
You can go really close, but hover above it.
All right then, that does it for this episode.
I think the podcast recording will be available to download later in the week on GreekSpeak.com
and we will hopefully do another stream next week.
I'd like for it to be a weekly affair though, as I mentioned, it's all about scheduling,
so we'll see how that goes.
Thank you to the Greek for joining me once again.
And thank you to those who tuned in as well as future podcast listeners.
Feel free to shoot any email queries about the podcast or the website to info@greekspeak.com
and unless the Greek has anything else that he wants to sign off with, I think I'm good.
Not at all.
Let's just see what we talk about next time.
Okay then.
Well then until next time everybody.
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]