[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening. This is the Greek Speak podcast featuring the
Archon in the Greek. I'm the Archon creator of greekspeak.com and joining me for episode 2 of
the podcast is my co-host the Greek who will be with me in just a second. So it's been a few weeks
since episode one and I would have hoped to do these streams at more consistent intervals but my
schedule hasn't allowed that to be the case. Luckily though I've just offloaded a bunch of work so
I think we'll have less time between the recordings moving forward. The previous podcasts have been
getting some plays and some downloads so thank you to those who have shown an interest in that.
I've hit the download limit for episode zero at 100 downloads so I'll have to switch to the
soundcloud premium tier before people can get more of those but I'm working on it. With regards to
this stream you can use the live stream group chat in the greekspeak chat room if you have
any questions and I will be checking that regularly. As usual greekspeak.com has no political religious
or commercial affiliations and is completely funded and managed by myself and that's it for my
introduction. I hope you enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
Hi greek. Are you there? Yeah greetings. Yeah how you doing? As we said we'd meet up and do
another sonic event as I call them. Yeah that's that's how I'm doing and let's get started.
So for this stream we're going to be doing the themes of mindset and objectivity. You've talked about
that in the past a separate subjects but I do think that there's a relationship to be found there
so I'd like us to highlight that and we'll see if we can perhaps merge the two towards the end.
By the way for those who are interested there's an article on greekspeak.com called the question
of perception that you can check out if you want and it's my first writing on that theme.
So yeah let's get started greek. A lot has been said historically about people who know versus
people who don't know and I think one of the reoccurring sort of boasts throughout history is that
people get to a point or mankind gets to a point where he becomes enlightened through access
to special knowledge whether it's the Greco-Roman philosophical text during the Renaissance or
the scientific achievements of the 20th century and we see some things similar to that in ancient times
with the Nostics and various mystery religions but when I look at those developments I don't really
see any suspension of cosmic censorship that we talked about in the last episode. So that same
censorship sort of persists in the face of whatever knowledge has abounded and you've talked about in
the past how having knowledge is not actually the key to arriving at true insight but that having
the proper mindset should actually proceed that pursuit of knowledge. Can you expand on that a bit?
Well yeah maybe work around what you just said. Let's say well in the mindset and the knowledge
aspect of it it is knowledge is very important but the mindset does not let one arise to knowledge
objectively. In other words there's plenty of knowledge of many events that are rationally
proven as being false as they are projected publicly. In science and medicine and religion for
example in the Christendom they project all of these high holy days which are blatantly false
and no one seems to care. What kind of a mindset do you need to gain knowledge of that?
You see but if you gain knowledge that Christendom's high holidays are true let's say based on what
they say they're based on that is the wrong mindset. I mean there's a lot of knowledge on Easter egg
hunting right? Or Christmas isn't there? A lot of knowledge about that but if you actually put it
in a perspective you'll notice that it's a farce. So the mindset is what puts the perspective you know
or dictates what category it'll be and how it'll be sorted. Think of mindset as sorting as a
sorting mental or spiritual or you know the psychological sorting mechanism if you will. Yeah.
The sorting mechanism will always hold up what sorting mechanisms do which are various bins or
categories or placements for what's coming through that sorting mechanism. So you have knowledge and
then you have how is that knowledge sorted? And then there's obviously the cultural aspect but
you mentioned also about the mystery schools and censorship and the no-six and all that. All
religions are mystery schools meaning the recently they're in the American intelligence agencies
one of the former leaders there came out publicly in some news articles and says yes the CIA does have
classes and how to cheat lie and steal. Right? Okay well intelligence agencies all over the world
through time have always been part of the ruling class and the ruling class always had a some kind
of deity or you know what you might call in modern-day's church synagogue or some kind of convention.
So the religious aspects of the current faiths in the world, desoteric all the way to the mainstream
are mystery schools in the sense that they employ several layers of perception. They have the
mass control perception you know the faith of the people categorically you know like in today's
world it would be Judaism Christianity or Islam generally and they kind of leave out the Hindu culture
but let's include those and if you look at each one of those cultures religious institutions
they have many layers in there they have the layer that they publicly put out then they have the
working layer the administrative layer which is what allows them to influence other institutions to
maintain a position of power and remain as an institution and then you have another layer which
is the secret goings-on behind closed doors where only you know the initiates are into and yes it
sounds like a lot of the what you hear in secret societies Illuminati Freemasonic.
You know other societies like that they're they're all based on the same template so the same
goes with science the same goes with medicine that's why for example in medicine you'll see that for
example cancer treatments that are prescribed to the public at large are never used by the higher
ups within the medical community right what are they doing right see so there's many levels you
know to it you hear now there's a lot of stuff talking about the deep state that runs the regular
state that's kind of a spurious thing because they don't understand what a sovereign state is
you know there is no hidden government that government is simply an institution that is
corporatized and it has a private shareholders it could be anywhere from you know a handful of people
to several scores of people owning groups of countries and people just don't understand that
and that's fine it doesn't mean that we shouldn't say it so there is a secret aspect to everything
even food people go to the supermarket and they purchase food to eat or whatever or even if they
grow it they don't do it autonomously they engage in commerce to obtain things and they're
you know how many times do you find out later on that something was dangerous or cancerous well why
wasn't it explicitly shown when when it was initially introduced to market it was always known
to be such I mean they're not that devoid of the knowledge of what they're putting into the food
chain let's say so every aspect of what people engage in consciously whether it's the mindset sorting
mechanism or the knowledge there's many layers to it I like of referencing Demetri Callizov he's
a sort of a nonchalant internet celebrity regarding the events of 9/11 he talks about the three
truths you know the first truth is what you give the public the second truth is what you give
those are administer the public and then there's the third truth which is really what's happening
right now from from the sorting mechanism there's many ways to discuss it you know the mindset like the
average they call them the masses the public at large seven billion plus whatever the number is
they're not viewed as individuals are viewed as a single group or an entity just like you would say
I went to the beach you don't the word beach does not include all of the billions or
millions of grains of sand it's just a single entity made up of many components you see so when you
address the masses it's one way because they're actually a single component forget about all the stuff
you're told about you you're an individual and you have a right to do this and you're for you're not
actually in private whenever you're confronted with this authority in any institution they always
say you have to be like everyone else so you know that's another part of the that that third truth or
that what I call the bovine reality right bovine excrement reality then there's the second truth
let's say or you go higher up behind and then there's the story or the ideology of those that run
these institutions whether it's educational religious governmental medical scientific whatever
they have another credo another mindset to run you know they need to keep things in order because
that's their task they're the administrators the facilitators and then you have those that are
behind that make all of the deals and how to maintain something an institution through time or
actually evacuated from a memory or eliminate it right there's institutions that have gone by the
wayside over the years those guys that are or and gals that are behind the scenes that are
maintaining power or negotiating to keep the power or monitoring the system have a different ideology
in mindset again now just to interject something when you go into the whether you want to consider them
higher or lower as irrelevant when you go into the first tier with the let's say the oligarchs or
those that are running the the administrators that are running the public they their mindset you
can discuss the things we discuss on Greeks because they get a chuckle and they laugh they're like
yeah it's totally fine that's exactly how it is right and when you go to the second level
the administrative level they're all like well you know well yeah who are you going to tell that too
right meaning like you know your information we can discredit then when you go to the masses which is
the seven but with this in for this type of Greek speak information they're like oh that can't be
true that I get out of here I don't believe that see so that is again another form of sorting is
in it so same thing religious medical scientific whatever all of these institutions and parts of
the human culture have the same structure what is told to the masses what is told to those that
are running the masses and then those that are actually in control of those running the masses
right and and just in short in summary Greek speak is not a dialogue or a narrative directed
towards the masses or the mass could whether it's seven billion or a million or a hundred million
they're all just consider them one thing they you know you you know you've seen one you've seen them
all kind of thing with slight difference of course people have their individual traits but
it's like if you go to a bread a bakery a bakery where they bake millions of loaves of bread a day
they're monitored so they all look the same but I'm telling you no two loaves of bread or bake the like
but they're all packaged and they're discounted and they're thrown away very easily they're not
considered very important but they do make the substance of the food chain people are the same way
they tend to have individual qualities individual character individual thoughts but really when
when you are on the level thinking and absorbing as truth what is put out to that group you're just
you're all the same you meet you meet one in other words you go outside your door and you run
in someone on the street chances are how many more people you run into the street on any day or any
week or any year they're all going to be generally the same that's what I mean by the masses and then
you have the administrators of the more privileged type they have a different mindset on their
position is to make sure that the masses act like the masses should based on whatever script has been
determined and then you have again those that are beyond those those that own or control the
administrators right in other words those are control the president or the CEO or the administrator
and they have a different mindset again so just to repeat myself the Greek speak is not
directed towards or anyone but it is more in line with that first group okay but let's look at it
at the level of an individual say right because ultimately there's always an exception and
if we're talking about a number of seven billion then the exception that pertains to that could
be in the several hundreds of millions right so we could still make a significant pool of people even
though they're spread out all over the place that could use this kind of information so in your
appearance on other podcasts you've mentioned something called the quote unquote proper mindset so
let's look at that and you also did mention an episode zero that definitions are important so let's
emphasize that here also if I were to venture the definition of mindset as being something like an
established set of attitudes held by somebody or a characteristic way of thinking how would you
triangulate those conceptions into understanding what a proper mindset is okay simple let's say this
is the earth and things are done a certain way well what is that way how are things done ultimately
you're going to figure out that it is a dictatorship meaning not the way that people are told
what a dictatorship is meaning there is communication and within those those communications there's
hierarchy the highest hierarchy within communicating on planet earth is what's known as a vow a pledge
or a contract okay so once that that is embedded within the society and just to go back for a moment
when I say this society we could balance back and forth between the three levels there that we just
mentioned but just like the old rits have written you know the poor man and the rich man or the king
and the popper are both born naked and dying naked right they all bleed the same they all need food
and water and drink so when I mentioned the three groups prior yes they all generally come from
the same pool bloodlines aside right so well and you mentioned also that there might be someone more
exceptional that can use this information in any one of those positions right so so we we
toggle back and forth to the general group that's been sorted and subdivided the way that we
mentioned earlier with the ultimate top controllers the administrators and the masses they all
come from the same pool essentially that have been sorted into those positions but essentially
to go back to to the question I would say that the how would you how would you align in other words
what you say do you mean what you say and you say what you mean right the concept of a contract that
is basically the the idea on how everything runs give you an example and this is actually how you
keep the masses in control and why they need to be kept ignorant giving example in the financial
system anyone even even if you're not considered with sharpest tool in the shed and not that smarter
intelligent now with the what's facilitated called the internet and information access anyone within
five or ten minutes that has a clear mind and seeks comprehension can discover the world financial
system is a credit based system and when then in other five minutes if you ask where does it come
from you might start going on the fringe because it's not polite to ask where to credit where to
the credit comes from but actually comes from a system of pledges right so for example again
and spend another five minutes and either fifteen minutes into researching this on the internet
let's say or even a law library you'll find out that there is no money and essentially when you
make purchases with financial institutions or government institutions or corporations or banks
what they call banks they have no money to lend you they actually take your signature and whatever
is written on the paper that you sign to is created out of thin air essentially based on the credit
that you have basically the credit you you you've been pledged as as a child to a birth certificate
and that has a certain value right this is very easy to discover and this is actually
not discredited or or denied by anyone in the first two that we mentioned earlier sections of society
this is absolutely agreed to but then how can someone who's walking around with a long frown on
their face they hey why are you so sad is because I am in debt and I am in trouble if I don't pay
that debt well how could there be a debt if there is no money it's a credit based economy and they
actually just took your signature and monetized it all right and gave it to you in the form of an
account that you can draw from or something right and the reason these are not really accounts because
in reality an account has to have something in it but this is how the merchant system is always
worked by the way within merchants so the people are actually sad they're people being harmed
by not being able to quote unquote pay a debt now if you go back to try to counter this on the
very regular convention in the what they call the courts or the bank they always say well we
have a contract here you agreed that this is a debt even though there was nothing right you see
now the same thing goes with religious all the religions with the stuff they put in front of
people if you start bringing up the let's say usually there's a text an ancient writ that that that
leaders of that religion professed you adhere to well if you read any of those texts in any religion
you'll see that the religions are not doing anything in the text or maybe resembles it but not
not doing it well at all when you bring that issue up they'll say well we don't go by that really
we go by our tradition and you agreed you see your how dare you question is you agree to be part
of our congregation the same thing goes with the medical system right you when you go to a doctor
you have to sign a consent form which really releases them of liability of anything they do to you
if you ever read the consent forms the doctors it's pretty scary you see it goes on and on and on and
on so what pretty much most of what people are engaged in is based on falsehood and it's a falsehood
that we can can be described succinctly like I just did with the financial system but the true the
the reality of it is that what's pressed upon them well it pressed meaning to oppress them is
that they vowed to do it anyway see the issue with people with for example money and debt the
issue is not whether they let you anything you sign a contract saying you're going to do it but
right but I never got anything well that that's irrelevant that's your concept what are you talking
about know what you know everybody knows you know the plausible aspect dream you see so this is
basically how the earth is run it's by pledges and by agreements that's why for example even today
one of the well actually in many ways yes in many ways no even today one of the gravest things you
can do to someone other than extreme physical violence is to insult them i mean times that you heard
that right right they feel insulted or humiliated or dishonored right so it's basically what you say
and when you say it and and if you mean what you're saying that holds everything together
and knowing that would lead one to actually be more careful about what they say and what they
agree to especially if it's in what they call legal contract form right or or beyond you know
because the proper mindset because you have the faculty is to investigate or read or study
a little bit about these things before you engage them but you have something called culture
and tradition which is which is what steers the individual into doing how and what they do right so
I mean it's very easy to to if you were to visit the earth from somewhere else where they did have a
proper mindset and there is such a thing as a proper mindset by the way as you brought up and hopefully
I'll bring that forward a little bit more is they would say they would come to the earth and say
these people are insane it's not a meaning not healthy as a group it doesn't matter what country
you go to again the masses right so but then again if you go to the administrators those that are
controlling the masses and you poise the same you know or come to them with the same posture let's see
if they're doing the right thing they they don't even know what to do right they're just they'll just say
this is how we do it and this is how we've been told by who well eventually when you find out who
is telling them what to do and how to do it in any institution or any aspect of human society you
will find a small group of people that are let's say we've brought up the word esoteric
nonetheless extremely sublime and esoteric and their belief system and their mindset has absolutely
nothing to do with who they've hired as administrators and ultimately not only the masses that they
rule but actually the masses that they believe they actually own and if you ask them how do you
own the people they say well they pledged everything to us right so people also have an idea of
knowing things when they have not studied it simply hearing about something is not knowing it or you
know hearing hearing or listening or engaging something as it is done superficially by most people
through their whole lives about everything even how to raise children for example is not studying it
example would be let's say studying an ancient manuscript is not the same as reading it
right study means to actually look at it and comprehend it so if you were to say that the majority of
the people if not if you were to put let's say a giant rubber stamp on the earth and say no one
here is paying attention statistically that would be very accurate statistically there's a very
small group of people that do I mean even from the three levels that we've discussed so the proper
mindset based on what you're saying is the ability for somebody to assess reality based on the
empiricism of their surroundings to commit themselves to studying that as opposed to just going off of
assumption well study it and also understand that the most important thing on earth is what you say
and do you mean what you say and are you going to do what you say it's one of those things
people don't discuss it for example years ago there was a one of these law enforcement
TV shows back in the 60s or 70s and the as the as the show opened they have the opening credit let's say
and they have the star of the show I forgot the name of it but it was a detective speaking and he
says well we're going out to stop crime and make sure people fulfill their contracts and make sure
that what this is a made for TV thing back in the six they actually just set it you know so
the thing is it's very simple in other words the things that people find
disharmonious in their lives are there because they put themselves there well how because
what happens is the the disharmony that they're experiencing is nothing but the follow through of
what they said they were doing going to do and not doing it so again the financial system is an
easy one there it's you cannot be expected to fulfill an impossibility of law right if something is
impossible the law cannot demand you do it well one of those things believe it or not is debt in a
credit-based economy you can't be a lender and a creditor the same person can you have let's say a
silver coin or coin in your right pocket and say I'm going to lend it to myself when I move it over to
the left that's kind of ridiculous and this is the way this financial system works the same with
the medical industry but in order for people to properly comprehend that because we do understand
that too so a certain extent you're speaking over people's heads because they haven't studied it
so we'll get we'll of course have to take it on the face of what you're saying and then people
have to go and look into it themselves but when we talk about developing this proper mindset which
perhaps we could do a little better job of quantifying it but at least we can say that it escapes most
people so whenever people discuss mental phenomena such as mindset things get a bit abstract which is
what I want to get away from because it's not like the material world for example when it comes to
feeds a physical prowess you either run the distance or you don't you either climb to the top of
the mountain or you didn't and the difference between success and failure is pretty well defined
and understood but when you're trying to encourage or build up a mindset it's easy to encounter
resistance in the world where people don't agree on what's proper what's not or what's important
or what's not so the development of a proper mindset why is that so difficult for people?
Well which people is it going to be the masses which are seven billion that are all act as one
and then you have the within the society who are you running into an administrator like someone
who's been tasked by the owners let's say to make sure that the masses are in line or in check
or going about you know certain amount of stability which I want to talk about also what stability
in peace means to man right now and or you can run into albeit and secret they don't show up with
pomp and circumstance and limousines and big announcements the people that own everyone they
think they own everyone on the planet at least and they can prove it on paper. So then we say it
like this you're talking to there's three people behind a curtain you don't know who's who and you
don't know who represents what mindset so now you have to make a sort of general all encompassing
statement so that whoever is behind the curtain will be able to absorb what you're saying.
Well then what I would say to them is I want nothing to do with any of you until I find out a little
bit more of what's going on on this earth right and as you start to find out what's going on
on this earth then you you have to address each one individually like for example a simple way
to do that is with the masses you completely avoid them you know but it doesn't mean you have to be
on civil and if you're running a business and you have employees you just deal with people on a
level that is strictly what you're dealing with them on right and sometimes you have to be cordial
and you have to always be polite and impeccable and how you look how you perform you know
what you especially when you say you're going to do something but there is no hope in them there's
no you just you know if the one emerges that it seems to be extraordinary then you take account of that
the administrators are also to be avoided right because they're not in that position because they were
chosen for their merit they they they look for merit but also they're heavily heavily compromised
and then you have those that think they own the world and they'll just laugh at everything you say no
matter what okay so we're going to make we're going to have to operate based on a presumption that
we're talking to an extraordinary person who happens to find himself among the masses by being a
victim of circumstance well then you have what's called a potential for a fellowship right because
the typical aspect of fellowship is people that share things in common right but let's say you find
this person and even if you want to fellowship with them that's very fine and well because you realize
that there's something to be developed but that person is still going to be censored to a certain degree
and that person is still going to have a lacking mindset to a certain degree so my wondering is
why would it be difficult for even that person to escape the norm that has infected everybody else?
Well the thing is well okay you could look at it from many ways from the initial aspect of you
determining that this person is extraordinary they would have already overcome most of the pitfalls
of the censorship and the poor mindset or the low quality thinking or the pitfalls that the masses have
right so you've they've already that one of the ways you would determine or qualify that they
are extraordinary is that they've already passed many of the hurdles that would be considered
basic which would be why you would be very simple to say avoid the masses because they can't even
overcome the most basic thought form right so this person obviously in most cases if they
if they deem to be extraordinary has overcome that so now you're going to be working on another
level of the censorship which again goes back to perception studying observation discussion
good science for example right we don't know about this but we could be this it could be that
take good notes and observe it right so the the aspect of some you know when we break away from the
the general three groups let's say and the the person who is extraordinary has already
overcome many of the these basic things and I think we've gone into in the past what the cosmic
censorship is because initially it's very easy to lean heavily on these three categories that I
just presented but essentially there's an even higher category because we just don't perceive it
directly at this point and that's called the divine or the things that we don't perceive that we
know control or we we we don't see them but we see their effect let's say and the the only reason
we actually give in e credence that that's such a condition exists is because it's been memorialized
meaning recorded throughout history and you know of course the people preempt
study into these things based on their upbringing their personal desire and all that and the
other thing is if you lean heavy on your own personal desires what you like in other words your
favorite color your favorite food your favorite shirt your whatever if you lean too heavily on that
let's just not even say to being narcissistic but if you still lean heavily on what you prefer strictly
you're not going to be able to see things objectively anyway you see so the object
of thought form is not your own right because if something is clear in other words for something to
be objective it should be presented with clarity and anyone can see it but no not anyone can see it
so what's going on if it's so clear and so visible and so discernible yet very few can see it
is it really that clear and discernible or is it still hidden or is it that those that can see it
are blocked and I would guess the latter actually more than guess let's just say softly I guess
but I know it's the latter and it's for sure the latter meaning the people are blocked
and why do I say this because you can you could see it's been memorialized.
You've talked a lot about the elite classes whether it's the people that you know we want to
presume are at the top or the people that have administrative positions that are still considered
to be elite and in the past you've lampooned for example the academics by describing them as people
that only have the appearance of having knowledge and some of the markers for that is you know
the circular way that they talk or their system of peer review where they just approve of each
other for not breaking rank so to transpose that kind of analysis to what we're talking about here
what are some of the markers of somebody who doesn't have the right mindset but does have the
appearance of having the right mindset just so that you know people can recognize that whether
it's somebody who looks wise and isn't or somebody uses it kind of rhetoric that falsely indicates
what they understand. Simply put like you said the academics are typically going to find them in
the educational institutions from the preschool kindergarten all the way up to the doctorate level
what they call university though that's a very you know again the institution you know this is let's
say a pork sausage factory do you expect to go there and see millions of gallons of strawberry ice
cream being made. No you're going to be seeing slaughtered pigs so this is the academia for example
and if you study the history of academia you'll see it is another one of these tools
and if you study for example the educational institution is a well-known fact very well
established especially in the western world that over 50 years ago education has been brought
down the level is been brought down that it's actually laughable right so to pursue a higher education
is to pursue higher laughability and ridiculousness. I used to have a saying that if you actually
believe anything that you've been taught beyond the eighth year of school it most likely will do
irreparable damage to you. So with these academics they typically want them to have higher
university degrees so that means another eight or ten years of school right at least so what we're
talking about people that are at this point lost and they're basically tools being used by that
first group as a buffer zone and if you study some of the ancient societies I remember coming across
over a decade ago how the academics with the law merchants which are known as attorneys
where are held firmly within society as a buffer zone between the elite and also to keep society
on a normal path let's say right an example for that would be let's say someone invents a small box
or something you put in your pocket and it powers an entire house well the first that that's determined
that news goes up to the if they the way things are now they would know it as you were doing it
because you go online and order things and talk and all that's being flagged for example
but once you establish that or on your way to establish let's say a device that can do such a thing
the first thing they do is sick academia on you where did you get your degree let's say this is a
bus driver that did this you know it basically no he's not even a high school education let's say
the first thing they do is they sick academia on you where did you get your PhD in physics oh he
doesn't listen everyone he thinks he has a device in that that's all fake you know all the
demonstrations that he's showing it powering a house little tiny device doesn't use any fuel as we know
that's all fake and he doesn't even have a physics degree ha ha ha 99.99% of the masses will agree
with the academics and this man will be shunned you see the same thing if someone comes up with
quote unquote a cure for cancer the first thing they do is sick academia where did you get your
medical degree ha ha he doesn't have a medical degree all those are fake testimonies you see how it
goes on and on and on the same happens with the legal stuff the same thing happens with the science
stuff same thing happens with the religious stuff you go on and on and on categorically and this is
how academia is being used also it's to waste your time also it's a form of entertainment in the old
Roman courts they used to bring in Greek scientists academic academic admissions to demonstrate things
to the royal court of the seizures and others as entertainment many of the magicians the illusionists
that you see a borrow from they always have their ear on the door or know a quote unquote scientist
to use their right to deceive the public right you see how it's used so it's basically a buffer zone
that's that's a simple way to see that you know are what kind of a tool are they right another thing
is by just sheer experience if you're working amongst institutions that are educational or academic
and you start revealing things that just simply aren't true you're kicked you're ousted from the
institution right the same thing let's say a doctor comes up with something that really cures
something in a simple way what's the first thing that happens to him that's you know that gets him
out of that field he will be no longer practice medicine if you try to do it we'll put you in prison
for practicing about a license because we took that from you right people people in the religious field
the same lawyers don't know attorneys don't know the law how do I know that's a very general statement
but it's very accurate because if an attorney knows the law and he tries to actually use it in the
court he will be disbarred right doctors don't know how the human body works because if they actually
learn how the human body works and they started practicing that way they would lose their medical
license so so the way you get real information is by some form of congregation in other words of
extraordinary people communicating and this is the way it's been for thousands of years I'm not
just this is not news even though some people might tune into this and say this is really different
than what I've heard before but however we can already establish and we have already established that
the elite classes act as a buffer so what I'm trying to say is if we turn away from the elite classes
because people still go about their daily lives interacting with each other for example their
family members or their friends particularly the young children are influenced by celebrities and
so on and so forth so what is the identifying marker to look for when you're going about your
daily life and you aren't in constant connection with an elite person like how does it child even look
well hands to see that she doesn't have the right mindset well the people that are
administering and controlling are not elite at all they're actually even less
they seem like they have privilege but if you knew what they had to go through or to sustain
that position you would you would turn your stomach right this isn't any field right
in other words be compromised heavily so the elite are just sitting back it's just livestock
management for them and the way that you know how discerning it is by if you if the person is
functioning in an institutional capacity they're full of crap because they can't be there by telling
but with true knowledge and really you see what I mean this has been throughout history
even during the times of the Renaissance the European Renaissance it was the same thing
right so if a person in that this is a long this is the long in the short of it
essentially you're going to have to spend more than five minutes in your lifetime discovering the
truth about any subject you're interested in on your own right and within five minutes of studying
it meaning you have to know the history of it right you go back from the beginning when this was
introduced in the culture or humankind and then move forward you you can make a personal determination
there and say well this is not for me or you might say this is not for me but I need to know it
because I run into this stuff all the time it's an anarchistic point of view and our means without
our coast means leader it's a leaderless thought pattern you know like all revolutionaries
are actually closet aristocrats right a Frank Herbert said that there's no such thing as
someone that wants to be a leader or free of people or change society that is not
in a secretive way just like those that are ruling right now and he's just envious of it and
they may not be personally responsible for such a thought but they're raised in that concept
so don't buy into any form of a lead movement organization with a human leadership that's based
on the the normal way you people have been taught society goes through changes is done the normal
way we've been taught there are changes is there is a discarding absolessence of old things new
things come in or revival of new old things or there's revolution and that's I wanted to touch on
that also this might be pertinent to the question but I wanted to get it in there and how much
we are on time but people essentially if you want to learn how these creatures work meaning the
masses they hate peace and harmony now if it sounds crazy Greek because I could go out on the
street and interview a million people in the next 10 years and they're all going pretty much say
they like peace and harmony yes but don't listen to what they say watch what they do peace and
harmony to the average masses is is really a stagnative death to them how do I know this well
for centuries newspapers in print have been sold based on what sensationalism how many times have
you heard people gathering together and forming you know unity and productivity for I don't know a
holiday or some cause that should be let's say to edify or help other people on what scale is that
done compared to people coming together and productivity when war is declared right so you're
going to see that people get they do like violence if you look at their what they call current events
for the nightly news or whatever if there isn't anything violent or scandalous it's I was the news
out there was nothing on the news tonight right people like violence they like scandal and this goes
all the way up because aren't you going to have the principle let's say presidents or the chief
administrators say we have to go fight this enemy don't you have the religious leaders say the same
thing on and on and on people just hate peace and harmony what who was put in front of you as the
head of a religion is the administrator he's just a figure you see the same with governments it's the
same you know you know all the even the if you study your monarchies in the world today
they're they're not real monarchies right they were just like if you look at the Middle East they
were put there by the British and the French in the 1920s if you look at the English monarchy the
Queen that whole genealogy fell apart in the late 1400s King Edward that lineage the real for example
the real king by lineage and bloodline lives somewhere in Australia in a small you know thousand
square foot house I think he's like he operates a rice mill or something all right it's not hard to
who he is yeah he does yeah he it's well he found out later on in life but it's not hard in other
words it's not these are not these are actual things anyone can look up the king of Jordan is not
he he's he was just a bunch of people that the British and French that you're the king now okay
that's your might kingdom yeah I mean all the all they're all like that the the only one that
might have survived something was is the the show of Japan right so this is a ridiculous ridiculous
world and it doesn't mean you have to plunge into it as you've been told wholeheartedly you know reserve
yourself in other words the advice that I would give to especially young people I feel sorry for
the young people because the older people have nothing to say worthwhile anymore but if you're going
to do anything other than food clothing and shelter see if your belly grow growls you need something to
eat if you're thirsty should drink something and if you need to sleep you should find a comfortable
place to rest but anything else outside of that you should spend at least five minutes studying
what it's based on let's move on to talk about objectivity and then perhaps we can tie that back to
the idea of having a proper mindset so it's safe to say that it's better to know something than to
think that you know something right although people endlessly debate the difference between those two
things but in any case I think most people appreciate the comfort that comes from acting out of
assurance rather than assumption so I bring up the concept of objectivity because I think to fully
make sense of something you have to be able to first grab a hold of it with your rationality and
examine it so what I want to ask the Greek is how would you say that objectivity is brought to
bear on the process of parsing the world and you sort of touched on that a little bit but to make
it more concise well to make it the most concise right now what's called the information age people
are being dying a slow death through information the same way it's been any institution is there to
protect those that control pretty much what they think is everything right so you so again just to
go back to I guess maybe how do you object to find how where is the knowledge and knowing versus
thinking you know on one hand you could say it's shameful for someone to walk around saying that
they have a credit card debt it's actually absolutely shameful for me to even hear that right and
if you listen to them they'll say well they'll come and take my stuff away now they're being
motivated by penalty right they look at all the stuff that's been put in front of them as being
knowledge when reality there was right it's they agreed to pay it back right if you ever look at a
credit card application it says we can report on our credit experience with you doesn't say that
you have to pay your debt there's no debt the same thing goes with the medical people on both
ends the patient you know those receiving the care and those dishing it out they think they know
but they don't know so on many aspects of it again five minutes spend five minutes researching it
and then you'll know if you want to continue researching it or not right now people are having
death by internet right and in some cases literally with the type of power and am putting meaning
an amplitude that they want to put out with cell phone towers you know you hear a little bit about
that some of those rumors are are spurious but the truth of it is that it's true it is a very
un and there was death by information indeed so what is the importance of the objectivity aspect
for parsing that reality when to get the objectivity allows you to operate in a higher on a more
efficient level I've given the the example prior to years ago when there was a big
good survivalist movement in the u.s. about prepping for a coming disaster that was supposed to come
around whatever 10 years ago and it ever did right there are people that went out and invested in a
lot of photovoltaic panels 12 volt systems off the grid type stuff that's just sitting around
doing nothing now what kind of efficiency was that because they took in the information thinking
that they knew but it was just bovine excrement so how do you discern that you know I use the
thing about edible corn you know if you're really hungry would you eat corn digested corn
in out of someone's poo how tempting would that be well depends on how hungry you are
but the I noticed that the masses are always eating they're not even corn they're leaving the corn
they're eating the poop I would rather have fresh clean corn not stuff stuff that's been eaten and
that how many times have you heard spinning of information or it's been processed you know
it's been filtered out that's what the mass is you know everyone agrees to how many times you
heard that that's what everyone agreed to right going back to what I said earlier everything on this
earth is based on what you agreed to your contracts your your vows do you say what you mean in mean
what you say it's a it's a place of secrets but yet the secrets are hidden in plain sight
and so what I'm trying to sort of look at is the interplay between objectivity on one hand and
subjectivity on another hand in how you either uncover those secrets or come to understand those
secrets of their presented to you because what you've said quite often is that these things are
hidden in plain sight so the secrets are still there for people to observe but they don't necessarily
know what they're seeing so right let me present this there's a way that the world has been conceptualized
in modern times which is that there's an external world and it's full of objects like buildings and
vehicles and people and such and these things exist whether anyone likes it or not independent
of your belief or your opinions or your preferences so that is said to be an objective existence and
then you have the subjective world which consists of internal states of mind that are not ontologically
objective so if we presume that to be accurate then what I'm seeing is that modern man has a sort
of difficulty in in describing the objective reality which is a little bit of what you're saying
and as a result of that though what you have is a form of skepticism that has arisen where people
discount the objective reality altogether now so we see that with postmodernism we see that with
social constructivism and so my question is what kind of response should you have to this over
emphasis that we're seeing in the world on subjective worldviews where people just make stuff up?
People would rather have the subjectivity because it's a known assailant
right it's a known assailant they've already agreed on what is not known and is known and even
what is known as false it's okay because we seem to be living another day where when you begin to
know the more you do know the more you subject to yourself to what you don't know
where the subjective person will say well I don't know anything about that but I'm just going to do
what everyone else is doing so at least the assailant there is known at least the unknown is known by
others and I have some protection by numbers where the one who is objective the more he begins to
know and he moves on to another thing to know he's actually does because he doesn't know of it yet
or know much about it yet he is subjecting himself to pure unknown it's an unknown assailant
on the psyche so it actually takes the bold and the strong to know and the weak and the cowardly
to be subjective. Another thing that is reoccurring that I see a lot is this idea of the truth right
sometimes stylized with a capital T and we see it talked about quite loftily by philosophers and
politicians and religious leaders to the point where a version of that kind of rhetoric has been
created for the masses now and promulgated mainly through new age and you know leftist media
and public figures who encourage people to speak their truth right so it's not the truth but
speak your truth and so people have a lot to say about truth today either way but when you hold
their feet to the fire it's revealed quite quickly that their truth is just conjecture and subjectivity
like I like this or my belief is that how would you say that that becomes the de facto mindset?
Well just like that they're cowards and they're weak it's very simple and that's the norm
actually the what you hear when you hear people being in the military and proud of it those
are all the cowards and the weak ones the special forces even the special forces of subject to
that the character right now I believe it or not but a true warrior will never admit that he's gone
into a campaign in with pride you see another way to say it is truth to a pig is just pouring
slop into a trough it's time to eat the same thing the same truth for the pig would be if you had
a let's say hut cuisine five star meal prepared imported into the trough that's truth also now which
one is more effective for those managing the pigs to just get whatever slop and satisfy the pig
or to be more perfect and get a five star meal and put it in the trough for the pig when the
pig really finds them both to be quite adequate so what you're actually witnessing with the crap that
the masses feed on and the different levels is actually operating on a high level of efficiency
based on the fact and the known established observation that humans do not like peace and harmony
they say they do but a pig snorts and grunts right he grunts the same way and snorts the same way
when he's happy and when he's sad the pig does but when he's in extreme discomfort they let
out this really your piercing squeal right so most people will say they want peace and harmony
but i see them get very excited when there's controversy um scandal and war yeah but can you show
me a time in history with that's not the case i'm not saying that there it was not the case at any
point i'm just saying this is a cross sectional view if we're going to take a cross section of
humanity at any time in history it'll pretty much be the same the interesting thing of it the shameful
interesting thing of it is most times most people that are apologetic uh try to like they're representing
the good side of humanity will say well they didn't know any better that's the shameful part
because okay it was not difficult to know better okay where hold up though
because if it's if it's not difficult to know better than we should be able to find some
reasonable sample size of people that knew better so if we're saying that that cannot be found at any
point in history then we're talking about a condition that is internal to the human existence right
you can't separate a pension for violence from what it means to be a human being so how can you
then also say that it's an indictment when it's a permanent condition it is well the those
you'll never hear of the of the reality of what's happening on earth institutionally because you
can't exist in an institution unless you tow the the bovine extraments right but if you look closely
there are how many times have you heard of writers philosophers scientists have very stark
criticism about the things going on in their day throughout history all the way all the way back to
ancient times right so there's always been a small group uh that might be you like we said earlier
the extraordinary ones if you read any of their ancient rites in any culture there's always a
small extraordinary group and there's actually two there's the one that's put in front of the
masses which is total you know crap usually they can't be substantiated and then there there's
the reality of the extraordinary group that are just sit by the the wayside patient whether they have
a good life or not for whatever you know age they live to is another story this is just the way
this planet operates and the reason this is quite obvious the reason we discuss this is for
anyone who can grasp this and comprehend it and actually apply it right this is all a pliket of
you have a more efficient mindset again back to the financial people say well there's going to be a
big financial crash is going to be problems right well they change a lot of financial systems by
first creating a depression well what does that mean well on paper that happens often but it
doesn't happen often when they're when the people lose their ability to gain food clothing and
shelter then it's time to put on something that they wouldn't have accepted before
so right now they let's say there's talk about a financial let's say meltdown or whatever they
whatever they put out there you have to say to yourself well we know it's a credit-based economy
and we know that the amount of currency that's put on the market is based on the birth rate we know
that for sure meaning the individual to himself and as all the facts to prove it so the only way to
actually crash the financial system which actually it would actually raise the the value of the
currency very highly for whichever country did it first was to lower the birth rate so if you lower
the birth rate because there's less babies being born there's less currency put into the market the
value of that currency will rise according to others and it could rise to the point where no one
else can use it because it's too expensive to use it and then you can you can't do trade and that's
the really how it works and you won't find this on the internet really even though it's the truth
and this is actually you know this is common knowledge amongst the first and second groups that we
mentioned earlier but the masses don't even bother because if you throw in the pick trough that
information next to it oh you owe debt they're going to eat it up the same and they're going to be
more focused on the one that's going to come after them later right so when you hear us something
about this or that or the other you have to see what is the topical nature of you know what's
being discussed right and what do I know about it and then you make a judgment call is it a really
call to urgency or is it just another thing they're feeding all the you know the trough put the
feeding trough and you'll find that the majority of anything and everything you've encountered
outside of providing food clothing shelter for yourself is that way it's just rubbish quality
let's unwrap up on the objectivity a bit with one last thing so when you try to bring
objectivity to bear on a situation the pushback that people give is that you're being cynical or
pessimistic or even judgmental right they don't want your evaluation to be based on the observable
reality but rather on an attitude or a belief so the conclusion that I draw from that is that
a certain type of judgment has become taboo in popular thought and we've all heard someone say
that you shouldn't judge or don't judge and they say that as a sort of transcendent moral claim
that they feel is backed by let's say the biblical text or some other text if we fall back on a
definition that I've heard you use previously then judgment is essentially making a decision that
allows you to navigate objectively versus saying I don't know what's going on so let's just close
our eyes and hope for the best can you expand a bit on that as far as how you can't be an effective
judge of things without being objective well of course it's another word for judgment is discernment
the reason we're having this stream right now or sonic event is because I've been very judgmental
today meaning that when I was out traveling in an engine driven wagon known as an automobile
I had seen a red light at intersection and I made a judgment call should I speed up or should I slow
down and stop yield and stop now that when the people say it's too judgmental it's because they're
just more interested in you know is he filling the trough the way that I'm used to you know having
the trough filled right give you an example on that years ago I was those a particular group this
is more 30 years ago so they they had a lot of pride in doing organic natural food and it was a
holiday and it was New York City so they said well we have all this like a food left over from this
banquet it was really high cuisine and so let's go down and feed the homeless great so we took a
bunch of plates and covers and all that and prepared all these meals with wonderful food you know
dishes and we went down to the homeless in New York City and we present this plate to them that you
know you it would be very expensive at a restaurant and the homeless people look at it and they
threw it on the floor and I said no I want hot dogs right so so at that point do you do you become
judgmental if you say well look at the sun grateful son of a bitch or do you just avoid the entire
thing saying of course because that's what you're right the reason they're in such a condition is
because they don't recognize you know this or they are mentally unstable there's many reasons
do is that a judgment call to actually make a determining factor like that right so that's what
you see in front of you I mean some homeless people wouldn't do that but ones seem to have done that
not all of them I'd say out of the 50 that we encountered half of them did that which is actually
pretty damning right so when you look at the masses and when I say just leave them alone unless you
have minimum just keep it in a cordial you want to look like a spot you want to act like a
a the spy in another country you know you're you're you're far and you're just observing you know
you're not going to say well you're not going to tell in your life story but in what they're doing
wrong you just you know you go to the auto part store hi how are you great okay I'll eat this part
thank you very much by and in the background you might hear the guy saying well my way for it not
my credit card it or I have high blood pressure I mean you're going to stop and try to educate the
fool now he might be one of the extraordinary ones you might just give a an investment in the
opportunity not in him but in the opportunity because if you don't say anything and you walk away
there's an opportunity lost there for you to discern whether this one is an extraordinary one
that'll actually understand what you're saying or take heed to it and change his life and be
more efficient instead of saying he has credit card debt and high blood pressure which none of
those things exist it unless you agree to it right so if you don't say anything there's an opportunity
to lost but then let's go back to the homeless people chances are if 50% of the people you talk to
about objective things to to kind of like change or make what they're doing better based on a
judgment call of what they're saying is false or on the general perception if 50% accepted 50%
rejected that would still be pretty high acceptance factor but I'm telling you you'd have to go through
a thousand people before one right 0.01% so you're going to have to learn to live your life with
efficiency right and of course fellowship with those that can only because from a spiritual sense
meaning to keep your own peace in harmony which you hopefully you strive for it's best to have
others to speak to about these things but guard yourself because the general group is is not
is not ready for it and you can take that whether it's mis-entropic or not objectively it's very
mis-entropic but it doesn't mean you have to act as such on each individual level in other words
the healthiest way to perform on earth to anyone visiting this planet you should learn to
hate the entire culture and society and ebb and flow of our things are done but love the into each
one that you encounter as much in other words do the right thing that's what love means right
the actual group the institutions the structures the religions the culture is hateful
is hateful and can be hated very easily as something abominable something improper something
repugnant but the individuals themselves if you can if if they are open and if they are want to act
in a more efficient manner right they can be addressed maybe on an individual level not in a
group form though it doesn't work in a group the ending point of this stream is to find a way to
tie together this idea of having a proper mindset and being objective so if i were to ask the Greek
what came first the chicken or the egg you would give me an answer because there is an actual answer to
that it's not just this kind of open-ended question it's a clear case of cause and effect so to
transpose that idea to this case is there cause and effect relationship between having the proper
mindset and being objective so basically which one comes first the proper mindset or the pension
for being objective the proper mindset's assorting mechanism oh this is this is bulk this isn't
right this is going to waste my time this isn't right this is this is this is the how i'll get hurt
here here i won't assort you know you sort out perceptions and information leading to you know
you might say established knowledge and you can't do that without having objectivity now the
masses that are that are subjective they are not this is not this doesn't apply to them right you see
what i mean because if you run into the masses for example they go to the the the which doctors
in white lab coats and the big buildings that are expensive for example and they tell them they have
blood pressure right and their blood pressure is too high so they have to take medication well what
happens when the medication kills them they get the sympathy from all the other ones because saying oh
i'm sorry that didn't you know it's so sad you know that he had blood blood pressure it took the
medication maybe you could sue the drug companies but you can't but whatever you could try but
you know and this is they have this harmony in this disastrous mode that they're living in
but you know when i see when i hear someone dying of blood pressure medication like that's ridiculous
because there's no such thing as blood pressure in the body at all anyway if you go study it you'll
see that it's not even based on blood pressure itself it's based on heartbeat right so um
in other words there's no positive pressure in the human body whatsoever it's all slightly negative
and everything moves under a slight vacuum but if you if you actually try to bring this forward
well there's no sympathy there what are you talking about you know this person is dead they always
bring this up you know let's say you look at a story that's put out by government institutions
science religion or whatever you know um let's say let's play their role let's let's do their what
they do this is a very simple way of saying it right uh you're gonna say uh for example you're
gonna say oh i went to this restaurant and i enjoyed the meal now if you study that let's say
i'm a government or an institution science religious whatever well the Greek just said he went to
this restaurant i checked up on it that restaurant doesn't exist right it doesn't even exist how could
he go there and eat well my response to that person that says that is are you trying to question
what i like to eat how dare you question what i like to eat right never address the point that the
restaurant never existed you see so you see how it's not clear objectivity and subjectivity is mixed
if someone dies from blood pressure medication and you go to them and say there's also just
thing as blood pressure and say oh well they're dead how dare you right to hip-hop because
you say you can't there's nothing to work when there's nothing to work so what's being put out by
institutions in mainstream for thousands of years even now even more because like i said death by
information you can't work there's nothing to it to work with their in reality uh the best you can
do is is reform it in other words take what you need and leave the rest right and then you might have
to process it you know like the other day i went out and picked some carrots right i can't just pick
them out of the garden throw them on a plate and eat they have to be washed they have to be peeled you
know whatever you know depending prepared so what's the you know so there's an objective and subjective
mixing that has to be sorted via the mindset so let's say that someone wants the right mindset
and they want to be objective so that they can better parse the world but like you say it's a sorting
mechanism so you have to know what to sort you have to know what's important versus what's
unimportant which takes us back to judgment how would you even identify what's important or develop
the right value system to judge things simple uh the easiest way to do that is uh you prioritize
your existence now objective you can't be more objective than that food clothing shelter meaning
your physical existence because if you don't have if your physically ceased to be your your consciousness
goes into you know the abyss let's say right in other words you're you're you're uh you're dead
so in other words the opposite of that would be alive you need food clothing shelter food drink right
clothing and shelter here it well there's but there's also mental identification
well uh if you're seeking out to be objective and raise the quality of your food clothing and
shelter there's going to be a tremendous amount of mental edification on just on that path alone
that's enough to take up several lifetimes alone to do it well right or you could just get public
housing and food stamps let's say right yeah no thanks but actually that is the proper thing to do
because when they took money out of the society you were supposed to sign and get all the things
that you needed but they figured out that if we told people they just signed their name and get
everything they didn't know one's gonna want to work so how are we gonna maintain the streets and
the industry and farms and see ultimately you hear a lot of commentary about how the earth is set
up and the power structure and oh the pope is bad oh the government's corrupt oh the deep state
oh the drug companies oh the bankers you know there's no one out there discussing you'll find
to you know podcasts uh and all this alternative media but no there's no one out there um being
apologetic for the elite yes even though they worship the dark demonic beings that you read about and
all those things you don't want to read about let's say things that you've never read about like ancient
rits they they have discovered that you know how many times you heard like you know satanic Hollywood
which is true right all these actors that you see on tv in the movies yeah they all took it up the
butt right uh all of them not some of them is as it's called the 20 million dollar club right and
this is i mean this is wicked and where it comes to human sacrifice uh this is prevalent and all
of your industries uh uh and institutions right i don't mean defending that aspect of it that's
horrible and that needs to go but what i mean is uh let's say you were put in charge of controlling
what the masses see here educate their religion their food their medicine system would you want to do
that i wouldn't want to do it right so the people that are controlling the the administering is the top
let's say those that believe that they own the world they do have a pretty even though they laugh at
everything pretty much and they're foolish themselves they are um they've got quite the task right
because they have to have remember people hate peace uh and harmony so they have to throw in
enough chaos to keep the people happy but at the same time maintain enough peace and harmony that
there isn't it doesn't go out of control the other way right because then you can't control it all
right because even they even these let's say quote unquote Satanists that rule the world um do want a
certain amount of beauty also let's say right at least up until now hey that's the other thing you know
there's um people are very naive uh when you go look above the middle and higher part of society you
know the first of the guys that and gals that think they own the world in the middle is the administrators
which are your president's kings leaders of industry and then you have the masses right and then there's
you know it there's these are not distinct lines they're they're in medium lines because when you
look at the people that rule the mass as the presidents and kings will they have mayors and governors
below them right and then like assembly people and people below that and finally you get to the
masses um what when you start to look at how they're all set up um it trickles down in other words
it's not a when I said earlier that the people that run this world are satanic or worship dark forces
that is not a conspiracy theory that is a known established fact because you if you see how it
trickles down right they consider the masses their slaves or their property uh threat human history
when you were a slave you had the religion and the culture of your master right so if a Chinese
lord bought an Italian slave that Italian slave now has to take on the religion of his Chinese master
you see it and so forth and all the ways now if you look at the way architecture is presented
right uh it go it it it it goes back to ancient gods that were malevolent let's say or
what we call pagan gods if you look at for example the dollar bill on the us right on the back that is
all free Masonic stuff you know free mason's you know say well that's a conspiracy theory know it's
true that it's secrets you know and eventually it's not difficult to study that it is malevolent
at the top but again all of your all of your religious institutions are male all of your medical
scientific governmental whatever social sports anything Hollywood are all malevolent at the very
top in other words they have allegiances to malevolent beings whether it's human or nonhuman all of them
there's no exception to this you've heard of the pete felia rings in the in the Vatican right it's
even mainstream and not the pete felia rings but the abuse right Hollywood is made it's been put
mainstream you know and they always financial it's been put mainstream years ago to give an
example there was a guy I won't mention the company lie Lilly anyway he walked in a little early to
work one day was like a 40 story high rise somewhere in Chicago I'm any 80 story hires on the 40th floor
he goes in there it's early it's like five in the morning it wasn't supposed to be until 7 30
and he goes down he sees the hall the lights are up but there's a door open and the chief executives
of the company were in there doing a satanic ritual sands with the candles and the pentagram and
chicken blood and all that stuff right over a bunch of paperwork that they had formulas of new drugs
that they were going to put out right this was told to me this is pharmaceutical people praying over
their their formulas you know with ode to anyway very often when I speak on these matters I don't
want anyone to to say oh well I'm going to follow the Greek or I believe or I don't believe him or
where is he all of the speculation and the way people hear because the very few people are actually
listening is a difference the way people hear Greek speak is irrelevant what is relevant is
that you've heard it and file it away for a later date I think we've gone quite far as far as time
so we're we're gonna have to wrap up and I will endeavor of course to get these podcasts uploaded
as soon as possible undoubtedly we're going to revisit some of this material in the future hopefully next
week so unless there's anything else you want to conclude with greek I think I'm good you have any
finishing thoughts all the finishing thought is always considered would you would you always deal
with an enemy you know or an enemy that you don't know and the objective one that seeking knowledge
does not mind encountering an enemy he doesn't know because he's brave and bold where the coward
and the weak will always want to encounter an enemy they do know right one is subjective one is
objective the subjective masses that are weak and cowardly well if they don't know about something
what do they always say this is just a recap I'll just do what everyone else does and I'll be fine
and I agree with them because of we've already made a judgment call that those that say that are
not extraordinary at all right and they're all the same yeah they look different they smell different
they speak different but they're generally the same just like no two loaves of bread baked alike you
can go to the store and see all these loaves of bread pat kitchens identically and they all look the
same just grab one but I'll tell you go look very closely you'll see there's a small discerning
difference but for general purposes and statistically yes they are the same so most people you'll ever
meet whether they're friends family they're all the same don't be fooled and on that note I thank
everybody for listening and for tuning in and greek speak will be back next time with a podcast
on a different theme
you
(music playing)
[MUSIC]