[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening. This is the Greek Speak podcast featuring the Archon and the Greek.
I'm the Archon creator of GreekSpeak.com and this is episode three of my conversations with my co-host, the Greek, who will be with me in just a minute.
As I mentioned in the last episode, I'm aiming for more regularity with the live streams, so I've been able to stay on schedule for this one and I hope to continue doing these streams at one week intervals.
So let's hope for the best with that.
Episode two is available to listen to and download through the podcast page on the website. Also downloads are once again possible for episode zero since I've upgraded my SoundCloud tier.
For this episode, feel free to use the Greek Speak chat room as always to ask any questions and also GreekSpeak.com has no political, religious or commercial affiliations and is completely funded and managed by myself.
So that's it for my introduction. Please enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
[Music]
Hi there, Greek. Greetings. How you doing?
All right. Let's do another stream.
Right. So for this week, I'd like for us to examine a theme that's been mentioned here and there in previous episodes and quite a bit within the totality of Greek Speak itself, which is that of communication.
So for our purposes, I've broken that down to two subcategories, which are language and technology.
But let's start with the parent category that is communication itself.
I guess communication is generally thought to be a pretty unassuming word, whether you know you're associated with machines that you use to send messages or the etymological meaning of imparting information.
But from the kinds of things that you've talked about in the past, I've gotten the impression that the word carries a lot more nuance and implication that isn't touched upon much.
For example, you know, you can talk about art as a form of communication or certain aspects of nature that act as a communication.
What do you mostly associate that word with and what kinds of concepts are associated with it that don't typically get brought up?
Let's see. That's a pretty broad opening to walk through.
So let's walk through that opening and look left and right and up and down and a little behind.
I would say that, you know, by now maybe people have gotten the gist that when we bring up a term and focus a term on a term like communication, we should look up what it really means, right?
And the only way to figure out what things mean is to start on reference material and then lastly how it's being used in culture from an etymological dictionary or regular dictionary.
They seem to be both in agreement. It's a communal kind of, I guess, not to use the word again, communication and how to relate or I would say signaling is a synonym for it.
Like as if, you know, commonly someone would be traveling in the street and someone signals to stop by putting their palm, you know, gesticulating up towards the person who want they want to stop and you do so and you take it as a communication meaning to stop.
imagery, right, can communicate very often when you see something in red or across or an X or a circle with the universal lines a red circle with a red line through it, meaning not.
So these are various concepts that are already seemingly understood.
But in order to go through it in Greek speak fashion or let's say the more purposeful would be based on the communications that people are used to and even just the word itself, I would suggest that taking it for granted is what most people do and I would suggest that it requires translation.
And when I mean that, I mean literally and very often when I say that people will say, well, we use the word translation when we take information from one language that we don't understand and transferring it over so we can understand it in a language that we do understand as in the basic term.
And I mean translation in the form of the same language that you are using an example would be what's being communicated to the public at large by what you call institutions, you know, government school authority religious authority scientific authority on and on and on.
You cannot take what they're saying as it is, it needs to be translated. So how is that concept of translation and communication working for your question?
Yeah, it's a good start. I mean, what comes to mind for me is what the purpose of the translation serves, why is it that there is an obscuring of the actual meaning at the source that it would even need to be translated?
Well, because you know, it's very difficult to do anything that's intended to be for public distribution or expression or consumption without involving the society that's listening, you know, for example, this sonic event or the stream at large.
I think it's most useful to maybe delve into the communication requiring translation and meaning that even though it is the same language, it still needs to in other words extract, you need to extract what's really being said versus what a what someone would take as in passing.
For example, when people are communicating, they try to keep it very simple and colloquial terms and to get things done, you know, it can be the shovel or good morning or where are you going?
We try to keep that very simple and so society can function, but there's another level of it where when people are listening to what let's say information or hearing information very few people know how to listen and we might go into that.
Because that's essential for translating what's being said is when you're getting authoritative information or signaling being communicated that's outside the most basic rudimentary function like a stop sign or traffic light or something like that very basic it requires translation meaning what does it really mean?
What are they really saying to us? It is hidden very much of the time and you may not be able to extract what it really means what's being told to you by let's say religious authority government authority scientific authority medical authority even by translation.
You may not get the truth out of it, but you will discern whether it's hogwash or not right well quick example of it would be you turn on the television or the radio or the news media and when they give you let's say a critical event whether it's their active terror or a murder or some crime or something that's it's always allegedly right you ever notice to say allegedly right or suspect.
Now if you understand what those words mean it's just a presumption but when the people hear that and you ask them well what just happened they'll tell you as if it's fact you see so what I'm trying to say here is from a day to day point of view the common people try to communicate to signal and communicate and again relate to each other some kind of intent to get something done.
But when you're getting a communication from an authority and I'm not being anti authority very carefully crafted by the way by the legal society and that requires to be requires a lot of translation because the way people take it and the when what is actually being broadcast or communicated are two very different things and I guess that again results to show the schism of who's paying attention and who's not.
Yeah and that's very much tied to the overall theme and I think we'll explore it some more another thing to consider is that most things if not all things have a quantitative and a qualitative side so even though it's commonly known that consumer technology has created information overload on the quantitative side what would you say constitutes an effective versus a poor communication qualitatively.
Again it goes back to the mindset we've discussed that before very commonly most people would see the quality of the communication be as being high because they're not listening to what's being said or they can't translate it like I mentioned earlier very often what will be put out as a story or news item or whatever piece of history will always be shown as being in a presumptive light it's always an allegation or a suspect but the people will take it as being fact.
You know give an example on 9/11 they never said that Osama bin Laden was the culprit for that event they said they alleged him as being as such but if you go on the street and ask anyone you know what happened on 9/11 they'll say Osama bin Laden blew up the towers and you say are you sure.
And they'll say yes well that information was never put out that way and the same goes for pretty much everything if if someone is at large or the authorities are looking for someone who's dog rabbit dog let's say bit a bunch of people it's always suspect and allegedly bit people but the people take it as if that really happened and the point is not whether it really happened or not the point is what's being communicated and how the people receive it.
So initially they view it if you're not a.
Deming that these communications need translation you view them quantitatively and qualitatively very high right but once you see that actually what's being said is there's really not much there at all you actually start viewing as the quality and the quantity is being very low right now the other thing the if one maintains to.
Produce high quality and high quantity let's say quantity good quantity and good quality communication it's it's out of the norm from what people are used to hearing society at large and they will sort of say well that guy sounds nerdy or he sounds to book smart or that's too factual or I don't really like that you see so again this aspect of presumption is what people are using.
And it's interesting to watch because basically they're taking things and you know threads and ideas and fantasies and turning them into solid concrete things in their minds when there was nothing to say that it should be that way and again this is just tying back to the way people receive the information or process which I think we might have gone into in the past that people aren't really listening they're hearing things.
And when they receive a stimulus through the ear or the eye especially after adolescence they don't really discern what they're hearing or seeing they're just trying to take the initial part of that stimulus and attach it to things that out of memory.
And then it's not just about the fact that they're hearing things that they've already experienced up until about nine or 12 years old right so very often you'll see that in conversation people someone will bring something up so you're heard of this and the person will say yes and it's and they don't need to hear anymore think because they received enough stimulus that it recalled something in their memory files.
And they might have mistaken it is something they've already known or clearly if they haven't heard of it now that a little bit of a conundrum because they'll they'll come to a drawing point say well I haven't heard of it and I'm not interested or I've never heard of that and gosh you know more I have to do more and out learn about something else.
You see so that's basically the human on this basically I heard how they function so once you understand that you'll see that what is being communicated again through the religious community scientific.
The government authorities medical all of the main institutions university they don't have to be very accurate they don't have to communicate.
Truth they don't have to communicate anything of that is that even edifying they just have to communicate to satisfy the situation and you know so if we're going to look at communication again how to translate is is an entirely different sonic or stream.
Because we can spend hours on that but I would just invite anyone to consider to listen very carefully to what's put in front of them what input they're getting and they'll notice that what most people walk away as thinking of what they heard is not what really what's being said.
And if we not only limit ourselves to talk about institutional to the masses communication but also include person to person communication what kind of value or damage would you say could be generated by communicating well versus communicating poorly like what's at stake in the quality of how people communicate in general.
Okay essentially people are what that you've heard of the term visual kinesthetic meaning the when you hear something or when communications being done you should be able to get a picture of what's being said and I mean that literally in your mind.
You know a visual on it not just an abstract concept like for example the word nothing is one of the most difficult things to communicate because it's very difficult for someone to paint a picture of what nothing is right so very often I especially with young children if I were let's say be put in charge of educating them I would always teach them or have them develop a discipline let's say where when they're communicating and speaking to other people it actually creates a good way to communicate.
It really creates a visual image of what they're saying right or puts a picture in the other person's mind and I mean that literally so I would say that other than the basic most basic communications that I see people having in their day to day lives whether it's friends and family or even co-workers or whatever is on a very very basic level unless there are pre pre designed and pre acknowledged.
A precepts that have been set in place before you know which you'll find mostly in technical situations right like shop situations like a car mechanical have a different set of communication then a then a nurse in a hospital or whatever now the the most basic communications that you see people have can actually be mimicked and reduced by grunts and moans that actually communicate the same thing right and I mean that literally
someone might say would you like some and the other person may not even you might just wave their head from left to right and go mm-hmm right it's a very and that means no so basically from the basic runs and moans to up down yes no thank you please give me this take that that is what most people are engaged in of all walks of life so I think when we say communication I think it's a little bit larger and you're going to have to breach or broach the social
concept of it which is why I went into the aspect of it requiring translation right something that comes to mind for me is that I've long had the sense that the vocabulary of these times don't serve the needs like I see that as far back as the 60s where many of the counter culture movements for all their protests were really unable to formulate the heart of their issues and also at that time we see the rise of things like entertainment
driven punditry thanks to the gorbid alvers is William F Buckley debate in 68 and we know that that kind of medium is resistant to effective communication so fast forward to the present where those things have become standardized people now have a preference for vague rhetoric that lacks definitions which I think confounds the whole purpose of communicating how does such a development progress so uninhibited over the decades where people lose track of how to say things clearly
well let's put it this way it's called dumbing down and I call it dumbing up because the dumbing is increasing so it's not it's all right so it's being dumped up
just just consider this for a moment this is an abstract thought within the conversation we're having the amount of damage that has been done to society in the past 100 years regarding
quote unquote their education level or their comprehension level if we were to classify it as an entire generation has been dumbed up by the education system society and their traditions and culture that's accepted it as it stands right now I would suggest strongly it would take over a thousand years to recover from the present condition
let me just repeat that whole concept again the full generation may be two generations that have been dumbed down worldwide in the past 100 years will not recover from any social change let's say in the next 5, 10, 20 years or any effort that can be made to change it within anyone's lifetime
it will take over a thousand years to restore any kind of sensibility or rational that might have been let's say pre hundred years ago this is how critical this concept of dumbing down is that no one is as ever really brought up you know
you'll hear a lot of discussion on how people have been dumbed down and they think well maybe we'll just reform our education system and people will get smarter again no they won't accept it it'll take over a thousand years minimum to do it maybe never
so this is just from a secular point of view and this has been proven through history if you look at the most of the traditions that people engaged in are which are just dumb
they were put in place thousands of years ago basically over a thousand years ago and people still do it and don't know why
and it didn't take very long to put these things in place maybe 40 years or less so if you are looking at the needs of communication and how things are being communicated and what is being communicated from a necessity point of view other than the direct physical necessities that people have
the rest of it has to be viewed as a culture by culture social society by society basis you know other than I'm hungry I need food okay we all understand that no matter how dumb you are let's say
so when I mean dumb I don't mean lack of conventional schooling it actually means how much of you've accepted the cultural norms in whatever society you're living in
but anyway I don't see anything other than commenting on a cross-sectional profile of the existing condition and any time and let's say my life time because don't expect anything to get better in that respect
because once the again this might be a little bit off the question but once the society is quote unquote dumbed down I call dumbed up because there's more dumbing
it does not recover within that time frame it may never recover or it would take a minimum of a of a thousand years minimum or more maybe two thousand to recover now there is a way to recover a situation like that
and it's very drastic very draconian it would require a level of harshness that most people cannot even imagine an example of it would be
but let's say in the biblical story of Exodus you have a culture of slaves and yet they cannot be set and be reformed to take on an independent life for life of freedom on their own
so they're kept in an area sort of uncivilized area as I call the wilderness for 40 years until the people that were brought up in slavery died off
so their offspring can go in you see meaning when you have a society that is so dumbed down as it is now anywhere in the world the western world especially what they call America the United States is most definitely the worst
the only way to fix it less than a thousand years is to separate the young people that the children from their parents
and let's say properly educate them you can't have them going back to their grandma or elders in society or parents or uncles or even older friends or influences because the influence will be negative you see it'll be contrasting
so it can be fixed unless in a thousand years but it won't happen that way you see no I get what you saying right but let's also try to address one small point in the question which is that
these things go even when they go challenged the effect still comes to pass regardless of who says anything so what I'm wondering is that you said for example 40 years let's just take it as 40 years what is 40 or 50 or 60 but how is it that during that time that it takes to enforce a new type of
new type of substandard norm that nobody does anything to change it I mean anyone with an IOTO of intelligence can see it happening and you know when I look back I can see a lot of books that were written in the 60s 70s and 80s about the fact that the mass media was stupid like some
examples are amusing ourselves to death by Neil Postman and I can think of dumbing us down by John Taylor Gato the people write the books the books going to some of them become best sellers and yet we're still in the position that we're in which is a bit of a puzzling thing
well the we is very interesting because there's always been a society within a society within a society and there's always been secrets within a secret society as well and things like that that try to operate with all together seeming like a big mass in society but separately right you can see there's a
discernment in social I wouldn't say class systems but the ideologies that tend to separate themselves within a culture unless it's a draconian culture that tries to go target those individuals but to go back in from a
literary point of view here in the western world especially what they call the United States of America and the states there was a tremendous boom of what's called yellow journalism in the 19th century meaning like the most
senseless things you can ever imagine in print that the people enjoyed reading and purchasing and buying as newspapers are indulging in as in as various forms of communication information and that went on in
because of its sensational nature people were attracted to it and then it was adopted by the authority figures right if you look at every aspect of a culture or
what are the basically they're putting out nonsense now even people in from university degrees which I do enjoy encountering from time to time and I always ask them what they've studied and I just pick their stuff apart and you know especially when they're on a
graduate level and they get very frustrated because they don't want to admit that they've been defrauded but anyway I would say that if you go back through any recorded period in time there's
always been a class of people meaning the majority that did not want to be did not want to be edified or wanted purity in word or purity and thought purity and communication so this is part of the human history known human history.
Yeah I guess that does touch a bit on some of the things we talked about last week I'm also seeing increasingly that many people today especially those in the elite classes haven't been faced with the necessity of having to say exactly what they mean which touches on what we talked about last week as well about the proper mindset so because of that people's language ends up becoming sort of impenetrable because of how it's full of contradictory meanings and you can't really trust that someone knows what they're saying or that they're actually not
or that their actions will line up with their words because when you insist on them being clear they'd rather say well you know what I mean or you're just picking over semantics what would you say is the source and consequence of that kind of mentality.
What you see a level of inefficiency that you see in anything in society right now industry you know every aspect of their culture.
I mean the question there might be well level of efficiency do you need at a minimum for society or the culture to still function in other words would would 20% suffice in other words if 80% of what they did was wasteful only 20% percent mattered can it culture still function right or is it half you know 50% what say can they waste 50% of everything they do you see.
So I would say that the level of efficiency is very very very low I like using automobiles what they call automobiles they're really engine driven wagons they're not even motor vehicles unless they're electric because an electric motor gas driven engine.
But anyway those are really a very simple example for example I like going to car dealerships and I and they're very happy if I'm dressed well and groomed well they approach you right away thinking your potential customer if you wake up out of bed.
And you just go right to the car dealer in a holy t shirt sweatpants and flip flops they ignore you by the way they're very prejudicial that way I just wanted to bring that out as an experiment that I do with young people to show them how they should present themselves but nonetheless when you go to a car dealer I like kind of build them up and then pull the rug from under them because they deserve it by the way some of them might even be ex attorneys but nonetheless I asked them this is the brand new model this current year or next year's model and they're very proud.
They're very proud say yes and it's much better and I'm like well it's it's very it's different from last year and I'm like oh yeah it's very different.
Okay so so every year you say the consecutive year is different so that means you guys really haven't figured out how to make cars yet right and he's like what do you mean I said well you know I went and bought a hammer and at the hardware store and it was identical a hammer that I have from my grandad from 75 years ago.
And obviously they figured out how to make hammer 75 years ago and they don't have a new model now do they you see my point.
So in other words the design of the hammer is is a far more established effort of efficiency because it's not changing anymore.
I mean of course there's going to be maybe shock absorbent treatments and better levels of manufacturing but they haven't changed for a long time because it was established this is the the highest form of implement right.
Where if you look at an automobile now if you look at it a little bit more discerning what they call a car even an electric car by the way you'll see that it's hundred year old technology at a minimum reciprocating engine and all very wasteful very heavy and either the efforts to get away from such a device have been stifled of course by the you might call them elite.
They seem to have settled on this level of inefficiency now the reason I gave this example of the what they call cars or automobiles or I like to call engine driven wagons is because this is going on throughout whether it's the medical the technological at large.
And just again governmental all this stuff is highly inefficient by design because it is better to be inefficient this is just now not a direct quote but an indirect quote from people that are let's say running the world it is better to be inefficient and stable then more efficient and unstable right like unknowing just like we mentioned the example earlier if you wanted to get people out of a society out of a dumbed out.
In the condition you really have to separate the children from the older people parents uncles grandparents neighbors and educate them properly right enough and someone see squirming in their chair listening to this wherever they are.
And it would be very harsh right so the change that you are to expect in any society will be very radical if it's real change I would suggest that the the old stuff there's nothing really new and the old stuff just gets rehashed over which is basically obsolescence and inefficiency and it's by design.
Because it's better to have things that are in place that everyone knows and their stability.
A lot of what you said touches on the consequence of the things that I mentioned that because people are lazy you get this inefficiency as a result and then it spreads and become standardized let's also not neglect to look at the source of it so when someone says well you're just nitpicking over semantics when you insist that I should say something in an accurate way.
What is at the heart of that and what is it that people are trying to guard themselves from when they say that like it's almost like they don't want to say what they mean but they expect you to understand the many way.
Well they're protecting even though most people will say yes it is dumb yes we are dumb as a society yes the movies are stupid and the schools don't teach anything but you know they still follow through and support all those things because it is an evil that they're familiar with you'll hear this in politics better the devil you know then the devil you don't know.
It's very simple you know it's counterintuitive to think beyond what is the social norm for most people.
Yeah I think we'll probably end up revisiting that a bit more too but let's now move into the one of the subcategories within communication which is language so one of the best ways to tell if you're communicating something well is if it's understandable and memorable to the listener I think.
But there's a visible division in the west about how to achieve that so for most of the modern era the primary tool for sharing your thoughts has been language and literature where you wield your words as expressively as possible to convey a point but as the new age and other subjective minded movements have gained steam since the fifties.
If not the twenties with the western Buddhist explosion the idea of language being an effective tool has gradually been switched out for using shared emotions or shared experiences as a vehicle for communication instead and I think some examples are what we see with recreational drug use or secularized eastern practices like group yoga and things of that nature.
So I want to know why the power of effective language has become so discounted in favor of these other things even though throughout history language has been the most prominent communication instrument.
Well those other things are also subject to the dilution let's say or dumbing up or dumbing down of language also like for example if you ask people what is yoga or what is the Hindu culture you know they'll give you an answer that is it couldn't be farther from the reality of it.
Right. Right. Yes there's the sense that people don't necessarily understand what certain words mean but to look specifically at the reality right not just the fact that people don't understand words they've moved away from generally a word based form of communication to an experiential thing where it's more popular to just have an unspoken understanding even though that understanding is erroneous.
Is that a development you know as an older person that you saw coming that you saw sort of taking place.
That is the limitation of the spirit dwelling in a physical state you know the mind or the spirit is it can be with the mind is very disciplined and odds with what the body wants and vice versa.
Right. If someone is for example trying to pursue a high moral ground they'll find being sexually attracted to someone that they shouldn't be to be very difficult physically and mentally where someone for example who doesn't have a high moral ground might be sexually attracted being sexual attraction being the physical aspect of it.
I'd have no problem pursuing it you see because the the the spirit or the mind is not developed and disciplined so in essence the desires the physical desires and expressing themselves as you know as such just physical desires manifest it through the physical is is one of the signs of a very base culture or base state of being.
And is there anything to be said for the fact that chasing after an experiential forum to commune with people is like a cop out because it absolve you of having to say things in a certain way or to be specific with your speech.
No, I don't think that it's either one or the other I think it's it's it's that when when there's lack of discipline or let's say let's just use the word education I'm using it loosely.
Well rounded individual they will if they lack that for example they tend to go after the physical stuff let's just take for example a cliche of of a commoner in the western world they pretty much grunt and moan to communicate they have a very simple language they're attracted to sports which is very physical right and to get even to that beyond the sports aspect the the bloodier the sport is.
The bloodier the sport and the more physical the better their form of entertainment tends to be more action violence based horror based right they can't handle cerebral story lines or film or art they're going to be pursuing superficial physical trinkets and stimulation you know that will eventually lead to again limiting them there.
Themselves to a physical nature of existence so the the more physical let's say carnal minded individuals the masses at large they're always going to go for the physical aspect you know they'll they'll always want to watch a TV show or film then read a book for example you know and because let's just look at it from a comprehension point of view it would make no sense for the public at large to study or read books or study information.
Because they lack the comprehension where if they are watching let's say a an action film the level of comprehension there I mean even pets in the room will stop and look at the screen you know the dog in the cat will wonder what all that action and sound is you see.
Another aspect I think of today's language that's worth highlighting is how definitions have become twisted and perhaps to be fair that contributes to people's aversion against relying on their words because they might feel that certain words don't mean what they've been told and yet some of those words are the ones which possess the most influence so words like democracy freedom or rights and things like that.
I think those kinds of words coalesce a lot of aspirational sentiments and yet they're largely devoid of their original concepts today so how does something like that come about Greek or not only does an important word lose its meaning but in some cases it flips into its opposite.
Well it's just just like you said I think what you just said should be contemplated by many I mean it's very easy to evidence that things are not being used well I mean things those things being words but yet again let's go back to the concept of efficiency what does it take to maintain a stable society not a good society stable one.
Twenty percent efficiency thirty percent efficiency in other words have twenty percent eighty percent of the words lost their meaning I would say more than that you know but you think still function right you don't see other chaos and destruction yet when you go out your door.
Yeah but I would I would suggest that anyone find out what words mean for self edification it doesn't mean you're going to end up being happy about it because you'll notice that the people around you don't know any don't know what they're talking about right but yet still thing you know things still get done you brought up the question several times about semantics well you know well that's what you believe in or that's I'm using the word a different way or whatever yeah that's a level of efficiency again.
A good one in the English language is the word nice people use it frequently to mean something pleasant or good or blessing or a well wishing on another person have a nice day but the word actually means in reality as the word which structured to be used meaning foolish stupid and senseless.
So that is a very stark contrast you know that that's an easy one to look up and then you might be in dismay if you continue studying now reading or making yourself available to information is very different than studying the information I hope that's clear to people right so an essence of the concept of word study will not make you happy at the end of the day but you you might feel like you're not in the way you're doing it.
You might feel more rest assured that you know what things are supposed to mean and what the right thing is or the right definition for a word is.
And I think one of the at least in my mind the pushbacks that people give towards this kind of the elaboration that you just gave is that well words can mean different things or the dictionary says such and such and so it's easy to sort of get caught in a closed loop of conversation there where what is the proper reference for what the words mean anyway.
And there is something to be said for the fact that language is malleable but as far as having a fixed reference for those things there's no consensus really well there is yes there is and there isn't like you said that there is no consensus really when the social aspect of it and the tradition and the culture accepted then that's pretty much locked like the word nice for example most cultures most societies will in the English speaking tongue.
Well we'll say the word nice means something pleasant or good but I don't see I don't see there ever being a division where any part of society will use words accurately in the other will not and you know this is where the people say what they mean and mean what they say and this is the side of the town where the people don't know what they're saying that will never happen within the society unless it's going to be used as in a weaponized form.
A good example of that which is a society within society that is taking it to the next level would be the legal society.
There are a group of nasties that most societies have had for the past few thousand years it's a seriously depraved individuals that call themselves attorneys or part of the legal system which mind you has nothing to do with law and they they've developed a seemingly commonly.
There are seemingly commonly sounding words that have a total totally different need relevant meaning to what people consider those words to have like the word person or the word legal or the word crime or the word commercial don't mean anything of what people on the everyday street do but the legal society uses it against them.
For example when people go into what's called judicial settings they feel like they just went into Alice in Wonderland like what just happened here why are they not listening to me right.
So that is one aspect of it the other one is the scientific community the scientific community is very notorious about when they don't understand a process or something in nature within their scope of study they make up a term that fulfills not only a made up term but fulfills their way of life.
Explainings or describing what's going on a good one is electron or photon.
You've heard those terms mentioned before if anyone has even taken eighth grade science those things don't exist.
There are many scientists that have gone on record saying well if you don't understand a phenomenon we just make up terms to describe that fictional things you know.
So there's another way to look at it the governments of the world tend to do that also they speak in circular forms they do very careful studies when.
Officials of the administrations make public speaking that the what they're saying is in a circular form in other words you can listen to a speech from any government official anywhere in the world in any time through history pretty much and.
It sounds very good but if you asked even if it's a twenty second speech or two hour speech if you ask anyone listening to what it is say you really don't know what was said I mean something good hopefully.
So it goes on and on the religious stuff is utmost really mostly ridiculous.
You know that's we'll probably get into that in the future so I think the weaponization of language is really what most people are not aware of other than the meanings of the words.
And just to revisit a point because I think there's a bit more that we can flesh out there is there something that should be especially noted about how the most important words that shape people's broadest understanding of the world like for example democracy are visibly being demonstrated to not be in line with reality like on one hand many western countries are said to be democracies but something like the US was evidently created to be a republic.
And then allegedly all the parks and lobbyists buy so much influence in western countries that it undermines the democracy so why aren't these concepts challenged on their face.
That is an interesting aspect in history if you take the what's called the US or America very specifically you know if we're if we're not going to be myopic myopic or amnesia or believe the crap that we're being told you can go do a little bit of study.
And there was the term democracy was a very unfamiliar term here it was a really heavily pushed by FDR Franklin Delano Roosevelt he says we are now a democracy actually it was that a thrift store about a year ago and there was a poster someone was selling there from the 1930s about that it had a picture of him and of FDR saying that we are now in a democracy in big letters underneath you know it was like a new thing just like terrorism is a new thing.
You know now more than 20 years ago there were no terrorists you're either a revolutionary or a hijacker or an assailant or there was the word was not in common use as it is now.
So the concept of democracy also if it's coming out of a administrative form these are just administrative officials by the way they work for the owners.
The absentee owners of the of the sovereign states which are not nations but anyway that's another discussion again I would suggest that when you get information from administrations or governments anywhere in the world those are carefully crafted and legal ease so when they talk about the people they're not talking about you right they're talking about the people of the administration.
This is also very clear if you look at any of the codes of any of the laws which if you spend 10 minutes looking at the definitions of laws in any law book of any country you'll know more than even the highest judges in the land because they're not allowed to acknowledge it.
But you'll find out that in the definitions of the laws what the you know they actually provide a definition section you'll see what I'm saying is true.
It's a very limited access concept right so when you hear democracy it's democratic it's a very limited access concept in other words you don't have access to it because you've been denied let's say the rights of ownership there is no more you're not allowed to own anything anymore in the world at large pretty much maybe if the costumes in Afghanistan can people in the mountains maybe if they can defend it but for example if you are not allowed to own anything.
You're not allowed to own anything and you're just pretty much a resident right you have no money you don't need any money because ownership is impossible legally right if you don't believe that if you think you have a house it doesn't say you own it you're a tenant.
If you think you have a car you're an you're an operator you know you don't even own the children that you have ownership meaning that they are yours beyond just possession rights.
If they have a birth certificate on the child right you don't have so so how can something like democracy apply to people that have pretty much been depraved and deprived of anything that is considered mutually beneficial right.
It just it's just bizarre I think considering well you could read Alice in Wonderland or something like that a bizarre world again consider how efficient.
This is society have to be to remain stable right is it 20% efficient 50% efficient you know and you have to figure democracy into that I think that people have been deceived willingly that's what they want most people will say well Greek doesn't make any sense because I don't want to be deceived well you have been and you seem to be attracted to it so that's just a simple cross section description of what's going on most people enjoy.
The comforts of things that sound good and for them to discover what they really are about or what they really mean is very uncomfortable so they would always lean towards what makes them comfortable.
You see.
No that that provides a lot of food for thought there so everyone has things that they want to say but I think that finding the best way to say it is more than half the battle so let's wrap up this bit on language by contrasting to errors to look at that idea a bit I think that at least once in each episode thus far the subject of the Renaissance has been brought up usually not so flattering the light but for whatever blemishes you'd say that that error has.
I think it's most lasting merits have always been the stylistic aspects of its art and its literature so even if you want to say that the content is erroneous the aesthetic quality of the rhetoric of that time has really never successfully been discredited and I think many of its forms continued well into the 20th century where it eventually starts to fall off because of consumer driven mass media so my question is what credit should be given to how in size of the language of the 16th to 19th century
were for communicating interesting ideas what's interesting about that is that if you think society was really bad is bad off now let's say as a general cross section it was even worse back then to a degree that I would say over 95% conservatively liberally 99% of the population of the world of the world were basically primitive peasants
not very different how they are now let's say from that perspective but now they have a little bit more access and less constraint and travel and things like that right we're back then if you mentioned someone in the western world something about China they simply dismissed it as being a mythology doesn't exist you see what I mean we're now it's evident that you know you go buy things in the western world is made in China well you know it's not fantasy there's a place over there where people make things so
the people were very very primitive in a sense that shouldn't be regarded as anything just limited to that era it also was another era as well so it would be very easy to contrast something a bunch of people putting things together that looked real pretty and sounded real good and supposedly advanced certain things as a renaissance
so I don't see as I see it as an area of the city the renaissance and anyone that would study it where certain controls were put in place in limitations were put in place
but the detects do still exist or at least translations alleged translations exist that we can examine and it's very easy to see that the level of rhetoric that's being applied there is beyond the level of most people can even read today like you could you can't read
original Shakespeare today the average high school student like they can read simplified translations like it's very clear that that's a completely different level of constructing language though
right you would say that at that time you had more of a it was more of a proto-English even at the time of Shakespeare English by the volume been around for a few hundred years I think the earliest evidence of English we have as we know it would be chaucer right go back another was a thousand AD twelve hundred AD or something like that
and Shakespeare was later he was in sixteen hundreds right my belief and of late fifteen hundreds or so I would say that's still the old what the as it is today coin is old English
it's a mishmash of Germanic gall you know French and various other tribal languages mishmash together to be more universal for empire you see because when you have an empire the language ten years ago
the language tends to smooth out a little bit look at Spanish for example right you have the Spain spreading throughout South America in other parts of the world and the language had to have been smoothed out to a degree for it to take hold as a colonial you know part of the colonial culture
so the English I would say is much smoother beginning around the mid to the late eighteenth century sure smoother but also as far as being a vehicle for communicating ideas when you read the works of you know certain people like
a dito or jaffrey saucer or maca valley like these are not on the level of the type of best sellers that are being put forth today as worthwhile consumption well right the ideas that they're conveying are at least sophisticated on their face even if you want to say that they're erroneous at their heart
I would suggest they had yellow journalism back then pumping through the the masses I would suggest that the men that we know about and women let's say that we're in producing high forms of language art or memorializing texts you know they didn't do it on their own they had patrons
and in order to have a patron you have to satisfy the needs of the patron so you would look that there were dukes orals probably even monarchy is involved that summoned commissioned works of these people
so they would have to satisfy their needs which would be more of the higher culture.
I would suggest that the people we just mentioned represent such a small less than one percent of the people at the time and of course it's it's canonized as you know it's put up as as a high form of you know culture because most cultures tend to do that they're going to try to put their best stuff forward to represent what they are when in essence the majority of it is very primitive and crude as you can see today
well you certainly very resolute about maintaining that nothing good came out of that time well I say the same thing with Greek philosophy was if it was so good how well is it served you today and it has not
you care to develop that of it well yeah well there's not much to it you you have to accommodate you see you you have the masses so you're either going to say we have let's see
here's a hypothetical example which is actually more than hypothetical this is really how things a good cross section of how things really are when you look at a geographic location whether it's subdivided like something like Europe or an island nation or you know something separated by oceans or whatever you have a large group or a quote-unquote masses of people
and those ruling them say well do we are we satisfied or do we want to or do we want to change this you see now the way the masses are always the masses are always going to demand what accommodates them
right so he give you an example today if you ask the masses would you rather have a sports holiday or go to school right or study day 99.999999999999% would say we'll have a sports holiday
so now the sport could be blood sport and basically the dumber and the more vile the better so the the people that run the monarchies or the even now you have the owners or shareholders the lead that own the monarchies they look and say well how much more longer do we want to accommodate this and they are accommodating it now if they want to change it it's not going to change you can change it within that confine
but to change it and quote-unquote elevate it let's say to a higher form of thinking those people can exist any longer that you can't have them around you see that's why you have all of the conspiracy theories that you hear in the past few decades starting in the 90s oh the elite one will reduce the population of the world to 500 million you know from 7 billion or 6 billion or 5 billion back then you see the people you know
you know are either the you hear this often in their language i will defend to the death you're right to say what you want to say and they never think of that someone might accommodate them so in other words nothing has changed the earth is a very brutal place in order to evolve a society it has to be done in other words to make a society better you have you heard out with the old and with the new that's a literal description
the other the other way to do it again is as you have new burgeoning generations you know the new generation comes up you have to separate them to not be polluted by the old right that's where you have the discrete you know how do you think it'll go over if the elite or the people that run the world
it's just not your government by the way wherever you are doesn't matter what country or maybe Somalia the people there are warlords or the Congo are really running as the thing but anywhere else in the world all the other 200 countries or so no no what you think is who you think your government is is just a it's just an office and administrative office they make no decisions there at all
that's a short for sure so how do you how well do you think it would go if there was an announcement made the gradual softening of the population to comprehend this or softening through media and
the government or brainwashing or mind control to say that net from now on given on a certain date when people have children they will be taken away and raised in a town or a camp or a facility and you'll never see them again until their adults how well do you think that will how well do you think that will go and what I'm telling you right now is actually what those that rule your planet are thinking and I've been thinking for a very long time since the 20s
you know they say it with privilege education privilege lifestyle like well is this what it means to be human let's let's go in disguise and go out in the street and look at how these people are doesn't matter even the most advanced culture that you think is advanced would be Western Europe or Asia and they're just primitive and dumb right so how how well sorry these people are not that's why for example if you study the world wars you're like that's total bovine extraments why those wars are not going to be a lot of the same way
extraments why those wars started it was just a calling can we reduce the world's population through war right there's no there was no reason you can't show any feasible irrational reason for any of the world wars or any of the wars in the past 200 years right so and just a message to those people that you hear very often on the yes I call it stupid rectangle
oh the America's ready for civil war revolution it's not going to happen and if it does happen it's fully controlled any revolutionary anywhere in the world give it up it ain't going to happen you might as well get off this planet and try it somewhere else
because in order to pull it off whether it's peaceful or violent you're going to need resources and all of the resources are being controlled from a central location on the entire planet
right now if the elite let's say the people that own the world a small handful say well let's just have some fun over here and let's just make or let them have a revolution civil war well you will see if you study it the people that pulled it off or started it were supported by some pretty big power behind the scenes
so genuine revolution something like Napoleon tried to do for example is impossible on the planet right now and I mean it impossible try this example if you have one of those smart devices or phone or whatever just have it on and through your day mention some key words
you know like let's say you want to cherry ice cream or you want to just keep say whether you're by yourself other people just bring up the concept of ice cream several times bring up the concept of you need new tires several times or bring up the concept that you need a new couch just with the phone on or a smart TV or sorry or an iPad or something in the room and I assure you by the next day you will have advertisements for all of those things you mentioned
right yeah it's true you can try it I did I did one I have a phone that's not activated through the phone line but it is actively through Wi-Fi and I kept using the word mausurati and after the third time within a few hours I got an ad for mausurati so how are you going to have a revolution you it's impossible right there isn't or civil war or you know change like you hear these pro
this is how do you go to a planet right another another world let's say objectively study them and tell their inhabitants what's really going on okay you can do that right you just met communication right that's what you're just going to communicate them objectively what you see happening on their planet because it's easier for you to do it because you don't have the biases by being raised there and being decentralized certain things
okay you can do that but what are the chances of them heating or comprehending what you're saying very slim to none so again one of the purposes perhaps just interject about Greek speak as today we were talking about communication and again it's it's more than just that but it's can you be objective and when you're objective can you be efficient again to raise the example if you look on the internet they they're saying
oh America's ready for civil war do not pay that any mind whatsoever right there are people out there that believe that are losing energy don't even lose one watt of energy or one breath towards that direction because it's not going to happen and if something like that does happen is fully contrived just like a movie set and but imagine it's a snuff film movie said if you see people dying well you're in a movie where people really do die right so it's kind of
it's kind of like the the interesting reality that I've witnessed this personally I remember back in the late 60s people coming over from Europe it'll
be Greece what have you mountain people I mean people that there was one light bulb in the village of 500 and this is in the late 60s right and they sat down in front of a television on the use
coast let's say New York area in the late 60s watching a cowboy in Indian TV show and they're actually crying because the Indians were being shot on television right
this is a you know some bananas a show or they actually thought people were dying that's how they didn't understand the concept of this was
thespian or these were actors and it was all props now to go a little bit further this is true you could look this up they had a show here this is now this is not the the more primitive mountain people
that are just mentioned from Italy and Greece this is just your average American in in from your average Americans in the late 60s there was a show called Gilligan's Island that was aired and it was about some cast
ways on an island and the actual coast guard of the United States had received thousands of calls from everyday citizens about going and rescuing those people that were watching on TV right this is true I'm not making this up by the way you could look this up
so whether my example here is whether you're going from a primitive let's say mountain people that think cabboys and Indians are really dying on TV at 6 p.m. in black and white or your people that were raised in the western culture thinking that they're real cast
ways on the show they're watching you see so to both people the mountain people and the people that were raised in civilization they thought what they're
watching was real now let's fast forward to what people call the internet when you go on the internet and you see whatever garbage they're putting up because to me the internet is like garbage day when garbage day meaning like if you live in a city or
semi suburban neighborhood you'll see this garbage day and that's when the people roll their garbage cans are their bins out to the curb and the service comes and picks them up once a week or whatever
okay that that's when you put stuff on the internet that's like rolling the garbage to the curb for to be picked up that is essentially what it is generally not doesn't mean you're not going to find anything good in there right
so if you're into electronics and someone puts out an old microwave in the garbage well that's garbage to them but guess what there's a few or take that old microwave apart there's a thousand bucks worth of spare parts in there that you could use
so that's a different story there but in essence it's garbage day so when you look at the internet and you start seeing political religious scientific stuff that is not being put out for you let's say that is being put out for the masses that think that cowboy Indians are really being shot on television and crying about it or calling the coast guard because there's some castaways on Gilligan's Island I see it the same way what's being put out
on the internet today so hopefully with some Greek speak people be able to act more efficiently and again since we brought up communication just to interject you could look at modern culture the different ages that you had you had the industrial age how did that serve you right you had the biggest problem when that was no longer touted as being so wonderful was what we had garbage dumps chemical waste environmental damage right
opposite planned obsolescence okay then became the space age well what did that give you some maybe some space junk and the rest of it was just fake stuff in the movie studio right and now you have the information age what kind of rubbish trail is that going to leave
just think about that well I think it's timely that you mentioned the internet and technology so let's conclude the stream by looking at the relationship between
communication and technology so what I've observed is that people don't really talk with or even to each other as much as past each other now so they say something that often fails to resonate with the other person who meanwhile is just waiting for their turn to speak and there's little exchange of ideas or propositions
I think that some of that has to do with the fact that people's communication abilities have diminished alongside the rising in consumer technology like TV's computers that stuff has shaped each new generation to redefining how to communicate because of how the products are designed what has been your observation of how things like that TV and computer driven devices not only change people's way of interacting but possibly dumb them down also
let's shift around a little bit let's say we had a time machine and we brought an ancient but you know let's put you all at you pick it from 500 a thousand or 2000 years ago pick one 2000 okay they would laugh at you they if you showed them a smart for
or computer they would just laugh their ass off for like two minutes say what good is that do at first they'll say well what you know look in front of it behind it the what's going on here right and after five minutes of explaining electricity and that they'll just laugh at you they they'll say well what's going on they point out the window out the door and say what's all this crap on the street here and they're like what are you talking about looks fine that all this asphalt all this black stuff that we see bubbling out of the ground that we avoid and use for special purposes you have spread it everywhere on the street
you have a cold box with food that I wouldn't even feed to cattle to an animal basically you know your refrigerator right I mean they would look at you and just laugh at you you know even the most primitive one of them because they would see how far away you are from what it means to be a living being right and how you're trying to stretch a feeble mind into something like a computer or a television and say
you are actually paying attention to this beautiful you know you call beautiful big flat screen TV HD or O.L.E.P. or whatever watching the movie that is so stupid right you're letting your cat you're taking your mind right
and give you another example a list fast forward to the early 20th century the poll rate cameras took instant pictures of explorers take going to islands in the Pacific and other parts of the world of natives
and when the natives saw immediately the photograph they would tear it up and take the camera and break it because they thought it was capturing their spirit or their essence if you could capture an image of me
then you might pull out a machine that might capture my body and shrink it down into a box you see now we might laugh at that but they just saw it as an impulse like look what look what how you're manipulating my perception you see and I find that offensive
I think I've mentioned on other streams in the past the first thing an ancient would say is why are you dumping this asphalt is black stuff everywhere meaning your roads right
they would find that offensive so they would look at a smart going back to the technology you know staring at a screen kind of thing as being spiritually devoid meaning mentally devoid now fast forward to right now
I have many times if you heard or seen people sitting next to each other and texting each other right you this is a popular thing years ago that was shown at how stupid people are whatever you see
we'll come back to the communication the technology but can you just develop the asphalt thing so this is a dangerous thing because many aspects of it well first of all the bubbled up out of the ground pretty much everywhere in the world believe it or not
there's some of it bubbling up right now in places in what's called Russia and the giving the people some excuse of what it is but it was used it was very toxic it was known to be toxic because the gases that followed it were toxic
if you breathe that you died or got sick they were tasteless and oralists like hydrogen sulfide will kill you and it was very sticky when it cooled and it was not friendly not a friendly substance and it came out of the earth out of the dark
and they viewed it as a specialty item and it was to be respected in something that was limited for limited use only
and that's very simple now if you fast forward to modern times you can prove to you the dangers of it that are not discussed by anyone pretty much it is known I have spoken to civil engineers and they all acknowledge it but they don't say anything
and that is how many times have you heard of clean water acts that they're all over environmental protection acts all over the world right in other words if you have a toxic substance in industry or even in someone's home don't dump it on the ground or don't throw it down the sewer right don't you know you'll get fined for that right you have a special waste disposal you know
pretty much anyone in the civilized world is heard of that well if you're so civilized and so let's say whatever you know I'm going to illustrate how hypocritical society is this asphalt mixture I don't know what people know about asphalted mixtures if you ever go to an asphalt plant where they mix this black tar hot stuff with gravel to pave roads with what's in that asphalt do you think it's environmentally friendly
and it's loaded with dioxins and benzines and carcinogens right it would be the latter and what do you think happens when rainfall occurs on these roads and the runoff from the rainfall happens well you know you have a tremendous amount of runoff
and if you ever look at it you ever notice the newly paved asphaltic road well how do you know it's newly paved well it looks really black and sticky almost you know if you're walking in around it and you know you know 25 or 30 degrees Celsius or 90 degree weather
you're the the the souls of your feet actually stick to it they have to pour sand over it sometimes well how do you know when the road is weathered well you could actually see the gravel on the top it actually you don't see the smooth blackness you see a
the aggregate that makes up the asphalt it's no longer black it's like a light gray sometimes right well what happened to all that asphaltic material and what's in that asphaltic material all of the solvents and toxic stuff it's washed away where well how well I thought we're not allowed to dump toxic substances into the environment you see
oh yes understood but there you see it's you want food an ancient wood laugh at you to see where people bought their food these days you feeding this poisonous stuff to yourself willingly here is the interesting part if you are to do a cross section of society and how it is you find it's pretty it's a horror movie really
I say it's a movie because fake scripted but at the same what makes it even worse than a horror movie is that people are volunteering into it and they're very accepting of it where in a horror movie when the the star of the horror movie which is usually the villain is chasing down they have to chase down their victims don't they the victims rarely say okay you can hack me to pieces right they very rarely do that
what what makes modern society worse than a horror movie is they actually are being accommodated by it and they're willingly accepting it
well yes that was a slight side tangent but just to get back to the original question I think it's safe to say that we've seen the rise of smart devices come to fill the role of not only medium where people call or text with them but also mediator between people like an iPhone is very deliberately designed to impose certain restrictions
on how you can communicate with others and it guides your thoughts along certain lines what kind of effect do you think the designs of phones and tablets and laptops have had on people
well I'd say it's an obsession you can see let's say let's go to the even the I don't know about the postions in Afghanistan but let's go west your
in Asia the what they call the Middle East you ever see these things called worry beads if you go to the cafes are on the street you see usually the older people they have a string of
beads and they're flicking them or they have them in their pocket it's like something to do right cigarette smoking was very much like that up until the 60s if you watch any archived television shows
anywhere in the world up until the 1970s and prior you smoking publicly or on even television was normal it was almost an accepted and if you fact and if you didn't smoke there was
something wrong with you so just something to do let's say what gets the people into the smart devices is the tactile nature of it just like the the beads that they play in their
hands in their hands with all day in the Middle East so not so much now because they have smart devices so there's the tactile aspect of it because no matter how smart that as they say you notice the people are
never smart just the devices are no matter how beneficial the technology was if it didn't have a tactile feel that was pleasurable to the senses the people would not accept it so it's it's the tactile aspect of it they like the
picture they like the the get sound they like that they can quote unquote communicate with it doesn't mean that the substance of the communication is worthwhile is just that they can do it they just something about it that they like
but there is an aspect of what we see with things like Syrian Alexa where there is no tactile aspect but it's hugely popular that people just speak in the AI does something well that's also I believe that to a certain level when I first saw that I said oh look they're just mimicking a
bit of a Butler think about that for a minute and if look up what the Butler really is you know he's the manager of the house the Butler manage the gardener and the cleaning crew and the wait staff and the cooking crew the
butler was the manager of the house for the master you know of the servants so the Alexa and these talking devices that are not as directly tactile as a iPad or let's say a phone or or
or pad as known today it's the manager the managerial aspect because when you had a Butler or wait staff or staff you call out right and if they didn't hear you had bells that you
would ring or an intercom literally was like a speaker in the in the wall is a tube and you spoke to it you spoke and gave orders or commands and the servants back into your call
that's all it is if you look at it from that point of view right to conclude the stream in the interest of time you've remarked in the past on how the designs of some of these devices impose an almost child like mindset particularly of a nine year old can you develop that a little bit well the mindset behind it you see it's prejudicial in other words if you don't follow the mindset they punishes you right you can see the mindset very simply every
time you interact with a smart device whether it's to go to a different function or again let's just keep it to go into a different function it sort of queries you and gives it serves you with a little
verbal notion or you know a text notion oh would you like this or you know this is just the language that's being used and how it's being directed to the mind would be the way to accommodate let's say a nine year old girl not a nine year old boy and I'm using those terms literally because you know when you're young you're a boy and a girl
so you can see that it's quite obvious and a very simple way to to look at that is look at the child culture ghost study what has been gear towards let's say between seven and eleven year old girls in in media or entertainment things that have been specifically designed for that age group of girls and then go look at your smart device the same vernacular the same attitude
yeah I think that that will make for some interesting study for some people yeah okay I don't know if that was deliberate by design it just happened to be that way I'm not I'm not actually interested to see the psychology behind it I find the smart phone repugnant yes you're quite fortunate Greek some people are not that well actually if more people took my stance they would still be the services would be accessible to them but if more more
and more people took that stance then there would be fewer fewer smartphones and then you would go back to not having remote access to the internet because that would be the only difference you know there were cell phones around the bin cell phones were more than popular twenty years ago
right so all right I think that does it for me I feel like we've tackled a range of things in the stream and some of it will undoubtedly resurface in future themes do you have any final
do you have any final points you want to touch on before we make haste not a fair the only final point is the beginning point which is discussing communication that is too wide and just to
leave maybe the final point which might be the most salient point is what would people consider to be sacred in iconography and in you know their objects that is another form of communication you could take for example any nation's flag
is viewed as a sacred item in like you know raising it up and praising it is considered the norm and the good thing to do or trampling on it or burning on it or pooping on it is considered defilement right
but if you're in the dark and you have you just washed something down and you need a dry canvas to dry it off you can easily grab any nation's flag and do it in the dark without knowing that it's
a flag signal printed on it so flag and sacred devices iconography things like that are another form of communication you've seen it in Hollywood and movies where the vampire they show them a crucifix right
and the vampire goes away you know that because it has some power in it so these things need to be considered and studied for those that have the time and want to
cool and possibly will sense you brought it up you might touch on that theme sometime in the future thanks to everyone for listening to this episode of the Greeks be podcast we will endeavor to be back next week with another stream and see you then
you
[MUSIC]