[Music]
Greetings to everyone tuned in to yet another episode of the Greek Speak podcast.
You're listening to the Archon creator of the series. My co-host the Greek will be joining me for episode 8 of this podcast in just a minute.
Things are starting to move towards their end with the series. If you haven't guessed it yet, I'm gonna round off the podcast at episode 10.
I think that provides a good enough scope of subjects for people to digest and it's also a matter of not being able to squeeze in more time for these podcasts.
I've had people email about the excessive delays between each episode and so that frustration caused by the waiting time is being felt on both sides.
But I will endeavor to finish things off strongly and the Greek and I will continue to offer a useful discourse for the remaining episodes.
Greekspeak.com continues to have neither political, religious or commercial affiliations and is completely funded and managed by myself.
So that's it for the introduction. Please enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
[Music]
Hi there Greek, you there?
Greetings. Yes, I am.
Hey, it's been a while longer than usual. How are you doing?
Good, I'm doing all right. So we have another topic.
Yes, we do. I think we maintain some continuity in the last two episodes talking about science and food and we'll be moving on to a different topic today, namely that of politics and the military.
You've often touched on different political realities throughout the series without really expanding on them and so I thought we'd taken an episode to break some of that down in a systematic way.
So to get us started, I would say that prior to the modern era of the 1600s, Europe, the Middle East and North Africa were largely controlled by empires that usually had a monarch or an emperor and you also had the Catholic and the Eastern Orthodox churches that had political influence as well.
And you also had the feudal system that we developed when an empire collapsed, but a lot of that changed during the Napoleonic Wars, which I'll ask you to speak on later.
But as a start, what can you share about the pre-Napoleonic European powers and how was the empire based government different from what came after and how are pre-modern states structured differently from today's nation states?
OK, if you want to consider the concept of race or nation or tribe and by the way the word nation was more pushed by the British, but it was sort of a familial grouping.
You can see it in ancient texts, biblical, especially lineages were divided geographically and somehow maintained borders and things like that.
And then you had the rise of leaders, which would typically in the form of monarchy or priesthoods.
And it coalesced into the European model that you saw up in Tolonapole and some of it, and if not most of it, did persist after Napoleon, but the European model consisted of basically religious and empirical leadership, religious being the Pope, the Vatican, and then you had an emperor of Europe.
And most people are not familiar with it, you hear about the kings in Europe of the various countries, especially the British or the English kings and the French kings.
But Napoleon was interesting, he wanted to go against that to sort of in an altruistic way, which maybe was the problem, to free humanity from the limitations of such a system.
So without getting into a discussion about Napoleon, which I've been picking up a little bit of research on him recently and picked up again on some research, maybe a decade ago, but put it down because it's a very narrow focus to look at just Napoleon.
But he was he's been demonized because of that altruistic sense that I just brought up.
There's a fellow named Walter Bosley who recently put out a book on the occult Napoleon, I was made aware of, and how he was very much into hidden mysteries and what's called natural philosophy and science and things like that.
And not necessarily endorsing Walter Bosley is very heavily censored, in terms of what's in the world he actually believes that most of these things are real.
But he might have done something worthwhile or worth looking into, I just heard a podcast about what he wrote about and seemed to line up with a lot of the things that I had found out, which is very difficult to actually discern because of the negative brush and Napoleon's painted with through history.
But just to maybe not focus on Napoleon alone or just Europe alone.
What had happened after let's say that Napoleonic period is a level of secrecy that had never been done on such a large span put in place on the on the world scale.
In other words, what is really going on and what is really affecting the people has been swept under the rug, not in a minimalistic sense, but taken away from you and seriously occulted.
And again, just to go back to Napoleon, he pretty much gave the world alligarchs, which was pretty much centered in most of the world around the British Empire, a black eye.
And they said, we're not going to let this happen again.
And one way by preventing on a poll, another Napoleon from arising or such a, let's say, anti establishment of movement is by going secret and not having a target for them.
And the anti establishment movement, let's say, to focus on and we will still provide a target for them, you know, a leadership or system that allegedly rules the affairs of most civil societies will be basically figure heads and puppets.
And basically at that point, you had the termination of any above ground surface level power.
So just to some things up for contemporary matters or contemporary parlance, I would say that today or within your lifetime, unless you're 200 years old, if you if you hear them and see them, they are not the real power.
It's what I would say, meaning if you've heard of someone and you have seen someone, whether it's in history in the past 200 or so years or on television or the radio contemporary, doesn't matter who they are, they are not in power.
They are just put propped up by the powers that be.
So all your presidents, kings, popes, your black Jesuit, whatever the people scream about, the builder, Bergs, all these people, Rothschilds, Rockefellers, none of those people are the real power.
So if you've seen them or heard them, they are not in power. They are merely what's put in front of you as the power.
Yeah, and there's some other things I'll ask about that as well, moving forward. But still though, the power structure that was prior to the Napoleonic period was largely based on the fact that you had ruling monarchs or emperors, like you mentioned.
What's the European emperor think? Can you expand on that a bit? Because I've looked into that and it's very fuzzy.
And they didn't wholeheartedly agree. In other words, back in those days of 10% of the population agreed they did it where that was considered the majority.
That was enough because they had enough power to quell the other 90% and also there was no reaction time.
You know, there was no internet, there was no airplane. So if you didn't like something that was going on a thousand miles away, you had to get there on foot or by horse or by a saleship and it took a long time.
So it didn't really matter. But the emperorship, again, I can't expand on it right now. I'd have to go back and look at notes which I don't have in front of me.
But that's basically a spin off of a lot of the, what you call the Netherlands Dutch Empire.
If you understand like the East, the Dutch East India company, which also worked with the British monarchy.
Again, just to go off slightly the Dutch East India company, if you look at the largest corporation in the world today, the Dutch East India company was I think a factor of 10 times more influential or bigger.
Right. And they didn't go away. They just again went underground around the time of the Napoleonic affairs.
But the concept of the emperor was always in the Netherlands area north, northwestern Europe versus let's say the, the south eastern Europe part, which would be the Roman aspect of it.
So they kind of met in the middle. So you had the Pope and the European emperors.
Pretty much at the King's answer to.
And this concept of the Dutch East India trading company, there seems to have been a bunch of East India trading trading companies that popped up in different places, most notably the Dutch one in the British one.
But you also had this French one and the Swedish one and some like a bunch of countries had that.
What was the sort of underlying political motivation behind that? Because obviously it's not just go to Indian get spices.
Uniform commercial aspects like what the people will refer to as uniform commercial code put in practice.
You know, they they're seeking a uniform form of commercial enterprise kind of like, you know, your big box stores are today, you know, like a Walmart type thing or whatever.
And how much sway did the church has in this period and can you contrast how Catholic church influence the European empire as versus how the eastern orthodox church influence the buzantine empire?
Wow, that's a big question. I can't be answered even in an hour.
But essentially, let's let's go back to the essence of it. When you hear the word church, it's the it's the word circus.
And you know, today when you say the word circus, you know, people laugh because you know, we take children and get popcorn and cotton candy and you see all of things and things.
But if you know anything about what was what was called the circus, Maximus and Rome, that was a spiritual thing as well.
It was just like today, if you if you see like people come out of a movie theater, their their visage their face, their expression is very different than what it was before they went into the movies.
You know, depending on the film, I've studied that and you know, sometimes they look agitated, sometimes they look relaxed because that's a spiritual change or mind change in the individual.
And that's what the circus Maximus and the Cirque or Kirkay was was to do to the population.
It's like a reset, right? You go to the circus or the church every week to reset your mind and it's a day off or whatever.
So that is the real influence of it. You see, whether it's a circus Maximus, you know, where a large place like the Vatican or a small church in their neighborhood, that's the main influence of it.
Versus the Byzantine, it's the same. The Byzantine, I would say, was more mythoric, ancient, mythoric or that you would find in.
By the way, everyone wants to look at this. The original, well, not the original, I would say for over a couple of centuries, the religion of Rome was myth reasem.
Right? So that's a whole other thing again. You see that? Well, these are eggs we shouldn't crack open because we don't have a pan big enough to fry them.
Well, I mean, it's still interesting nonetheless. We don't hear too much about the Eastern Orthodox situation. It's almost as if it's in a diminished state right now as if it fell from prominence, even though it's obviously still influential in Eastern European places.
But they have a seem to have an odd relationship between the Western and the Eastern. Well, a lot of power. 1000 AD was an axial period, a minor axial period. That's when the, I think it was around 1020 or 1050 or something like that or 980, 1000 AD, let's say, on the Pope's work schedule that the Catholics overcame the Byzantine and there wasn't a split.
It was takeover, let's say, an invasion. A lot of things happen. The Masteredic text, you know, sort of unifying what's called the Hebrew scriptures was around that time.
This is just a whole slew. I think the Vatican was construction started soon after that or slightly before. There was a lot of change. You know, it was that mold. It was the first millennia, but it's influences minimal because it really had a strong reflection of the Persian Empire.
And though you had the alleged Greek empire, well, the Greek empire take over the Persian Empire. And even today when I meet people from Persia or Arion or Iran and say that I'm Greek, they say, oh, you're my enemy. And it's like, wow, we must really get kicked your ass so hard that you're still sort 2000 years later.
I don't know if you're going to know about that. I don't know if you're going to know about that. I don't know if you're going to know about that.
I don't know if you're throwing, let's say, the over influence of the Persians or the Farsi, really, is what they are. They're the Farsi people. More assimilated them, then then reversing their influence on the world and their influence religious cultural influence stayed around as far as Europe, Eastern Europe. And that's what the Eastern Orthodox is pretty much.
For many years, I would do some X and people would talk about Greek philosophy. And I'm like, if Greek philosophy was so good, how well has it served you? Why is society still in the crapper, so to speak, right?
It was so good because the Greeks really were not culture builders and they weren't that great. They assimilated cultures and actually destroyed some of the finer ones. If you look at, again, there were some smaller cultures that were Farsi and there were cultures like Throssi and other smaller, let's say tribal nations that would go under the Greek umbrella that were far more advanced and more subtle in their perceptions and finer perceptions were simulated or destroyed by the general Greek.
And general Greek empire consensus, right? So the Greek is not so great, by the way, because if it was, why are we in such craps still today?
So again, just to overlap, they did not obfuscate or remove the Persian influence. And that's basically what you see in the Eastern Orthodox Church, that's Mithraism, straight up, other than going, you know, building straight up Mithraeums, you know, which are the temples of Mithra.
Under ground and things like that, it's pretty similar to it.
To touch on another thing, one thing that I've always wondered as far as these sort of political systems and also the church aspects of them having power is to identify where, you know, the most power lies in kings prior to the Middle Ages ruled by something called the divine right of kings.
It doesn't really get talked about much nowadays, but no one seems to know where the concept came from except that there's a record of it going back to biblical times, but it seems as if it was something that people thought as self-evident for thousands of years.
But to me, at the end of the day of monarch is really just one person, and I don't know if the divine right of kings supersedes the monopoly of violence that you have when you have an army.
So we all know of Kuditas not being uncommon, it happens a lot, and so does the power really lie with the monarch who's here today and gone tomorrow or does it lie with the military which tends to be more long lived.
Both, because if there is divine right to a king, he will also be given the divine protection of a military that is coherent and protective.
And bella coast, of course, meaning aggressive and ready to fight.
I would say that these things change. If anyone would consider that there are non-corporal, non-material, or let's just say spiritual forces that rule this earth and are behind everything that you see, it's very cohesive to see when you say divine right.
Certain cultures, when you say divine right, most people in the Western culture will say, "Well, God put them there," like the biblical text, especially in the book of Daniel's loosely states or suggests.
Basically, he says he puts the leaders in place, but if you read the book of Daniel, it's not specific whether it's all the peoples of the earth or just Babylon, you see.
Or who's being addressed there? But either way, if you take it in a specific sense or general sense, most people think there is a figure directly responsible for it, a spirit.
And certain cultures, especially in the east, when they say there's a divine right to rule, the divine right doesn't come from a being, a spiritual being, it comes from the actual form known as the sky or the heavens itself.
Like in certain Asian traditions, when they say divine right of the emperor, it's that the heaven has given him the right.
And there's no God figure, like a personification of a singular spirit.
So when we say that, we have to look at the culture, but either way, it's non-corporal.
And to take that a little bit further, as far as contrasting where power lies, a political dynasty versus say something else, I think of let's say finance or banking dynasties like monarchs need money or they wouldn't be able to pay their armies or their subjects, which tends to lead to revolt.
And you even had a family like the Medici who were able to leverage the power of their bank to create their own political dynasties.
And I don't know that I've ever seen the reverse happen where a political dynasty is able to become all powerful and finance.
So between those two, which would you say is more dominant, the people that have the money or the people that sit on the throne?
It's neither really because when you hear about bankers, bankers don't have money and people with money are not bankers.
A banker is something like a gardener or a chef or cook or an accountant.
So a lot of people are confused when they mention these banking families that they are very wealthy. They are actually financiers.
In other words, if you're wealthy and you hire someone to, let's say if there is money versus the credit or even with the credit system, you hire someone to manage your funds.
Let's say the bank accounts and assets and things like that.
The person that you hired or put forward as your manager is not the one that's wealthy.
You hear about all these quote unquote banking families. They are not really the wealthy ones. They have the appearance of being wealthy, obviously, because the way they work, their fees are based on either a percentage or, you know, a contract.
You see.
When you say something like the Mediches, were the Mediches bankers or were they wealthy people? I'd say they were wealthy patrons and they had bankers that were got into banking themselves.
Sort of like how large corporations self-insure themselves sometimes instead of getting an outside insurance company.
So that's not so cut and dried as people think it is.
If you have control over a certain, because hundreds of years ago you would have had legitimate money in the form of some kind of mineral, whether that's gold or silver or something else, it wouldn't have just been meaningless pieces of paper.
So if you're controlling that resource, whether it's the mining of it or the storage of it and you call yourself a banking dynasty, that's still your money though. That's still your wealth.
Well, let's go back and do something regarding mindset.
Let's just toggle back to something you just said about meaningless worth pieces of paper.
You know, even I use the term fiat currency because that's what it's referenced as, but really it's not meaningless. The current credit notes that people have and all that that's based on the banking system, the central bank having a first lean on everything in that country.
Look at a bank note and whatever numbers and things are on there and names and institutions and countries or whatever. That represents a lean and that lean represents some business that went bad at one point, meaning one of the parties was not able to fulfill a contract so they were bankrupt and put it into a receivership.
And it's all by presumption. So for example, if the United States government decided to print its own money instead of Federal Reserve, that would be really fiat because they have no substance to base it on.
But if you have a Federal Reserve note, which is the Federal Reserve bank and it has the United States of America, well, that's just like a regular check when you have a check book printed it has the bank name printed on the check then your name on the check and then the amount in the amount on the on the Federal Reserve note, those serial numbers represent a lean against the United States.
They actually not fiat, they actually represent a legitimate lean where a contract was not able to be fulfilled and the business went bad.
I would suggest that just by illustrating that condition, you're in a, you're in a, in other words, humans are in a situation that they cannot get out of and will not get out of intact.
In other words, you're going to, in other words, you've gone to humanity has gone to a point right now with the banking situation that the only way it could get out is by pretty much either completely changing the mindset of humanity and just not using it anymore or just utter destruction of the infrastructure.
What I mean, utter destruction meaning no grid, no, no, no, no, no, no internet, no electricity, as you have it now, no roads, no highways, no, because the, the people that are behind this, the power that has allowed this to happen worship death.
And what's interesting when I talk to people about, or, you know, if someone drank, what do you think of chemtrails or the fluoride or vaccines, and I say they're toxic and, and they come back and say, wasn't it hurting them also, meaning those that are putting it out of, yeah, of course, and they don't care because they worship death and if they die from it themselves, they'll just be closer to their God.
You see, so it's, it's kind of, these things are very difficult for the average person to not only imagine it's beyond what they can imagine, you see.
Yeah, it's very interesting. The worship of death thing, it's not put forth explicitly. They, you know, most alternative spheres of conversation would love to put forward the bathroom at figure or some kind of other imp to be the focus of this sort of satanic,
like, filthy, but the death thing is not really talked about very much explicitly.
No, they don't. They, they, well, humans are cosmically known to be morons, by the way, I just want to interject that and I'm doing that in a, in a kind way, you don't want to hear what I feel or want to say actually in a public forum.
But in a kind way, humans are morons. That's why you're always left alone cosmically, you know, always wonder left to wonder because in, in an ideological sense, humans are at the point right now that they don't deserve any more knowledge and so they start pondering what's right in front of them, which they don't do.
But anyway, the, the concept of these minor gods and, and impson demons are what's always put in front in the, in what's called that nasty thing called the internet.
Because that's as far as they can go. They don't, they can't, people are, if they're not accommodated, they don't pay attention, you see.
If they don't like the information, it can't be true or if they haven't heard of it before, you know, it's not, they're not interested.
You see, so now you have a dog chasing its tail scenario and they're locked into a very, very highly limited aspect of knowledge and so.
So again, to bring up something like the baffamette and other things and satanism, it's not what people think it is.
Those are very small and minor entities in the spiritual world.
Yeah, it will give us some, some interesting things to talk about perhaps in another episode.
But to get back to the politics thing, it's, it's really only after the Napoleonic Wars and the collapse of the Holy Roman Empire that this nation state starts to proliferate itself in the early 19th century, which I think is very curious.
We've reached a point in history where most people don't really know the difference between a state, a nation, and a country, and those words are kind of used interchangeably, but from a legal perspective, the distinctions, I think are significant.
So according to academia, a nation state could be defined as an independent state with a written constitution ruled by a political body in the name of its citizens, who are all considered equals.
But prior to the 19th century, that structure doesn't seem to be very legitimate because you would have a king who ruled in the name of a god, represented the house of whatever family was on the throne.
And he didn't really represent the nation as a whole.
So the natives of the state were rather his subjects, but then comes along the French and the American revolutions and that seems to rebirth the ideal of self rule in the name of, you know, equal citizens, which I think they borrowed from the Greeks and the Romans.
To the best of your knowledge, Greek, why did this nation states start to spread in the beginning of the 19th century, and particularly after World War I, when the Habsburg and the Soviet Empire is broke out?
Okay, you could even go mid 19th century. I would suggest that these, the concept of nation state or whatever you want to call it as you mentioned earlier, it goes by many names.
And many names are actually all theocracies loosely presented as such, but they always have a deity behind them. The current deity behind almost all of these nation states is the goddess religion personified through what's called justice.
I think all of these nation states have a department of justice. And let's just take a slice of history.
Let's use the American mid 19th century to now as a reference or as an example, and you'll follow suit with most countries similarly.
For example, you had the, what's called the Revolutionary War at the end of the 18th century, which was basically to expand the wealth and power of the people who had the most interest in the United in America.
Throughout the geography of the land, if the Revolutionary War had not happened, it had nothing to do with the main reason had nothing to do with what people are told that it was oppression from King George.
It's because they wanted to expand across the land and King George had performed edicts or put proclamations that the native people were to be left alone.
You see, and the people that were the revolutionaries or the founding fathers didn't want that they wanted to expand one of the reasons was because the English had an anti Catholic sentiment.
And when wherever the Catholics went, they integrated, they converted into Catholicism, the native people and King George didn't want to do that.
So he had a series of proclamations to protect the indigenous people.
So how are George Washington and company going to expand if they can interfere with the people's lands?
So you've got to get rid of the monarchy, form your own government and then terrorize and kill the population. They didn't even do what the Catholics did retain their population or retain some of their society and convert them.
They just went and burned and destroyed everything.
So that's your revolutionary war and nothing to do with being oppressed because they were actually the initial federal government in the US was more oppressive than the King.
If you look at the whiskey rebellion and all the seizures and captures that they did not paying their soldiers, at least the British King when you fought and they didn't pay you, they gave you, they issued you land rights, right?
So that's the revolutionary war. Then they side with the Napoleon, a conflicts and campaigns, which was the war of 1812. That doesn't pan out very well.
And then the oligarchs in England want to get back to these scoundrels or rascals in America, you know, Washington and company, I call them.
I haven't brought up the Constitution and anything like that because that I see the Constitution as a seditious document against the articles of Confederation, which were drafted way before that of a decade and a half before.
So anyway, to me, the Constitution in the United States is like the Patriot Act was, you know, recently, right? It's a seditious thing.
And I've warned that this is not, this is an, I could voice it as an opinion, but it's, it could be shown that there is something called the articles of Confederation that were just totally ignored prior.
So, okay, so now we move past the war of 1812 and the oligarchs are like, we still have to make these, these guys pay for the revolutionary war and siding with Napoleon or the war of 1812.
So what do they do? They infiltrate Abraham Lincoln's office and they give, they said, you need to boost your executive powers.
The president, the, the, the distribution of power between the legislation judicial and executive is a load of crap. You need to become king or in other words, the executive powers need to be flexed and put on steroids.
So you started passing all these laws for taxation and all this and of course nobody listened to him because he's just the president, right, which is just the small part of the government.
So you started pushing orders and executive orders and things and people just ignored it says, okay, well, we're going to back you up.
You're going to start printing money a whole bunch of it and then you're going to go and blow up your own fort and say that the South did it, right, the Southern States.
Now the Southern States were supporting the Northern States, right, in other words, they were growing all the material and providing the material through shipping, transport and agriculture for the manufacturing in the North.
And they were not supporting, let's say, a centralized government.
There were more of a Confederacy. That's why they were called the Confederacy, right.
So the North and the South were very tied together and the feds were this little entity, the federal government central government, which is left kind of like as a small third party.
And the oligarchs were like the only way we're going to go back and take control of this entire region is by creating a central authority known as the federal United States.
So what they did was they promulgated a war of the states. It was not known as a civil war in the North versus the South till 50 or 60 years later, right.
But at the time it was known as basically the war of the states and it was basically the federal government versus the rest of the states.
I know this sounds kind of harsh for some people, but if you actually do a little bit of research, even just it shouldn't take more than 30 seconds.
Abraham Lincoln in several speeches, they are online. I said, I will never address the institution of slavery. Right.
So again, it's not about slavery at all. It was about how they were going to create a powerful central government.
So the if you said that, you know, was it half a million people or really more than several million people died.
It was a false flag. It would be very correct, right. Kind of like a 9/11 thing or whatever. So what they did was they threw the country into disarray.
Then you had amendments to the constitution that created the central government district of Colombian, all of 14 amendments, citizen and all this.
And what's interesting, a few years or a couple of years after the Civil War, you could look this up, even there's stuff fun. I haven't looked at it in a long time, but from memory serves me right.
Or on 1869, 1871 or something like that, the Department of Justice is formed.
DOJ. And if you research that, no one knows where it came from, kind of like after 9/11, the Department of Homeland Security came ready to go out of nowhere.
It's like no one knows where it came from, but it was right. So no one knows who set it up or what it was for or whatever. And obviously they got to the president at the time.
I think it was Johnson who was impeached, by the way. They made him sign by executive order, the Department of Justice to represent the government legal affairs.
And no one knows where it came from. So in other words, now they have a formal temple with what would you call an army of attorneys if you want to talk about military, right?
And their whole purpose was inimical, you know, under what's called the Libra code, which is, you know, I'm throwing a lot of things out here and hopefully where resisting can look all these things up.
But even if I think if you look up what's called the Department of Justice, it's a historical anomaly. It's like where did this thing emerge from?
So now you have the goddess religion in place. You have an army of inimical soldiers to the side known as attorneys brought in out of just overnight, almost within a year or two to represent the government, which is a fictitious entity.
So at this time also the central government becomes the DC corporation 1878, 1871 district of Columbia. It's a corporation known as a sovereign state, which you could look up a sovereign state is a fictional juridical person does not exist. It's just an entity like a corporation like McDonald's or whatever.
So what I just I throw out a whole bunch of terms and scenarios and things like that you might consider being the Greeks opinion, but I assure you all of it's true.
If you do the behind the scenes researcher besides the crap that's told to the public or even in university.
And you will see that now I'm using this American model that I just put out. Apply that to other countries and you'll see similar processes taking place.
Right. So now we have a formal centralized government which doesn't exist because it's a fictional juridical person with an army of inimical attorneys behind it.
Right. And this is what you'll find in all the European countries and even Asia.
And it's always tweaked according to whatever culture and tradition, whatever country you put it in so it's accepted because if you're if it's too radical, it will be completely rejected. Right.
And so if the poison is too viral, the victim will throw it up immediately. You want to put just enough poison where it will not upset the digestive system so it can be ingested in the victim dies. You see how it works.
Yes, that makes sense. I mean, it doesn't seem that like that system has been smoothly adopted in certain places, notably, you know, African countries where there's a lot of political turmoil.
And there's been some South American countries, I think, where it's also been viciously sort of pushed back against historically in the 20th century.
Well, when you look at those countries, what's interesting, they didn't have major revolts with assembled armies and populists against the authority.
I guess not, but you did have a situation where military class, you know, rose up to provide some kind of opposition. I'm thinking maybe, you know, places like Sudan or Somalia where you still have something like that ongoing. I don't know if that applies.
Yeah, it does Congo as well.
I would suggest the Congo region.
It's power to them. I don't think that they're quote unquote good people or better people, but at least they're going against, you know, a worldwide evil that's that really will not change until there's cosmic interference.
So it just shows you that, you know, they can't take 100% of the of the planet, but they could take 99%.
And this proliferation of the nation state or the sovereign state does seem to be something that evolved once empires broke up because once you had the empires in place like the Soviet empire or the Habsburg empires, the monarchs were ruling with their own system.
So it seemed as if getting rid of those empires was also something to facilitate this agenda.
Yeah, well, what happened was the empire was made more uniform and it was taken out of view.
So it was out of the purview of the population. So it's so anything that any massive group of people or uprising or anything will be like a carnival show when you go to a shooting gallery at the carnival, you're just shooting at paper ducks or whatever.
And yeah, we can get into more of the like we wanted to perhaps talk about military and politics and the thing is you cannot separate that from each, you know, considering each culture, how the money system works and various other ideologies and perceptions.
That's why you have the various systems throughout, you know, parts of the world.
But essentially it's all one, you know, it's all one union on a 99% scale like we mentioned Congo and Somalia and places like that might and the post June tribes and parts of Afghanistan and there might be some in you at people.
And there are most definitely people in Antarctica and other places like that, you know, that we don't even hear about or hear, you know, much of even though we know it exists on the map, let's say, that are still somewhat independent, but nothing really that would be considered ever formable or to change the current condition.
We're going to go move ahead, but I do want to ask one sort of side thing based on what you said, could you contrast a bit the purpose of the articles of confederation versus what the United States Constitution brought in and how that changed the scenario for the country.
Well, the articles of the Constitution mirrors the articles of confederation, which was very loose.
Like money, there's a lot of academic criticism on the articles of confederation because it wasn't specific enough will duh if you're going to have an ideology where the people are told they're free.
You know, how many specifics do you give someone to be free?
If you want to enslave people, you do that with specificity, right?
Like if you're in prison, you have a whole bunch of rules where if you're out living in the country, there's very few rules, right?
So the anyone could look at the articles in confederation, I still consider it a pagan document. They do mention justice and a few other things like that, but it was generally loosely defining the operation of the states and the federal government, let's say, or the central government.
And of course, when you have things loosely operated like that, that doesn't benefit the oligarchs who want to put what's called a corporation or a sovereign state in place, which is neither sovereign and it's neither a state.
That's the interesting thing like federal reserve, it's neither federal in order to have any reserves. A sovereign state is not sovereign and it's not a state.
Right, you know, like American cheese is not cheese and it's not American, you know, I mean, you look at all these dubious terms, you know, and you started to get the hang of what's going on.
Yes, there does seem to be some sort of pattern to that sort of thing.
You brought up the idea of the corporation a lot in what you just said the past 15 minutes or so. So if you look at a corporation as an organization that is authorized to act as a single entity and is recognized as a legal person by law for certain purposes.
And you talk about the nation as a corporation. Can you explain that a little bit? Where is that idea memorialized and what are the implications for the citizenry of the sovereign state if they are subsumed into such a corporation?
Well, the thing is the purpose was not just to make it a corporation was the there is a final plan, which is basically subjugating the entire, you know, all societies, right?
And you have a usually a three step plan like if you're going to bake cookies, it's more than one thing, right? It's not just cookies. You have to have an oven and food preparation and you have to know how to do it.
So what they did was the reason you create the corporate model because under general corporate rules.
A corporation can be bankrupted and put into receivership and leaned right through legal agreement where if you're trying to do that with a living being or let's say a sovereign group.
They can call they can examine what is being put on them in that fashion and protested, argue it or call it fraud, but a corporation can't do that.
It just follows along whatever the dynamic parties around it do. So they figured let's call this a corporation and then we're going to bankrupt the corporation and and either put it in receivership or liquidate it.
Right. And you can see liquidations, I think like the bulk inization of states is a liquidation when you see something like the, you know, a certain empire and it's broken up into countries.
It's a liquidation, let's say, but nonetheless the purpose of creating these corporations was not just to make a corporation as such, but was is to create a model that can be manipulated.
So instead of having a model where you have a monarch or a sovereign make promises to people and then reneg on them or change.
You have a corporation that puts out a veritable plethora of conditions and has people volunteer into those conditions and then you change those conditions on a level that is beyond the education level that the people have so they never realize what just happened.
And then they're stuck with their commitments that they made and the conditions that they never and they don't even know what they are like given America you can go right now and ask people are they free and like we're pretty much free, but you're not your slave and I illegally your slave you registered you have a serial number.
Yeah, you don't have any rights or freedoms you're under privilege.
You're managed through the securities exchanges, the world wide securities exchange houses you can go on treasury dot gov if you're less than 35 years old go to bonds and I think there's a drop down menu I haven't been there in a long time.
Hopefully it's still around on the drop down menu and treasury dot gov look up bonds and under bonds on the drop down menu it'll tell you what kind of bond and you choose double E like the shoe size EE the two letters.
And then you put the bond number in it will ask you the date of the bond number and you put in the date of the bond number.
And guess what you're going to use as your bond number you're going to take the birth certificate number under double E bonds and put in the number and then and it's going to ask you the month in the year and you put in the month in the year then it'll get more specific for the date and years ago used to show you a origination of the bond and guess what the origination of the bond was it was the hospital where you were born.
So anyway so the interesting thing is when we brought up the history after the civil war in the sovereign state and whether whether it's what they call Russia or you know France, Italy, England, whatever these are sovereign states in the U.N. and all this was the purpose from the mid 19th century to the 1950s create a series of these sovereign states was not to just make a corporation but it was to create a corporation using corporate rules.
Bankrupt didn't put it in receivership and put a lean on everything that is you know all the land the people the labor the resources and hold that lean.
Because when you lean holder has to be satisfied when there's an exchange so any exchange that people or anything is performed any transaction the primary lean holder is always considered right so that was the idea was never to really just make it a corporation and leave it at that and before they did this with the federal reserve in America they practice in Canada practice in England right they practiced and you know then.
They did it here because this is the place where everybody thought they would run to escape right so when I say here meaning America what's called the U.S.
So this was a global or worldwide system that was put in place not to just make a corporation but to basically create a presumptive lean or on it's not like they own you if you like you run into the power brokers or
whoever is behind the system is do you own these but no we don't own them but they you know we we have a first position lean on everything they do including their bodies well you know what I mean it's if you put if you do something let's say work on the house or
a automobile or something you put a mechanics lean on it you don't own that thing but that thing cannot be transacted until your lean is satisfied right and there's no limit to how big that lean is so it could be everything see it's it's sort of that's the real satanism where you you know they tell you what you want to hear and when you find out what's going on they never admit it but they give you a whole round about of stories about how you're wrong and made it
or you're wrong and maybe you're right here but never a clear picture right and you see this with with every aspect of human society every institution whether it's the medical field whether it's the religious field you know gone and on and on and on physics science psychology
and the entire tree religion medical I mean every field it's all it's always never a straight answer round and round and round about and they always want you to argue you want to argue this you know they always say no I don't want to argue you want to debate that always these are these are the real
the true aspects of satan right argue debate separation division lying no clarity suggestive presumptive right so that's the operation of of the model it's not just the sovereign state being a corporation but it's to throw
everything into a position where people it's so complicated they can't even fathom the current condition and the only thing they can do in their material sense is go back to their original history where their founding fathers were right and that's it that's where most people are stuck no matter where you go in the world they cannot
a delved into the current condition they always have to refer back to something that before this condition came on because it's just too ugly to ambiguous and just paradoxical to them you know in paradox is basically something that someone doesn't understand they call it a paradox so
that's pretty much the condition and by the way this will not get better it cannot get better because the ideology and the mindset of the people in the world except for maybe those in Somalia the Congo Afghanistan couple places like that are fully entrenched and they know nothing else like there's a lot of Americans that talk about make America
great again or restore the republic or this that or the other they have no idea what it's it was like to be lawful instead of legal or to have a nation or a country and not a sovereign state that's legal you know they have no there's no way they can do it it would be you would probably be just as effective as having trying to train a school of fish to climb a tree it's just not going to happen
I do just want to throw out when people hear the word lean I know that some people struggle with that if you're not familiar with any you know financial concept so that's just the right to keep possession of a piece of property belonging to somebody else until they pay the debt or discharge the debt that they owe you
something you put on because you've performed there's some you have an equitable interest in something like if I were to have an agreement with you on something let's say I'm going to let's say cut the grass in front of your house and for $10 let's say
then we agreed to it and we we can show that we had agreed to it I cut the grass and you don't have $10 to pay me and it doesn't look like you will so what I do is I do a public filing or public notice that you owe me $10 and because you have things of value like a house I'm going to post it and attach this debt to your house
so because it shows that you don't intend to pay me now or in the near future or later eventually you might sell this house and when you sell this house that means you'll be getting a whole bunch of say cash flow and when that cash flow starts coming to you I'll be able to bypass it before it gets to you and get my $10
that's an explanation of lean so long term bypass it's basically a bypass because you owe someone money for example and you don't want to or can't don't have the means to settle that and when when money starts coming your way before it comes to you in total your debts are settled or satisfied before the resulting some comes to you that's all lean is it's a bypass what you call taxes or leans they're not taxes because there's no money to pay to tax
right indeed okay so what does the corporatization of the nation imply about the leaders because there seems to be a consistent display of incompetence by world leaders that it's easily explained if we accept the supposition that they aren't really needed so what role are those politicians really filling
well their actors the current American president is a reality show TV actor we had one that was a film actor before that and in between there there were a series of attorneys that no one know how they rose into the position they did these are people that are groomed from a young age or even pre-generational I would suggest you can even suggest again the right divine right to rule the gods don't think much of you
and proof of that is look who they give wealth and power to you don't have you don't have anyone of any good character anywhere in the world that I have seen in the past 30 or 40 years and power do you think any of the popes presidents or kings or good character
well I will have seen any and in my life that means that if there is divine right to rule they don't think much of humanity because if they did they would put a proper individual in place there's a system you see there is a system in place that we mentioned the dark forces and delicious to skip around for example something called Hollywood right and I brought this up before the movie industry
it has to agree with what's taught in school which shown on TV what's in the history books what's in the textbooks right you can't have too much of a difference in the general sense yes there are some films that break the rules right shown as fiction usually but they all have to be an agreement if you understand how the Hollywood system works and why it is where it is and not on the east coast and other places like that of America
that is a satanic it has a you know the sort of a life and say satanic dark dark ritualistic aspect to it like for example when you in order to become popular when you hear of like Michael Jackson or Bruce Willis or you know name any actor that is a big actor Tom Cruise or whatever that's done by contract when you're in Hollywood
they look at the actor and they say can they perform in other words if we bring them up in popularity and when they do that they get into other contracts where they have to perform secret rights and rituals so not on you to get into to that right and the more they sacrifices and rituals that they do the more popular they become this is exactly the same thing with the political world
for example you could look up one of the rituals that they do is they it's to introduce a particular entity into the body is they knock you on the side of the head usually on the left side of your head knock you out so an entity can enter your body in their stay or leave you know back it's a ritual
just informing you know so go online and look at the left eye satanic ritual how many people in public prominent actors the Pope presidents the Roth child have appeared in public with a black and blue left eye
right on the bruise on the side of their head politicians it's always the left eye sometimes the right they even have one with Tom Hanks holding up a sign you know I can't talk about this you know so this is this is again you know we brought up the bathroom and all these are really small minor impson demons that basically we can discuss when we discuss the occult let's say satanic stuff the real satanic stuff the higher up level is control of the
whole world and in everybody's home in everyone's traditions and cultures you see because if I you mentioned the baffin and let's say the rituals in in Hollywood and the politicians have to go through those are the minor impson demons you see but that's just a reflection of what these people are influenced
or you know influenced by so you can say that the same power group of people their religious aspect of it runs Hollywood also runs the politicians because they go hand in hand by the way you know anybody could do a little bit of research on this the state departments give awards right and
and look at how many they give to people in Hollywood and show business the actual state department people not aware of these things because they're promoting you know the genders oh yeah I mean I know the British one is the British order of something that the Queen is always giving to some famous entertainer that's been around 3040 years right right so you can see that again the the real dark stuff that people see on the internet is nothing compared to the reality you can see the reality
you can also look at for example sacrifices that are done like people's children you know like a son as 30 years old the position son and he dies and it's a mysterious death you know and there's no investigation you have a Supreme Court justice Scalia you know it goes to one of these parties he wakes up dead right no investigation you know you have Mike Tyson's daughter four years old strangles are self running on a treadmill right yeah sure you know I mean we're talking about human sacrifice on a major major level
a major major level cannibalism all this other stuff and have all of your politicians engage in this it would be safe to say yes and if there's any exception I don't know of it but I would suggest that they you don't become known all of the known for example there's five or 600 you know representatives and senators in the US not everyone can name all of them I sure can't you but you name like maybe half a dozen or a dozen so that are very popular they have of course
engaged in all this there's you know the obscure ones probably not let's say or on a minimal level and this is across the the world that's why you'll see they all have the same agendas you know and just let's talking back to you know they you know they you know they put down the people in Somalia like if you see anything written about anyone from Somalia
I was able to self-proclaimed republic that's a bad thing right they can defend it why not but they they're not goody two shoes are they engage in cannibalism big time if they have a victory or even a sport soccer team wins they celebrate by eating the liver of one of the players you know I mean it's not uncommon to be in places on the continent of Africa
in the Liberia or wherever and have what you think is beef jerky on the street and it's human flesh cut into dried strips you know sold at as food so you know we're talking about if you want to look at it from a fantastical point of you if you're a spirit in the heavens let's say before your incarnation here and like no you're going to send me down to earth
you've got to be kicking and fighting and screaming to be incarnated into this world you know if you if there is any consciousness before that we you know we had before we were sent here there's no way any conscious benevolent conscious being would come down here and want to live a life on this planet
yeah it would have to be unconsciously yeah that you're by lot sent here unfortunately and I'm I'm I'm being positive now this is up the optimistic side so yeah sure you are good so continuing with the topic of the military and how that connects to politics
I once read a definition of a state that was the following a state is an institution forced on a defeated group by a conquering group with a view of systematizing its domination and safeguarding itself against insurrection and attacked by another party
I do recognize what's true in that although I wouldn't say 100% definitive but the idea that a primary way to create a state is to subjugate an existing one is very plausible so the presence of a military class seems like a prerequisite for the endurance of most states
what can you share about the preeminence of military in today's times and how active do most western militaries tend to be in what power do they have in you know their countries given that it's said to be democratic in blah blah blah
well that's okay let's let's be truthful all of that is done after the fact not in real time in other words the time of war in every military is it just creates chaos so all the stuff that we go back and look at as a result of military action or war is is not what really happened it's what's written decades or you know later about it and that's how it's remembered
an example of that would be let's say if you take the American conflict with what's called Nazi Germany well guess who was time man of the year on the cover of time magazine in nineteen thirty three
you got a time magazine and look it up because they have a page for it they don't show you they say not available why because it was eight off Hitler such a great guy right just like Osama bin Laden was a great guy in the eighties let's say
so nothing is as we say that and if you bring up let's say the let's say the faction of the warring states let's say the Nazi state or the national socialist party in the American state if you look at a place like Yapank long island in New York
yeah panic is YAPHA and CK I guess the there was a German town there in the nineteen thirties and even still today they've they've cleaned it up somewhat but if you go on on the internet and look at Yapank long island
they even had a little German town it was not just a German town as as you know for Deutsch lem but it was a national socialist party enclave where they had you know Nazi parade they even had eight off Hitler Boulevard and there are videos and photographs of you know
Nazis in uniform goose stepping just like you see in the Nazi propaganda films for example right and this was going on for about a decade where in in long island New York Yapha and even today it's a kind of a weird place still
so you when you consider what we're told about it you know we this black and white picture it was the you know the Americans versus the Nazis and they were always evil and all that a bunch of a crock of baloney even throughout till what what's considered the end of the war in nineteen forty five German submarines would come to the coasts of the east coast of the U.S. and they would
you know come up to surface to recharge their batteries because they're electrically run underwater in the diesel engines on the surface charge the batteries for a few hours and the people on the shore would wave to them back in fourth the Americans would wave to the German you boats recharging their batteries you know and sometimes the Nazi Germans soldiers would get on a boat and come to shore and say hey you know I have a cousin that lives here you know can I you know check them out say hi and I'll have a party on the beach
this is very different this is the reality of it this is very different from the reality that were told right so and also like for example you can take an alien invasion like Mars attacks or all these alien invasions you know the aliens show up and there's an outright war or you know chaos it's not like that at all ever you see you do you you so the point of a state being formed and all this comes much much later
and it's it has to be based on the ideology then what the people accept for example from a religious point of view you brought up South America earlier and Catholicism that is the the indigenous populations had certain religions and deities and ceremonies and they are still in place today they just put up a sign that this is a Catholic church but it's this everything that's going on is according to the previous culture
so what you do is you again form the state and you people sign up towards it which is a corporation and you control them through that corporation
and connecting that to the military like what is what is the power structure within the military tend to look like I understand that you know general outranks a private for example does a military attorney outrank even a general and what are some unexpected hierarchies within the military that don't get taught
about well the interesting thing is you could you know follow the money if you look at America half of all of the energy that's generated is put towards the military even though represents less than 2 or 3% of the population
really 1% of the population but you know it's a 2 or 3% because of the supporting networks and industries all right so I think it's the concept of the military is is is an institution
it's a society within the society just like when you talk about the leads and all that and it's really the military that runs the the countries if you look at it the in other words if the military did not agree with certain policies let's say put up by the government and say laws because they don't do law anymore
they have the hardware to physically change it right you see what I mean like you've seen before in the coups military coups and revolutions and things like that so from a military perspective it is political
that's why when you look at you brought up general has a higher rank than private if you do a little bit of research on the bios of I would say American generals they all have according to the you know the public full system the education system university degrees in what field finance
the fake money you know the lean you know the the system of what we call fake money but you know I can mention earlier it's serious the fake money take it very seriously when you have a lean on someone you take it very seriously right when you have a lean on someone and you know they're going to sell their house you take that very seriously because there's your chance to get what you lean them for you see there's no money so it's just a matter of transaction so in essence what you
if you want to be very truthful of the matter the the aspect of the military is redundant and obsolete because if it's about a dressing and take over or just to say it plainly killing people you don't need bullets and other things like that it's done always done through by biologicals and food all of the battles that you see that you're touted is winning wars are not the way it works the way you subdue a population is by
biological you know a plague a pestilence or food shortage because you have a cultural mindset some places say we'll fight till the last man right now you won't because if you don't have any food to eat you're not and you're sick let's say because we've dropped biologicals on you you're not fighting you know at all none of you are it is absolutely the whole military thing is just a you know
it's a the plant obsolescence like for example consider the cell phone you know that cell phones have within their circuit board within the CMOS meaning the main operating chips a timer and after certain amount of time it stops working and you can't bring it back
right I'm sure that you know there are some people know how to bring it back raise a phone stop working printers do that you know these devices have built in obsolescence because let's say you have an apple iPhone one and it's built so well because you know it's a good quality phone it lasts you 20 years
20 years on two years stops working get the next one same thing with the military we need better planes we need better tanks better you don't because the way you take over society is by either cutting off their food supply poisoning their food supply or poisoning them or giving them disease you don't need better tanks or planes for that
that's the way it's always been done just like you know poisoning the well you've heard that's a cliche when the Romans laid siege or the Babylonians or the Assyrians if they had time they went after the water supply and also a disease putting disease on the population to a certain degree where they capitulate because you don't want to give a disease that won't go away
because then you know there's no sense of taking them over so this is how it's done on planet earth now the propaganda about military and war and state and all that is just propaganda that's just like the iPhone you know we got old equipment and whatever we need new equipment it's just an industry people again are more too moronic to realize how things are done so they have to accept what they're told
but you know i think we've talked at least privately about the connection between the military and crime or the criminal classes can you expand a bit on the notion of how the military and even maybe the police have not only a monopoly on violence but also on crime and worked actively to you know profit from that well you have to you know when you say ethics and morality morality is more of a personal idea of what someone is right and wrong the need of the ethics which is what is the blanket ideology right
it doesn't take a genius or a good researcher to figure out that you're no longer in a lawful environment unless your tradition is held on to some lawful ways or means or laws so everything is now legal which is you know anything goes so when you see for example what people attach to as being valuable you want to take control of that because now you know you can't do that so you know you know the lawful rules are all right.
People of that because now you control what people see is valuable and because the people see it is valuable they'll do anything to get it and that's basically where the police and the military come in I mean to manage that and by the way there is no police and law police you could study this police started in Europe when the the private bankers had you know pretty much influence the government so much that they told the government we need our our own private security for the government.
So if you're ready for us is to manage our stuff that we have leans on and they agreed so they brought in the created police and also to make sure that everyone does what they're supposed to do so if you're a dentist you don't take any interest in astrophysics right if you're a car mechanic you don't take any interest in medicine that was another purpose of the police to make sure everyone stays within their station or within their profession believe it or not.
This was publicly defined years ago that's when you hear people like Wilhelm Reich who was trained in psychology and psychiatry when he started going to biology they had a throne in jail from you know some obscure conviction right so make a long story short on the police and the military regarding what we call the black market.
What you see with the politicians is when they start regulating something what they're doing is see whenever there's regulation or prohibition the answer to that is the black market.
You see so it's always in reverse people think oh this is regulated now the only way to get on the black market no.
They people look at these things people in power and say how much will the market bear and they say the white market or the black market you know the surface market or the underground market.
And if they determine that something's value will go up 10 to 100 or a thousand fold in a black market what they do is they have policies that regulate or prohibit the item so then they can quote unquote make the profit on the black market.
See it's backwards you see what I mean.
So when see laws prohibiting or preventing something that's because it's been assessed that it's value will you know arithmetically go up if there's a black market and the military in the police are there to protect that.
People think the black market emerges after his regulation no it's something called what the market will bear here have been around industrial engineers or people that advertising or put out products is it what can we sell this for you know.
You see and that's always assessed no matter what it is.
And if again if something comes up to the assessment that it's value will go up many fold in a black market they create the black market by regulating it on the white or surface market that's all there is no the politicians what they call lawmakers you call them lawmakers it's so funny you know every country has lawmaker asked about any law they don't know any laws just a name.
It's like a giant shrimp you know or military intelligence or whatever it's not it's an oxymoron this is planet earth you know if I knocked you over the head and you're unconscious and you woke up in a zoo how long would it take for you to figure out you're in a zoo.
Right well you've been on this planet for more than 15 minutes you know what's going on here no.
And that's just a general statement that I usually make and if you haven't figured out by now you probably won't because what's going on is not only hard to imagine it's beyond what you can imagine.
Indeed.
In what way does the military tie into the sort of the one world corporation of nation states because I mean if the whole world is one corporation why do the states fight each other or go to war you know even Burger King and McDonald's don't mind setting up restaurants next to each other because it's good for business.
So then war sort of would defeat the purpose of a one world unified entity wouldn't it.
Yeah not not really if you live in the country they have things called duck season and deer hunting season because when you have improvements like roads and railways and things like that and you have too high of a deer population it gets really messy and dangerous if you're traveling down the road in an engine powered wagon and a 300 pound stack jumps in front of you and you're going 50 miles per hour 100 kilometers per hour that's that's not going to end well in about a third of a second.
So you need to start calling the herd right.
It also you have to remember military is a right of passage in many cultures you know I remember a meeting people from all over the world in the 70s and they I would see like two people say have you been in the military and they're like no I'm like oh they frown on him like what's wrong with you you never be a man.
You see so it's it's a cultural thing.
And there's I've heard that there are certain other aspects where the military have a certain allegiance where they have to go to or in order to appease you know there.
Well again we were mentioning Bafemut in the minor impson demons most of the military battles and things that you see that you see are unnecessary especially a good example again it's many do it.
It would be the American military about 90% of the engagements they have is not with other military forces but with civilians you look at the kill sheet the American American military 90% of it is civilians like women children old people only 10% is military other military.
And they look at the bombing of Dresden that was a human sacrifice they even had prisoners American prisoners in Dresy very heard of Kurt Vonnegut sluss slaughterhouse five was student house Fulfon German right that you know it was they had open air prisons in the Americans like great it's full of Americans let's bomb that too.
Americans don't they're like they they're a pretty good more they're very sloppy and it's it's very easy to discern that a lot of the American militaries actions are a spin off of what's called the hellfire club in England which supposedly doesn't exist anymore you know but you know they just over sacrifice you know.
What was that again because I looked into it once but you could look at the founding fathers of their sateness you know like Ben Franklin it's no mystery you could look up they they were restoring one of Benjamin Franklin's homes and they dug down and they found a whole bunch of headless bodies and dismembered bodies you know.
I was like torture for sport yeah or or you know he was until electricity so he figured why don't we start chopping up people putting them back together and using electricity to reanimate them you know how well we've seen that portrayed in certain fiction yeah I think Barry Shelley was inspired by the stories the road Frankenstein so yeah none of your I mean this is a very dark dark place you know.
You know if you remember being in certain places you know don't go down the street there's a haunted house or that's where the crazy people are whatever that's that's planted earth cosmically.
But again the military is if you were to see it's just part of tradition and culture there's no purpose to it doesn't defend and it doesn't and when it offends especially if you look at the Americans it's just you're just killing the population.
Give the Iraq war is a or any other when they want to go and oust for example the Iraq war or what they were talking about North Korea with Trump oh yeah we'll just go and turn your whole city your whole country into a fireball well so now you're now you're saying
we know it's not just Kim John Eel let's say that's a bad leader we should get rid of we want to kill all the North Koreans all five or 10 or 20 million of them look at Iraq you know Saddam Hussein Saddam Hussein well you know we just don't want to get someone else say we want to kill a million Iraqis you know you see it's not they always give the whatever reason you hear it's total crap.
It's this is old fashioned religion it's the goddess religion in place which is to destroy the way life is naturally done or it's been put in place and create another way that life is procured right that's the goddess religion or this particular goddess because there are other goddesses like you know wisdom for example that is not of such an ilk so yeah you know here's the other thing.
Like I thought you when I mentioned the character of the politicians do you do you know anyone in the military it's very rare to find anyone of good character for example about 90% of the veterans that I've spoken to young and old say when you get to know them they'll tell you that oh military was horrible.
It was mostly insane people and just people that wanted to really stupid people or people that just wanted to kill other people for just for no reason just just wanted to kill people right that sounds about right you know when you say well of course you want people that want to kill other people in the military right because that's what they're supposed to do in the being of the military it's a bellicose institution you know but when you start hearing this especially from people that were off
pursuers and they say that I found that my own men were more dangerous than the enemy you start to wonder you know this is not just about the military it's just another active part of human society like it's very accurate to say that humans are morons and people in the military are just weaponized morons it's very simple you know most people take offense to it and you know you hear a lot of you know stuff on the
Internet was always not saying this to offend anyone how can you not I mean if you are dressing a million people or 300 million people or a thousand people there is no way anyone can say anything consistently and not offend one of those people in some way whether they voice it or not so the whole thing is to bypass all that nonsense and start thinking cosmically like you know like you're not from here and you don't live here but you're visiting and you're trying to be an astute observer and objective
right you'll find that the it is it is just a moronic existence and again humans are morons and the military is just weaponized morons there's nothing much else to say I get your drifts I mean there's a lot of things that can be said as far as expanding things to give more nuance but I understand the overarching idea of what you say that once you understand it it's sort of a
sort of yeah there is a very small choice group of humans of course just let's look at it from an agricultural perspective if you're ranching and you ever heard of cows there is a small choice bit of cattle that you would you know have as LC on the milk carton photograph right or if you're an apple farmer there
it had of all the tons and tons of apples you harvest you'll always present a small choice group right select group of right of course there are select group of humans and I'm not going to say good or bad because no one is good enough to go to heaven and no one's bad enough to go to hell in the Christian mindset right even though we know that's not how it works in reality
it's everyone does good stuff and foul stuff but amongst that condition you have a select choice of premium samples or specimens and they do exist so when I that's why I say lovingly humans are morons and and the military is just weaponized morons the the amongst that there is a select group and of course a choice
you know sample very small on the planet that if you had to say this is what humans are when they you know at this state of the art do exist but you know when we do a sonic like this to describe a condition it's a general condition with some specifics for hopefully the specifics are to support the general statements
and further on anyone's research to give them a head start if they want to look into something just like I went into what's called the civil war I gave you a pretty honest and objective breakdown on what the American history was about earlier
and I have to shroud it as opinion because the whole thing in one small package like that is you want to find anywhere but I gave enough specifics you can look up that you will be able to not only form your opinion but actually see it for what it is which is the truth
and that much appreciated I'm sure people have you know a lot of time on their hands at some point to look into that if they're interested
but let's round up because we've been going on for quite a bit the last thing that I want to ask is if the political class is actually subordinate to the military class why don't we see more of a preponderance of military run states or coups something has to keep the military in check even though they have the hardware to do what they want
they ultimately don't seem to do whatever is that they want so what is it that keeps control over that the same they're all the same basically there is no division between them in other words the same the the the active military what you call campaigning that you see you know like for example you see you're in the news America is against North Korea or Iran or whatever that's just in the news
but when you see them actually doing something that is the active aspect of it you know it's usually you don't know before you usually find out after it happens right because they call it a you know breach of security if you find out before right where those orders come from from the military are the same ones that
that a prop up the politicians and of course you have to create a division that you know I'm against this and you're for it you know whatever but no there is no division there is no they're all puppets all of them if in other words if you've heard of a military figure or seen a military figure they don't have any power
the same with the politicians if you've heard of them or seen them they don't have any power in them 100% sure for the past 50 years 100% more than 50 years ago maybe 1% might have been you know in there you might say you have gateway people or liaisons like someone like that just won't go away like a Henry Kissinger for example right
or a Rockefeller or Rothschild those kinds of people they're like liaisons between the surface powers what you who you're told is in power and the the powers that you know are behind the political and military and all that other stuff and policies
you know when you see these people just don't go away you know like Blair is one of them you know he keeps popping up in political scene every now and then you don't hear from from rear to and all of a sudden
he's in the news he's like a liaison you'll see these people that just don't go away they're elected liaisons but that's the most you're going to get they have no power also so again for sure for the past 50 or so years if you've heard of the character or the person's name or seen them they have do not have power they are put in front as a leader or whatever
all right I think we've been able to offer up quite a comprehensive talk on the subject of military and politics I feel that we can lay that subject to rest at least for now other any other points you want to touch on for a week
no but I would suggest that like a sonic like this one might be helpful to some people because again going back to what I said how the American Civil War is an example for other countries as well
I have not found anyone out there that can piece something together like that very quickly I'm not saying that I'm better or I know this stuff I'm just saying that if you're going to look into any of these subjects in other words the real history political or military or whatever
you could actually waste a lot of time because there's so much misdirection and misinformation you know so the only thing I would suggest is be poignant you know look at the money sources the technological sources again the political the military sources that have created the conditions in whatever country as being a faade and misdirection you know in the academic and orthodox history that you're given
there is always a very simple secret set of let's say outline behind all of that and I can't stress how much that anyone trying to do this on their own
just off the cuff will waste a tremendous amount of time with the standard academic crap that's put out there
so the only final point I could make is if you're studying any of the subjects we mentioned tonight try to get your hands on reference materials that were published back during the time you were looking at instead of what's written about that time now
so that's pretty much it
yeah you mentioned the website that has a useful articles from 18th 19th century rare yeah they've really a internet store it's called rare newspaper articles in magazines
if you could find an archive just you know whatever period you know if you want to study Napoleon you have to go back and find stuff that was contemporarily printed even though it was still misdirection because it's always misdirection
if you look at if for example if you're a student of the bible and you look at you know not just the king James but you know more original forms of preservation and you read it with comprehension and then you look at what supposedly came out of that the religions you're going to scratch your head and say how
the two couldn't be more different and more further apart but how can people think they're the same right so the same thing is with history so you're going to have to go back and find what was existing during that time and commentary on it and what was really going on very difficult
as far as websites I think there's something called the Mitchell archives and another website that's called the back issue newspapers so there's a bunch of different ones that you could use
and remember this is not when you're doing research you're you're probably you know you're doing good research when you run into things that were never really completely addressed for the general public
because the general public has always been ignorant and primitive and savage at best you always want to look for things that were private correspondences or correspondences within whatever body it was or institution
because throughout history anything that was put out to the public was always been bunk I mean again if you go back to the biblical things stories if you look at the biblical Christ within less than a few decades they had publicly within that time period in the first century twisted the whole story and no one knew what was going on what happened you know 10 or 20 or 30 years prior regarding the life of Christ it was totally changed
so you know any this is this is true with everything
All right I think we'll put a full stop on that and it's been a good discussion thank you to everybody who tuned into this episode
we'll see you at the next stream
[Music]
[ Howling ]