[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening. This is the Archon speaking creator of Greakspeak.com
We've reached episode 7 of this podcast that I'm doing with my co-host Greek.
For those of you who have stuck around for the series, I hope that each episode has helped to build up your insight into the subjects that we're discussing.
Thankfully the feedback has only been positive thus far, so I'm encouraged by that.
I hope that we can finish strong with these next couple of episodes.
I don't really have a lot to say for this introduction, as everyone is probably familiar with at this point greakspeak.com
Remains a website with neither political religious or commercial affiliations as it's run by myself as a solo project.
So please enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
[Music]
Hi there, Greaks. How have you been keeping since the last time?
Hi there, greetings. Sure, I'm a little hungry.
Do you know what I mean? Hmm, I do know what you mean.
Okay.
So I figured that last week's discussion about science serves as a good segue into this week's theme, which is food and diet.
We'd already touched on some topics regarding that the last time, like how food is digested and how the body transmutes nutrients.
So I thought we'd do a deeper dive into similar subjects starting with examining the nature of food is something that is beyond just a consumption item, which is what?
It's been reduced to in the eyes of the public.
So food, I think, has sort of gone from something that's grown locally to feed a native population to something whose origins and contents are kind of unknown to most people, thanks to the corporations in charge of the food chains.
And also because of the level of convenience in the Western world, many people think that it's just something that you eat to not be hungry rather than a particular kind of fuel for the body.
And since we know that that's not the case, I was wondering if perhaps you could pick apart some of those misconceptions as far as food being more than just something you buy at Walmart or Walgreens?
Well, you know, you just made a statement about the corporations being in charge of the food.
That's only because they were accommodating the people.
If the people didn't want it that way or did not feel that they were being accommodated by them, that that that condition wouldn't exist.
And hence, as you might have been aware of in the past few decades, there have been many quote unquote alternative movements towards quote unquote organic food, local food, you know, different types of diet schemes, and which then eventually the corporations do grab on to again to accommodate the masses because of demand.
Essentially, if the people are feel like they're being accommodated by that situation, I should say, when you say corporation, this corporations aren't really bad.
It's just a group of people getting together forming a legal entity, let's say it could be done lawfully, but rarely is for a purpose.
And, you know, corporations have gotten a bad name because not what they are, but what they do.
So I just wanted to put that in as a qualifier.
Okay, and regarding food, what's interesting is I like to go back to historical references.
And if you go back into many historical references, even as a cliche, basically bread was considered food.
You see, or just a single staple was generally considered a, you know, what people considered as food, you know, meaning that it seems historically, I mean, there are many accounts for example in many, you know, Roman and Greek or Egyptian or whatever courts medieval courts where they had elaborate feasts and varieties and all that.
But generally, you'll find that there is a staple base in every society and it's typically a grain based product.
So, you know, maybe that could pretty much settle the idea of, you know, gluten free and all this ridiculousness stuff about grains being, you know, whatever.
I just wanted to throw this in also when you hear people allergic to gluten, they're not allergic to gluten. They're allergic to a animal grade or poorly modified grade of grain.
And of course, the gluten will irritate you because that is the most tenacious part, you know, if anyone is familiar with the anatomy of grain.
Look at what gluten does, right? It's like the protein, the fiber, let's say, not necessarily the brand fiber, but it is a, it could be get very tough on the system, especially if it's coming from a lesser grain species of grain, lesser grade of grain.
So, I just wanted to throw that out as an idea because you'll find many cultures use grains, you know, rice and cereals and they're staple. So, that should be, you know, maybe one of the points to be considered when we discuss food.
Yeah. And as far as it being something that is not just consumed to not make you hungry, but also something that affects neurological functions and energy levels and overall health.
That is something that I don't feel is particularly emphasized to the masses because they just look at it as something to consume.
So, once you come into that understanding that this is something more than that, what are the sort of considerations that you have to then take when you're looking at what to buy and what to eat?
Well, you mentioned health and food and let's just say we will focus just on the food aspect, but I would say more than a 50/50 split ones mental or spiritual or psychological condition could take priority.
Could take precedent in many cases over their health rather than the food that they eat. In other words, a really happy, ignorant, blissful person eating junk food might do better health wise than a pretty sad, panicky, paranoid,
and a sounding smart type person that eats health food. I used to tell people, for example, you know, when they looked vibrant and whatever and they had talked about health food.
And I said, you look too healthy to be eating health food, you know, because they were already vibrant, right?
So, we're going to just focus on perhaps the material aspect, but I would stress that there's more than just the material food, you know, like there's food for thought or thought for food also, right?
These, these, the psychological spirituals, they call it psychosomatic, also aspect of health, which is a very broad subject, but that needs to be considered if the concept of health is brought up one's mental state, which is again all those things that I mentioned.
I would suggest though that, ignoring the material aspect in a qualitative way, on what the food basis would be a, you know, critical mistake, and that's what we're going to pretty much talk about how to pursue, you know, qualitative, not quantitative way, the best way to source food and what, you know, what food is, I hope.
Yes, of course, and in keeping with what you just said about quality, I think one of the most reoccurring statements that you've made concerning food is the higher the quality of your food, the higher the quality of your life.
Can you elaborate a bit on that? So, how does an improved diet improve your life and what constitutes an improved diet anyway?
Sure. Well, you know, let's just put it this way, you know, maybe let's just reverse engineer the concept, what I mean by that is, let's say, and from, let's say from a biblical sense or a lot of ancient rits, you know, they almost always indirectly promote vegetarianism.
And I say indirectly because very rarely does it state anywhere that you should not eat meat, for example, right? But for example, you'll read many times that, you know, a certain spiritual state or state of health or condition in the body is preferred when you don't even touch meat, right?
I just wanted to bring that up from a reverse point of view that it's almost an indirect dictate from ancient times to to be vegetarian, let's say.
But then again, there's also the aspects of, you know, eating animal flesh or flesh, like, you know, what's interesting about that is if you were to go to a hardcore Chinese restaurant where, you know, they cater to a Chinese clientele and you happen to look at a menu.
That is in English, if it's a real hardcore Chinese restaurant, the English menu will just be a rough translation of the Chinese menu written in Chinese, Mandarin or Cantonese.
And what's interesting is when you look at meat selections, especially from who have animals, it'll state organ or muscle meat, right? And most Westerners, you know, when they go out and buy, quote unquote, a steak, well, that is the muscle meat of the animal, not the organ meat.
You know, the organ would be the intestines, let's say the stomach, the tripe or the liver or kidneys.
And the muscles would be your sirloin and your fillets and your chucks and your roasts, right? And the reason I bring this up is because it is shocking, for example, to go to a hardcore Chinese restaurant.
And when you're looking at beef selections, it'll say beef muscle and most Westerners will say, what is beef muscle? I'm like, it's steak dummy, you know, they're not used to referring it as such because what they have there is a qualitative breakdown.
For example, in the in the kingdom, in the animal kingdom, I don't want to drift off too much for I want to come back. The when a predator eats a prey animal and the prey animal is from as a ruminator, in other words, choose the cut.
When they eat the animal, they go after the organs and actually go after the ruminor or that second stomach that the animal ruminates on, which is vegetative matter that it stores in one part of its body, right, to bring up and chew on later.
And it's interesting how a predator will eat a prey animal and go for the ruminor, or the vegetative matter that's predest- partially digested in the animal.
As the primary aspect, if anyone studies predators, you know, a bear, a cougar, a lion will go the most delicacy part of the prey is the ruminor, where the vegetable matter is.
So, you know, it's kind of an interesting topic to look at, not that we humans do that, but it's interesting to see where the vitality is always in the vegetative matter, you see.
So, and also there's more vitality in the organ meat than there is in the muscle meat where the adrenaline and things like that are stored.
So, that is qualitative to a certain degree, but in our discussion, I think maybe leaning towards the quality when we discuss, well, what was to say in Greek speak when I like to discuss quality.
One of the first things I bring up is eating seasonally. And what do you think should be, perhaps, traverse that topic a little bit?
Absolutely. We will do that. I'll say a little more for later, because I think that we can still dig into a few things here.
One of the things that I'm sort of still wanting to hear about is when we talk about pursue a healthful diet, like we have what the mainstream says that is as far as things like food pyramids and balanced diets and blah, blah, blah.
What in your experience has been the best definition of that?
The mainstream? You mean the terrorists?
Anyway, there are many names. That's what I call them. They're actually, they are the terrorists.
It's always backwards. It's just a small adjunct to this discussion.
You know, like in America, you know, the 9/11, they brought the terrorism to Ford to the people's minds and you know, they must have won because, you know, they said the terrorists hated the freedoms of the Americans will obviously all the victims were taken away after so the terrorists are winning.
You get it. The food terrorists are the medical community and all that.
There's several levels to that. You know, they tell you, you know, well, red meat it. Well, first it was charbrowled meat is bad, then red meat is bad.
And then I don't know, sugar is bad and then now it's wheat is bad and that's just just terrorism.
We have to keep the population ignorant and in fear. I think stupid and fearful.
But on the other hand, the mainstream, you know, especially many of the regulatory and government agencies, they are not approaching, let's say, nutritional information and, you know, mainstream information that people get from a health point of view.
They're doing it from a, how would you, what would you call property management?
See, they view people as livestock. There's legally, you're registered as livestock. You know, it's called human resources or human services, human, you know, livestock and people be livestock, of course, because they're alive and they're in stock.
And just like anyone managing livestock, you want to predict if let's say you're running, you're operating a ranch with 300 million bits of livestock on there.
You have to estimate how are you going to feed them and what certain feed parameters you should have to have a consistency, you know, with the livestock. And that's all the mainstream is.
But unfortunately, you know, you're in the age of terror, so you're going to be terrorized about it. I think that there is no, let me just say this again, with a capital, oh, there is no valid information regarding food in the mainstream.
There is a lot of information, but there is no valid information.
They are still basing nutritional information with a caloric count. If anyone doesn't know how they do caloric count, they take like something looks like a test tube. They put a bit of food in there and they pump oxygen in their gas, pure gas as sure as they can get it.
Then they have something akin to a spark plug and they seal the mechanism or the capsule and they ignite the oxygen and then within a flash of a moment, the oxygen burns everything to a crisp and they measure the heat given off and that's the caloric intake.
So I don't think the intestines work that way. And also if you were pooping charcoal, then you could say that you've absorbed all the calories as they say, right, but that's not the case either. So there's nothing valid in any science, university or government or social stuff media that's regarding food.
And I don't want to be a part of a loyal resistance because the moment you just start talking about how something or an organization or group or social aspect is not good, you become this resistance and they like that because in order, you know, an opposition, you know, most entities or groups like to have an opposition, you know, makes them stronger in a way.
So I don't want to be their opposition, but without opposing them, bring up how ridiculous on their face, the information that is brought out another one is cholesterol. That's high in cholesterol. That is a misnomer.
And cholesterol is something that's created in the body is there's nothing you can eat with cholesterol in it unless you're, anyway, the the the the amount of stupidity, it's just sheer stupidity that is out in the in the world regarding food is unfathomable.
So it should it needs to be discarded in order to have sensibility. So regarding nutrition on what you should do, if you want to really know, like I said, eating seasonally and promoting indirectly promoting vegetarianism, seeking out traditions.
What what you found being eaten through culture, you know, I'm talking about the cross latitude aspect of, you know, you have Asian and Western cultures, Northern and Southern cultures. If you look at their many of their traditions, that would be the most advisable way to go.
And also, by the way, I like to say amateurs give advice and pros give diagnoses, right? So when I say advisable, it's kind of like it doesn't really get people very far because you have to diagnose your condition, which means, you know, cross, you look at it across, right in a good way and figure out what's really going on.
I mean, you've talked, I mean, a lot of those points will develop them as we go on, but I thought it was interesting that you talk about how the establishment is clueless and how the masses need to be accommodated because that ties back to sense, it caused me to censorship.
So given that that censorship has to be in all encompassing condition, it makes me wonder in what way does the food have to be manipulated or altered to cater to that world where people are blind to what's important.
And the matter of putting something into the plans or the animals that the food is right from or altering the traditions of how food is cooked in the home or making certain foods favorable over other ones, etc.
Yeah, indirectly promoting non-meat or vegetarian is would be the indirect best way to say, you know, vegetation as a base diet is best.
And putting things in all that in food that would be the spraying and storage shown on transport, you know, yeah, and then there's the deliberate, you know, cynicism that one might tend to hear if I say that the people that rule you have certain beliefs.
And whether you believe them or not doesn't matter, I'm stating as a fact and for sure the people that rule the world take control of governments, food supplies, water supplies in the military.
Right. For example, if you look at the symbol of the United Nations, that is not a map of the world with any kind of geodesic lines.
And it is that is not an hall of branch going around it. You could anyone does research and what an all of branch looks like.
We'll see that is not the United Nations symbol. What the United Nations symbol is is wheat going around what looks like a map of the world in the crosshairs of a rifle.
Right. It's very cynical, but no one sees it because you're not supposed to see it, right. You're only supposed to see what you're supposed to. So again, the people that rule you control the food industry.
So for example, if you look at the darkest deepest conspiracies on the internet, you'll find that there's good enough evidence that a lot of quote unquote what they call it from a generic sense of satanic powers.
If you look at their dossier, they actually own food corporations, real big ones, right, like satanists, right.
And of course, you know, control the governments and all that like most people don't know that all of their government leaders have to do a ritual where they crawl on their stomach and in front of a group, religious group.
And there's a bowl of feces, a bowl of blood and a bowl of urine that they have to partake. And yes, your leaders do that.
So without getting down that dark road, these are the people that are running the food also, you know, distribution.
What they do to it is very, what they can do to it regarding by and engineering and all that is all mythology.
What happens is they just revive strains of food that have certain characteristics. And an example of that would be if anyone's been in a large office building in a major city, you walk into some of these lobbies and they're magnificent indoor lobbies and you'll see like citrus trees.
Right. Well, those are what's called decorative citrus trees. And one day I just grabbed a, you know, what looked like an orange and plucked it and I tried to open and eat it and it was all pith.
There was nothing resembling an orange fruit inside. It was like a solid, starchy mass.
So there was a decorative variety of citrus tree that has no nutrition really and, you know, other than fiber.
So, you know, there are decorative strains or strands or genes of plants that are inedible. Then there's like what's called animal grade or not for human consumption.
Like a lot of soybeans. There's an animal strain that they grow for feeding animals. And there's, you know, like if you go to China or Asia or Korea, they have many, many varieties of soybeans.
And you'll see, I've seen someone who is distributing soybeans ones is it those look really large. Yeah, that's the animal soybean that are grown for animals, not for humans because they doesn't have a lot of nutrition for, let's say, you know, being a high quality soybean.
So let us, the example giving here is, for example, take the consistency of the grains that are being produced for most consumption throughout the world.
And most parts, especially the Americas is there because of the environmentalism, they're seeking out grains that grow fast and require less irrigation or less water, right?
Because economically from, from an agriculture economy, if it needs less water, it's cheaper. And if it grows faster, you don't have to wait as long time as money for them.
So they're putting out, oh, actually sowing and reaping this type of grain versus one that required more hydration, more irrigation and took longer to grow, you see.
And the one that required more irrigation and took longer to grow is more healthful and beneficial for people to eat than the one that doesn't.
And also there are, there are plants that are naturally insect repellent, you know, insects won't eat them, you know, as much.
And things like that. So the variety goes on and on and on. If you look at the majority of the vegetables that you see that is, like an example is iceberg lettuce that is a hybridization, you know, plants can be hybridized.
You know, give another example, people, you know, there's an old cliche that says what came first, the chicken or the egg, well, I'll tell you, as you ask that question, the chicken farmer did.
And what you call a chicken today is the product of crossbreeding by chicken farmers for the past 500 years, because if you had seen a chicken from more than 500 years ago, you would not recognize it as such.
It would be very thin and tall and lanky and you might recognize it as a chicken, but nothing like you would consider seeing today.
And so there's a tremendous amount of manipulation, natural manipulation, hybridization that man has been doing to ultimately end up with the food sources that you see today.
And I mean, there are a few corporations that are sort of in the most front facing public life for that sort of thing.
I'll just mention a few of them later, but now I want to look at the connection between food and health and what the interrelationship is there, because you want to say something interesting on a different livestream about food.
I think you said some people say olive oil is healthy, but actually that's inaccurate. Food is neither healthful nor unhealthful.
It's rather the body that's either healthy or not, and those two things aren't the same.
Even though I know you said a healthy kind of grain just a few minutes ago, maybe you were saying that lightly, because I want you to develop this point a bit.
Some would say it doesn't reconcile very well with the fact that some foods are said to be toxic in and of themselves, or at least have a toxifying effect on the body and so on.
Well, there's food combining for many people, for example, well, if nothing is really healthy in itself, it's healthful.
I like to use that term more.
Sometimes I was like healthy, but healthful, meaning it promotes that versus the opposite, which would be difficult for the body to recognize as nutrition, for example.
But there is something called food combining, and when very often there might be a semi-toxic substance found in what's considered a fruit or a vegetable, and they'll promote that as being toxic because of that without sensing the combination of the rest of the things around it.
Like food combining, for example, for many people, if you eat melon and dairy, or melon and citrus, it becomes toxic in the gut.
If you want to make someone sick, play a joke on them, have them eat a good amount of watermelon and then drink a pint of milk that will create a toxic effect in the body.
I used to say for melons, for example, anything that's a melon for type of fruit, eat it alone or leave it alone because there's a different type of enzyme that works specifically on a melon than would do dairy or other things or grain.
When we start discussing what is healthful for a healthy, you know, being, you have to consider again seasonality, food combining, then the average outlook.
If someone has an average outlook, like it's more beneficial to indirectly be vegetarian, that doesn't mean dogmatic, like I don't eat meat and get that away from me.
You need a chicken nugget or something, right? That's not the point. The point is the general outlook to promote a body that is ultimately in a healthy condition would require food that promotes that.
Of course, goes again to the understanding of what human body is and how it works. In essence, we've indirectly touched on that on how nothing is absorbed by the body.
You're not a filter bag that's under pressure, right? That's what they're trying to tell everyone for the past half century.
In essence, it's a very broad subject, but for food, again, throughout this whole sonic, however long it is, I'll have to keep repeating that mindset is very important and indirectly being vegetarian.
We, and also having, you know, knowing how to treat water, having clean, clear, cool water. Also another thing is hygiene, proper hygiene.
You know, wash your groin and your armpits often and you watch, you know, basically that is the pride and underneath your fingernails that promotes health, by the way, promotes a healthy condition.
For example, and we're talking about food, but for hygiene is also very important as well. If you want to understand hygiene, get 100 year old or more nurses manual.
They don't do this anymore, nurse current nursing manuals, but if you have an old nursing manual, especially from turn of the century or before, when a patient came in to a clinic, they made sure that their fingernails were trimmed and their hair was trimmed, right?
Because of, you know, just stuff and washing their armpits and groins. I mean, that's not really in the purview anymore. Now they just spray antibacterial on you.
So, so when we keep bringing up health and food, there's more to that. Again, it's the actual hygiene and the mental state that is required, like I said earlier, someone that's really happy and blissful eating junk food will always be better off than someone who's missing.
And then, you know, they're often someone who's miserable and eating health food. Give an example years ago, I remember someone came to me and bought a very expensive bicycle because they had stage three cancer and they were going to die and they wanted to on their bucket list right across the United States of America, I was a bike.
I didn't care if they died trying they would what's what they wanted to do. Well, I saw the person about eight months later, they were real slim and looked real fit. I almost didn't recognize him. I said, man, I don't have cancer anymore. I rode my bike across the country. I ate hot dogs and pizza and I have no more cancer.
So, you see my point, I mean, it's a very touchy subject. What I do like to discuss is how to improve the quality of what of their of people's intake, you know, because everyone eats just like everyone poops, you know, you remember that was a little children's book, everyone poops.
Anyway, no, I missed that one. Yeah, it was a little like for four year olds and I was a little dinosaur on the cover, you know, anyway, so everyone eats and I would suggest that because you're going to eat anyway, why not listen to a sonic that is rational?
If you want to listen to the terrorists, you know, the scientists or whatever the government agencies, the scientists, the universities find that's, you know, it's voluntary, right?
Or you can listen to sound information that has been stored in front of everyone for a very, very long time, simply by the way things are done.
So, and by the way, I have no qualms in calling the establishment terrorists because that's what they're doing. They're inflicting fear and chaos and actually hurting people for political reasons.
The definition of a terrorist is someone who does something for political and economic or social reasons. And if you don't understand the medical and food community, the established medical food community as being terrorists, you don't know the definition of the word terrorist.
So, I have no problem of using that term accurately that way.
So, you're going to eat anyway. So, might as well discuss things. See, if you, one of the fastest most rapid improvements you can do to your life is changing what you eat qualitatively because you're going to be eating anyway.
I hear you. I just want to dwell a little bit on something that you've mentioned, I think, twice thus far.
So, this idea of people who, like it's better to be happy and eat junk food than to be overly serious and sober and say that you're going to pursue some kind of a, what you perceive as a healthful diet, it may not necessarily be what you think you need.
Because there's this trend over the past 10 years or so of turning everything from food to exercise to religion into some kind of lifestyle branding that's suitable for social media because that's how people manage their public image.
So, for those people eating food that looks good on camera can be more important than the food's nutritional value.
So, one of the things you said before was how many people do you know that are super concerned about their health and diet and yet they're doing worse than people who barely care at all?
And so, I was wondering if maybe you could share another anecdote about that because it's interesting how one person suffers although he's making all this effort and then another person gets by hardly making any effort.
Well, like I said earlier, maybe better than a 50/50 split ones mental condition is important, right?
I mean, think about a healthful person. Let's say you consider yourself healthy and you register down for a meal and you phone rings and you get some really bad news.
Very rarely do people of a sane mind will continue very often. They will say, "I just got some bad news and I've lost my appetite."
Oh, yes, that is true.
That's why I said it's probably better than 50/50 the mental state of an individual.
Then there's the personal tolerance that some people have in reproducing the toxins.
Like, for example, if you ever heard someone saying that little girl there, you know, meaning a young lady would drink this big guy under the table.
Right? You've heard many times that you've heard something like that. You know, someone can drink you under the table.
It means they can handle more alcohol than you. It's not because they're drinking the alcohol and it's being absorbed into your blood and they put the police put the monitor on you to see how much blood content you have in your blood.
It's absurd that if blood, alcohol was absorbed into your blood through the intestine, you would die from sepsis, septic shock.
It doesn't happen. The body actually produces that substance.
And the person who can drink the other person under the table is not reproducing that alcohol in the blood stream as quickly as the other.
Where someone is very light on their drinking or feet.
Let's say you can have a little bit of some alcohol, whether it's a hard liquor or beer or wine and feel really tipsy.
It's because their body has a propensity to produce that substance.
So the same goes with someone, let's say, who's eating toxified food.
If you're wondering if you're eating toxified food, if you're eating food that comes in a very colorful package, it most likely is toxic.
And their body may not recognize the toxins in the food and reproduce it.
And where someone who's body who can recognize the toxins and reproduce them will be more detriment, you see?
Yeah, I follow you.
Yeah, this is a science. This is all based on reality, real science, real science, where it's not just material based, energetically and ethereal based as well.
You see, even though this is a materially based world, right? They want material, everything is material or chemistry.
It's ironic how in many cases, even when you do produce evidence in material form, it's ignored.
So that tells you there are hypocrites and that it would be abandoned. In other words, it's like it's kind of hard.
It's probably harder to tell someone to abandon the society they live in mentally than to abandon their family.
You always hear about people abandoning their family, you know, whatever.
And you don't know, and they try to start a new life.
Well, try to do that with the society you live in. It's even more difficult, but that is part of the necessity if you're living in a six society or a society of such hypocrisy and evil.
As far as this idea of things being different from what you might think with regards to food, there's another thing that I've noticed, and perhaps it's a bit tangential, but there's this thing in professional sports at the moment where TV pundits will remark on how improved training.
And conditioning has become, and yet pro athletes suffer more than twice as many injuries now as 30 years ago, which is ironic.
Like you didn't see this many injuries in the NBA when Michael Jordan played basketball, even though the level of training facilities in medicine was considered to be lower back then.
So to connect that kind of idea to food, why is it that for all the alleged upswing in jimming and fitness and dieting and variety of foods in medicines and blah, blah.
People today look less fit than in ancient times in that for all the health care options available. There seems to be a wider variety of ailments affecting people now than before.
Because there are more on. Look at what we talked about sports athletes. Let's go to another type of livestock. We could look at race horses. They suffer the same.
I would invite anyone to consider looking at race horse statistics from 70 or 80 years ago, track times and things like that.
And look at supposedly if you're so advanced, look at the track times that horses race in today. They're much slower.
And also they're more susceptible to injuries. And again, race horses or human athletes, just another livestock again.
Again, you're being led by basically pretty bad. Let's say you have the how do you say maybe I try to hint us in every sonic that the earth and all societies in earth are being guided by very malevolent, you know, ask, let's say entities.
If you want to consider them being human or not human, that's up to you. But nothing good will come out of it. You know, that's basically it. So what are you going to do about it is make a qualitative change.
I would suggest that I've always made a suggestions to people who were in reasonable health to go to a sports doctor, by the way, than a regular practitioner who is used to looking at really old people and sedentary people, right?
Because for example, if you have someone who's considered fit as an athlete, go to a regular medical practitioner, they'll always say they're great, right? Because they're always looking at people that should have died 10 years ago, they're being pumped up with pharmaceuticals, you know.
So you always want to go to a sports doctor because they'll they're tend to look at better specimens. But even they have been fallen the the idiocy.
You know, there's a film called idiocracy. I think it starts off with the top research is, you know, a penis enlargement and hair growth or something like that. So, you know, yeah, they're pretty much more on. I have, I was enough firsthand experience with top level surgeons, doctors, practitioners to tell you that they're all more on.
And I'm sorry if any of you guys are listening that, you know, I'm not pointing you up by name, but you've admitted to me that what you're doing is stupid anyway. So, yeah. Basically, the thing is that I get from most of the people that I've spoken with that are surgeons and whatever they say, well, you know, if someone's in a truck accident, they're going to need me. That's the best they can do. But in terms of understanding.
See, you don't have to understand like, for example, you can go to the, what is it, Foxconn that makes the iPhones and you'll see hundreds of people putting the iPhones together. I assure you no one putting those phones together knows how to put what an eye, how an iPhone is engineered. None of them do.
Right. Basically, when you go into a doctor, it's an assembly line process. And how do I know that? Well, you have an eye doctor, an ear doctor, a foot doctor, a hand doctor, a skin doctor, heart doctor. Right. So it's on assembly line. They don't know the whole, they're not supposed to see the whole thing together. And again, I've never spoken to a researcher in biology or surgeon or doctor that knows how the body works and can explain it at all.
Accurately, and they think they do when they get upset when you show them, for example, a cross section of the intestines and the lumina, you know, you know, as they show me how anything gets absorbed. What is the mechanism of absorption they can't. Right.
My favorite is neurosurgeons, you know, when you show them a bundle of the human nerves anatomically and then you show them a bundle of fiber optic cable and they're exactly the same. That's, that's the best for shutting up the neurosurgeons.
So you ever heard of people having light, you know, love and light and your internal light and all that. Yeah. Well, it's pretty literal believe it or not.
And how many times have you seen an animation of neurons on, you know, the movies or TV or a video and they always show you the neuron in action. What are they show you accommodating the image flash of light, don't they?
Try it in front of you the whole time.
I once came across some information that talked about how the modern idea of a balanced diet and food groups and the food pyramid and these kind of things were introduced or at least emphasized in the 70s and that they were pretty much arbitrary or product of that time, but they've persisted this day.
And I think you've talked about that on other streams prior. So as far as food or diet categorizations go, how useful have you found those things to be and is there any such thing as what they're calling a balanced diet.
Okay, let me just give an analogy and I'll answer that indirectly. If we were to open a cattle ranch with 300 million cattle on it and we had a corporate meeting about running this ranch, because remember 300 million cattle. That's a lot of cattle.
We're going to have to produce charts in the diagrams and how we're going to feed these cattle and what parameters we're going to follow, right?
Remember, these are just cattle now. We're talking about. Right. Yeah. Okay. That's sort of have to say about that.
It has nothing those pie charts and charts of nothing to do with with with people. That's for citizens and residents and whatever you want to identify with that they label that they give you to put on.
But I but I think but somebody would say the cattle only eat one thing and human beings kind of don't.
There are more omnivores, but cows they they ate a lot of bugs, by the way, when they're eating that grass, you know, the problem with variety.
Well, the problem will lady bugs, hopefully, but the what's going on with prioritization with cattle.
Where they, you know, the idiots say, well, there's the cattle meat is needs more protein for, you know, for grooming and these cows for slaughter or for food.
So they need more protein. So they go to a catalog and they buy protein to add to the feed, but they never kind of really consider that that protein is cow flesh protein.
So now you have cows eating cows and they get prioritization in the brain mad cow chickens eating chickens, you know, actually chickens are one of the foul is one of the birds are one of the interesting things.
If you know anyone who's ever been in a war zone.
It's not talked about much, but when they come out of the war zone, they those in you try to serve chicken or ask about chicken, they'll say, no, I'll never eat chicken again.
Right, because they've what what do you find a lot of in a war zone, typically as corpses could have her as bodies human.
And when you're in a war zone and you see bodies and they're not being buried, guess who else you see picking on those bodies and eating those bodies besides dogs and things like that chickens chickens come out.
Nice fat chickens out of a war zone, so they don't get prionization, but that easily, I'm sure it is possible if they just a chicken.
But I would say the nutritional information and all that is a joke, just like calories and everything else. I mean, I tell people I was having a discussion about food and energy and health and prison wants is athletic.
I just wanted to get rid of them because no matter what I said, they just bounced back with the standard be stock BS, you know, academic stuff.
And I said, you think the food is really giving you energy directly. I mean, I basically wanted to get rid of them and I started to get more on the insulting side of things.
And I said, do you think those baloney and margarine sandwiches you eat every day or that was what giving you energy?
You know, you think the host is twinky that you eat allows you to get up and walk across the room, not at all.
The food powers you indirectly, not directly. So it's kind of like an engine oil in a car if you remove from a reciprocating combustion edge of the engine oil, you know, any mechanical tell you, well, the engine will run for a few minutes or less and burn up and blow up because it's there to cool the engine.
Well, is it no, is there to lubricate the engine, but it's also to cool and lubricate, you see?
So it's in direct and indirect, you know what I mean?
But nonetheless, if there's no oil in the engine, it will, you will destroy the engine. If there is no food in the body, you will destroy the body eventually.
But it's indirect. It has an indirect purpose.
Let's also touch real quick on this idea of organic food because the organic food is an industry that provides itself on providing what they call a good alternative to what's being sold in the cheap end of the supermarket.
But you've taken a broader view of looking at that and you know, you want said that organic food doesn't speak well of a society at large because it now people have allowed the regular food to become so toxified that certain corporations have to come along and offer market solutions through organic food.
Is that something that you've ever brought up to the people in the organic food world?
No, because the people in the organic food world are just as idiotic and moronic as the rest. They're just taking advantage of a market scheme or market share.
For example, when I was made aware of it, it was in very, very early, late 70s, early 80s of eating organically, it was never on any commercial level.
Well, a very slight commercial level. It was always on the most local base where, you know, like a farmer's market or a small, small health conscious store that would say that these plants and vegetables are not sprayed with insecticides and synthetic fertilizers.
They wouldn't use the term organic and because they're not sprayed with such and such, you know, you won't be toxified by eating the ones that are.
And that was still important there because there was a strong undercurrent up until the 60s and 70s that wasn't discussed much that a lot of neurological diseases were associated with and neuropathies were associated with what's being sprayed on plants.
For example, people don't know this and you know, you might have deniers of what the truth is that polio that crippled millions of people was because of the spraying of DDT because of the flies.
And people are not aware of in 1920s, 30s and 40s, there were swarms of flies through cities and suburbs.
And the outcry to the municipalities was allowed enough that they resorted to having spray trucks. And during the day, they'd be crowds of people. They would just start coming through spraying DDT, which was later banned.
And there was even a panel of doctors that spoke in Congress. This is where you guys call it polio, call it whatever you want. You're crippling your citizens.
There was a book written about it by a woman who was viewed on very poorly and to show you how evil and rotten the medical community is they actually said we came up with a polio vaccine and it worked. Aren't we great? And most of the people applauded the doctors for that.
They need to make a vaccine for stupidity. So you see what anyway, then there won't be any more doctors.
Yeah, well, there'll be a lot of classes that will disappear.
Yeah, not just the doctors. Yeah, you'll just have emergency medical. I mean, it's just like there's certain countries in Europe, they don't really have a standing army because every man between a certain age has to once a month go and do target practice and have an M16 or a rifle in their house to protect the country, right?
And in a proper society, you won't need doctors. I mean, actually doctors have been made fun of even in the biblical times. Basically joking around like they can't even heal themselves, you know.
You just basically have with each community a group of people and know how to address emergency situations. You don't need doctors.
I mean, it's a ridiculous. It's just, yeah, it's just a sick, you know, sick society. I mean, we're too bad. We're stuck on this planet. But, you know, just like any issue, it boils down to state of mind.
And that's, that's, if you manipulate, you know, even the American presidents, when the recent wars, they say we're doing this to capture the heart and mind.
You know, what was it? Citizen Kane, you know, you, you, you, you get the war, you know, you figure out where you want to go to war and I'll make it happen. You know, meaning the newspaper will make it happen, right? It's a state of mind.
Indeed. Let's not forget to talk about the seasonality thing. So as far as correlation between health and food goes, one of the most emphasized points that you've made is about how the time of year affects the conditions within the body and how food intake should be brought in alignment with that.
So I want to look at why eating seasonably is something important and you've touched on it a bit already. How did you come to learn that this was sort of a pertinent concept and what's the most obvious evidence that speaks in favor of that?
Well, I learned through observation from a very young age that the diet changed during the, when it was, let's say, warm outside the hot seasons, you know, late spring, summer, early fall.
We ate differently than we did in midwinter and anyone will notice that, you know, I'll have a hot fresh, a cool first salad and some fruit in the summer and in the winter, I want a hot bowl of soup, right?
That's your anyone will realize that that is an occurrence, a normal natural occurrence in most societies.
And then I started looking at the contrast from coming from a European background to the American background that I lived in on how crappy and tasteless the American food was.
And I also noticed how consistently bad it was because they ate almost, they tried to eat the same stuff all year round.
They discovered macrobiotics, which was a short stand. It was a good, it was something that was formed in the 70s to 80s and I came in in the middle of it.
I actually knew some of the people that formed it in this country.
Shizuko Yamamoto and Michio Kushi and Avalin Kushi, Herman Iharra did not know and George Asawa had died before.
But I was around those people and a lot of what they said made enough sense for me to remember the aspect, not to be so sino-nipocentric, meaning Japanese centric.
But taking with me the idea that it's seasonal affects the body.
And also there is a blood chemistry that's involved and it's provable that in colder climates the blood tends to be a little thicker, not that the blood is the be all end all.
But the blood is a little thicker than in warmer climates.
For example, in a cold climate you get a hot fever and in a hot climate you get a cold fever.
So there's a reversal, right? So there is a difference there. So the cross-seasonal chemical aspect or influence would be, for example, if you're living in a cold climate and you eat something grown in the tropics, that food will tend to adjust the body to a tropical condition and you will feel uncomfortable and you will not be able to warm yourself.
And if you're in a hot climate and you eat food that's grown in a cold climate it will tend to acclimate your body to a colder climate and you won't be able to cool down.
But you know, another analogy would be if you're up near the North Pole or the South Pole and you eat a banana you won't be able to stay warm.
And if you're living near the equator or the tropics and you eat salmon fish from the Arctic you won't be able to cool down.
And I found this to be true through experimentation.
But for somebody who wants to be a detractor of what you're talking about they might say, well, but look at all the people who don't eat seasonally which constitutes, I don't know, only like 80% of the world's population and they're fine.
I mean sure they get sick but not outside the realm of what's reasonable. Everybody gets sick anyway and it's not like your diet will cure contagion or cancer or even prevent headaches.
So how pertinent is it really beyond being just a recommendation beyond many other dietary recommendations?
It depends on what quality you're looking for. It's just like headphones or bicycles or cars or bed sheets.
You know, I like these bed sheets that everybody else uses. Yeah, I get a little bit of rash but it's okay. Everybody else is using them.
Right. Or these headphones work. I paid a dollar for them at the dollar store. They're great. They work.
Everybody else buys them. They're always out of stock. I mean, it's just a qualitative issue. Now in many cases, I have not found that people that had let's say advanced forms of illness do much better by eating seasonally.
But I have found nine out of 10 times if not 10 out of 10 times that when people do eat seasonally, they are far more comfortable during that season.
I've had to direct experimentation and subjective and objective experimentation done by others. What I mean by subjective and objective objective would be where they're actually doing a study and being strict and subjective means yeah, I cut out some of the things I used to eat, you know, kind of, you know, more loose about it.
Yeah.
It's okay. So I mean, it's something to be considered, but it doesn't seem to be observably the BL end all because we have at the end of the day adjusted to or people have largely adjusted to a world where they completely don't eat seasonally and they're not dropping as flies in any case.
No, but it's a cumulative thing. You know, like for example, with race cars, I remember some people buying the Porsche 911 body to race on a track.
One of the things about a race car is making it as light, you know, the horsepower to weight ratio. You want to make it as light weight as possible.
And the way you do that is not by changing one component, making it lighter, but taking off a little bit of weight off of as many components as possible.
It's done in the airplane industry. For example, years ago, I remember if it costs less than $300 to remove a pound off of an airplane, part do it.
Right? Because you're going to get the returns on that on the fuel. So you know, it's a cumulative effect.
Again, better than 50, 50 split, your mindset is important. Eating seasonally is important. Seeking quality food is important if you can get it.
But basically what they call heirloom or more original type grains and vegetables, right, versus the newer ones that are being presented and faked as allergies, just like that they fake a polio vaccine.
So there are many aspects to this when you look at it cumulatively and then the cumulative effect is the gross effect, you know, the single effect you could look at.
Let's also look at fake food by which I mean food that observably does the opposite of what we can all agree food is supposed to do.
So at the broadest level of analysis, we can agree that the purpose of food is to provide the body with nutritional needs and energy levels that allow it to remain vitalized and healthful.
And yet anyone who's paying attention will have noticed how certain foods, particularly fast foods, leave you feeling less vitalized or sometimes even groggy or sleepy.
And maybe if you're, I mean, maybe if you're not a child, you know, I noticed that children seem to eat a lot of that stuff and it doesn't seem to have visibly affect them.
But for me, it became noticeable as an adult when I stopped eating fast food for a few months and then came back to it that it had an adverse effect.
What can be said about that type of thing where processed food seem to not really help you with vitality and health?
Well, it's the intent behind it and the actual quality of the food again.
Like for example, certain types of cheeses are processed food, you know, I mean, how do you make cheese, right?
And then there can be beneficial. I mean, for example, if you're doing a vegetarian diet and you look at something like tempeh, which is a fermented soybean or miso, which is a fermented bean paste, those are processed, you know, they're crushed filtered, salted, cured.
It's the matter of quality again. I mean, is there such thing as a quality fast food? Of course there is. Have you ever heard of like a bean burrito? You know, that's quality, I mean, that's fast food.
And if it's a quality flower tortilla and quality beans, it's good. But you know, again, I think we go back if you go back to the earlier intent of the major corporations, which are the government, by the way, there is no government. There is no corporation.
It's just as big a modulation. It's hard to discern. But for for typical discussion, you would say that their intent is evil.
But evil is real evil is always presented as good, right? And whenever you bring up fast food or because fast food, by the way, is not just for convenience. It's also a subculture, right?
I mean, for many people, I know, for example, in the ghetto, it's prestigious to eat McDonald's. I remember in the 80s and 90s, if you lived in the ghetto and you ate in McDonald's, you were living large, right?
So, I mean, it's more than just calling it, calling it when you say fast food. I'm not sure if it can be defined outside of the negativity that's been acquired by the term through the, you know, the corporate industrial mal, mal intent aspect of it.
Because I eat fast food very often. Like if I want fast food, I will prepare something that is easy to prepare and take it with me, if I'm traveling.
But it's not the fast food when we say fast food is as a genre of food, which is basically industrial mal intent, you know. I think it goes beyond,
beyond just profit. I think it's everything is becoming a religion, right? You know, or there's a spiritual aspect to it. What I mean by that, again, like I started out earlier, you know, the people that are, what are generally referred to as Satanists, they are interested in controlling the political scene, which they do, the food and the water.
That's, that's a fact, if anyone has done research on that and I'm talking beyond the satanic panic from the 80s and 90s, which is covered up.
But if you were to, you know, these are malevolent people with malevolent intent, you'll find that they're very much into the genre of fast food.
Like, I don't know if anyone remembers a couple of years ago, there was a radical rabbi that said they had some McDonald's beef patties tasted and there was evidence of human flesh in them, right?
And in, you know, most people will laugh at that, some people say that sounds kind of scary, but I'll tell you if, if even a rumor of that would ring more true, not because it happened by accident, but because it's actually part of the religion.
You see, they're part, the table, what they believe in, you know what I mean?
What are some of the more significant industrial developments that come to mind for you in terms of the degradation of food quality?
Because a lot is said about them on Santos and the bares of the world, but whether we talk about factory farming or spraying of pesticides or the prevalence of food labs or the rise of 10 foods, etc.
Is there anything that you would put your finger on that has contributed the most to today's date of food?
No, it's cumulative.
It's, it's, you've ever heard of the term, it's of what's in the water and it's true that people who don't have municipal water that rely on a spring are more intelligent or IQs are higher.
You know, if you're going to use that as a measurement, it's water, it's air, it's food, it's mindset, it's education.
Right.
It's, it's all of it.
It's the packaging, believe it or not, you can take good food and wrap it in packaging that has fungicides on it because if you're adding the chemical to the packaging, it's not a food ingredient.
It's a packaging ingredient and there's no criteria for listing what's added to the packaging.
I remember once it's going to a convention and asked someone, what are you doing here? And he says, well, you wouldn't know.
I said, why is this because I've been food chemicals and packaging chemicals. What do you mean? He says, well, I make preserves that we add to, you know, food packaging.
Well, really, he says, yeah, we've fungicides, bacteria, sides and things like that.
Yeah, and they added to the package, not to the food, so you don't, it doesn't have to be labeled.
I mean, that goes beyond food, but it has a detrimental effect as well.
That's very interesting. I never really given them a start. That's worth looking into.
There's very little information on it, but there's enough information that's, you know, with facts in hand that you could see it's, it's, it's indisputable.
Another thing to, that I want to look at is this, is this idea of taste and perhaps, you know, it's a bit tangential, but I think it's, you know,
dis, dis-dis-dis-sently related to this whole conversation about food. I was reading something by George Orwell a few months ago and he said something interesting about food because he doesn't usually talk about it as far as I know, but he said in the highly mechanical, in mechanical countries that is the western world,
thanks to tin food and cold storage and synthetic flavoring, the palette is almost a dead organ.
As you can see by looking at any green, gross, earth, shock, what the majority of English people mean by an apple is a lump of highly colored cotton wool from America.
They will devour these things with pleasure and let the English apples rot under the trees.
It's the standardized machine made look of the American apple that appeals to them and the superior taste of English apples is something that they don't notice.
So when I read that, it made me think about something that you once said that I don't remember the quote exactly, but essentially you were saying that people, what people describe as the taste of their food, they don't use the proper adjectives for that.
They just say, oh, this tastes good or this tastes bad. And meanwhile, good and bad are not indicators of taste or flavor adjectives, they're moral adjectives.
And so the language to even describe taste doesn't really exist in people's vocabulary. And one quote that I think you did say was that some people can't taste their food very well because they don't want to.
They're already attached to their established palette and they can't move away from it. And so all food is either good or bad to them because they haven't developed a sense of nuance in their taste.
Can you elaborate on that a bit more and how, you know, those sensibilities are missing from people's awareness and what contributes to that?
Sure, there's a level of conditioning and there's a level of let's say categorization that I like to use and then we'll try to bring the conditioning part in as well.
I typically categorize people as either having a good palette and that means they have a good sense of smell and taste and that means they have a high potential of producing very tasty food or good food preparation if they were to be employed as a chef, for example, or the one who does the cooking.
Then I have the one that I call a juvenile palette which tends to prefer foods and tastes that young children do.
And then I have one category that I consider to be the corrupted palette, which is either from it's so decentralized physically by eating poor food that might as well turn it off.
Just like someone, you know, like if you saw someone cut in half and thrown into the street, you would probably feel sick where a seasoned paramedic was decentralized to that, you know, an emergency technician would just say, let's hurry up and clean this guy because I want to finish eating the sandwich I have in the car, right?
So it's a matter of conditioning that way and from eating bad food from what I call standard American diet or standard white people food, you know, like northern Europe as well.
And you know, there are places on the continent of Africa too that I have a ghastly diet, so it but generally most people will be aware of the white people food or American diet is being very poor.
But I would also suggest that the corrupted palette is from eating just overly flavored like you mentioned the synthetic flavors added to food.
Like for example, you know, someone who's let's say likes to drink strong alcohol won't find a beer as being accommodating.
It'll be like water to them because they're used to a stronger brand, you know, a stronger type.
So that's another way of corrupting it, you know, certain drugs, for example, a drug tolerance to synthetic additives and natural additives.
Like for example, I'll just throw this in as a natural additive, if you take celery juice, if you juice celery, that has like in in in Japanese that would call it OSU mommy, which means delicious flavor when you added to things that are savory.
So for example, if you had a menu that you cooked at home, general variety of food, savory dishes and you added celery juice to all those dishes, whether it was a pasta or rice, a stew, a savory meal, anything and you consistently added celery juice to it for a few weeks or months.
And then you stopped adding the celery juice as an ingredient most of the savory dishes, you would find them to be very bland and almost not taste not tasteful.
Because you got used to that extra very flavor enhancing celery juice, you see one one aspect of that is again typical Americans that don't cook and buy a lot of prepared foods.
There are things called modified food starch, modified corn starch, natural flavors or MSG are all the same usually flavor enhancers and they don't find food that has that that lack set ingredient as being tasty.
For example, I had years ago had a client, pretty wealthy client who went on a vacation to Rome and various parts of Italy and Spain, which and they you know they didn't slum it.
They actually went to the you know the better end of travel and they said that the food there was terrible.
I was like, you know, this is a typical American pallet that he had and of course it would be because he was used to this corrupted, you know, stofers and McDonald's and Chick-Fuller sandwiches and his wife, micro-waving preheated, you know, precooked meals and things like these are wealthy people too.
And he went to places like Rome and Spain and Barcelona and places that had some of the best food cultures and to best tasting food in the world and found to be distasteful.
You see how subjective it can be.
So and it's not like this person didn't have access to food.
I give you an example, I'm not giving their identity too much, but this person's family was you could trace it back to the Costa Noga wagon. They came here building most of the wagons that were that were used to settle the country, you know, and they still had the, you know, they were pretty wealthy.
All money and they still did they didn't know how to eat and they were fully corrupted. So again, I think your social status as hasn't much to do as culture and tradition in this case.
I think we would be remiss to talk about food and taste and things of this nature and not mention something about one of the most common sources of people's food which is restaurants because they don't want to cook it themselves. They want to go out and let somebody else cook it for them, especially if they have money.
So I want to pick your brain as someone who has some no out about that sphere. What kind of trivia can you share about how the restaurant business sources its ingredients or compiles its menus or anything that wouldn't lighten someone as to what it is that they're eating at their average restaurant.
Oh restaurants, okay, from from a decency point of view, a good food experience has always gotten from what I would call a supper club, not a restaurant. Most restaurants will no matter how much good intent they have, they will fail to make a profit if they seek out only quality and do exist.
And that's why when you do see, you know, Hutt cuisine restaurants, they only stay in business for a few years and that's intended to do that because it's not necessarily a money making scheme.
But supper clubs are different. It's a whole different genre, less public, more specialized, but I would suggest that for restaurant eating, the rule of thumb is clean kitchen is better food. If a restaurant is not clean.
And I don't mean an obvious cleanliness with that as well, but there's also a deep cleanliness like look up at the ceiling if there's dust by the vents or the lighting.
It look at the corners of things, you know, if it's not really clean, it's not going to taste as good as it could. Also, if you're going to a restaurant know their kitchen, if you can't see the kitchen.
And you ask to see the kitchen, they almost take that as an insult and typically refuse. I like to put on the retard move, you know, like I do.
Like if they have the kitchen clothes and I want to go in there, I'll just, you know, I target what I think is the kitchen and I just barge in and I keep walking and I look around and say, hey, what are you doing here?
You know, get out of here and I'll just turn on and say, I'm looking for the bathroom. Is it the bathroom?
You know, or something like that, right? I say, I thought this was the, right, I thought this was the bathroom, right? Oh, no, get out of here. The bathroom is the other way. Of course I knew you better just want to see it.
Then I'll go back to my seat and say, honey, let's get out of here, right?
Another thing is when you're a waitress, waitress brings you a menu and you know, before you look at act like you're looking at the menu, you know, and you look at the wait person and say, what's good here? What do you eat?
And believe it or not, more than once I've had the waiter of the waitress say to me, eat here? No, I would never eat here, right? Meaning the waitress.
They're like, okay, thanks very much. Bye bye.
You know, and I might even leave a dollar or two as a tip because that's actually worth, you know, their service. You know, they actually provided you a service by the waiter or waitress telling you that we don't, I don't eat here.
Right, I mean, they deserve a tip just for that and there's walk out. You see what I mean? Yeah, so those are some basic tips. If you know, there's also a lot of masquerading of an open kitchen being a benefit. Yes, there are some places. Many places more than not, by the way, new establishments that are kind of more of a casual, but yet tend to be higher quality, have open kitchens. Right? And that's good also, but but also you still look at the floor. Is it clean? Right. You know, look at what?
You know, there's an Asia, I'm not going to mention the name, but there's an Asian fast food place. I have discovered some good Asian restaurants again here.
You know, not even there are a lot of Asian restaurants where you bring your own cat and you get a free egg roll, right? And don't laugh at that because there are some Asian restaurants that are hard core Asian restaurants that do have cat on the menu on the Chinese menu.
And unless you know what cat tastes like and you happen to get that you won't know, you'll just say this is something very gamey, you know. But you know, I've had a fight experience with someone who was an anthropologist who traveled the world and once you know, did bust a restaurant here and down by serving cat and they did. You know, you called that, you know, the authorities on it, by the way, on them.
Anyway, so there's an Asian restaurant that has an open kitchen fast food. You can guess who they are. I mean, they have a logo, which is an animal. But anyway, they they have an open right. You could see how where they're going to the food prep. But when they have certain ingredients, it's just this big frozen slab, you know, of material.
You know, so you and you could see that's sourced from a, you know, not such a good quality. But at least it's an open kitchen, right. So I mean, I remember once, you know, barging into a kitchen that I wanted to eat at a certain place or it was traveling barges into the kitchen like there's, you know, kind of thing.
And they yelled at me and I looked on the floor and they had, you know, cooking pots with mobs in them, you know, and I mean, and I was like, oh, we're out of here, you know.
Yeah, you got to have fun. You know, I mean, the, you know, here's the thing. History, the current society, any, any society you look at right now is not going to be on the good side of history.
You know, in the future, so you can make you just don't get yourself in trouble, you know, you know, publicly, you know, was making demands or too many crazy comments. But, you know, I do, I will speak if you want to know what I'm thinking, just listening to what I'm saying.
And you're probably thinking the same once you're made aware of it. Yeah, it's so.
I don't want to stay on this thing a little bit more because it certainly is funny, but there's a serious aspect to it. I mean, you once gave an analogy that was connected to something other than food. I don't remember what it was. But I think you were talking about inefficiency within industries and or efficiency or how to be efficient.
And what you mentioned the thing about rats in the hot dog factory. So basically one would think that health and sanitation regulations would forbid food factory owners from allowing rats to fester in their factories. But in fact, this is actually such a challenging task that it would effectively halt the production of certain foods if the regulatory bodies were insistent to follow the rules.
So in order to allow for the business to continue a minimum amount of, you know, unhygienic things like rats are allowed to exist in the, for example, hot dog factory, although it's presented to the public that this is, you know, not the case.
Well, there's a tolerance for rat fecal matter in the hot dogs, for example, all right, that right. And you know, it was never really zero.
That's the testing got more stringent and more quote unquote clinical. They found that all hot dog, whatever suppliers had fecal matter in their food. And they couldn't shut them all down. So then they just noticed that they just will just raise the acceptable limit. So what we do find in it is still acceptable, right.
So I wanted to pivot from that into the subject of unsanitary kitchen conditions that you may be aware of are tolerated in the restaurant business, because I've seen many a rat in restaurant kitchens and everybody knows it in the kitchen and they just, it's just known.
You know, but the guests wouldn't guess it.
Yeah.
Well, you're living a society.
Let me just divert from the topic a little bit. You notice that there's been certain agendas regarding people's gender and sexuality and gender fluidity and all that.
That's been politicized. And if you oppose it, you know, it's a crime, right. You've noticed that it's been happening in the past decade.
Let me just put it this way. What's in the works right now is it's already finished. It just hasn't been implemented is the promotion and adherence to cannibalism.
So if you're going to be served a fellow, let's say humans that are processed in your food knowingly and you can't say anything negative about it, what, what, how bad is rat material?
That's pretty benign. Yeah. So just get ready. That's the next one of the next few things that's coming. You know, so it's already done. The whole thing is put together and you've been actually aborted fetuses and other things like that are in the food chain already.
And in the drug chain.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I think one of the more disconcerting things that I found and perhaps you mentioned at some point was the prevalence of human hair in the bread. I think they use it as some kind of a binder.
To conditioner. Yeah. Yeah. There's a protein is lysine or something. It's correct. I don't want to say I'm not sure what the price. I think it's used as a doe conditioner. Yeah.
Because of the in China, there's a grooming codes, you know, the fact when you work in a factory and met a lot of the mainland Chinese government fact, you know, big corporate factories, you know, you dorm there, you sleep there, you eat there, you work.
You know, basically it's like going to the military, you work at the factory and you might take off a few days or a week a year, go back to the town where you came from, but you spend all your time there.
And they have grooming regulations and you know, they just like Google where you go, you work at Google, you get your laundry done your haircut. Yeah.
Well, you work in a Chinese factory, they cut your hair and basically by the end of the week, you have billions of, you know, pounds of hair.
You could process it into doe conditioner for all your, your big take out pizza, corporate pizzas, you know, they have the laboratory, you know, the food is designed in the, it's called a food lab and they say we need doe conditioner who's got the best price on it.
Right. That's how it gets into the food chain.
Yeah, anytime I go to supermarket now and I see bread for under a dollar, I'm like, nope, we're not getting that unknown. It has to be studied, you know, to a degree, but
but I'll tell you if you have a hearth and oven or something or even a pen, you can make your own flat bread, you know, very easily takes literally once the doe is prepared in a few minutes less than a minute to make and it's delicious.
Yeah, I mean, I think that's a good segue into the last thing that we'll look at, which is food preparation. And I mean, I think you want said something interesting about how people view cooking food.
You said people act like cooking meat kills the bacteria that might be present in it, but if there's that much bacteria in it, why are you eating it in the first place?
If you think the meat is tainted and that cooking will prevent foodborne illness, it's already questionable in quality. It's not even like you got rid of the bacteria. It's just cook bacteria now.
It's not bad bacteria. You are beck, your body is 90% bacteria anyway. What do you think it sells are?
It's about is the animal disease or not? It's called a downer, a downer, like there are a lot of downer animals. And I think up until about seven or eight years ago, most government regulations told food, you know,
you know, agricultural people, if you have a downer animal, you can't put in the food chain, not anymore. Now, downers are allowed into the food chain disease because they're all diseased anyway.
There's a big concern, for example, seminal and eggs and chicken. That's a disease. You shouldn't be, you can't cook it out. There's a lady I wanted to give props to.
I don't see she's about 50% there, which is a lot to say. Her name is Dr. Lorraine Day. And you just go into, she's a couple of YouTube interviews. She's fascinating. She doesn't know she's somewhat censored, but she's had tremendous success.
Look at her recent photos. She's 82 and she looks like a well-kept 55 year old. And she ended up using juicing and distilled water and a few other practices to beat stage 4 cancer. And anyone can, if you do what she says, her regimen to a degree.
And I guess I brought her up because she has a few analogies, you know, because like she gives one analogy with chicken. You know, when you buy animal products, now it's a package says it may contain up to 10% water.
Well, the chicken, when they process it at the slaughtering house, when it's initially gutted, it's dropped into a pool of water and it's fecal water. And they let the chicken sit there for a given amount of time so the chicken carcass can absorb the water.
So it's basically absorbing fecal matter water into the tissue. And as she made a comment to someone who says, well, I cook my chicken well and she goes, well, you're just cooking your fecal matter well. Doesn't matter if you cook the fecal matter well. It's still eating fecal matter, right?
You want raw fecal matter or cooked fecal matter? How well did how good does that sound? Right? Yeah.
You know, do you want to diseased? You want to eat diseased animals raw? You want to eat them well done? What's the difference? And a drennel and cannot be cooked out of meat, by the way. If you anyone wants to look up what at what temperature, the drennel in a hormone and enzymes break down, it's three or four times beyond what well done is.
It's in the hundreds of degrees, right? It's amazing how the is is all by design is almost, you know, when you start to get a society forming with evil premises, you know, the thing it's very easy to turn their natural surroundings as weapons against them.
It's such a fine delicate balance. You have to love the perfection of it. You want to be evil, the thing that you, you know, normally do now will be your evil will be the two. What would you call would pay back on you?
It's unfortunate that that goes beyond so many people's preview, but I think yeah, if you pay attention to things, you have to ask yourself those questions. Why certain malevolent things are so prominent.
Right. It's no secret. Anyone has access to what we're talking about in terms of the dark side of it's not that you need to be a vehement student of it, but be aware of it and as your curiosity leads you, I think just avoiding it completely.
You know, as some people might say, well, my, you know, my spirit, my brain doesn't need to know any of that. Let's find, but I'll notice most of the time those people fall, you know, forward into many of the agendas, you know, thinking that they're good.
Okay. We're an hour and a half in, so we'll just wrap up with them. I got three types of food that I'm just going to throw at you and maybe you can give me some recommendations for how to do them well, cook them well, prepare them well.
So let's start with salad. I know it's very generic, but you know, take give it your best shot.
Oh, salad is a very general thing. I would say instead of saying salad, I would suggest vegetable leafy green. Right.
There's a fruit salad also. Most people would in the West consider a salad to be, you know, a leafy green with seasonal vegetable.
You can also call the slaw or a pressed salad, which I would like to make people more aware of, like the something goes coniferous vegetables or things like kale and collard and Swiss chard, which are tend to be more hearty, which are more associated with, you know, a savory pot dish, cooking it, you know, in a pot.
I would suggest a cabbage, cold slaw, right? Ca, cabbage is a very hearty leaf and it's sliced real thin and mixed with addressing, right?
A pressed salad is very similar to that, you know, you could remove the stem material, even with cabbage if you remove the stem material and makes it more pleasant to eat.
But you just, you would cut the hearty vegetable or the hearty leafy green and add addressing to it. It could be an acid, you know, citrus.
I've been using citrus more than vinegars lately, you know, for the acidity aspect, then using olive oil and both raw sesame oil and toasted sesame oil as the oils.
And mixing it all together and then actually putting weight on it, you know, so if you have it in a bowl, you, you find a small plate that's correspondingly smaller than the edge of the bowl.
And if you were to put a weight on it, you know, a jar with water, let's say, or a lead weight or another small pot to weigh down the salad, actually press on it.
It's a form of cooking the vegetable, right? It's a pressed salad.
You know, it ever seemed like wilted lettuce, you know, if you take lettuce and you kind of work it in your hands and wilt it and mush it up, it's very soft.
It's sometimes not pleasing for a lettuce, but for a hearty green vegetable, like a kale, a collard, or a swish chard, I would recommend our cabbage make a pressed salad and it's breaks down without using heat.
And it's actually far more nutritious than, you know, a wimpy lettuce, let's say, that's what I have to say about salads.
And in terms of fruit salads, when it's melon, eat it alone or leave it alone. If you ever see, I would suggest from what many people, whoever has heard me say that and has followed that says, yes, I always feel better by not eating melon with other things as they're presented fashionably in many times, you know.
So that's what I have to say about salads.
Okay. Pizza.
Pizza is the most popular food in the world, believe it or not, supposedly according to the media that I watch occasionally. And I think Norway eats more pizza than anyone else in the world.
So or or per capita or is the number one food there? What is it? Well, it's a flat bread, essentially, or semi-flat bread.
Some styles are very heavy, very easy to prepare is the idea and it's savory. Of course, there are toppings. Personally, I'm not into toppings. I think that if you have a high quality, what's called crust or dough, a set of bold with a high quality sauce and cheese or no cheese is enough.
The more basic, the better. If you want to get into making pizzas, I think there was another chat that I used to the new Greek speak, I think I haven't frequented that in a while, I've kind of tried to stay out of public eye other than this.
I think I've posted photos of pizzas that I've made in a hurry and they would rival anything you could buy at a store.
So what I would suggest about pizza besides being popular and having if you like to eat that sort of thing, learn how to make it yourself.
Indeed, but that's where we want the tips Greek. Why are you saying that you wouldn't have ingredients that flies in the face of convention completely? At least, I want to respect that convention. We want ingredient pizza.
Oh, ingredients on the pizza. Well, there's many, like I said, if you're going to go, let's say, quote unquote on the vegan side, let's work it backwards.
You don't have to have cheese on pizza and you don't even have to have sauce on pizza. So what are we talking about? Basically, you're making a low rise or flat bread with some kind of savory topping or sauce on it. That's basically it.
As a matter of fact, some of the more elaborate exotic pizzas don't even have saucer cheese or it might just be cheese or just sauce, right?
There's a high end pizza place that was open that opened here and the pizza is just bread and sauce. There's no cheese is cheese costs extra. I was like, what the hell is that?
Well, because they're striving to do the best quality dough, the best quality sauce. Well, what do you know about making dough or bread?
Right? Well, well, one thing you might learn is when you make a loaf of bread, you know, with that high rise, it takes, it's leavened.
It takes a long time to rise it and it's very tall. It takes a lot of heat, long time to cook, right? Relative to a low rise dough, which is relatively low. It takes less heat and less energy.
Another thing about making pizza is you can make pizza in a pan. If you have a low rise dough, something yeasted or not, you can spread it out and put it on a pan and flip it over.
So it cooks on both sides and you wouldn't have your toppings immediately ready. So when you flip it, that is still hot and put your toppings on that and then cover it so steam or put it under a broiler.
I mean, there's so many different ways. My I would suggest there's a if you want to learn how to make quick pizzas, there's something called a Greek pizza.
Literally, it's labeled Greek pizza. It's like a pizza pocket without the pocket. It's kind of more of a spongy low rise dough. They're commercially available.
Get that if you have a toast, oven or an oven or a pan, get that hot with some sauce on it. You can buy a pasta sauce or tomato sauce and the best way to make a sauce, by the way, is not just with tomatoes, but adding some tomato paste to it.
It takes the acidity away and also cooked onion takes acidity away and a pinch of sugar takes acidity away.
And then a cheese product or if you don't want to use a cheese product, use a vegetable product on top or put as much of it as you want.
So a simple Greek pizza will make a quick piece as a matter of fact, I make those here at home very often it go out and get a pizza and I'll be told, you know, the pizza, the pizza pizzas that I make here are better than the one pizza than you buy at the pizza place very often.
So I would suggest just learn how to make a low rise bread and you're not going to be successful until you are. In other words, practice, practice, practice on it.
All right, steak or beef, I'll just say beef less steak.
Muscle, right? Yeah, muscle, beef muscle or bovine muscle. Let's be real, right? That's what it is, right?
Well, if you're going to eat bovine muscle, what I suggest many times is, well, of course, you know, get the best quality you can. And if it is a very well, good quality beef steak, depending on the cut, of course, if it's a roast, it needs a lot of cooking, if it's a steak, it could be broiled or roasted.
The advice that I give on cooking steaks is that of course it should be a high quality grass, and if you can get it organic, if you can get it, it costs three times as much, but you know, you're not eating this often.
You should have a low moisture content very often if you buy beef muscle and you want to cook it, put it in the fridge with a paper towel, come back the next day, notice how much water is in it again because selling water is the most profitable thing, right?
But if that's why if you look at the many of the prized places that serve beef, they call it aged beef, right? And what that means is literally low moisture content and the, what their enzymes and the meat that tenderize self tenderizing.
But what I would do is if when I if I can pervade a good quality piece of beef, I would try to put it on a paper towel or rack in the refrigerator so it dries a little bit, you can actually see it shrinking slightly.
And then I would bring it up to room temperature and salt it and just cook it over a fire without anything else on it and some salt or in a pan with some fat, like butter or beef fat.
If it's a steak as such, right? To be eaten because if it's good quality, you want to taste that beef just salt and maybe some black pepper or something.
Now, they're cooking beef in other ways like in stews and pot beef. I always prefer very often using what considered French or Vietnamese spices, meaning if I say Vietnamese style spices, that was influenced by the French, you know, where you have anus, star anus, ground or not.
Cinnamon, bark, right? Ground or not ground? Some cardamom, garlic, whole garlic, fennel seeds, you put that in with your liquid and to make a roast or to cook the meat that way.
It makes it very fragrant and delicious, right?
No, quite the enlightening exposition there. But yeah, I think we'll have to wrap up on that note with this is, you know, it's funny how this is the longest episode that we've done and yet it's not something that I consider myself too versed in, but yeah, it was interesting to explore.
So, yeah, I think I'm good if you have anything you want to conclude with on the topic of food, Greek, I'll let you do that.
No, that would be it. I mean, it's too big of a topic to actually cover any amount of time. So we'll just sign off here and come up with something else for the next Sonic.
Absolutely, of course, there will be things to talk about next time we get together for one of these, but I hope that our listenership has learnt something new today and that it gives you food for thought.
So thank you for tuning into this episode of Greek Speak and we'll be back again next time.
[Music]
(dramatic music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]