Greetings and welcome to yet another episode of the Greek Speak podcast.
I'm the Archon creator of the show with the Greek as my co-host.
This is episode 9 of what is an almost completed series of 10 episodes.
My apologies for the record setting gap of time between this and the last episode.
I had hoped to get my schedule on track and the things were going to slow down for me,
but that did not happen.
And so things have progressed as they have, but I do hope to still finish within the next
few weeks with this.
We only have one more left to go after this one, so I think we should be fine.
The Greek Speak website and podcast continues to be run by me as a personal project with
no commercial, religious or political affiliations, and it will most likely stay that way until
we're done.
So that's it for the introduction.
Please enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
Hi there, Greek.
Greetings.
Hey, it's been a while since we last spoke.
Have you been keeping yourself busy?
Sort of a while, I guess.
Busy, I'm not sure if you really want to be busy in this world.
But, yeah.
Well, I guess each is on.
Some people need to have things to do, otherwise their idle hands fall into things that they
shouldn't be doing.
But yeah, we're going to focus on a new topic for this week.
The last episode was politics and military, and I felt that the next topic should be about
something equally pertinent to the structures that exert the most influence on the world.
So I picked the economy and the legal society.
Those are things that you've broached on before when talking about the credit system and your
view on attorneys.
So I think it's fitting to dig a little deeper into that and we'll start with the economy,
which I've divided into two segments, namely money, and then Vax and the credit system.
So, the word economy is widely defined as the production, distribution, and consumption
of goods and services in society.
But the end goal of a lot of that activity is often what people call money, which is I think
a very curious and diversified artifact.
It doesn't seem to have one meaning, although it's commonly touted as a means of exchange,
but it's also described since ancient times as being connected to evil doing because
of people's attraction to it.
So I think there's more to impact than just what academia or financial institutions choose
to share with the public about that.
So my first question is, Greek, what is money really and additionally, what does it represent?
Okay.
I would suggest that let's go back to the definition of economy.
Nome, nomos or nome meaning law and eco or eco-s meaning house.
So literally means it's taken from the Greek roots, two roots, eco and nome, meaning law
of the house.
And if anyone has ever heard what we call Greek speak.
In the past you might have been aware of interjection of a concept called the gods or for most
people's perceptions.
It's probably where they would consider to get their religion, ethics, morality, etc.,
or the entire order, conscious things are within the realm of divinity.
The sense of the law of the house or economy ultimately stems from there, which of course
we're going to be talking about the legal system which will also tie into that.
But remember, before we even get to the legal system that the legal pertains to law, it
is not law in itself.
So back to the what is money, well, it is such a subjective feeling because thoughts should
be objective and feelings are always subjective, let's say.
I would suggest that people's subjectivity will always override any clear meaning to the
term of what is money.
But if one retracts themselves from the subjectivity and tries to, you know, soar above the landscape
and literally meaning a society living on the earth, Terra firma uses the goods and time
and services and labor and productions and all these things that they do on the earth
as part of their economy.
So as you're on the earth, you tend to be fairly stationary within what you call where you live.
But once you start traveling outside of that, you need to a portable sense of your society
that lives on the earth to be brought along with you and to be used as trade or exchange.
But in essence, I, from Greek speak point of view, money is portable land.
That's why if you look at the lawful money concept or the lawful money establishment is based
on precious metals which are extracted from the earth, at least, you know, most people
would suggest still that they are extracted from the earth.
I would suggest that the concept of portable land will also carry over to the discussion
on the legal system and what land and ownership and things like that are.
Before we go into what money is, I just want to bring up a few things.
This is basically like a nomenclature that could be used to objectify what you hear about
money and the economy in your travels in this world.
Gold and silver, well, you know, are precious metals and there are other things that are considered
precious like minerals as well and things of rarity, treasure, hard and things like that.
But the precious metal and the rare items and the precious minerals and then we go down
to the different aspects of what we mentioned as being economy and use for trade.
But the gold was used by nobility and royalty.
It was a storehouse of wealth and it was basically used as a reserve.
That's why when you read about let's say 19th century land purchases between the United
States and Mexico and France and such, that was the established quote unquote ruling body
or the government.
They had put in the contract that the exchanges would be made with silver, not gold.
So you can look at that, how many millions or thousands of pieces of silver were used to
make certain purchases of land between nations.
Now the gold is in the reserve of the nobility but they do use silver in the market or to
make exchanges.
The silver also was used by the common man to make exchanges and consequently went both
way.
Silver was used as a reserve and also gold by the common man.
But typically the money was based on silver whether it was a bank note or coinage or value
of things in monetary terms was in silver.
And that would be for the working class, the middle class, if you want to go cast system
of classes, pretty much was the silver base.
The poor, the disenfranchised meaning those that were not considered to have mobility in
society used barter.
They used barter of goods usually.
They had the five out of pound of potatoes and you had two pounds of corn.
That was a fair trade.
But if the corn wasn't doing well in the potatoes where it might be two pounds of corn to one
pound of potatoes.
So the poor usually do barter.
And then we have credit.
Credit is reserved for the slave usually.
Usually when you have a slave class again in the cast system, they operate on a credit system.
What I mean by that is that's a very broad topic but I just nailed it in a very narrow description
and explanation by giving an example.
When you are a slave and you are under a household, the master of the household might have been
traveling or he didn't do certain meanial things or any of the meanial things if he could
afford slaves.
Believe it or not, one of the meanial chores or labor is to do for the household or the
estate was to go to the market place and what we call shopping today.
To buy either any item that the estate would need from food clothing to supplies various
sundries.
Well guess what happened?
The slave was called and given the list to go and purchase things at the market and he
did so with credit.
They would have a signet either a bronze plaque or some form of signet meaning something
represented the house and it would be rubbed on a piece of leather or parchment to make
an impression kind of like the old credit card devices were.
So this credit aspect always went through the private ownership concept and the concept
of exchanging debt.
So I hope we went down from the gold as reserved silver as the common currency, the poor
use, barter and the slaves are in credit.
So maybe that is a good place to start.
Yeah so I think that there are a lot of things there that will give us topics for further
conversation and that is cool.
But I heard you use that definition before money is portable land and I certainly see its
applications especially when you expand on it like that but if money is really just land
then why isn't fruit and weeds considered effective money?
Why does it have to be precious metals?
I don't know that we've gotten to the heart of what it's supposed to represent as an
item that also has social and psychological effects.
What you're saying is one aspect of it but I sometimes feel like we need a broader understanding
as well.
Well the more valuable the substance, the less of it you need for an exchange with a
comparably less valuable substance.
So if money is portable land gold would probably be in a common sense the most valuable thing
you can carry.
Yes there might be other precious metals based on commodities and things but let's say a
kilogram of gold will buy you 100,000 kilos of wheat.
The more valuable it is you can get to the point where you have let's say a new substance
as even more valuable than gold and a grain of rice, size piece of that metal can buy you
100,000 kilos of gold.
But we are in this crop of more valuable than gold.
Like diamonds are considered more valuable than gold so it's platinum.
Well that's the subjective aspect of it.
Like diamonds where you won't see any adportizments or propaganda for diamond wedding rings
until debiers came into and diamonds are not rare by the way.
You're taught to believe that they're rare.
They're very common.
That's one of the social conditioning things that you'll find as you go along any research
path.
Okay.
I hear you.
So I will make an attempt to push into the areas that I'm talking about and if you see
anything valid there then maybe you can expand on that as well.
I personally don't have a completely comprehensive definition for money yet but from what I've been
able to discern I would add to what you're saying that money is also a representation
of something and it seems to be a representation of power where power is not some indeterminate
or bland word the way that the entertainment industry makes it out to be with you know cartoons
or superhero movies but power meaning ability.
More specifically the ability to manifest your intentions whether that's something industrial
social destructive edifying or logistical which is why someone like Bill Gates seems to
be able to do anything he wants but homeless people on the street are some of the most limited
people in society so because the world agrees that money will be used to mediate almost
everything it becomes the most identifiable source of power that most people know of.
Well it's not it's only power until you run into someone that says it's not for sale then
it then it puts a stop on that power so what you do is you retract and you find people
that you can influence with the money to go and do more of a you know plans within plans
treachery within treachery against that which was not for sale so you can acquire it take
it by force.
Have you heard of a concept called a hitman or an assassin?
Indeed.
Great.
So yeah I mean force obviously when you have enough of it out ranks most things as far as
being able to affect your will but this sort of social contract that exists in place today
where things are not outright chaotic in most parts of the world and people have an order
that they have acquiesced to money is the means of greasing the wheels between most interactions
and that exists as the dominant form of hard power second only the violence which most
people don't want to resort to.
Well let's go back to the aspect when you have money and you equate that with power until
you find into something or that you would like to have or acquire and it's not for sale
by the person or the organization bearing it then you result to force.
Okay and well you don't result to force you you you find those that will perform what
you want them to perform for that money that you have and then you get your power that
way but it also has to do with the ideology like if you couldn't find people that were in
let's say savage or simple or materialistic to accept money to do anything what you do
is you start diminishing the culture and you start breeding a new culture that will do
that and that's what you see in place today throughout the world.
But I mean the people that are doing that you know they don't lack for anything as far
as being able to use force I mean that's a very sort of long term I think plan for somebody
that wants to engineer the world in a certain way but anyway we may still find a satisfactory
definition I think moving forward I'm certainly seeing what you're saying but I still feel
like there's a slightly missing component that we might stumble on to as we continue
to talk about it.
Well the missing component is the ideology of the society meaning what kind of what form
of law they they they have allegiance to and lived to uphold and so the first thing you
have to do to take control of the economy is take control of the law right and and then
you subject the society to a changing law system not legal system but you know which is
an ideology and what something you live by and then you either eliminate those that don't
want to go with it by many ways disease or whatever starvation financial crashes right
you withdraw the money and then you breed a new culture just like you would domesticate
a chicken for example a domesticated farm animal and at this time what you what you experience
is an education system of history a law form a culture that is fairly new it was revised
and redone by what you call the 1950s on the Pope's work schedule it started in the end
of the 19th century anyone could go do some research on economic textbooks not really textbooks
but economic commentary in the 19th century there was many economic schools of thought and
pertaining to you know various cultures you know this is before the rise of communism capitalism
and such you already been over 200 years into the industrial revolution which started in
the 15 or 1600s so you you're looking at a social engineering that that is now manifest
that began in earnest by the mid to late 19th century didn't take very long to redo the entire
world so when you look at culture changes tradition in law form changes the concept of finances
understood and also it's very difficult for people to perceive it objectively because they've
been raised in it and you know their parents and grandparents also reinforce this new
breeding program or social engineering so there's no way they'll be able to see out of it
if they're looking for approval from those around them all right I understand that sort
of the thing that I mentioned before about this other aspect of money that's been talked
about since ancient times is that it's most notably appropriated from the bible love
of money is the root of all evil is there a rational reason that we can give for that is
it because perhaps people seek power perhaps above all else and because they see money as
representing that they go for that most people seek power with money I've encountered certain
individuals that live an extremely modest life and almost to the point where where they'd
be living out of a trailer or a mobile home and their billionaires and you wouldn't know
it and they and they shop they never buy new clothes they buy used clothes they sort of
look not well kept so those are the exceptions so it's not a rule that money is power the
and again you really don't need religious fanaticism right can breed power or followers that
would go back to the Gustav Lebonne authorship of the crowd let's say to understand power but
in essence for this conversation you're at the tail end of a 19th century social engineering
platform which pretty much gave up about ten or twenty years ago and now on a new social
engineering platform which will never really come into fruition which is designed to go
out to what's called twenty fifty right so I just threw in a whole bunch of stuff there but
without getting sound into philosophical and and being more empirical perhaps maybe discussing
how the money system works today that most people are not aware of well certainly going
to get to that of course we're not going to skip it I just thought it was curious that I
mean you've given these other examples of power mediums but I don't see the ancient record
saying that those things are the root of all evil it is the love of money that is the
root of all evil so clearly there's a part in there well the love of the the the it's not
money but the love of money so you can be poor let's say in have a love for money or you
can be wealthy and have a love for money it's indiscriminate it's just the love for money
it doesn't it doesn't denote any kind of quantity or possession of ultimately when you
when you consider even lawful money it's still a fiction give you an example if everyone
was able to produce gold tangible sellable elemental gold in their kitchen how much would
it be worth not very much right so now the the empirical what's seeming empiricalness
of gold becomes ephemeral so it is a fiction in other words it's not absolute but what is
absolute is for a certain age what is given as a moral an ethical and loss standing in law
gold is the storehouse of wealth and until it is made more public or commonly known on how
to produce it in mass it stands you know is it possible to live in a society where there
is no money I think Bradbury showed us that in Star Trek right if everyone just did what
they found they should do to upkeep you know the themselves in society and all that and
there was equal sharing whether it was meritoria you know based on merit or not wouldn't you
wouldn't need money and just to interject you know you don't there is no money in society
today at all so you know like you said earlier there's no chaos so the the person who has
a love for money in this society is a real sick individual if you really consider that
because there is no money today in circulation or used well yes in the strictest sense of
following the definition but that which money is used to achieve I think is perhaps more
worthy of consideration than just the medium itself which is ultimately just a rock a precious
metal you're using that to achieve some kind of social gain or material gain which is a
far more interesting dynamic to analyze than the rock okay there is lawfulness and then there
is what is being done and what is being done in the world society today is not lawful so when
we say something like money that is rooted in lawfulness when you compare to the activities
of the current society on the planet it is unlawful so it's very difficult to carry over let's
say a thought or an explanation to an unlawful group meaning it's okay there it's spontaneous
it's unpredictable in a sense unless unless you know the future and it's unstable and dangerous
right so then if you start looking at all the other things that if you're going to plan a society
as it is today you're going to have to put things in place called policing right regulation
and other things like that to control the volatility potential volatility of a society
that has no money but still engages in exchange and to make it even worse that they think there
is money the next step is you have to remove any kind of reference to anything lawful so you
introduce a legal system you introduce attorneys you eliminate any knowledge of history or science
right or in you eliminate education you eliminate any kind of a spirituality that is edifying you
know you give them garden variety demonology today Judaism Christianity Islam Buddhism all these
things so they just play around Satanism same same same stuff you form a society that from a cosmic
point of view is actually worthless because it spends most of its time and intention and engaging
in worthlessness with the small group of people that that are behind the scenes and when I say
people I don't necessarily mean human either but people nonetheless that are in control of this
this planet so that that is basically it in a nutshell and you can go off in any direction you
want on all those things you know meaning the military aspect the industrial aspect the education
aspect the science aspect the religious aspect and all that and the underpinning element
all that is finances because you know most people want to do things and they need the financing to do
it so when you start discussing the financial element and once you get outside of that it's the
lawfulness in other words it's not operating lawfully it's a very very open conversation because
anything goes in other words any type of fraud or any type of scam that's acceptable becomes the norm
all right well like you suggested before let's um perhaps move on to the banks and the credit system
having looked at money you said before that what we have today are not really banks but some kind
of financial institution so perhaps we can start with historically what is a bank many ways to look at
it but for you had it was it was a proxy storage of wealth meaning if you didn't want to store it
within your estate or your personal or land that you had control over you brought it to the bankers
all the way down you know the bank being you know a physical place with physical money meaning
precious metals or notes representing that all the way down to a bank meaning a table
or for a money changer people that traveled and they use a different rate system so in other words if
you had a coin that weighed a certain amount you wanted for one country you wanted it to exchange it
for the type of coins weighing whatever other amount for another country so you can do the common
exchange you know in purchases so that's basically what what the banks were basically to change money
from one jurisdiction to another one culture from another all the way also from the storage of
you know holding someone's wealth which which would be there for personal reasons for their family
or estate or for trade and then you get into what's called the law of nations which is in the U.S.
Constitution and the law merchant which will probably cover a little bit about both ways with the
economic and the legal discussion okay so I believe that the banks also had a religious component to
them going quite far back you have clay tablets from 2000 BC that show that the earliest recorded
accounts of banks were actually the temples so for example the sun god of Babylon would lend
well not the sun god but the priests would lend money to the farmers in exchange for portion of
their yield and would be very demanding and collecting the interest and so that activity seems to
have always been managed by a power based and not just some random part of the public yeah you
could say that well again what was considered lawful money came from your gods so of course
and what can you share about how banking developed during the first and second millenniums it seems
that it was always something that was connected to certain ethnic groups or certain races or even
certain countries like Italy or Austria after a certain point how did that industry find itself
being centralized around very specific groups and regions it there was a division that happened
around that time between the eastern and the western world as you can always see references to
to such even today the east and the west so we we can discuss it either way but there that
that bipolar existence in the world that still exists east or west is simply the way to describe it
the east always had more of a xenophobic isolationist and the west had a more expansive
view on the world you could look at the colonization of the continent of Africa by the Dutch for example
as one essence of expansion where you don't see colonization of the sino culture the Chinese culture
or the asian culture beyond that area so I would just say that it's not in a phenomenon or anything
it just is the way the west expanded and it's also it also borrowed more from the east meaning the
Persian farce or what you modern what we call modern day ran many or Arabic even would
Persians and farce are not Arabic but also from the Arabic concept and the Judeo concept of finance
and of course brought to Europe and mixed in with their ideology there so it has a reputation
for being a central point because of the presumed Christian era that you're living in right now it's
from a secular point of view it's this is the Christian era and the harkens back of course to the
Vatican and all that so I don't see it much as a phenomenon or a change of anything other than more
of a worldwide standardization it does extend into the east though given that it is a world-wide
thing so it's not like you have these two separate systems of banking of finance and the east and the
west as far as I can tell the ideologies are different but the Babylonian system extended to the east
as well which is you're not supposed to know about in other words you only know about recent phenomena
a recent historical occurrence is like I mentioned earlier you're not allowed to know the real
history of man you know of civilization how things change you only know the most for most people
the past two weeks but generally academically you don't go back more than a few years and then the
rest of its all lie going back you know how however far that's commonly accepted history
but the the world standardization happened with the Egyptians that was that's well known with
artifacts found in us even in Australia where there was an Egyptian system there's a well-known
established facts that artifacts of Babylonian weights and measures and money are found in places
in South American Columbia during the Babylonian period you know the early iron age let's say for
example this standardization basically what focal point and now it tends to be the IMF out of
Washington DC and the Bank of London in England or the city of London so these things change somewhat
and so banks and economies they underwent an enduring change in the 20th century with the spread of
central banks and fiat currency and centralized authorities for governing global finance
and a lot of people in the multimedia will point to the federal reserve or bank for international
settlements or IMF or blah blah blah as the culprits of some nefarious global agenda that has
orchestrated that and but usually they can't name real names other than the usual suspects of
certain families there are the guilty parties what more accurately can be said about how this thing
evolved in the 20th century well it was tried out in earnest in the 19th century from the beginning of
the 19th century for example Canada was experimented on with a federal reserve type system in the 18 late
1800s before they put it in place in America now when you say fiat currency it's fiat
an operation because it's not really a bank note but it's not fiat all of the bank notes today because
they're called fiat in other words you can't get anything for them are not fiat they're actually
backed by they actually represent a lean on the people the land the birds the trees all the legal
artifacts meaning whatever can be described on paper all of the bank notes represent a lean
by the central bank on the government and the people of that country so they're not really fiat they're
actually backed up like for example if the United States or Spain or you know even though the part
of the EU or any other country wanted to bring in lawful money they couldn't because they have
nothing to back it with you see so it's fiat an operation but in essence it's backed up by what
you hear bankers saying all the time it's not backed up by anything but the faith of the people
what's faith it goes into the religious topic just like y'all we'll show later how the legal system
is a religion also and i mean that literally not figuratively from a fanatic sense all right i hear
you but pertaining to still though the developments that took place that put in place the current credit
system from what i understand is that you had a series of events that took place in the 30s
around okay time can we talk about that yeah let's let's let's just show a very simple way in how it's done
based on how most countries are set up that doesn't matter what the type of system that's in place
monarchy communism capitalism whatever uh the they were either convinced or what was put in place
was to go into a contract with a private bank or banking cartel known as central banks
so what they did was they go into a contract they usually amend their constitution
or whatever form of government documents that they have to allow this to happen they
in by legislation let's say or by decree and once this happens there instead of the government
itself being in control of the money hands over all the tasks and responsibilities to this private
banking cartel which is always disguised as you know using the country the country's name and
and uh but always being a central bank the central bank is the giveaway uh so what happens is the
the central banking system starts to go about all the business of producing and distributing money
like a government would but for a fee but every time it does a form of production or finance
or financial activity um it requires something tangible from that particular government and when
the government runs out of everything tangible then that central bank by contract puts that
government into bankruptcy because the fees are still owed okay an example here in the United
States would be the federal reserve act comes into play and they produce all the financial requirements
for the government at a rate of 6% and all the financial activities require you know
to put gold deposits and deposits of deeds and you know tangible items meaning land titles and
things like that so what happens is if you know as time in per per seemingly in perpetuity as time
keeps going on and on and on the government runs out of things to give the private bank the federal
reserve to monetize or produce in you know financial products in the in the economy whether it's bank
notes or coin or whatever um and but the government still requires these financial activities to carry on
but the federal reserve won't work for free right they work at a rate of 6% so what happens is uh
the government says it's federal to the federal reserve I need money for this year's economy
in the federal reserve as we have nothing else to give me well that's because we you know
the government says because we've given you everything well that's too bad it's not my problem and by
the way if you have nothing else to give us you still owe us 6% plus you need to still keep operating
the next month year 10 years or whatever so what do we do so what they do is the the government
goes into bankruptcy it's already been incorporated because a non-incorporated government cannot
go into contract with a private entity by the way I hope I haven't lost anyone into this point
by the way there's not an economics professor or or academic idiot that knows any of this but you
could look it up yourself even if you're eight years old so so what happens is they go through this
elaborate but yet quiet bankruptcy which instead of shutting down the government in bankruptcy they
put it in what's called receivership and if anyone knows what receivership and bankruptcy is
you can see things try to remain as the same as possible so when an entity a corporation or
organization goes into bankruptcy and receivership you don't you try to change as little as possible
all that means is that the creditor meaning the central bank now owns the government but keeps it
operating because it's a fixture in society that society shouldn't do without and that's pretty much
it and that's and that's how it works in the American system in the European system in the Asian
system as well and basically the main commodity is the human it's called human resources
or however you want to look at it basically you're living on as a slave but not
understandable in the way that you've been taught what a slave is but legally you are a slave
a quote-unquote citizen as a matter of fact you could look at the 14th amendment they kind of spell it
out in the US constitution it says it will be no more a slavery just US citizens I mean it's used
in the same sentence so that's pretty much how all the systems work it's kind of like the stuff you
see in the entertainment system with Hollywood when you start dealing with them off here
a businessman needs some money to run his business or expand and it deals with them off you by the
end of the film he loses the business to the mafia or organized crime it's the same
story with the financial system all right so we're looking at a global bankruptcy of multiple
nations that took place somewhere around the 30s 40s ish and yet there's hardly any paperwork on
this I mean there's a guy called rod class who's the only one that I know of that does comprehensive
talks about that but he's also tangled himself up in the US legal system so he can fight his own
court case and prove a point to his patriot social circles so he doesn't reach that far but other than
that there's not really much else to access directly about this congressional record you could do
them sure there's plenty of people out there that have gathered congressional records regarding
commentary with congress which congress by the way in America was shut down in the 1860s
so I mean they just show up as actors now a civil war was not the civil war you typically have a
revolution or a civil war or a severe depression and all of this by the way is it has a very strong
spiritual component to it if you understand what's called human inspiration literally in other
words there is a non tangible component behind all of this and you see it constantly
in in the language you know banking the financial language and also the legal language
and also in the symbolism most people always point to the all seeing eye on the dollar bill or
something of that nature okay so let's look at how today's economy actually functions professors
and bankers will talk about things like GDP and loans and stocks and interest rates and taxes
but what are the principal determinants of how money slash credits move around who gets first dibs
on accessing them etc etc yeah see okay everything is in receivers should meaning you have a small
cartel that runs and owns everything by presumption that's why for example when people
get an IRS lien it says notice of lien well they don't need to provide a lien because there's a
presumption that everything is under a lien and you just got them upset so now they're saying that
we you know we don't presume that we have a lien on you but you see so it's all by presumption
the the the backbone to all of that is understanding the different like you said who gets first
dibs on it the different levels the different tiers like you have though the primary market
which is how the credit is created for example every time you sign a piece of paper that piece of
paper or or or now it's digital gets monetized that's primary then you have the secondary market which is
the the servicers or the debt collectors or the the banks that you the the part of the bank that does
deposits and things like that and checks actually check as part of the primary but anything that you
sign is primary the debt collectors and all the the legal the attorneys all that stuff is secondary
market now and then there's a tertiary market which is kind of like the entertainment business
you know where they promote all of these things one thing to to comprehend is when you're going to
put a new system in the society it doesn't matter what it is religious technical financial whatever
you have to make sure that a good portion or enough of portion which could be only two or three
percent in some cases of the society relies on you your system as for its livelihood in other
words a government job for example if you the more government employees you have there are the weaker
the the nation or society is because for example if if the government starts to become quote unquote
evil very few people are going to quit their job they're going to continue working and they're going
to yell out and scream what do you want me to do this is my living right you see so the secondary
market the debt collectors and the attorneys and all that then again involved with finances you know
are there to uphold plausibility because people are still going on the ancient notion that if you borrow
money you have to pay it back and when you start explaining that there is they actually just monetize
your signature and you're the one providing the credit you're the creditor not the debtor but they
switch you in a contract that now you're the debtor they can't understand that it's like it's called
the 800 pound girl in the room that no one sees that that's a whole concept of I like to put the
forward the term cosmic censorship it doesn't matter what's in the room if if they're blocked from
seeing it it doesn't matter what it is you know the how big or how small so the secondary market the
debt collectors and all that like for example if someone gets a $10,000 loan this just use the regular
slave parlance that they're finished they actually provided at least $80,000 for the bank just
with signing because it's a 10 to one right it's so they provided $90,000 in the bank has to keep
10% in reserve so so you know it's basically the creation modern money mechanics of federal reserve
you know Chicago money a federal reserve bank out of Chicago a modern money mechanics I once had
an economic professor say though that's fake document even though you know the federal reserve puts
it out so basically the secondary markets there to maintain plausibility that's where you're
the the the the main backbone meaning the millions and millions of people that rely on this
system and will not question it because that's how they get their quote-unquote paycheck you see so the
most important aspect of it is not really that there is a small cartel or of you know people that
have usurped the money system of the whole world the the main component is the 2% 3% 4% 5% of the
population that works in the legal field and in the financial field that's all the secondary market
they actually are a proxy army for this private banking system you know for example everyone knows
someone right that works in the financial system or the legal system or the government right so
you don't want to see them lose their job do you what kind of a person would want that right so that's
and the more people that work for the government or the financial system or the legal system the
weaker the society gets but we know what this type of system and that's the secondary market
you mentioned a bit about you know cosmic censorship and the fact that people cannot understand
certain concepts and I find that people don't seem to grasp really the difference between credit
and debt and even in the elite classes of people that claim to be experts in this area whether
the people that run shows on money or the economy or its politicians they don't really seem to acknowledge
that it's a credit based economy and they talk a lot about debt can you differentiate between
credit and debt and parse that a little bit sure that goes into the legal system it's all wordplay
short of being a boy and writing a signing a contract that you're a girl right anything else is
possible even that's possible now so what happens is you sign a piece of paper and it's monetized
right in other words the bank has nothing it's just a storefront or it could be digital all it has in
its inventory are transaction numbers preset transaction numbers a certain number of transaction
numbers are given to each bank and they're just sitting there in the moment someone that can sign
their name or given autograph for a mark a transaction number is brought up and the details are filled in
this person came in for loan for $10,000 that they sign it yes okay next the transaction number $10,000
appears and everybody's okay but we can't do this for everyone all the time because people will
will say well I don't have a job I don't want a job I'll just go sign my name and get $10,000 a week
right and then nothing will ever get done in society so you have to maintain plausibility so then
within the contract that they sign or forgetting the $10,000 it says that for the loan that I have
received you actually lie they lie and you swear to it right if you look at any more
gauge or anything it says for the loan that I received I will pay back right that no so this
document creates the conditions and anything before that document will never be looked at
by the jurisprudence or the jurisdictions if it's ever comes up for arbitration it can't
because the whole system is based on that you know the last thing you want is these patriotic idiots
to realize that their government sold them down the river and doesn't exist anymore the meaning
the government doesn't exist in the way that they think it does right so you can't for
normalcy you have to start you know turning of princes into frogs on paper yes I follow you
but let's not forget to differentiate between credit and debt though well that's well on the credit is
created when you sign and it's monetized but then it becomes debt when you sign a contract saying
for a loan you received you're now a debtor but you never received a loan you're the one that actually
financed it it would be like going to a coffee shop and buying a coffee and the moment you sit down
before you take a sip from it they take it from you and they give it to the next patron who pays for
it the same coffee and then if you say well I want coffee we have to buy another one
how dare you want to drink the coffee you just bought okay follow you but but it's this thing is
interesting though where you say that the bank has nothing and it's just a holder of these transaction
numbers but then by that sort of understanding let's say you and I decide to create a bank we get
rich today it's got we we don't need any to hold anything well the bank is a national association
like you could name any bank city bank JP Morgan Wells Fargo whatever Deutsche Bank go on and on
right robber bank what those are national associations the national associations like the Boy Scouts
Girl Scouts Sierra Club environmental groups all right and they're there they're in NGOs non-government
organizations but they have cage codes which is a corporate and government entity code okay so the
reason why the banks are wealthy is not because they're running as a bank it's because they set up a
corporation you can see this if you do business with banks let's say you do business with Bank of
America there's Bank of the America NA which is national association then there's Bank of America
trust and there's Bank of America Inc. Incorporated there's Bank of America this right so they use the same
name to create different entities which they pile and dump the funds if they can into it or have people
buy shares and things like that it's the same thing you see in religion is it a black Jesus is it a white
bleeding heart Jesus is it a Jesus that you go to hell if you don't believe in is it a Jesus that is
this or you know which one which Jesus are you talking about which Buddha you're talking about this
is all based on fanaticism and religious underpinnings all of it I remember at one point when I was in
Chicago and I think they have it in other cities as well you walk past a certain building and they have
this big national debt number that's in the several billions so this is just a joke no the debt is
actually the government's debt but the government convinces you to pay their debt it's kind of like you
get a handful of bills at the end of the month and you go convince a stranger to pay them for you I mean
and they keep doing it and you get used to that and then when they don't want to do it anymore you
want to kill them that's what's going on today also when the new banking system is put in place this
banking system everyone that lives in the land that you have solely given over to the banks is your
enemy all right like in America they have the trading with the enemies act various other countries
they call it hostilities belligerence this and that they're talking about you right because if
the people of any given government find out what the government's did not as do and is doing they would
clean it clean it out right away but they don't but the government preempts that by declaring
them the enemy and the people don't know that they are the enemy so when you hear whether it's
for military industrial or television or media or government whenever they talk about the enemy
they're talking about you it's a it's a that's why I mean you're witnessing the decline of the society
and the plans to create a new breeding program you know where there is no male or female and you
have cybernetic you know people that are part machine part and the rest are just drugged and then
the other another group of people which are used for food you know cannibalism and you know this
plan to create a new society by the 2050's just like in the 1890s they wanted a new society by
the 1950's right you see but you're in decline because it won't come into fruition.
Last thing on the subject of banks and credit systems it does seem to be the case that a lot of
activity centers around certain places like Switzerland and Luxembourg are you do you know why that is?
Well because these things are like Switzerland and Luxembourg in places like that even places in
Holland the hagg that is strategic it's not an accident in other words is strategically set up that way
and they're not you know a sense of neutrality that's like the hub of evil for example right
like everyone looks at Switzerland as being oh yeah they're neutral they're peaceful they're great
no they're actually probably almost evil groups on the planet all right uh in terms of what good if
you're going to go down the road of good and evil right good being beneficial and evil be evil being
non-beneficial so no that is a strategic location uh Babylon was a neutral place in the ancient world
really yeah is that how so well it ran the world through satellites it the whatever you see a
group going out and conquering uh their home base is always neutral yeah even Rome was neutral
you know even though Caesar sat there it was considered uh separate from anything else you know
like the all all the roads lead to Rome well why would you why would that why would that be so?
if my memory serves me right there was a few occasions where Rome was invaded by foreigners who
identified it as the hub of the activity that they had to go and cut down so they the enemies didn't
view it as neutral sure but if you look at Switzerland Switzerland in 2002 or so was cut down also
right economically they became a sovereign state right i think Demetri Kalazov talks about that
one of his uh youtube videos in other words they became a corporation and fell into the rest of the
group because there was no need for them uh to be neutral and also the more people became educated
then they would start focusing on it so they made a cover for it by destroying uh Switzerland in its
legal state they changed its legal standing into you know a schmuck country like the rest of the world
okay so um let's look at the the last topic for the episode which is how the legal system works
so firstly we have a group of gatekeepers that mediate between the legal authorities and the public
who are called lawyers and attorneys but you've remarked on how those two groups are not the same so can
you differentiate between them lawyers and attorneys well lawyer was always known as someone
learned in the law an attorney was someone that was uh used by a feudal lord to interact with his
the fee the you know the fiefdom the slay the surfer the slave and there's no there's no going
around that but what happens is because everyone is an attorney now meaning that deals with the legal
system people have forgotten that what an attorney really is or really does and because it's normal
it's normal in other words it there's nothing alarming about an attorney right but but an attorney
is there for representing legal fictions corporations or serves since slaves are incompetent people
and uh that's that harkens back to what i started off early uh in the sonic event this is a slave system
so why would you have people that are learned in the law or why would you be learned in the law
if you're a slave and you have a credit-based system if you proclaim and try to exercise
a knowledge of being learned in law you'll be punished for it because it goes against the norm
it's just like thinking imagine you it was normal for all the people or 99.9999
percent of all the people in all the countries all the nations all the corporations whatever
were all cannibalistic and you started saying well cannibalism is wrong you'll be promptly locked up
and and well you'll be laughed at and then you'll have ad hominem attacks against your person and
then you'll be you know sequestered from the group or and or you know eliminated with extreme
prejudice the same thing with the attorneys if the entire planet is based on a credit system
and people are legally enslaved meaning their chattel and their issue to serial number
and they're treated as property and charged with crimes and things like that
to say that attorneys are not good or you know or whatever any criticism against them
is is viewed as irrational and it is actually think about it it would be irrational to negatively
criticize attorneys if it's already been well understood rationalized and established that
everyone is pretty much a slave all humans are slaves except for very small enclaves on the planet
why would you criticize attorneys aren't what are you stupid or something don't you know that
you're just a slave right you're operating in a credit system why would you of course it's natural
to have attorneys right you see the point yes of course to shift a bit away from the attorneys
which I think are a bit like a lower level of the wrong let's look at the lawyers a bit
what are the first historical accounts of those people coming onto the scene where did they come from
and where they always consider to be malevolent from the start no the the original lawyer is the
original doctors the original professors were the priesthood the original banks and the original
universities and government buildings were the temples right so as these things grew and expanded
and you had annexes right if you had for example as we said the temple being the base for the
the noble things in society if that society expanded and became empiric an empire there's only one
temple but you you're going to make annexes of that temple another you know along your empire so then
you in a diminished sense have a lower priest he's not a priest but he knows everything the priest
should know can you call him a priest if he's not a priest no you call him a representative of the
priest whether it's a matter of knowledge whether you know based on education history money health
you know medical whatever you had people representing that priesthood throughout the empire or
throughout the land but they weren't the priests so they became the doctors which means teacher
or the attorney which is the representative you know usually the the attorney worked from the
bottom up not from the top down in other words he his authority came from the top down but he
worked from the bottom up he brought the unwashed masses to the hierarchy oh I see I didn't know that
right that's why you have to get an attorney to represent yourself when someone tells you
get an attorney representing means he's telling you nothing but a surf or a slave and you can't
stand in front of the lords or the you know the the master okay that's why they don't like here's
the interesting thing like today even today in the courts they're all sham courts anyway
but all of them by the way because if you try to have a real court it would be closed down by fire
or extreme prejudice the the aspect of representing yourself they don't like that because if you
are capable and learned in the law you wouldn't be wasting their time because you would know already
that you shouldn't be in that court you get it they only want people that are represented by
attorneys because if you're going to go in there as yourself you're learning the law well if you're
so learned in the law and you're going in there as yourself you should have avoided the entire
matter from the beginning which I've talked about before you do that by going through the administration
not the judicial or the justice court which is a sham or religion or whatever you want to call it
based on the justice religion you know the female goddess I think I've talked about at nausea
for years now to be forced into a justice court is actually religious suppression
they don't know that and they they would laugh at you if you brought that up but actually if you
went if they're laughing at you you're on two you're dealing with those that are really too low on the
on the wrong on the ladder you need to go up higher and they they know exactly what's going on
so yeah all of this stuff has a religious underpinning to it yeah unfortunately we don't have
enough time to dig into the religious underpinnings but that is always something that people can
look into it's things that I think we might have mentioned at some point in earlier streams also
you won't find you won't sorry you won't find much on on the justice system being based on the goddess
religion in in what they call the search engines you're gonna have to find some stuff that's
printed from 19th century or before and you're gonna have to open your eyes and look at all the symbolism
just like who is it Confucius Confucius say right ancient Chinese secret symbols are the great
communicators in a society not words but symbols and he wasn't talking about the pictographic nature of
the Chinese writing system he's talking about the what is hidden is is revealed through symbolism
yeah I think that there's a general sentiment of that being the case now in the mainstream I think
people generally know that but they don't seem to know what the symbols mean so they speculate
in all kinds of rumors about so in this society where the imperative of the legal system is to maintain
the order on behalf of these nameless patrons of the corporate state can it be said that crime
actually pays since what we have is really just criminals judging other criminals
sure but the thing is the real criminals are the ones judging the people that are presumed to be
criminals in a factual lawful sense the the entire society is a is criminal society so if everyone is
criminal are there any criminals no so now you you basically you've turned everything over to a
new paradigm now well because everyone meaning it's kind of like with the police there are no good police
the reason why there are no good police is because those that are deemed good know about the bad
police and don't do anything about it so there are accomplices you see and by the way the police are
a function of the banks we've talked about that their lawful societies don't have police only the
ones that are bankrupt or we're allowed private banks to come in and and you know basically mortgage
up everything right I'm not against the police because I have no interest I'm not against anything
that they're doing on this planet because it's all bad so I can't say that I'm against any
specific aspect of anything in this society I'm against all of it from A to Z from young to old from
high to low because it's all unlawful like we just said so I just retract and I can just give
an educated opinion with references and an objective report like I've said many times
if everyone wants to band together and hold hands and make the world a paradise I'm still going to
be a separate from them as possible if they want to want to band together and create a living
hell on earth I'm still going to stay separate from them either way whatever they do in the state that
they're in right so this is the the the intention of the sonic events is to be is to give an
objective report and a quote unquote opinion with references but at the same time to remain set apart
from it and indifferent to it so again what they're doing with the attorney just to go back because
everyone is acting in a criminal sense or supporting it the the the attorneys are just they're
to monetize charges you know from traffic tickets to court cases all those numbers all those things
are monetized in other words they're deposited into the bank for credit and there's nothing you can
do about it to some do in other words there's no way to fix it it has to be redone and it is I mean
the destruction of man society is done by the quote unquote good guys not the bad guys the bad guys
are the ones who are running it do you know what Shakespeare was talking about when he wrote the first
thing we do is kill all the lawyers in in that Henry the sixth play yeah that's well that's a
conversation between two of the characters and there's more detail than just kill all the lawyers
well yeah I know but I'm just referring to the quote well yeah that's something that has to be read in
context there is a wolf hill or something there is a a PBS series wolf haul or something about
an attorney for the king that's a good series to watch it's about one of the head attorneys
there another treachery in the lying that he did and the the feigning of power to maintain the
British monarchy or the English monarchy during that time I believe it was Thomas Cromwell Cromwell
yes based on him his life and there's several those Cromwells it's the original one it's a pretty
good series to watch the PBS I'm not promoting it but it's it'll it's just it's like watching something
you can reference most of the things that they show but it's in real life you know it's like
watching a film like most Christians know about the bible by watching Walt Disney or the movies that
they made it's incorrect obviously all of it right none of it's correct but at least you get a
flavor for it you know the time period and the certain things that were said all right well then
I think it's something that could be useful for people to check out if they feel so inclined
but I think that we're gonna have to bring the conversation to a close we've been talking for
over an hour and I think we've given people a lot of good things to mull over so unless you have
something that you want to reiterate or emphasize Greek I think I'm good not at all I mean uh well
the word is there to emphasize but to deemphasize what people think is true really and uh this
this last uh conversation or sonic event with the economy and the legal system is too broad uh to
to even get into other than giving half-hearted opinions like I did pretty much hopefully I gave
it with enough reference and and uh some kind of flavor that people can go and look up certain things
but with that said yeah that's that's it for now I guess all right well then I think we'll end
things off on that note it's been a good stream and we'll be returning at some point in the near
future for the last episode of the Greek speed podcast series sorry again for the long waiting time
but we only have one more left to go and we will see you next time so thanks again for listening
you
[Music]