Greetings to everyone, welcome to the tenth episode of the Greek speak podcast hosted by
the Archon in the Greek. We finally reached the last stream of this series and I think it's long overdue.
If you stuck with us this far then I presume you found the podcast to be something insightful and
that's great. Thank you for that but I look forward to bringing things to a close today and
we're going to be tackling subjects that are close to home for all of us given the current health crisis
and we'll also be looking at what the future holds so let's get to it. But as always,
GreekSpeak.com has never had any commercial religious or political affiliations and was always
something that I ran for the sake of the project itself and so that's it for the introduction.
Please enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
Hi there, Greek, are you there? Hi there, yes I am. Hello.
So I don't know about you but I'm relieved that we're about to conclude the series that's taken
a year when you should have taken four months not that I don't enjoy speaking with you but I think
even the best of things one of their course there's a lot of social and economic activity that's
being stifled in the West because of a reported pandemic. The cause is attributed to some kind of a
virus that said to be life threatening. They call it the coronavirus. It's said to have originated
somewhere in China, Wuhan China in the food markets there because of the bats that they sell
and we see a lot of governments that are imposing states of emergency on their people because
the UN declared a pandemic in mid-March. So first of all what can be said about the nature of this
biological agent, Greek? Well the nature there is no nature to it, it's fiction in terms of the
biological aspect to it from a mechanistic point of view. Just to time date this it's what they call
towards the end of March on the year 2020 on the Pope's work schedule. So as it is now I think
people that are familiar with Greek speak even beyond these podcasts have picked up perhaps
more than just a few bits of info on how the human body works. What the medical establishment is
really doing and people's perception of anything living which is at a minimum by the way.
So you know let's just let's just embed a little bit of history, a tradition, culture and all this
and let people actually come to a conclusion, the rightful conclusion on this.
During the Middle Evil ages and up to the Renaissance and beyond Europe was controlled by basically
an imperial system meaning by empire and you mostly hear of things coming out of the Vatican,
out of the Catholic Church and they had a pretty good stronghold on Europe and most of the world
at that time because of at least the Western world because of the financial center there which is
of course what you see going on now financial being embroiled with this but my point here is from a
what's called science which is learning or knowledge. What the church had done both privately and
publicly is stated to the quote unquote natural philosophers because there were no scientists
back then they were called natural philosophers people studied nature whether they call physics today
and just the material world or the world at large. The Vatican pretty much had a stance that they
can study anything as long as it had a material basis or material cause anything that was immaterial
was within the domain of the Catholic Church or the Vatican. Now in today's vernacular things
like radio electricity what people call microwaves or even light those are those are still immaterial
phenomena natural phenomenon but the because of this Vatican-esque Catholic mindset that was put
on 500 years ago they fabricate things like photons and electrons you know that like you know photons
are light particles and electrons are electrical particles and everything is a particle right it's
like the Vatican the Vatican cult of particles is really what you're experiencing so nothing can
be conveyed even as a concept unless it has a particular agent behind it. So when they're telling
you the strict cause of an outbreak or a pandemic is this little particular virus if you take it
face value and you have at least maybe a handful of brain cells between your ears and you have a
little bit of time on your hands to research this you'll find within usually between five or ten
minutes of research that it is a part of germ theory and anything that's defined within
being constituents of a virus is under the study of virology which is the study of toxicology.
Also you will find within the first few minutes that viruses are dead proteins but yet
what I the things I just mentioned that if anyone does in an objective study in what everybody
of knowledge medical let's say or scientific has been accumulated regarding the subject will find
it is in high contrast and almost direct opposition to what you're being told in the media by the
authorities and so on. So without actually calling it a farce it's beyond that it's basically a
mind game and from a personal commentary point you get what you deserve you know there's no way
you can go you're spending your life saying that I'm gonna do what I do and I want to know about
science I'm gonna look at these jokers and learn something without looking into it before it matters
right and now when it matters no one wants to look at it because they're into a panic. I see
so if it can be shown that it's not what they're saying can we say what it is or is it do you feel
like it's too premature sure sure now in other words to actually formalize and do a serious treatise
on this would require a lot of resources but what we can observe looks at let's say there was no
study of electricity and you wanted to embark on it you would have the most rudimentary and crude
things to start doing electrical experiments right you'd probably have pieces of wood pieces of
copper some chain right higher in chains right you'd be starting off in the most rudimentary way
so from the position that I see it if we look at the what I call grunt work that's grunt work is
just like digging ditches it's a lot of work but it's not technical meaning all of the diagram
schematics and anatomical studies of biological things all the way from the the roots of plants and
trees to the bodies inside and outside of anatomy of fish to insects to human if you look at the
human intestines in anatomy books inside the lumina you know the opening of intestines arteries
organs cell tissues and all that you'll find that they all have one thing in common and that thing
in common is that they're surrounded by a cytomembrane which is a cell membrane and once that
membrane is examined it's extremely robust it other than high mineral things like bones and teeth
you know if you're gonna have a pliable membrane it's basically the cell wall and nothing goes
through it by the way so you have a central containment system with mitochondria plasma
cytofluids you know nuke what they call a nucleus on and on and on there are orifices that are
that seem like projections inward projections in cells that look like for example the pores on skin
and nothing goes in and out of it you'll see it as a termination point so just by looking at these
rudimentary supplies you know meaning anatomical diagrams and studies that have been done
and looking at how things change in condition for example if you back in the days when you had
magnetic tape you bought or today would be a blank CD or DVD and it had no information on it you
find the correct format and format it and copy another disc onto it and that is an information
transfer for example people that are old enough to remember a magnetic tape you know you dubs
a magnetic tape and your formats had it be in line for the copying process to take place another
an example would be induction a contactless charging on these cordless toothbrushes they have a
charging bay and there's no metal to conduct so so-called conduct electricity it's by induction
just like two coils would induct next to each other so and I'm suggesting induction strongly because
if anyone does any research on late 19th up to the late 19th century anything on pathology and epidemiology
and let's say toxicology and ultimately pandemic and disease study most of the books were titled
within the either the book itself or chapters within the book the induction of disease
not the contagion not took no you don't con like now everyone contracts a disease years ago
used to induce it right and they still have that term induction like when you induce vomiting
right you actually find a pressure point that spurs a gag reflex and prolonged gag reflex probably
will induce vomiting you only see that word used very infrequently so the actual mechanism itself
does not exist in a material sense you see also the the actual science if anyone wants to get
in you know actually knowledge of it you're gonna have to understand material a little bit more than
than you perceive it in other words most of the information about what material is has already been
supplied except for the planetary model of the atom and electrons and things like that but the
properties of living things from a material perspective have already been supplied now you have to
piece it together on how let's say a pandemic or a disease would be induced based on lack of
material infiltration into a cell and there's only one way that can be done again and it's by induction
for example if you look at the a lot of the studies that we're done in early electricity
galvanic where you get the term galvanism galvanic reaction things like that he stated that most
metals have an atmosphere on them which is interesting and when I when I mean an atmosphere it's a
layer that is subject to the body itself it's a gaseous layer and people also have an atmosphere as
matter of fact you see it very often illustrated in cartoons where someone's really smelly they're
walking around and you see they act the cartoonist actually draws an atmosphere around them right
like little rays or lines like you know it's maybe sometimes then Charles Schultz drew like a fly
buzzing around right but within the atmosphere that individual someone sprays a bunch of
colonon you know once you get once you get into their atmospheric range you can smell the colon right
these things can be observed from a very practical sense so I just laid out the foundation of what
needs to be investigated you could look up Rudolf Haaska he was trying to find out the vitality
or what's called a vitamin and the vital essence of things by subjecting various yeast cultures
and bacteria to various things that were known to be have vital energy to them like spinach cultures
in various starches and proteins and he would mix it with the the simple life forms and see how
they would react or sometimes deprive them of it and see how they would react but eventually he
found out you didn't have to actually combine the substances together mere proximity was enough
okay so another example of a lack of direct physical manifestation in a particular way would be
people having electro sensitivity and it's already been well established that the the whole field of
radio is a non-material phenomenon and of course they'll always say it's electrons moving through
the air but there's nothing moving through the air it's an oxymoron because money of the older
radio systems were vacuum tubes anything going through that would compromise the vacuum and the
system would stop working so I don't think it's possible all based on culture in tradition and
what people consider to be authority in other words following the the academic authority or what's
taught in the academy to have any change from their perspective of a lack of a material constituent
which is the fundamental aspect of pandemic or disease okay so what we can conclude is that this is
not a disease that's spread to contact or one person coughing on another but by this inductive
process that you're talking about we have somebody in the chat who's asking if you could compare it to
a poison well it's all developed by the body for example when you take a poison and let's say it goes
it when we get back to it yes it can be a spread of course through contact and someone coughing on
you yeah that see this is the problem very often with trying to show what many many consider to
be contrary information then they bundle it up and say everything I've been told is no good no
that's not true whether there's electricity that is non-material going through a large AC wire or
whether it's electrons if you touch it you're going to be electrocuted either way
so the final the final the the the the terminal result is the same whether you believe it's a particle
or not but once you have contact well that actually supersedes induction what happens inside the
body is purely by induction when you take a poison something that is toxic to the body and it passes
from the mouth through the the throat into the stomach past the duodenum let's say into the colon
and all that that is the entire point you know let's say it's an ingestable one versus an
inhalable one that your your unless it's such a robust chemical that it actually disintegrates
the the cell wall and penetrates and cause sepsis which is bleeding from the inside out
what happens is that that poison has to be recognized by the body as something you could reproduce
and when I mean by reproduce it's no different than what you see in science fiction where you have
the genroddenberry series of star trick when you're hungry you go to a food replicator
right your body is constantly replicating things but it has to recognize it
so for example if you have let's say the ability to not reproduce a known toxin in your body at one
poison you so the the concept of induction goes beyond just pent what's called let's say the pathology
of disease and all that but it's also the way your body ingests anything whether it's the
longs or the intestines or your skin it's all done by transmutation again one might just take a minute
clear their mind and think about what I'm saying and if this was commonly known and it was because
it's it's actually very perceivable what I'm saying based on the work you can gather from the academy
meaning reference materials that they put out and based on having access to a living body by the way
ha ha ha right so just think about how fundamentally ridiculous it is that you don't even know how
your own body works and I don't mean you specifically but yeah you generally but imagine imagine
though that people actually were raised and yet a society that was built around knowledge of how
biological things really work which is the essence of transmutation or replication don't you think
you might want to apply that concept that now you've mastered and can handle very well and mitigate
problems with don't you think you might want to actually apply that to your your technology your
science and your culture do you know a kind of a what kind of power and accessibility to all things
a culture that knew and understood how to replicate things would have it be considerable
so I recently came across an article where a medical worker describes the lung failure that the
condition traits in their patients when the disease gets very aggressive
I'm so I was wondering if I could read some bits of that and then maybe you can comment on some of the
things that you hear happening okay so I knew it was going to be bad but we deal with the flu
every year so I was thinking it's probably not that much worse than the flu but it's more frightening
I'm seeing patients who look relatively healthy that are completely wiped out like they've been hit
by a truck patients will be on minimal life support and then all of a sudden they go into complete
respiratory arrest and can't breathe at all we have patients on a cardiac monitor and we're seeing
when their heart rate has a sudden increase or decrease or one of us goes into visit the patient
and then sees them struggling to breathe that seems to be what happens to a lot of these patients
they suddenly become unresponsive or go into respiratory failure and then the lungs get filled with
fluid normally this is something that happens over time as the lungs get more and more inflamed but
with this virus it seems like it's happening overnight in my experience this kind of issue is
typical of someone who has a near drowning experience or with people who inhale caustic gas
when someone has an infection the normal colors you associate with it are green and yellow with the
coronavirus patients they have a lot of secretions that are pink because they're filled with blood
cells that are leaking into their airways so they're essentially drowning in their own blood
end quote. All right the comment on that is very simple if one studies for example the nature of
pandemics you you might get well it's been highly censored but that sounds very similar but not
exact to the pandemic the what's the American army flu or called the Spanish flu in 1918 people
died within 24 to 48 hours it sounds like the description I was giving earlier when the intestines
or the body induce something it's different than if that substance that something was the toxin
let's say penetrating the cell wall and killing its victim that way so this sounds more like that I've
also seen several references online that it is a nerve agent reaction right which is typical the
the pink fluids and all that are not infection now just go back to the early pandemic what's called
the bird flu that was designed by the way there are people who designed and put these things together
and it's not done in a laboratory like people are told never it's it can't be done in a laboratory
it can be let's say samples can be stored in a laboratory but that's not how it's done and I think
we in private I have explained how pandemics are created and from the bubonic on and it's not
something I want to go on on a podcast and described but it's not in a it's not in a laboratory that's
clinical so again what with it what you read was from a clinical perspective I think it was from a
nurse was it not yes that's right right okay so again their her perspective is that the
viruses do exist and things like that so hopefully what what you read she had enough clarity the
clarity that we that we can see is the description of the fluids right because obviously this nurse if
she's working in there she's brainwashed otherwise she wouldn't be working there so we have to rely
on what we consider to be objective and if you objectify what is mentioned not only by her but
other sources that you could see they're all pretty much in in agreement it's very rapid and it
doesn't fall within the parameters of an infection yeah I would suggest that if you look at the
geographic components which by the way most of these websites that show the spread of this
pandemic were created I think last year november or october so that gives you a little bit of insight
on the timing of this right or well the well-known timing of it the other thing is if you look at how
it's been vectored throughout the world it just doesn't make any sense they have something called
patient zero which is the first one who started spreading it that cannot be identified anywhere
so I would suggest this is what's called a black op and it's a conspiracy just because you know
for example I was on a sidebar in YouTube is this conspiracy or fact well so if it's conspiracy
there's no such thing as a factual conspiracy right anyway so there is a conspiracy obviously to hide
uh it's a origination point uh uh and I think I've gone through the in brief perhaps about the legal
system and other things about the worldwide conspiracy that is unknown and most people today
are very well uh very well understand the existence um i don't mean right or wrong but just the
very existence of secrecy in their society through intelligence agencies secret societies people
keeping their own secrets but but basically groups large groups of people that are well-funded
that operate in secret and it's fully accepted right and because that's fully accepted this is just
you know one of the sidebars of it right so or in other words it's one of the benefits of accepting
secret societies intelligence agencies secret police secret government meetings secret corporate
meetings all these things this is i just see it as a um the benefit of secrecy so from the secret point
of view i don't because i'm not involved directly uh with any of these secret groups intelligence
or otherwise uh i can tell you what i can garner from objective objectively uh looking at the
situation and from the things that i've heard from behind the scenes is that this is a bio weapon
and again um that's pretty easy to determine but it's not a virus it's just a
classical bio weapon that was uh used prolifically by the Mongols as their
Mongol invasions started to taper down about a hundred years later they realized it was too
difficult to control the European population so why don't we just make a disease to get rid of them
and that was of course created with the rodents and marsupials and uh in a certain way and spread
throughout to become the the bibbonic plague and then uh you've had several plagues in between
that and then the next big one was in 1918 which actually killed uh about as many people
in one-tenth or one-twentyth the time uh and that also that was created by the american army
the same using the same methodology so um i would say there is a patient zero but it's not known
because too many questions will be uh asked you see for example where you saw the outbreak start in
places like Iran and Italy and the northwestern US uh and in china uh there are people that know how
it was started but and and they're not showing you that on television so if anyone were to look at this
very carefully uh there are some cases that people do get quote unquote flu type systems that are
very aggressive but are not flu the flu as such but are closer to the 1918 pandemic which killed people
in a day and there are also there is also enough evidence to show that there's presence of uh what's
called you could loosely call organophospho fluorines which is the seren gas type constituents
which paralyze the lungs for example the muscles of the lungs which i you can also see some people
that supposedly have recovered from that give a very similar um uh response or testimony to people
who have suffered a seren gas attack which for would be for example people that are survivors of
the first Iraqi war or various other chemical um uh think tactical chemical weapons used in the field
that is the it actually i think they're about a month ago when this started i started looking at
there's a couple of field manuals online army field at manuals i don't think it was the us army
was another one about a chemical weapon um protection and the symptoms of various weapons and
some of them sound very similar to what you see going on right now like for example the description
that the nurse gave so but again uh if you live in a society that accepts secrets this is simply one
of the benefits of accepting it and what are some of the uh conceivable countermeasures for this
ailment i know you've talked in the past about certain things regarding silver and baking soda and such
so there are certain things that you can put in place to sort of preempt a bad situation now
sure from the chemical attack uh you know i think a drop of seren gas from a liquid from a helicopter
on a large area will will whoever walks within you know half a kilometer of that area will be
induced or poisoned by it varying degrees for days so it's very very toxic um so that would supplement
for example what they're doing with the biological stuff see personally i don't think the people that
are alive today are smart as the people uh or as cruel as the people were around 1918 the Rockefeller
foundation and the surgeon general at the time uh to to make such a a a a pandemic as they did then now
i think the believe it or not even with the advent of uh constant violence and uh degrade degradation
of morality i don't think there is cruel as those people were back then so perhaps they didn't have a
biological system um in place uh to spread as well as they would like so they supplement it with
the chemical now if you're subject to the chemical aspect it typically has a very light fruity smell
but if you smell it it's it's kind of too late right it's like heavy artillery when you hear it's too late
i i would think with that would be just uh beware of suspicious characters you know a van
uh typically uh someone in society that shouldn't be there or if you get that feeling that intuitive
feeling that something's wrong here stay away uh most people are pretty good with that but again
that would be topical washing and there are antidotes for that uh they work mildly they're
meaning they may not always work for the chemical side and one of them is um a plant i think it's called
it's a it's a night shade uh belladonna plant uh it's small poise it's considered toxic and hallucinogenic
basically uh antidotes for this type of chemical that would disable the lungs that can be called the
flu antidotes would be alkaloids right maybe baking soda and water maybe the green cratum leaf
any form of alkaloid but it has to be a potent and specific variety uh the best found in the in the
belladonna plant and a variation of okay in terms of the biological side uh if you are not
formatted for example uh you might have heard that there've been plagues that ravaged a town or a
city or an area and some people didn't get it i was on a private skype call recently and someone says
yeah there are people that go and uh to a leper colony to help them out and they don't get they don't
get the leprosy for example or um so on you know you hear about uh humanitarian missions uh and the
people don't get sick um and on the other hand where you have these laboratory situations where you
had the the programmed or engineered Ebola breakout in Nigeria a couple of years ago uh most of the
observers that were there were wearing full hazmat suits with breathing tanks and even with that
kind of protection 20 or 30 percent of them still acquired the disease even though there was
they were completely materially separated um so to not induce it or not format it so you become one
of those people that i'm not going to use the term immune but just use it in a literary and not a
literary sense immune here you're looking at a formatting system so it doesn't read the disease
what i mean by that is um you know years ago certain computers if you hooked them up together
they couldn't talk to each other right because of the formatting the information wouldn't transfer
over so basically how do you change your body uh to not be format to not format the disease like one
of the things you hear well it spreads very quickly amongst humans but animals don't get it
well so does that mean that if i have i'm petting a kitty cat all day or have a pet dog that you know
licks my face when i'm sick it won't get sick yep that's right the animals don't get it well you know
the animal share about 90 percent or like really mammals share about 99.99999999 percent of biology on
that level and fruit fly has 90 85 percent of human DNA broccoli is 75 percent human DNA
so would a piece of broccoli catch the disease no because it's not formatted for that right so
what i mean by that is when the format is changed like for example again the people who did not
contract leprosy when they went to do the mission work or whatever disease when they went to do that
humanitarian mission some of them did but some of them didn't and the ones that didn't why isn't
there any study on that and why is it when they do study they just say they have a robust immune
system or whatever and that's it they don't study the mechanism because there is no material mechanism
behind it um it it's again it's a formatting mechanism uh now one part of me say can say well i
wish there was a mechanical mechanism like a virus that did it because then it's purely material
they say where gloves and masks that's fine but the mop gear that you're wearing on your face in
no turrets called the mop up gear to clean something right uh those masks are not even one micron
absolute um you know and the what they're calling a vyruses in the nanometers which is
hundred thousand times smaller than the smallest opening on a face mask so that's kind of ridiculous
everyone can has heard more than enough wash your hands day away you know what they call now a
social distancing and all that but there is no talk i assure you at all about the induction of
disease that was well known throughout history and also the formatting on how someone has to be
formatted to actually accept the information and that's where for example um i say that this is a plan
deliberate attack because if the if the authorities any authority religious governmental policing
academic or whatever was really concerned or allowed to show concern they would be suggesting
the use of colloidal silver every doctor that's looked into it or any scientists looked into it
they'll tell you i pretty much within 20 minutes gets rid of any biological um condition that's
considered hazard within 20 minutes and it would would just someone has it in their body or is
developed in their body within 12 hours there's no talk about colloidal silver at all there's no
talk about ozoneation you know where you have an ozone machine ozone machines are used in industry
very often to disinfect things because of the ionization um like giardia is one of the
was a big um parasite in in in water for a very long time and any place that installed
ozone an ozone machine within the water line uh you know a neutralized it or eradicated it so again
you'll always hear an argument uh they're always going to try to lawyer the argument we'll say
we'll greek you know look at all the stuff about this or you know it doesn't work or this is toxic or
this is whatever so again you're always going to hear a contrary point of view to this because
number one there's no money in ozoneating because once you buy the machine you as long as it keeps
working it's good for life and there's no money that to market colloidal silver because you know
a few grams of silver can make enough colloidal silver water for a million people so it doesn't really
suit you know the the economic model so again the um the research that someone can do there is on
i believe on on the internet a few interviews with some older people that survived the american
words called the spanish blue and there's an interview with an older lady and she's sitting
there telling people that well no one in our family caught it because every morning our mother would
put some soda and water and have us drink it and she says it balanced and cleaned our system and
whoever did that didn't get it now when she says soda i'm suggesting she means a baking soda
so when you some people say well that makes you alkaline and all that but you know okay that that's
all right to say that but it's not the alkaline because soda hydroxide which is more alkaline
doesn't help you see so it's the it's what the mineral soda is it changes your format just like for
example when someone drinks a lot of alcohol doesn't it change their format you ever notice how they
can't walk very well anymore their speech is slurred their thinking is dulled or not as sharp
their facial expressions change they smell differently right just a little bit of alcohol
if you compare it to the volume of the human body can change completely change someone's format or
even just a tiny amount of alcohol that gives someone a buzz changes their format you know they're
being you see so that's what i mean by formatting the colloidal silver does very much the same they
don't understand the vehicle and they don't want to understand it publicly because it makes you
self-sufficient the benefits of colloidal silver but if you search around there are mainstream
scientists and doctors that have been asked i'm sure i haven't looked at it but i've seen it in the past
because there are many suggested outbreaks in society worldwide and in and what they call the
United States for past decade or two but they always comment especially the older doctors that yeah
colloidal silver will knock everything out but we just haven't tested it on this one yet right
so and there's other things i mean other things that are are beyond mentioning that can
can still be discovered and with the level of panic that we've seen people display whether it's
the run on the supermarkets or the hostility towards certain ethnic groups that they feel carry the
pathogen what have you observed in your locale Greek how have your surroundings changed in recent months
recent months more like the recent two weeks or so no matter where i go even a premium shop i
can't find rice right to buy and i have rice but i'm just saying i see the empty shelves and all that
which again you know i don't know if you've run into people recently right and being sarcastic
here but they're not too smart so when you see consistent events throughout places it's been planned
you know let's some groups sitting around somewhere saying you know let's start getting the notion of
a run on the market you know you go in here today and buy all the toilet paper and you go over there
and buy all that some people come in they see it's empty and then all of a sudden they got the idea
you see otherwise people are too stupid to hoard or do anything even riot believe it or not
there has to be a provocateur this seems like a provocateur type thing and it's also on both lines
i think they are telling it they're they're i looked up online about the supply of rice i was just
curious and all the manufacturers are everyone saying there's plenty of food to go around and then
you'll be other talk about oh but the logistics have changed a little bit right so artificial
scarcity i mean the people that run this world or own this world and run it have no problem with
dumping food into the ocean so you can starve and the sooner you understand that the more
clear you'll have a clarity you'll have on why things are happening right and when they're talking
about health is your concern your safety they wouldn't want anything more than everyone pretty
much wiped out but would would just a group of not necessarily mindless slaves left because they're
already mindless but obedient unquestioning without a doubt type of slave to be left over in in the human
aspect but again what i see going on is i my my my needs are very minimal like for example
i did run out of paper towels and toilet paper and all that i've had a couple of rolls or whatever
and i've noticed for the past two weeks they're not around right so where is another supply chain to
get paper hmm restaurants supply i call up the restaurant supply i say do you guys have any like
table napkins you know and you know rolls of paper for the bathroom she said no toilet paper but hand
rolls and napkins we've got all the you'd ever want and happen to know some of these people and
i went and got about a year supply for less than 30 or 40 bucks of all kinds of paper goods but do i go
around and telling people go to the restaurant supply and you'll have all the paper you want you
know instead of the regular store yeah i just did indeed yeah by saying it here so last thing about
the um current health crisis the pandemics of the past 15 years you know we've had a bunch since
the 2000s with the SARS in the bird flu and swine flu and the merse outbreak in the bowl and zika
and so on and so forth they have not resulted in the level of crackdown that we're seeing currently so
i'm not sure whether this is something that will blow over and then resurface again in a few years
as the other pandemics have or if this is an outbreak that will reshape the world through violent
loss of life loss of business and the introduction of policies that curtailed people's freedoms from
what you know should we anticipate the latter or the former uh maybe uh let me just put it another way
i would say that people haven't been free for over a century uh they're perceived freedoms which
is fine like i've said another sonics you could pretty much do anything to people if you use psychology
giving example uh you have you ever heard me mention that there's going to be a pitophyllia
petarastic and cannibalism agenda thrusted into society and it'll be welcomed and put to put to use
i think i've said that in the past now if you mention that to people now they'll say no way but
you know it's coming and you will love it because you're going to fall for it so i don't see any
i just see the way things are changing a little bit uh to lead to what i've been saying for a long
time which is the the focal of power going from the western world to the you know what's called
southwest Asia or the middle east as you find in some of the ancient prophecies um again uh
the i just see dead people just walking around and they don't know where they are what they are or
what's going on so in terms of the authorities uh doing uh whatever they're doing shenanigans you know
even if they opened concentration camps and decided to put half the population in there i think
there'll be minimum resistance in other words the possibility to resist the authority that is put
in place right now is impossible because everyone's tied into the digital network and um that's
what i see all right then well i feel like we've talked enough about what's going on at present time
and how that might spill over into the near future but i also want to talk about the further future
and what lies in next year and beyond but i also think it's worth looking at one of the frames of
reference we're using for that kind of prediction which is the system of time keeping modern man
keeps time using the grigorian calendar something which the Greek refers to as a pope works schedule
with a bit of derision i think and i believe the implication is that it's a calendar system that
originated from a papal decree which serves more as a metric for monitoring one subjects than anything
else can you talk a bit about why the calendar the grigorian calendar is something that you regard
with such scoffing anything unlawful i try to regard as scoffing it's not lawful meaning it has no
bearing in in anything that is accountable it's completely arbitrary and it's based on uh it
in order for the Vatican system or Catholics to exist you need a uh an abundant crop of evil and
ignorant people not informed and not good people in other words most of the people that adhere to
this system are ignorant they don't know what's going on and they just tell if they're told it's good
they go for it then the evil ones that know what it is and just like having power over people
that's all i and there's no ex the only exceptions there are temporary where someone kind of
wakes up to what's going on and looks for an exit strategy either from the belief system or the
actual workings of the institution and i have met a couple of by the way Catholic priests who have
quick because they found out what it was about and by the way when if you're an ordained Catholic priest
and you want to get out of the clergy they give you a card and they say go go to this office or call
this guy and uh they'll you know continue this type of career and uh one of the guys that did that
had a piece of paper with an address in a phone number he showed up and he looked up at the door it
said central intelligence agency so anyway um uh uh uh it's completely unlawful for example if you
study the ref any references to the julien or uh Gregorian system it's considered arbitrary in
other words they just count days there are no weeks or months or years uh they started bunching
things up with different types of nomenclature for years and months they'll even tell you like the
first month of this year is a b year or a d year or whatever i mean it's kind of like a bizarre
aspect of uh of you know uh that's been adopted and it's not just that there are other organizations
and institutions that try to institute their own timekeeping system like myans that are 20-day
month right yeah Stalin tried to have a 10-day work week uh Eastman Kodak in Rochester New York
tried to develop his own time IBM did develop their own time schedule for their workers so basically
it's just the memorialization of events for scheduling purposes but to be lawful it means that anyone
can do it once they understand the process and there's nothing really to buy you're not dependent on
some uh fictional arbitrary system like for example if you study timekeeping it's in the language as well
for thousands of years people try to settle their debts before the full moon came which is the new
moon by the way rises in the east it's not the darks with their moon that they call the new moon that's
in a part of an Egyptian nomenclature which i may or may not discuss at the moment but
people always try to settle their debts uh by the full moon that's why today uh they try to
settle bills with you with every moon you get it they get a moonfully bill uh also you look at the
way that time is done in reckoning the days the day starts at high noon at solar noon and these
two things i just said about the moon and the day starting at solar noon are typically found in
astronomy not astrology but astronomy 101 classes or the first year of astronomy in university
they do go through this so you could look up that for scientific and academic purposes
the day starts at solar noon but for the people it's civil mid-knife right so for example uh again
regarding the the moon i mean or actually regarding the day if people remember the pre-electronic
banking conventions if you deposited a check in the bank before or afternoon i should say
it was counted as the next day right there's an old song i think it was the door as the night divides
the day right so basically you go from noon to noon um that's why uh you know you have uh something
like break fast right you eat break fast in the morning because you fast for the day and you break
your fast at the end of the day which is right before noon now this if anyone studying any older
ancient rits and understands uh timekeeping you will uh you'll get a pretty good handle on what's
going on in terms of the year the yearly cycle um again the catholic vatican principle is uh
got to jam it all together uh to make it work and the year is not about the year's rotation around
the sun but the actual return of the sun or the return of the seasons to the year the typical
measurable years go from spring to fall and then the winter is an interim period you could look at
spring as being a time of starting new projects or planting sowing um uh you know a new development
summer is the time for it to grow fall is a harvest and winter is an interim period
humans are agricultural like if you were uh an agricultural individual you'd be there at the
springtime you'd be there in the summer and you'd be there in the fall those are critical times
but let's say you needed to replace the roof or build a new wagon wheel or you needed
to go on a long trip somewhere you didn't do it in the spring or the summer or the fall you did it
in the winter the winter is an interim period usually for that for those things because if you
try to do it during the spring summer or fall you're taking time away from production uh on the
uh you know of agriculture so once you understand these cycles and people are still agricultural by
the way you you're not um uh you can also think of it you know uh your a society that started by the
by the development of fire or the discovery of fire in almost inner permethane way as a metaphor
and you're pretty much that's the type of society or you can daydream and imagine all you want about
how you'd like your society to be technological or so technological just means tools um but can
you imagine a society that developed magnetism instead of fire it would be very different than yours
so you're kind of uh all you can imagine and no matter how far fetched it is it still brings you
back to being agricultural and if in anyone that works with agriculture if you're not lawful you're
going to suffer great loss right so in other words if you don't handle the spring summer uh and fall
properly you're probably going to starve unless you have enough set aside and you'd have to do it
right the next year to keep it going that's what i mean by lawful timekeeping in other words having a
a record a way to memorialize events which is time uh that is there can be picked up at anyone at any time
uh for example what a lawful timekeeping system does is transcends various other arbitrary
modalities meaning like an arbitrary modality would be the Gregorian, Julian or the Mayan or the
Egyptian those are like brand name uh timekeeping modalities and once that society goes away at knowledge
of how to use their timekeeping goes away you've lost also their record of time you see um so if you
keep to record uh recording and memorializing events by lawful timekeeping means which is using the
earth uh the sun and the moon and then of course for longer durations the constellations uh no matter
where you are uh on the earth you'll always have a pretty accurate record of memorializing those events
all right but um even though the Gregorian system can be shown to be fallacious it is widely known that
we have a lot of other ones that outdate the julian system such as the Iranian calendar the Chinese
one the eastern orthodox have their own calendar i think the assyrian culture also has their own
which amongst those kinds of systems should be given pre-eminence do any of them map perfectly
onto the lawfulness that you speak of none of them none of them work because they they're trying to
use a form of divination and mathematics to make it work on a schedule basis and it really is
observational in other words they're not lawful systems for example you could look at those systems
and they consider the new moon to be the dark moon there is a small remnant of the old
bow religion which is now called buddhism uh which is actually a pretty horrible society back then they
were they were pretty nasty people but uh they do consider in their calendrical system the full moon
to be the new moon but outside of that it falls apart again i would say that that old bow system uh
they they might have come close to having something closely lawful but whenever you see the dark moon
being the new moon you're looking at that palio or i should say palio i mean yeah it is paleo-egyptian
first dynasty system and maybe i should just cover that typically they relied the priesthood or the
the pharonic priesthood the the kafaz uh relied on astronomical signs um and uh they relied on uh
a full moon system uh meaning meaning look there's also something as a lunar calendar but the moon
to determine the month which were debts were settled and also it's a turn of of of events based
on a grouping of weeks uh four weeks uh and there was a lot of you might call it uh consideration
that the celestial were not as they are taught today millions of miles away or whatever but they
believed that all of the celestial that they saw were within reach within the sky that we see
and they were subject to predation meaning uh what if a big monster or demon came and swallowed the
moon we would no longer be able to uh determine time with the moon and that would really suck wouldn't it
so uh if we if the big monster comes and eats the moon up in the sky uh how do we manage our monthly
you know things that we have to do well the only one that could really substitute that is what comes
out of the mouth of pharaoh well so when the moon started going towards the middle of the month you know
which was the the dark phase they told pharaoh listen you can't go anywhere you must stay in the palace
you stay here uh until the moon reappears because if it doesn't reappear and it's been perdated on by
some sky monster you now take its place right and you must guide us right so pharaoh is like okay
you know let's see what's on that flicks right i have to be in the palace for three days you know
send me some more young boys or young girls or whatever they were doing at the time and finally when
the new moon was cited what they called the new moon uh when the crescent was cited they said ah see
the moon has renewed itself it wasn't eaten pharaoh is free to go about his business throughout his realm
and that means that the moon was renewed so that is our new moon now
do you see how ridiculous this is saying that the dark moon can be used for accurate observation
as a fallacy because the one of the benefits of having the full moon as your new moon is he put a
stick in the ground and you get a shadow which can be recorded where you can't do that with the
a dark moon one is a dark one is it not dark it's it takes there's no way to record that where you
can actually have what's called quote unquote a sundial or you can actually etch a mark you know
it noon if you if you solar noon if you start making a sundial and uh you start marking it where
noon time is you'll notice that it moves several arcs every year in other words noon time is a little
bit more towards the east this year than it was last year right so you could see the progression of
the ages of the centuries and the millennia by where noon time is marked and that is could be done
by anyone you don't need a special clinical system so again um to just to get people's minds out
of their reference points these are things that we agree on to keep schedule and when if you start
agreeing that um you're going to run your life by something that is arbitrary and unlawful do you
think there are any side effects to that yeah of course there are yeah it's a so so if you how long can
a society uh go through unauthorized acts before they get a pandemic whether it's engineered or natural
it's irrelevant do you see is it well deserved i don't know if if i told you that there's a
society of cannibals and headhunters that all died of a pandemic on that on that island based on
way your what your were raised in how much compassion would you have for most people to see i'm glad
those savages died right do you think there's possibly uh beyond individuals in other society that
is looking at this society is being completely unlawful which it is saying pandemic how come it hasn't
wiped them all out whereas this you know why should we sympathize with them right nice either logic
there well the purpose of talking about the timekeeping is to lead into the next part which is
going to be getting to the end of the the stream which is that we're going to talk about
what the future holds and i think that when we talk about looking at things on the timeline it's
important to know what timeline it is that you're considering and how to measure that
and more importantly where the source material is for that so what what we haven't talked about with
regards to timekeeping is what the source uh literature is on where to get information on the time
pieces and how to use them effectively we're not going to look at that on this stream but that's
just to say that these are things that you have to look into um but now let's talk about what we can
see approaching in the coming years we've got this health crisis here that might evolve into something
that's worse we certainly know that there's an economic downturn that's taking place with the lack
of business activity um so i want to start with economics greek what do you see happening in the economy
of the near and far future oh well the economy it's not going to go into any kind of a lawful status
because the the economy is pretty much governed by uh unlawfulness you know you don't have a lawful
means of exchange you don't have a system of law in place you have a legal system that is not law
um uh like i think i've mentioned i've even told an attorney who was being sued recently
you should study the law and you'll beat the other attorney because attorneys don't know anything
about law and he says yeah that's right okay so there is no law uh you have uh uh uh a series
of events that are going to take place with considering the apathy of humanity right they're just
going to brush themselves off and like i said earlier if you uh turn you know turned on what they
call the news and they said well we're gonna have to report half of the society to concentration
camps that they'll that'll happen they can they'll do that that's how dumb the people are uh
across the planet right now um i think there was a financier back turn of the century and uh he was
asked uh what are you going to do if um the people find out that the financial system is a scam
it's all that's easy i'm just going to pay half i'm going to print enough money um to pay half the
people to kill off the other half right so that still holds true today i don't see any negative
uh anything negative coming out of this as people uh that are doom and gloomers i think this is
just another nine eleven type event um which i've mentioned in the past look for these axial type
mini axial periods that change the way things uh uh are conducted are the the common the common
conversation for example after what's uh september 11th 2001 they said well this is a post nine eleven
world right well now it's going to be a past corona virus world right that's that's you'll hear of that
a little bit now and a lot of the things that you see imposed on the public now that they accept
will carry through but that is irrelevant uh what i mean by being irrelevant is if you look at where
you are in the movie you're near the end of well the movie already ended you're looking at the
credits and simply these crises and quote unquote uh terror events and wars and all these things
that you're seeing are just rehashing things that have happened in history before to lead mankind to
the final wrap-up of their worldwide society before the new society starts so that was a lot to say
in one sentence but i would suggest that the next thing to look for after this is you know whatever
whatever restrictions you see that are put on society will be of course uh accepted there will be no
memory of anything before this as usual and uh you will uh continue uh uh to see what's called the
western world as being quote unquote a superpower and i'm including the russian system from a military
point of view they consider that a superpower also but the western superpower is being uh brought
lower and lower and lower in their economic productive ability and uh social moral standards
and whatever else you you want to judge a society by and within the interim you're going to see
a reorganization in rapid form and uh what's called investment meaning of time of thought energy
material goods um political affirmation in in the place uh southwest Asia known as the Middle East
and you will see the Middle East starting to grow by by by description that i just gave and beyond
and the western powers meaning Europe and the United States and what have you though the black
nobility the old way of things that's going to start to play second fiddle to an emerging
economy political status um uh entertainment status scientific status and all that in the Middle East
generally is what you're going to start seeing not yet probably beyond uh 2022 summertime uh 2022
the fall uh around 2023 you're going to see a lot of activity towards what i just mentioned
and by the year uh on the Pope's work schedule 2025 there'll be no doubt that there is a tremendous
amount of investment and uh emphasis being put on that part of the world meaning the Middle East
all right then that is something that people will have to keep an eye on and so having covered
the range of topics i planned for this episode i'd say that we're at the end of the Greek speak podcast
but i would like to conclude the stream by asking the Greek to restate some exposition that i've heard
you speak on the past which served as my entry point into Greek speak what i first reacted to was
when you spoke of how mankind is so utterly unable to identify the cause of their condition
and the underlying ordinance behind their traditions so you've illuminated that by talking about
where mankind gets lost from and by explaining how ancient practices of the past have been revived
through parity in a way that still pays homage to the powers that actually ruled the world so can we
end things off by revisiting some of those things sure one of the things that we might have brought up in
note recently was with two cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common and i think most of the people
unless there are new listeners probably uh i've heard this before also i will give you that
in a second but i also want to reiterate what you just said which is i've looked at most of the things if
not all of the things that men man kinds culture celebrate and they all have some kind of a root
in something very macabre either murder rape or the sacrificing of children and i have not found
very little if not anything that is not based on basically murder may ham rape or child sacrifice
and also i'm going to put out something that i haven't said before there's a whole myriad of them
but you know the clown face also you know the how clowns are always shown to children as being a happy
joyous celebratory thing and then maybe i should give you a little bit of that first maybe before
the cannibals birthdays and dolls and most people have been aware of my criticism of subculture known as
the kids culture and kids are baby goats of course which is a sacrificial animal but there there's no
if the future depends on your children you have none because all your all your children have been
turned into goats with your mouth by calling them kids in the english language at least
but one of the celebratory figures that you typically see in the kids culture the kids subculture
is the the involvement of this clown figure you see it in the Ronald McDonald's stuff you see it in
a lot of their toys you see it as something to be observed as you know a happy go lucky celebratory
humorous whatever and of course there's been a play on you know the killer clowns now and all this
other stuff but the clown face itself with the exaggerated mouth the very pale skin and the exaggerated
distorted eyebrows and eyes and distorted hair comes from an effigy or basically the recordation
of an event that was basically started with the gladiators actually came before the gladiators in
Rome but i'll give them as an example within certain of games the the victor in a glad in about with
another gladiator would of course kill his victim it was a fight to the death and then to celebrate
that death and to show his willingness to you know basically take on that person you know take
whatever that person had that made them that person was it the in front of the audience they would
remove and skin off the face of their victim and they would place it over their own face and of
course if you tore someone's face off and put it on your face the eyes would be distorted the mouth
would be stretched out in the hair would be right just like the clown face with the pale skin
there's no blood rushing through it so we're talking about a very macabre some people may not be
macabre basically if you spoke to the people in the audience back then they probably liked it
but that is what the clown face came from and this is what you're putting in front of your children
so another thing you're putting in front of your children is what do cannibals birthdays and
dolls have in common and that sounds like an absurd question because they don't seem interrelated
at all well yes they are for first of all when we consider the ancient cultures even in many of
the secular public fool systems or education systems they tell you the society started
in the middle east the Mesopotamian area and they had a language it was basically a vernacular
or a type of language known as Hebrew caldian and the the priests of that culture were known as
the cahons and what they would essentially do is from a very dark sense tell people if they wanted
prosperity they had to sacrifice a child and not only sacrifice it but take some you take eat some
of the flesh it didn't matter how much you ate just as long as you put some of the flesh in your
in your body that's why the eating of human flesh is basically the cahon ballism because the God
that you were doing it for was a ball or a lord today when you go to church they tell you to worship
the lord right so in essence you know it's it could be argued to some degree but most things do
show etymologically the word cahon ball or cannibal does come from that source from a western
word perspective and of course anyone if you mentioned cannibalism they do understand what you're saying
but they don't understand this was a ritualistic right in ancient religious practices and the term
ball is still carried over in the Christian and many other religions as the lord as well
so what was interesting about this is the people didn't notice much prosperity coming from this
so eventually what they did is they started doing a parody of this but before I get to the
parody I left out what the doll the purpose of the doll was because it's cannibal's birthdays and dolls
when the parents returned back home after the sacrifice was done the other siblings asked where
their sibling was their brother or sister so the altar boys of the priest of the lord or the cannibal
would make an effigy or a small model of the child and you call the doll so the children were told
here play with this because your brother and sister is away for now right they lie to the children
like they do today and the children at least had a doll instead of their brother or sister so now
you understand the you know little girls like to play with dolls oh yes they do because maybe the
little girls were more emotionally attached to their brother or sister than the young boys but they
did also develop dolls for boys later on as well so you're looking at the macabre again ritual
interstill maintained in current traditions now again this didn't bring prosperity so why not
do for those that were too squeamish instead of sacrificing the child why don't we do parody
the event so you bake a loaf of sweet bread which represents the child and you put lights in it which
represents the life and everyone attending the ceremony makes a wish of makes a brings presence
because the the person who this celebration is for usually the child is to make a wish of
prosperity because it's about prosperity and they blow out the lights which is the life and they all
eat some of the cake which is the body of the child in symbolism and to show that the wish of
prosperity was met gracefully the participants bring little presence or gifts to the ceremony
so there's your birthday cake celebration again mimicking and parodying a human sacrifice
you might even see very often when there's a lot of criticism even today on these
pedophile networks they're quote-unquote elites or upper level of society whatever they always have
a parody at the dinner table or whatever of a human body of some sort still even though they
they actually doing the real thing behind the scenes so there's your there's your wonderful
western technologically evolved society with your birthdays and your dolls and your clowns
yeah that is quite a recontextualization of the things that most people think are innocuous or
even worse enjoyable right and you can go on and on with what they call the Valentine's day heart
is not the human heart or a heart of anything because everyone knows that the heart looks like a human
fist those are the frontal view of a woman's genitalia you know which enroman in other societies
on that day were cut off and nailed to a door or what do you call mounted and dried so you can have it
as a charm yep and so let's let's end things off with the this idea that your law comes from
you God that is the maximum that is the standard on this planet the maximum meaning that everyone
knows this it doesn't even have to be written wherever you see any law form throughout history there
was always a de-effic defied figure attached to it and you'll see this throughout history no matter
where you look and just to point out in case anyone hasn't noticed you'll you have all countries all
the sovereign states which are corporations or brand names you know that whatever country you want
to associate with or consider has a department of justice or a hall of justice with a goddess statue
if you go that infinite bastion of knowledge Wikipedia ha ha ha they will show you photographs of no
less than 30 or 40 countries that have adapted this you know pretty much and they're
priesthood is the the bar association right so you might people say well you know what you ran
in is enemy of the u.s or North Korea is enemy of the u.s but they all have bar associations you know
it's kind of ridiculous again but wherever you look through history and even in modern society the
current goddess that's revered by the modern society is justicia it's a revived goddess religion
so no matter how you want to take that as negative or positive it's true you'll always have some kind
of a de-metron or patron god within your law form but there's also this is sort of also more general
idea that people have to get their operating system from something that is higher up the
hierarchy than they are whether it's children looking to their parents or it's grown men and women
looking to something else right the way things are done on this planet is you have an authoritative
figure and there's another maxim that if you make men your authority you're going to have slavery
in oppression where if you make the gods your authority you don't you actually have freedom
right because you answer to them and they're non-material so from that point of view you could look at
classifications and memorializations of law throughout history and you will find that it's probably
best memorialized in what's known as the biblical text i'm not suggesting you go read a lot of the
versions and things that are put out but if you're not familiar with it you can do a study on what's
called biblical law and you will see that it is probably the most diverse and most let's say
widest aspect of law form there you'll also find that historically they like to talk about
homerabi code and things like that and if you they attribute that for example to a king homerabi but
he had a god that he was justified to do this for you see so and of course the biblical god is Yahweh
and you don't see that in your verses oh you don't see this in your biblical versions because of
the Judean influence which put a ban on the use of his name 2200 years ago in fear of
one of the for example hedge laws or halaka laws which is to prevent blasphemy because if to prevent
well if no one spoke his name there's no way blasphemy could be committed you see so if you don't see
Yahweh written in your Bible that is because of a quote unquote a contemporary Jewish influence or
Judaism influence in the rabbinical sense which in essence is contrary to what the Bible says
itself because the biblical text says to proclaim his name freely so you're gonna have to
pro or not you but this conversation or this type of expository information could will take
of another set of sonic events to talk about yes of course and that does it I think there isn't much
more that we can say that would motivate people to look into these things if they still don't feel
like looking into it and so what remains now I think is to delve into the finer points of things and
tackle the high level subjects that concern mankind's existence and for my part I'll be doing that
by setting up a new website later in the year for that it's gonna be looking into things that most
people consider perhaps esoteric today but those things will become more familiar as time goes on
and can I count on the Greek perhaps to join me for a podcast for that when it's ready?
I don't know if you can but yes you may I'm just joking I'll take that all right well thank you
again to everyone who's tuned into the streams we've done quite a few and I'm grateful for anybody
that stuck around it means that the effort was reciprocated so even though the podcast is over I'm
gonna be directing my energies towards greekspeak.com still by writing articles for the rest of the year
before launching the new website which will focus on like I said the unseen realm of things
and then I also want to extend a thank you to the greek you've taken the time and of course these
podcasts don't exist without you I couldn't ramble on for an hour and a half on my own so thank you
very much for your contribution. Oh you're welcome and you know I couldn't ramble on for an hour and a
half on my own either but I seem to always find myself doing so. No you're good at what you do and I
think people appreciate that. Okay you're welcome and we'll see everyone again sometime soon. Thank you
to everybody who tuned in and we will see you at the next podcast series.
[Music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]