[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening.
This is the Greek Speak Podcast.
I'm the Archon, and this is episode four of my talks with the Greek
on a range of subjects about the situation that mankind finds itself in on a wholesale level.
It's been some weeks since the last stream, and these gaps are quite regrettable,
but I just have to make the best of a cumbersome schedule.
For this episode, as usual, feel free to use the Greek Speak chat room if you have any questions or input during the stream.
The status of Greek speaks political, religious, and commercial affiliations has not changed,
because there aren't any, and I run this project on my own.
So, please enjoy the rest of the show, and thanks again for listening.
[Music]
Hi, Greek.
Hello there, greetings.
So, we are back. How's life treating you?
The way life's supposed to treat you, I guess.
Well, I guess we all have different expectations for that sort of thing.
That's right. Maybe we'll get into a little bit, a bit a little bit of that today.
Yeah, let's see where things take us.
Well, the theme that I've prepared for this week is that of education,
which is meant to be a sort of continuation from last episode's focus on communication.
I think a lot has been said in the 20th century about the nature of things like formal education,
whether it's establishment institutions that advocate for it,
or those who have been sort of disillusioned by it and disparaged it, usually in their books.
So, it would be useful, I think, if we could break down those two sides
to examine what lies at the root of that issue, the school system,
but also general ideas of edifying yourself and others.
So, to that end, we're going to look at three categories with the first being education
and the others being learning and teaching.
So, let's start by looking at the idea of formal education as organized machinery
with its own mandates, which is what it seems to be today.
My understanding is that a particular kind of state sanctioned
almost factory model education arose in the 18th century.
Most people attributed to Prussia, the Prussian school system,
and that later spread throughout the world, and that's what most of the
anti-schooling insurgents point to as the creation of the modern system.
What do you know about that development, Greek?
Well, I can only say that just try to discern what anyone else can discern
based on the history that's available on it.
I'd say that it's much more nefarious than most people think,
because you control what people know or think about and you control the people.
I think the British had a big hand in it, not just the Prussians,
probably post-Prussian influence, but at the influence went even prior to that.
Which was no education.
Let me just preface something that if you provided a proper,
yes, there is such a thing as a proper education to society at large today,
even the past 50 years, it would be rejected because it wouldn't be recognized as such.
So that's a simple way of saying that everything is just too far gone, right?
So if anyone is listening to this, you're not going to hear,
hopefully what you think you want to hear, we're going to pretty much try to be as objective as possible.
But just like any objectivity can lead to a happy ending or not such a happy ending,
the current education system, formal, mechanized industrial, like you mentioned,
cannot be fixed.
It has to be completely discarded and started from scratch,
and very little of it will transfer over to a proper education system.
So this is not a recitation or discussion or a sonic event on how things can be made better,
because they can't, sorry, sorry to be the bearer of such good news, right?
Because bad news would be the false hope in trying to make it better.
So I guess we'll be, we'll sound critical and we'll be as objective as much as possible.
Sure thing.
We will get into sort of the more specifics of what makes these the system flawed,
but just to stick with the historicity of it, because I mean even sometimes people harp a bit too much on the,
the Prussian thing as if there wasn't anything before the 18th century.
I know that prior to that point you already had a sort of colonial education system,
for example, the monetary system where the Spanish and the British colonies in the 17th century
would have hundreds of kids in a hall and then you have one master who teaches all of them
and then you know the older kids will supervise the younger kids and it's sort of,
it was described as a factory model even back then.
So there seems to have been a ramp up of some point.
I'm not really sure where that point was, but we're going to educate these people like animals
and you know get the results thereof.
Maybe, maybe narrowly viewed in such a way.
And the reason I say that is because you cannot discount the type of society
or the goals of the society or the ideology of a society when looking at the education system.
I'm going to give an example, ancient Assyria or ancient Sparta,
what's known as Greece, were war-faring people.
Their industry was war when they wanted or needed something.
They simply went and conquered someone who had it.
The type of education that they received there was to create fighters and strategists and tacticians
and just soldiers, right, all the way from frontline cannon fodder to lieutenants
and others that could lead groups of people.
And then you have an education system that must reflect that, right?
Then you have an agricultural system.
And if you have an agricultural system, the education must be around that agriculture
because if you have an agricultural system and you base the education on let's say
what might be contradicting like industry or various forms of engineering
that are not pertaining to agriculture or philosophy or law or medicine,
you would force that population to use that form of education outside of the agricultural community.
If you, the same with, if you, you know, you can pick any type of society, see-faring society, nomadic society,
you know, whatever the society bases its industry, and I use that term,
not in the way that people consider industry to be in the modern industrial sense,
but in the way that they provide for themselves, it must be in accordance for that.
That's why, for example, fast forward to the modern system.
You don't need as many people as were needed at one point to do what, let's say, is necessary.
So why would you educate them?
Right. And the other thing is when you understand legal or lawful status of a slave,
slaves were not educated in a general sense.
They just received education in pertaining to whatever tasks they were, I guess,
purchased or held in slavery to do.
And let's just throw in, the word education means what people think it means,
but it also means the training of animals.
So it is interchangeable.
And you mean from an etymological point?
It means the training of animals?
Right. And it was used mostly for the training of animals in past, you know.
Because the words like "leabor" and words like "literacy" and, you know, "liber meaning book"
and "literacy" were more pertaining to the labeling or a well-read.
People didn't say they were educated.
You were like a man of the cloth. They had other sayings about that.
So it's sort of more of a modern term to say someone is educated.
They used, you know, learned in the law, learned in the agriculture,
learned in shipbuilding, you were learned in something that educated was more of the common terminology.
I see. I don't want to depart from the history aspect too quickly
because I know that there's a bit more that can be said about that.
What can be said about the efficacy of other school systems throughout,
let's say the 17s to 19th centuries,
because you've mentioned the Victorian grammar schools is something that conveyed more productive instruction than what we see today.
So can you touch on that and perhaps other variants that you know of?
Sure. The simple variant was the, it was the responsibility of the family structure or the,
the vicinity of the people. In other words, basically schools were a neighborhood thing or a tribal thing
and you had the one room schoolhouse more into the upper crusty upper echelon of society.
You had more of the well endowed better funded types, you know, the boarding involved and more what's called as a academy today.
I've always spoke about the what's called the Victorian grammar school system.
Not to tell as Victorianism in a positive light in any way,
but what is positive about that education was typically between the ages of seven and 14 of age, years of age.
And you, it was, it was not as an indoctrination program.
It was more of a providing the student with, with tools of literacy program.
And also it was a condensed limited in other words, it didn't take much of your life as modern systems take roughly anywhere from 12 to 16 years.
And it was far more effective.
Are there any other systems that you would put on par with that the Victorian grammar schools?
Not really, because the again, it was, if you go prior in history, other than what's known as academy, right?
Right, for you know, anyone could, it's a broad term, but you know, even like suck the socratic academies, right?
Pythagorean academies from ancient Greece.
Other than that, it was a tribal and familial task.
It was a, it was not centralized or as people consider it education today.
It was done locally and in a microcosmic way.
Depending on the tribe or the, let's say the neighborhood or society in a micro way.
You had, you can even see the concept of the one room schoolhouse, an agricultural concept was the predominant value in an agricultural society and an industrial, concepts were predominant in an industrial society.
If you go far back and yes, there were industrial societies.
If you look at the many of the major cities of the world that go back prior to the 18th century, they had industry.
People seem to think that modern industry, what's called mass production or artisanship or that kind of stuff with machines, making products is a recent phenomenon.
Just like the light bulb was around for hundreds of years, it just wasn't durable.
Electricity has been around for hundreds of years as well.
It just was not as available to the masses as it is today.
So you did have industrial cities back in ancient times as well and their education would be very different from, again, agricultural or seafaring or a warring type of society or tribe or what have you.
Is there anything that can be used to determine what system of organized schooling was the most effective in history?
Because I'm sure that even though in modern times we might point to the Victorian grammar schools, even if you go back to ancient times there must have been something you mentioned the academies of certain philosophers that have been known to sort of make a name for themselves in the world of being learned.
Well, you can make the safe presumption to say that if knowledge is power, which I don't think it is, I think the action is the power aspect.
But when knowledge was held throughout society, it was always used against the masses.
Oh, well, I wouldn't say directly used against them, but it was sequestered and contained by very few.
And this goes back through all of known history. So would we say that those academies, let's say, or those forms or education or schools were the best that raises a moral question either way.
The best school is the best school for for the each pertaining economy, let's say in the word economy means the laws of the house. It's a Greek word, a no-most meaning law and echo meaning house or equals.
So it's really difficult to say you would have to be more specific, you know, for an agricultural society, which would be the best school and again, would it be central and it would not.
Right, because you'd have different types of agricultural practices, even based on which region you're doing the agriculture in the same with industry.
I wouldn't say that there is a good, let's say formal institution, smaller, large ever that has been brought forward to this modern day at all.
So then that poses the question, you know, how are people educated in a good sense or what is the highest form of education? This of course will lead to, I think.
So as far as mass education goes, when I look at all of the schooling reforms in the 18th, 220th centuries, they all use the same sort of hackneyed rhetoric about personalizing education, quote unquote, freeing up students to be more creative and empowering teachers.
And yet they all seem to fail at their stated goals because they get replaced by something else. And that leads me to wonder whether it's possible to mass produce education.
And you've commented on that. I'm wondering if it's more the case that each person is ultimately responsible for his own education and society only provides the forms or the tools for that ideally.
Yes and no, ultimately, the self-responsibility aspect would raise the question is a five, six or seven or eight year old responsible for themselves and how responsible should they be or can they be?
It is a responsibility of the, those rearing those children.
But ultimately, it is a response when you become older and you're able to manifest desire responsibly.
Yes, it is from that aspect. But from the formative years of education, it's the responsibility of those that have guardianship over the young people.
And that's one of the reasons why it's so easy to manipulate a society by rearing the children into certain behavior, certain mindset or ideology because they are not responsible and can't be responsible.
Well, with the children, child aspect, I would understand it. I guess I was more referring to the idea of an adult who takes responsibility for himself because to a certain extent, we're all shoulder in a certain amount of folly that's been foisted upon us as children.
And then you have to unburden yourself from that as you get older and some people succeed and some people don't.
I think we've discussed before that your average human from a planetary scale operates mentally within the age range of nine to 12 years old.
So again, I think that's going to lead some very deep questions on what happens when you get older. You just get older, but the mindset is still very immature.
And from the majority aspect, there's always a very small minority of humans or earth inhabitants that tend to feel that it's an ongoing process for all of their lives.
And that's the other extreme, you know, to keep learning. And then of course, there's cosmic censorship, the ideology of the society that's put upon the individuals, you know, the people.
And the personal choices, of course.
I would like to know what is at the heart of how ineffective today's formal education is, because you can point to many elements from the incompetence on the part of teachers to substandard curriculaums, or you could look at the influence of charities and foundations with anonymous donor groups that dictate the direction of the school.
Out of those kinds of things, what do you think is the most guilty party for what makes things look the way that they look today?
There's status basically and there's a lot of people harping on this and I'm not. I'm not a constitutionalist or a freedom fighter or into liberty or anything like that that people told about.
But if you have a birth certificate, you're legally a slave, your property. So if we go back and look at the general aspects of what type of education slaves received, you can answer that question on your cell.
You know, anyone can answer that on their own, because even just the urban myth that slaves are not to be educated is still true.
So you have a slave planet essentially, right? Except for maybe a few postune tribesmen, maybe some people in Somalia or the Congo, then you have to address, you know, as if you just visited this planet and you have seven billion people plus, you know, in the status of slave, illegally, not necessarily lawfully, but legally for sure.
So how do you handle the education system or criticize it? And if you know, the unit leads back to saying, well, just to cut to the chase, the modern system is strictly about control, you know, how to control the population.
And you cannot control a population unless they have a sense of literacy, where, for example, the archaic aspect of a slave was someone working out in a field or some workshop with an overseer dictating to them.
That is not the case. I mean, you do have policing and other things like that, but that is not the case in the slave planet known as Earth.
They have to have some literacy to access the control mechanisms. An example would be, they have to be literate enough to be able to discern the numbers and letters on a television remote control.
And that is the most important aspect for getting an education or understanding typical earth inhabitant, or at least in the industrialized world, they're going to get 99.999% of what they think is true, what they should do, or what they shouldn't do from, yes, you guessed it, the television.
And how are they going to get that if they can't operate, let's say, a remote control or a television, which still requires a very minimal amount of literacy.
That's interesting. I never really thought about that aspect of things.
That in fact, you get educated so that you can become more of a slave.
Well, because there is no direct overseer, you have indirect oversight.
So the people have to be trained to go in a 1984 kind of way, you know, Winston wake up in the morning, you know, you have to face the screen and all that, you know, the, the, the, the Orwellian book.
By the way, a lot of these like Huxley and Orwell, all these guys that wrote all these modern dystopic novels, they were done under orders to write that right to disclose a very strong possibility.
But nonetheless, there is a certain amount of literacy that's required to maintain whatever design, social design, you want to put in place, you know, because you know, there are, there are some people that are completely literate.
In other words, if you handed them a television remote control, they couldn't discern the numbers or the letters on there.
So how are they going to watch the propaganda or how are they going to know what they should do and not do.
Right. So you need to have some level of access to communication again.
It can be done graphically, you know, but it's gotten to the point where even certain graphic symbols are not so.
Let's say you'd list it that you still have to have some literacy to comprehend them.
So I would say that it's just basically a system of control. Now the, the controller is from a, I think this is more of a secular sonic event, right.
We don't want to get into the spiritual side of it because that's just an avalanche of information that has to be covered before we even discuss the spiritual side of things.
From a secular point of view, you have to understand that everything is done in secret when it's, in other words, true power is held in secret.
Even from an over standpoint, no one wants a power plant in the middle of their neighborhood.
It's always put outside of their neighborhood, right.
The powers that are running from a secular point of view, human society are in secret and outside of their view.
Their desires are for the population is what you see.
In other words, in the education system.
So when you look at the formal education system and when I say formal education system, I'm really speaking more about university level.
As being rubbish as well because you can't have elementary and middle and high school being rubbish and then all of a sudden a university education is good.
Right.
So, and the true culprits or the real dummies or the ignorant are the professors and the teachers, right.
So the students of course will always admit, you know, I think it's only a few days after they learn something they forget it because they just glad they got out of that place.
So essentially the desire of the secular power control is even though they operate in secret is not a secret because you can just witness it by looking at the education system.
That is the desire they have for their property.
Just before we move on to the next thing, what do you mean by Orwell and Huxley, what did that under orders? I haven't seen that recorded it anywhere.
Oh, yeah, it's pretty obvious when you when you understand there were contemporaries and to a certain degree and when it came out, the new world, you know,
the concept of formulating a new world order is not something that happens overnight. Right.
And the mid century, mid 20th century was a very, very key turning point into forming, you know, the next hundred years, not not even an incremental fashion, but in a very gradual fashion.
And of course, it was done under orders. And of course, I wasn't there and I didn't and I ever saw a witness the orders, but I mean, I can take a hint.
Can you give some evidence too?
Oh, yeah, clearly. You can see that it wasn't necessarily as prophetic as people think.
It was basically people having again, in secret discussions that basically get around certain circles and when there are certain people that have talents in the media, which can be writing as a medium of communication art is another medium of communication, the visual audio arts, music, all that.
And they are influenced. There is there is literally armies of people behind the scenes influencing what you see as media education, the visual arts, the audio arts, you know, there has been enough information, even a lot of blame is or finger pointing is on the Tabestock Institute, but that is a very small aspect of it is even though it's influential for
everything that you hear in public, you know, from the conspiratorial secrets, that's the tip of the iceberg, right? How many times have you heard up until even now, but starting in the 60s, even groups like the Beatles and all that were influenced to put out certain, you know, social memes that will change the mindset and ideology of the society.
Sorry, very simple, but I would, you know, here's the thing that there is no research on that there's a lot of research on, for example, how Crowley influenced very, you know, and Jack Parsons and all these other things and the Scientology, there's a trio there and unholy alliance and how things were influenced by these people, but there is an influence that is underline that's been going on since time in memorial.
But I would suggest very strongly and then of course it's a presumption I said of course they were ordered to do that, but yes, it's quite obvious once you understand how things work, those were commissioned works.
Okay, I mean I will dig into it a bit more and perhaps bring that subject up again, but no, I know about the music aspect in any case and the film aspect of that sort of thing.
But to get back to education just so that we can wrap up this particular segment, I think it's interesting that the institutional wisdom tells us that children need school because they learn there and are best prepared for the world there, but that institutional wisdom is itself the product of the schools and people who graduated from the schools that shaped the world.
So how does a student who sees the folly in the school system escape from that or mitigate the effects of that if he no longer wants to be a part of it.
Well, the aspect that you mentioned that they'll do better in society is absolutely true.
If the power structure wants a very easily controlled, let's say from an individual basis, I want the individuals to be easily controlled and manipulated, you know, I call them the mushroom people.
You keep them in the dark and feed them bovine excrement.
Yes, you will do well on society and speaking from firsthand knowledge, being around people that are of the upper echelon of society, judicial, medical, political, engineering, community, they are pretty dumb.
Not on savvy or not necessarily successful in business, I didn't say that, but they're not smart. Right. They basically followed along and played with the system when they get into a, you find themselves not not by chance, but by usually positioning themselves networking and just hard work to be very wealthy, but they're not, they're not smarter intelligent in a general sense that you would expect, you know, they're not well learned.
At all, you see, but yes, you will do better if you believe all, you know, if you, if the power structure demands that the planet is inhabited by the mushroom people again kept, you know, kept in the dark and fed excrement.
Yes, you will do best in that society with their propaganda.
Sure, but if you are say a 15, 16 year old and you, you reach a point where you're like, this is garbage, I'm learning nothing, I want out, but obviously you live in, you know, first world country where this sort of thing is mandated by law, you go to school, you know, how are you going to extract yourself from the excrement, even though you're in, in, in of it.
You don't, you might be crossing the street in a month and get hit by a bus and killed instantly or you might live along and fruitless life into your 70s and 80s.
You know, that's just part of the existence of being human in this age or many ages, you know, it's not a good existence, sorry to break the news to you if you don't know that.
So again, it goes back to the basic credo that I've always been saying food clothing shelter and then you're going to have to wonder until you discover what level of quality of those things you'd like.
And then you're going to have to figure out how much compromise you're going to have to make, you know, to accept what the dictates are and follow through.
It seems to be a condition in which you're in quite a stranglehold, whereas the point should be to extract yourself from that stranglehold, not, you know, resign yourself to it.
I wouldn't say it's a stranglehold, I just say it's an unfortunate situation.
So since you're born in a society or an age that is unfortunate, you might want to seek fortune and fortune might be things that are beneficial to your being.
And all the way to the material fortunes that people, you know, are told they should have.
If you think that you're fortunate to be alive on earth in any of these ages, you're an idiot.
It's a very unfortunate condition to be here.
I think the passion evoked by the arts and romanticism and even, yes, the education system that things are good or even can be great is idiotic.
And it's basically a drug that fits between the ears very well for most people.
Just to wrap up on the education segment, I'd like to expand on the topic of formal education to look at perhaps what could be the inverse of that, which you could loosely refer to as informal education, I guess.
But the intuitive idea behind that term is that there exists a methodology of learning that is not based on predetermined pipelines of instruction or manufactured culture of compliance.
And that method of learning takes its momentum in the curiosity and the direct experience of a person.
Can you contrast those two approaches and maybe explain why they so rarely intersect that is learning in school versus learning by direct observation?
Well, there's direct observation and there's also an understanding the real history of something and going toggling back and forth between the creative direct observation and sense of discovery and learning versus the centralized system.
And if you look at trying to find out where things started or the history of something you're on your own, because if you go to the centralized system, they're going to feed you basically lies.
And if you want to, let's say, find the history on something on your own, you're going to be intertwining with the lies that the centralized system puts out, but you're also going to find a little bit more leading towards the truth, right?
And instead of wholeheartedly accepting what the mainstream says.
So the other aspect is if you want to have a population that's easily controlled, just like, you know, horses that are bridled, pulling a wagon or something, they can't have their own will and their own desires.
Right. So I think ultimately the there's going to be a crossroads and a conflict between who wants to learn by direct observation, understanding the history of things and of course morality as well.
When they try to compare it to what's taught by the centralized public system, which is immoral and amoral.
And it's very easy to say that that's not an opinion. That's the truth. And the example of that would be if you any, any university in the world, higher low, meaning, you know, well esteemed or not so well esteemed, you can go look at their law degree programs.
Okay, look at their curriculum. You could find them on the stupid rectangle. None of them teach any law.
The most you will get is some legal theory. Most of it is basically contracts, commerce, how to set up a legal clinic, right, and all that.
So essentially you have no law anymore. You don't have anyone learned in the law with the exception of those that have taken upon themselves to do it on their own.
And of course you can't practice or be in a formal, instant legal institution in that way.
So again, that's where I said you're finding yourself in a very misfortunate and unfortunate place. And the same goes with medicine.
Other than some basic anatomy, there are no university universities that teach how the human body works or anybody.
Right. And just dare anyone to look at the curriculum of these universities.
So if someone wants to learn about healing and how the human body works, you have to do it on your own.
And you will of course be at odds with the centralized system. And you won't be able to practice it or be prominent in society with it without major conflict.
And again, you will find yourself in a misfortunate and unfortunate condition. It goes on with any subject.
I mean, I'm trying to think of some example in history where you had somebody that did things through their own direct observation and they were able to have success in an industrial sense.
But on the surface, it seems like you free will, creativity and unabound learning and inspiration and all that is rewarded. And it's not.
That's done publicly. And I think we've mentioned before this the the quote unquote system that is set up in secret will always say in public in most societies, modern societies, you're free.
You have liberty, do what you want, but in private wants any agency or authoritative institution or figure gets the individual and private and brings up those those virtues that are bestowed to the public.
They say no, you don't have any of that. You have to be like everyone else. You see, so it's a very insidious system.
And and of course you have the system variance like in Asia, for example, you have a different, you know, like if you look at China, it's a very different mindset and ideology.
And then you again can contrast the eastern versus the Western, right? And then you have, you know, within those, you know, East versus West, North and South, you know, variance.
But I can tell you that wholesale being on a slave planet, when you start hearing this society says you're free and you have more liberty and all that, those are where the biggest liars are, right?
They just have a better deception for you.
I mean, at some point we're going to, we'll do an episode on entertainment and things of that nature too and arts to actually look at what some of those lies manifest themselves as.
But let's now move on to the concept of learning, which I think is less about what you do in school and more about how you edify yourself through self development.
I find it interesting how much the educational system tries to develop students through the provision of information rather than the provision of insight or understanding because these schools almost make it a point of honor to have big libraries and volumes of textbooks about all kinds of stuff and trivia.
Yet they gloss over that all that information is pointless unless the students are able to arrive at accurate insights about reality.
And then it's no wonder that the schools have free reign to teach erroneous science or fake history because there's not really any requirement for the students to actually grasp at the heart of those subjects.
What would you say is the key for a person to arrive at insight out of the information that they encounter such that they can perceive the folly of the things that are taught in school or in other places?
Oh, I simply put if it's put out for the masses, it's it's going to be either an outright lie completely or 90% if not best at best 50% false.
So you're going to have to sift through the old sifting through poop to get edible corn.
I think your question sort of in a roundabout way answers itself, but you're not.
It's about control, not about knowledge, you see.
So ultimately even someone seeking knowledge, let's just we haven't brought up that word yet regarding education.
But if you're seeking knowledge and you start gaining knowledge, real knowledge, not the the false aspect of what's put out by media, university and what have you and tradition.
Because tradition is also a look at your religious traditions, right?
You will find that the the person comes to a moral crossroad.
Moral meaning do I exist in the society lawfully?
And if you try to do that, you're going to find yourself in, you know, basically in a society, no matter where you are that is unlawful.
And you're going to have to compromise a certain morality to deal with even just to deal with them on the most basic aspects.
Or you will say that I have I will not deal with them at all and go find my own planet or my own island somewhere and that's not going to happen.
So on the on in today modern age, you might be left alone for a little while, but you will probably be discovered and threatened.
But so we have to lean on the first aspect is as you start gaining knowledge and as you start learning outside of what has been fed to the mushroom people again kept in the dark and fed.
I excrement as a mushroom people.
You will you will find yourself making more decisions on how much compromise do I want?
You know, or you can develop a what's called, you know, you see in the media as a criminal mind and take advantage of these morons.
You know, the ones that have believing all the mind control and all that and end up being a politician or industry leader or something like that.
Are you trying to suggest that the leaders of the world actually despise the people that they're meant to steward over and aren't just punking them?
Right. That wouldn't be reasonable to suggest, but a sort of say it is the truth. I'm actually happy to say that it's the truth.
I'm sorry to say is it is of course that way.
I've always found when you say that sort of thing that Silvio Berlusconi comes to mind because he was always such a comical politician and ultimately you can see he wasn't taken the position seriously, but they kept letting him get back into position.
And I would say that Trump is the equivalent of that today, but I think he causes a bit more heartache for people mentally, but there's a comical aspect to that that you have these characters that become political leaders, but they don't have the competence for it.
Well, here I'll go back, I'll harken back to Napoleon. He taught Napoleon taught the Napoleon Bonaparte. He taught the oligarchs or the wealthy power elite of the world.
A good lesson, you understand that they have to take a firm grip and keep clowns in position of leadership. They are the leaders, by the way, when you nut, nut the clowns that they put in front of you, the presidents and kings and all that, but even in World War Two where you had strong people like Stalin Hitler and FDR and Churchill supposedly they were still on the clown category for sure.
They had for talents and dealing with crowds, but Napoleon Bonaparte taught the oligarchs that to keep a stronghold and keep the clown aspect in place.
And you can have a sad and serious clown as well in terms of world leadership, what you put in public.
So to speak of Burlesconey or Trump is just like fifth generation or eighth generation clown, even Ronald McDonald's corporation knew that you need a clown, at least they were more honest about it.
But these clowns that you've seen as leaders for the past 200 plus years is an interesting aspect to research how you're not going to find the secret dealings or the secret to directly who runs the world.
But you'll research how the clownmanship has not changed.
Yeah, but it does seem to me just to move on to another aspect of learning the subject of learning.
It seems to me that there are three kinds of people when it comes to learning any subject.
There's the person who is able to arrive at insight on his own by way of his own curiosity and his own efforts.
And then there's the person who though he's capable of arriving at the same understanding as the first guy, that only happens once the subject is explained to him by someone else.
So a teacher that helps him grow through proper instruction.
And then you have the third kind of person who never arrives at any understanding in the matter whether by his own efforts or when it's clearly explained to him.
So if we presume that that kind of categorization is reasonable and we know that a person's capacities is significantly formed by their upbringing and their experiences.
Then I want to ask at what point can a person no longer move from one category to another between those three.
So like when is an unlearned person doomed to forever be unlearned or when is a student able to progress to become a master and so on and so forth.
The trauma aspect is a good one.
People will always learn through trauma not always and not all people, but usually.
You know, there is a that's the comprehension of the mind.
Of course there's the ideology of the society and the family that they were raised in.
But then of course you have certain individuals and I would call that the full aspect.
You know ancient rits never said anyone was smarter than anyone else is you just had people that had wisdom and then those that didn't and then you had those that were fools.
And I think that's very different than the measurement of IQ and all that.
I think of course I've experienced people that learn by by watching adaptive learning and by example and then there are those that need that and lessons and then there are those of course that even through example or lesson don't learn at all.
And I believe that is a on a a private individual basis.
You know the the the aspect that the modern quackademics or quackery fake science teaches that it's genetic is not necessarily.
I don't think holds water.
I think it's more of basically from the crib to when you wanted your first ice cream or something.
Or able to form form sentences is very important the formative years.
Up until about eight years old determines much of that.
Well I mean I can say from my personal experience that I had my life up until the age of ten you know mindless consumerism play video games go to McDonald's.
And then I got shipped off some other country where the situation was drastically different and I know that the outcome of who I am as an adult is completely different.
So even though I had a certain character that was baked into me from a young age being shipped off somewhere else completely reformed you know the outcome.
So perhaps there's something to be said for the fact that I don't I don't want to call it trauma.
But you can still beat something into shape as long as it's malleable.
Right and what happens if that trauma is in a negative sense in a destructive sense where causes the person to shut down and up let's say until you mention the age of ten let's use that.
So they would not adapt very well.
So let's just bounce it back to her from a personal aspect you're probably not beaten down and how would you say when you make someone feel bad all the time.
What is that called?
Abuse where abuse will know where it makes the people shut down.
There are senses and then they become hard.
So if that happens up until the formative years or so they will have a hard time adapting unless it's met by other trauma.
I mean again this is the how the spirit works and of course you know if we ever do sonics on the spiritual realm there's answers for all of that.
Yes indeed that is something altogether different and esoteric to most people.
Right because most people are comfortable with their lives as long as they're literate enough to use the television remote.
Because before you continue on any subject you know the person always thinks some modern people especially is this something I saw on TV.
You said something before about how the ancient rites don't really differentiate between smart or non smart people but more the wise and the fools.
So I'm just going to use loose language and I'll let you sort of fill in the blanks because I just think that the rhetoric works well for you know the secular nature of the theme.
What differentiates an intelligent person from an unintelligent person or if you want to say a smart person from a stupid person.
Where does that line go and if you want to say a wise person from a fool then we'll use that distinction as well but on one hand you have this aspect of people that know and even if they don't know they can come into knowing or learning and then you have people who cannot and I wanted to sort of explore what the difference is fundamentally between those two.
Well there's this spiritual side again we've discussed cosmic censorship you know if you're if it's not meant for you know why is it not meant is is a whole other aspect but if it's not meant for someone to see something they will not see it.
And if it's meant for someone to see something they will see it so it's the cosmic censorship right the those that learn and those that don't learn even though they have the same experiences again it's very personal.
I have four of my viewers have much to do with it there's the cosmic censorship the spiritual aspect of it and filling in.
You know what wisdom is and what a fool is is is very simple on its face but complex nonetheless because if we look at certain there's a certain figure that was known to be the wisest in the world in the past but yet as we come to the end of their story they had done things that were very foolish right.
But we had never seen any fool rise to any prominence where we were given much information about them and then they had become wise so it's a it's an entropic situation in other words you can be wise and be subject to foolishness but it's if you're a fool you're pretty much finished.
That's a bit harsh but yes well life is harsh have you gone camping lately have you been out on the ocean lately we gone to a mountaintop lately have you gone to the desert lately have you been in the city lately it's harsh wherever you go.
You've also said in the past that when a person decides to apply themselves to learning something they have to be able to approach things with the sort of child like curiosity which is not the same thing as being child like or naive or impulsive but rather you're a mature person who can exhibit the attributes of a child's curiosity.
What is the value in that and what makes it that some people are capable of such curiosity and others aren't.
Well I think the child like aspect is not literal but metaphorical meaning that you're new and you're not bringing presuppositions and pre form pre molded you know BS that you would as an adult as a functioning again an esteemed functioning adult in any modern western society especially or even eastern society has is completely formed and molded with with the BS let's put out by the central system.
And by the way we've been mentioning a lot of these things in a most people especially those that are weak minded will take it in a negative light the Greeks to negative i would suggest that it yes this is this is objective speaking you may not be used to it but i would suggest that it is a testament to the robustness and durability of the human body and the human spirit.
So yes you are so you if not succumb succumb meaning you can't you know continue anymore or recover but if you are constantly immersed in a society that is a falsehoods and maladies beware and be aware that it is a testament a proof on a how robust the human spirit and the human body is.
We're living in a world where people have sort of become accustomed I think to hearing meaninglessness or meaningless things and so they live with the sort of expectation that words have little meaning because they've heard it all before and the example that comes to mind for me is when a parent instructs their teenage children but instead of being mindful of how they communicate they just use cheap platitudes and cliches like stay in school or you won't get a job.
Meanwhile the next or teenager who dropped out of school to buy and sell you know sneakers or something he makes ten grand a month but the first kids parents have nothing to say about that just stay in school.
So even though they're urgently trying to convey something it's actually the urgency that repels the children because the rhetoric commands no respect so that leads me to ask what does it take to get people to listen to good instruction how do you make somebody listen as opposed to doing things their way.
That's a very difficult question and I wouldn't be optimistic and most people will hear but not listen right they'll they'll just turn their senses their ear towards what sounds are being made but they actually lack the comprehension to listen because they don't know what you're saying anyway.
And you mentioned the parents aspect here's the shameful aspect about being human is that it is very well known that when humans are subject to stressful environment or something let's a impeding dangerous environment they their reproduction rate tends to drop proof of that is that when the woman menstrual cycle stops.
Usually when they're under stress so if you have a rightful observation of the conditions of society on earth and to see that people are still becoming parents shows you that they're completely deceived and don't know what's going on the fully into the propaganda you know the happy be lucky kind of thing.
So and if it even if it goes down to food clothing and shelter well they have poison air poison water poison houses poison food not full on poison.
That has a that in a mortal sense but toxic toxic and they're still procreating so you brought up the the you know an alarm went off when I heard parents it's shameful to see that there are still parents.
And you know and here's the interesting aspect anyone who was raised in the 60s and 70s or 50s even later will remember striking and boycotting there is none of that anymore because you're finished as a society.
You know there is no consent there's no in other words if everyone is consenting all the time is there any consent.
No there just mindless idiots or slaves or automotrons it just means they're totally unaware of what's going on right in as far as listening or getting people to listen.
I find that that's a skill like let's take the Greek for example for whatever reason you have a quality of making people want to listen to you it doesn't mean that they're going to take your advice or that they're going to follow your example but you have a quality that draws somebody in because they discern that what is being said is person.
And now it could be something as seemingly trivial as the tone of your voice that makes that creates that effect but there is an art and a skill and an in a talent sometimes in getting people to just shut up and listen because they recognize that something important is being said.
And I'm just trying to examine like to what extent can that be learned so that you can put that into practice.
Oh that the public speaking or how to communicate is is is another discussion and I think it's it goes into the realm of personality there are some people.
For example if anyone has ever heard someone that they just can't listen to and other people can so again it's the personal subject of aspect is very subjective.
I think there's the manipulative art of public speaking as well you know yes like I just it's very easy to establish that people want to be manipulated simply because institutions and things to manipulate them exist if they didn't want to be manipulated those things could not exist because those things exist to accommodate them.
So there are ways of understanding again based on the culture how to get through to a person there's a psychology on that all the way from the sales the salesman that are taught on how to deal with the human mind.
But the whole thing again you're going to anyone has to make a determination are you going are you going to do something because you have invested the desire to have an effect or are you going to do it because it's the right thing to do you have to say it so maybe later on you can't be held accountable for having known something and not sharing it right.
Personally I say I speak because I don't want to ever be pulled aside later and said well you knew these things and didn't say anything.
To believe that you will have any effect on anyone or on any any capacity is like someone coming to you with a car that needs to be scrapped and saying well I need some touch up paint.
What are you talking about it needs to go to the garbage heap right.
Let's move on to the concept of teaching and look at the role played by those who have taken it upon themselves to educate others.
What does it take to be an effective teacher particularly having to teach in a world where many people are subject to a sort of defined spirit of wanting to do things their way.
Well here's the interesting thing and even from a personal aspect if I find that I master something I'm not looking for a student I'm looking for a teacher.
It harkens back to the concept do you teach do you give a man fish or do you teach him how to fish.
Well when you're teaching him how to fish in order to for him to be a successful student you be a successful teacher he must take on the mindset of the teacher.
So in the beginning of course when someone is fresh and learning something they always consider themselves to be a student but if you're going to have an equivalent amount of information transferred from one aspect or one being to another they must be equivalent.
In other words you can't put a leader of water that comes out of a leader container into a half leader container.
It also must be a leader so in essence every student must also be a teacher or be able to encompass the aspects of the teacher and let's just interject one more thing.
When you take the role of a teacher or in other words you're imparting something from an authoritative position the while that in part that information is being imparted what should be incrementally involved is the question to who you're imparting to let's say the student.
Will you be able to teach this also and that's that's what I call technical access like for example given example weather work.
We've been shown by William Reich Trevor James Constable and maybe a few others that the weather can be controlled locally and and let's say on a larger scale and it's not this shamanistic principle that is you know like you hear of ancient legends certain profits or shaman can do it.
Because if you're like that then when you die it goes with you but if you can technically access any in show someone how to do it.
Once they learn there's no reason why they shouldn't be able to show someone else and so on.
So that's where I think it's an equivalent factor you know like both sides of the equal sign on an equation should should be equivalent.
Right I believe that the concept of teacher student again is overly enforced by the modern mushroom people system.
But I do think that what you're talking about is more of what it takes to be a good student.
I think that what you're saying is that in order to be a good student you have to have the capacity to be a teacher but what does it take to be a good teacher.
Well can you have a successful download right is is a good student and can you upload something is a good teacher I'm using the digital age technology for a bitch there.
So what does it take let's say let's just think of computers and all that stuff even if most people now are more computer literate than they were let's say 10 years ago so giving this metaphor might be good.
If you're going to upload something to the internet what does it take to be successful. Basically is the question if you can answer that whatever capacity that's what it takes to be a good teacher.
And if you are in the internet and you want to download something off of the internet what does it take to do that is is also a metaphor what it takes to be a good student.
I certainly hope that those are just empty metaphors that are colorful because I feel like most people will get that well I can have to think about that and that's a you know that's something that they're not used to doing.
Well we could do a quick rehash if you're going to upload something to the internet it's a basically your hardware and the wiring connectivity right connectivity right it could be wireless right and the equipment must be in certain good order and also you don't want to you want to be able to back it up right.
Because if everything crashes at the moment you want to be able to retrieve it right so it's where notes takes play you know memorialization of some sort you know when you back up your hard drive your memorializing it in essence aren't you.
So you know the that metaphor I think is pretty close now I want to bring up something else too because in terms of teaching and learning there's an esoteric side of you heard of that urban myth thing called the hundredth monkey where just to recap some adventurous scientists went to an island and they showed some monkeys how to wash potatoes.
That they were eating full of sand and then they found after a while that all the non connected islands all the monkeys even though they had not been shown us were doing it on their own so there's like some kind of telepathic super highway that connects you know in you know things that are ingenious to people right you know telepathically well you know that that is always used in a positive light right that oh look you know you know a good thing is not going to be a good thing.
You know a good things you know ingenious things can be conveyed even though there's no contact but no one ever looks at the antithesis of that what if you dumb down one of the one a few of the monkeys on the island then does it does that dumbing down you know if you turn to month you know a moron and level in the monkey society with that spread.
And is it always that the ingenious side spreads and not the more not the dumbing down or the more the you know the idiocy spreading and you notice that's never been considered so when I think of the hundredth monkey my mind doesn't go necessarily to the subject of aspect look how wonderful that is I say oh that could be dangerous because if you can make them smarter by just affecting a few you can make them dumber also by just affecting a few and I think that holds more true in modern society than ever.
I think one of the responsibilities of a teacher is to help bring erroneous beliefs to a conclusion so that people can dispel them so a teacher should highlight and explain what's wrong with the fallacy and not just scoring it the way that a lot of adults more realistically do like oh you know this is bad don't do this or only bad people do that which is kind of infantile but sometimes even when you explain something at the level of a fifth grader people don't get it.
Or they hear you but then they I click the don't hear you so that they can continue living their regular lives so where would you say that the line goes between making a solid explanation to edify somebody and sort of throwing pearl after swine to people who can't discern the value of it anyway.
Well the answer to that is you don't want to do things by chance right first of all second of all you're going to have to learn to employ a level of efficiency right without going into a chance too much because you can't start discussing it with everyone all the time let's say you know you're going to run out of time and effort and or you will become embittered because you most people have a chance to do it.
Most people have the idea that they can convey things to the majority of the people and maybe if you won't get it but I suggest it's the other way around there's some people in history that have been trying to convey wonderful things to the majority and didn't even have a small majority react.
You know the in other words where you can put out information to millions of people and like one or two will get it right.
So this is just you know you have to make an objective determination where are you when on when are you and who are you right this is planet earth what do you know about planet earth.
Again I don't not take it out into the fantasy aspect of science fiction but I like the concept of the various societies provided by like the rotten berry series of star track.
You know it seems like there's almost an infinite number of societies you can run into and how do you classify them well how would you classify being on earth at this time.
You know that is the most objective way to do it and again just to go back to it I said before the good news is it's a planet full of morons that is the reality of it it doesn't sound good I'm not expecting anyone to agree and say I like what he just said.
But that's the reality of it again you got here something I'll lean on I'll lean on this from a secular point of view secular point of view you know you could look at all the illuminati conspiracies or whatever on the internet by the way any conspiratorial secretive stuff you see on the internet that you think is bad the realities ten times worse so don't feel bad.
By what you're reading because it's really much worse. Okay they want to reduce the plan is you know like they put it I like I mentioned earlier 1984 and brave new world was commissioned work actually.
It's pretty clearly known well known that the secular agenda political scientific judicial whatever religious agenda is to reduce the earth's population down to less than 10% of the existing one right now.
Okay the good news is that is clearly supported by all of your ancient rites whether you're looking at all of your major religions are supposed to have a book attached to them which none of them know anything in those books anyway but if you look at the ancient rites they also support that.
So we know one thing is going to happen for sure the majority of what you see a society now is it is will not exist in the future right and I'm not it's not a week from now or a month or from now or a year from now.
And I've discussed the specifics on that so you always have to keep that in mind is it a happy go lucky let's go let's go you know all learn something new and hold hands in a circle and sink who buy you know.
Because it's not going to be very long lasting.
There are a few things that are going to be longer lasting but unfortunately most people don't know what those things are.
So there's no sense in bringing them up but the aspect of this fact right does not mean you should be worried or debt in desperation about it it should mean that you're bold that you're efficient efficient meaning that when you hear about doom and gloom in next week or next month ignore it because it's not going to happen as it's been shown in the past.
And the major things that will cause social change that will quote unquote enlightened and put people in a dark state in since the subject is education will not be shown prior they're always going to be coming on the scene as a surprise.
So what does that mean well be prepared for surprises you know there's something called intuition intuitive or not intuitive would be the opposite counter intuitive would be the opposite.
Like once you become objective looking at what's put out in the world as science medicine judicial religion it becomes completely counter intuitive and they tell you what it really is when you question you know the authorities that it's nonsense they do tell you it's nonsense right it personally but on a grand level they tell you it's you know it's a steadfast reality.
Let's keep it going with the teaching aspect of things you had once said to me that when a person wants to master a certain subject they have two options essentially they can either try to reinvent the wheel by spending X amount of years to learn something that other people already know and has already been demonstrated or they can just find some learned person to study under who can communicate to them in some short period of time what it would have taken them years to learn.
And then because you pointed that out to me I put a certain quote on Greek speak dot com in the quote rotator which says where have all the masters gone so when you read about ancient civilizations where there's classical Greece or even ancient Persia there's always an emphasis on a sort of philosophical and sometimes priestly class of learned it man who essentially can put their money where their mouth is when crunch time comes so not you know academia who blow the it about nonsense but you know for example you have the stoics or you have the major or you have the Pythagorean.
Who attracted a following because they had leaders who knew enough of a certain subject to showcase high level performance in it right in such a way that you know the social or political landscape could change when they took action what has happened to that kind of mastery that you know makes regular people want to go out and follow people like that I don't see a lot of masters at work in that sort of way anymore well actually they does exist master clownmanship.
If you look at your religious leaders political leaders judicial leaders legal leaders medical leaders military leaders that's all clownmanship their clowns they're there to entertain and have a certain amount of they don't have a personal charisma to do it on their own they need the entire system to back them up the education system the media and all the institutions in place that so in essence that is what's left of the master's.
What's left of the mastery now it so in a sense are they really masters now because they need the the impulse of systems around them so in a sense that's the only way that the masses interact with master ship is the master deceivers the master clowns whatever you know even when you go look at all the institutions today let's say you look at the medical institutions universities or the labs are just its clownmanship there's nothing there the scientist the astrophysic is their clowns.
The religious I mean the all your religious leaders are clowns down to the local clergy so they have mastered that the art of deception the art of controlling the group.
And and it's mastered in a way where you they've oversimplified and used people's feelings so you know when most people say they think they they don't know what that is they actually mean what they feel they don't know what thinking is so the master.
Of manipulation of the feelings of the people because if you were to figure out objectively how many people are left on the planet that can think you can probably count them on just a few hands they're very few people just if I would say without getting myself and trouble later maybe a few thousand people on the entire planet that's pretty accurate most people are by feeling so the only master ship that you see overtly is controlling the feelings and emotions.
And the feelings and emotions of people right.
That now the true master ship where you start to have let's say the development of you know technical development of how the human body works the study of the ancient rits.
And the what they call the sciences and things to develop society they're all underground and they're working on their own in very very small groups or factions very and to say that they're complete thinkers is also a misnomer they've they most of these masters that are left have also been
by the by the lack of virtue and morality that you see in society today I can give you many examples of people that I think are a master in one particular field but they're not really masters.
You know because they'll you'll you'll you know I'll look at them and say wow they're really well in doubt in this particular field but then they talk about oh how there's a national debt and they don't know that there's no money they haven't figured that out yet right.
So the true master ship I think they're done I have not encountered any that I can say I think they're all finished and if there are the out there I'm sure there might be very few I have not encountered any.
Oh that's the same also being a good point with some masters but all well.
It's not the age of that that you have to understand where you are it's earth and the the the latent powers that exists find anyone with true master ship as being their true enemy right.
So I want some read a quote that was attributed to Socrates but I can confirm where it actually came from in the internet says Socrates but anyway mankind is made up of two kinds of people wise people who know that their fools and fools who think that they're wise.
And I think that that's improved for thought and it ties quite well into the one of the key morals of the story of Socrates which is that people think that they know but they don't know and that makes them fools but they don't know that their fools and so they remain blinded by their own folly.
So my question is is there a way for an enlightened person to show a fool that he's a fool and if so what is the most effective way to do that as somebody that's trying to teach that.
All right well considering the the fool aspect it's a matter of efficiency let's say Mark Twain said that it's easier to fool someone than to convince them that they've been fooled.
Okay so the in other words it's more efficient to condone let's say to support foolishness and keep people foolish it's far more far less energy than to get them out of that foolery for foolishness.
So if you're going to let's say be efficient with your time and your energy you would avoid the entire premise.
It doesn't mean that a fool can't provide something that is necessary for food clothing and shelter but don't go deep into their folly.
No we're not suggesting that you would go deep into their folly but essentially what you're saying is that there is no hope for the fool. The fool is to be scorned and rebuked and really nothing else is what you're saying.
If you're if you're going to operate in high efficiency absolutely there is no there to be avoided it's even in in ancient rites but if you don't mind investing a tremendous amount of time for very little return then go for it deal with them.
Attorneys are a great example anyone that has legal issues if you want to go deal with attorneys yeah it's the fool on both sides right you're going to fools.
You know most there is a small group of attorneys that know what's going on that it's completely there to you know it's even the smaller group of attorneys that know that they represent the evil forces in the lower you know greater group.
So you know they're there to enrich themselves in control society and then the rest of the 90% are just fools they actually think they're doing the right thing and they don't have enough sense to see that they never were educated in law in the first place.
That's a good example doctors or another one same percentage the upper upper tier of doctors are spirit satan is basically spiritually they know that they represent the dark forces of the universe.
And then the ones below that are know that they're doing it to enrich themselves then the 90% group doesn't know anything that don't you just follow directions and whatever they're told to do so again you deal with them you're dealing with just a whole sale objective way to show how that's just foolishness.
So what do you do well you better learn law and you better learn how to how the human body works right.
Because you're not going to get anything from those morons or fools you know attorneys and doctors.
Let's wrap up the stream with this there's a sense I think that everything that you could ever want to know about most subjects has already been said over the past 2 to 3,000 years the Greeks touched on that quite a bit.
Whether you have to go dig up library archives or study ancient history or travel to certain sites in foreign countries to uncover specific information that's on you but the relevant information exists.
However most people don't have the bandwidth or the way with all to uncover everything about everything and they don't have a master to teach them the basics of what's in front of them even.
So when your average person comes to the realization that he has to redirect his focus from mindless consumerism to something more edifying what would the Greeks say that he should focus on to teach himself these things.
Oh wow well on a personal level basically you're going to have to learn what morality and law is and that's basically it and try to try to follow a lawful life what's the right thing to do for humans on the earth at this time to do.
And then that doesn't come from a legal society or your political body and or your preacher by the way or e-mama or rabbi talk about more clowns.
So you're going to find out things when you ask questions about what is moral and what is lawful you'll find out that no one around you knows anything about those things.
So finding out that no one around you knows anything about anything is a start.
That's actually not a bad answer.
I can see that.
Well I think we're going to have to wrap up I think a lot of things have been said.
Okay is there anything else you want to touch on Greek before we conclude?
Not at the moment I think we'll have to continue this mindset a little bit further as the future goes on.
Okay. Yeah well thank you to everybody who tuned into this episode.
It's been enjoyable once again and I hope that we'll be doing it sometime soon.
So thanks again for listening.
[Music]