[Music]
Greetings to everyone listening. This is the Greek Speak podcast featuring the
Archon in the Greek. I'm the Archon creator of GreekSpeak.com. We've reached
episode five of this series of talks between the Greek and myself which marks
the halfway point of this season of streams and I'm glad that we finally got
in here as the series is dragged on a bit longer than I thought it would but
there's been a lot going on that has slowed things down but I anticipate we'll
certainly be done by the end of the year. I say that fully in earnest but
half-in-gest but we'll see how things go. So the live stream group chat is always
open for those who want to ask questions during the stream and
GreekSpeak.com continues to have no political religious or commercial
affiliations since this is a project that is solely run and funded by myself
and that's it for the introduction. I hope you guys enjoy the rest of the show
and thanks again for listening.
Hi there Greek you there? Yes greetings. I'm here. All right what are we going to
talk about today or speak on? Well today we're going to look at the topic of
media which is obviously wide-ranging in its themes but we'll try to cover the
most salient points and perhaps shed some light on some of the less talked about
aspects of how that sphere works. So in the broadest terms media is generally
broken down into mainstream and alternative and so for ease of use purposes I
think we'll use that categorization and start with the first one. Does that sound
good to you? Yeah it works. Cool. So when we talk about an enforced condition of
universal ignorance or lack of comprehension that we call cosmic censorship I
think that's something that seems closely tied to the proliferation of mass
media and I think it's more than just keeping people ignorant but also you feed
them lies and you teach them how to love their lies and so the media sort of ends
up becoming a stage on which journalists and entertainers perform fictions,
scripted fictions. As somebody who was around for the mid to late 20th century at
what point did you start to realize that that might be the case? You know I always
had a sense that it could not be trusted even as a child very simply you know
sitting in front of a black and white TV in the late 60s or so seeing a
commercial television commercial for a breakfast cereal and as you know it's
being promoted as being good tasting let's say and then going out and actually
getting that breakfast cereal and finding out that it was not good tasting was
was the one of the initial ways I know this sounds very rudimentary and primitive
was one of the initial ways of letting me know that the media can't be trusted
and if you just think about what I just said it is something that needs to be
paid attention to you know can they be trusted right and how did I mean how did
that unfold from breakfast cereal as a child into things that you would have seen as
a teenager or a young adult? Well ultimately you know I would say being mid
century beyond mid century you know born in that this kind of a world where I
think television came before both you and I were born so did radio and newspaper
and most other you know forms of media were born into it so there's no way we can
actually you know discreetly separate it from our existence meaning you know our
perceptual existence so it leads into you know something that is you know
something that's a part of your life and to actually market as with a sense of
distrust is no different than marking let's say one's community parents family or
friends with a level of distrust or authority with a level of distrust religion
with a level a certain level of distrust academia with a certain level of
distrust you see what I'm going with this in other words you can say buyer be
where caveat emptor and in a sense you know you are buying this stuff it's being sold
to you right so I would sense that a healthy level of distrust is what would be
let's say a good foot to start off on once you start sharpening your perception
and as far as you know the time period still though like were there any landmark
programs other like you put aside commercials and sort of generalities like that
but were there any landmark programs that made you realize that in fact this is
not your friend and something that shouldn't be trusted or could be antagonistic
you know what's interesting on that is you could look at it from a cultural
point of view that's the main thing that programming whether it's in print radio
or visual you know video has to be in accord with the traditions and values and
culture that it's being shown to and what's interesting enough being of a
multicultural meaning a born in American but a Greek descent I saw that the I was
able to see clearly through the heavy promotion of white middle America as not
being something that I want to associate with if you know what I mean
you know the white middle American culture is very different from the European
culture in many aspects right so especially when it comes to food and the way you
you know perceive basic things like food shelter clothing things like that
right so that right away showed me that it's possible that when you do look at
something like the media with objectively or from another point of view from a
different culture you'll see that it's it's basically a selling game or something
to accommodate the the majority but well I think we'll touch we'll touch on that
dynamic a bit later because certainly there's something to be said for how the
audience is react to to what the media does but could you contrast a bit 20th
century media to say 21st century media aside from the technological changes
brought on by computing what has been this cultural shifts that you seem to be
alluding to well you can't really change it in other words you mean you can't say
that there's going to be change without taking the technology into account so
the way the media changes is with technology you can look at historically first
it was oral and then it was oral and written and then it became oral written
and oral again through what's called transmission means the radio and then it
was again oral written transmission through audio and video which is also written
because you will see labels and writing and titles and things like that right so
basically capturing the the the message in with different types of technology does
change it I mean are we then going to insinuate that if the technology of let's say
FM radio had generally remained the same and television as well and say we hadn't
had laptops and smartphones that the media would still look the way it did 40 years
ago as far as the presentation of it well yes and no again the culture is
changing there's a agenda is in the culture to change the culture you know the
way people perceive reality and if anyone disagrees with that you have to
give it to them in braille because they're clearly blind you know there's clearly
an unseen hand that has agendas that are rolled out over 50 and a hundred year
periods and obviously that is part of the change you know I give a quick
example and by the way I don't think we need to touch on the the aspect of the
technology of the internet because that just brings everything much faster but
an example of the the agenda is the gender bending idea right where you can
choose your gender now that's been in place for thousands of years in certain
ritualistic rights and it was also put in place by the power elite in the late
60s as an agenda that should take hold by the 90s there are a little behind
schedule there are many other agendas that you see if you're aware of them you know
climate climate change you know whether you know man's effect on the planet
things like that which is actually minimal you'll see that the the messages
that have been planned out are played out through the media yeah I'm aware of what
you're referring to I also remember from last stream you spoke a bit about how
sometimes the intentions behind an age get expressed through entertainment or
literature and the example that you gave before was like George Orwell or
Alder Sucksley that their books are examples of that something that was either
commissioned or demanded or nudged into existence personally I think of a
movie I forget the year but the 80s movie was that they live right right I'm more
modern modern example what did you think about the 1976 movie network I think
that's another example of that do you think that that fits into that sort of
pressiant far-sighted category sure sure I would suggest there's a more
disclosure than people want to admit you know there's an old thing that they
say that they they being the the the power base that runs the planet earth ink or
one-world corporation let's say they have to tell you what they're going to do
before they do it that's part of their credo and they whether it's done very
secretively or encode up in the open it's it's still being done so that the
the film network I think includes some of that go and just to harken back to the
they live glasses if you had those now you wouldn't see them as aliens you would
see most people as little piggies oink oink but anyway that's another discrete
comment that could be expanded on later you'll see pigs goats and dogs no I think
that I think that is worth expanding but yeah maybe later the traditional idea
I think is that news is the manifestation of journalistic work done by people
whose job it is to mediate some kind of civil order by keeping the public informed
but in recent times because of how blatant the news has become its lies and it's
easy to go on youtube and google any outlet and put lies at the end of the search
term and you'll see that there's a lot that's been said about that because of
things like that many people have come to become disillusioned about the position
of the media and see them perhaps is more of a circus act that distracts more
than they inform but was there ever a time when the mainstream media was an
effective watchdog of the public interest because one would think that something
can move from a position of being virtuous to being less virtuous or esteemed
rather than having started out as something that was objectionable never in the
mainstream throughout entire history of mankind has it been has that had any
honor or dignity you can go back to what people call biblical times it was the
same it was all crap the the underground aspects of it you know what's called
let's say alternative in an altruistic way that did exist at some points but
had no effect just like it is today there the you know the the actual alternative
things that people can get on the internet that makes sense are actually truthful
if not entirely but mostly true have no effect on on the reality of the the
mainstream point of view of things is that something that we can back up with
say some more facts because yes fine to say that but you sure I can give you
discrete examples like for example let's just go to the internet would have been
and what made aware of for more than a decade and then someone more recently all
name names and people could actually look at this stuff if they want to give you
example one of them regarding the 9/11 event is Demetriak Hallisov he whether
you believe his credentials are not as not as relevant as taking a look at his
accounts and what really happened to the towers on 9/11 and he backs it up with
as much technical information as you'd like and actual you know good perceptive
reality that's easily discerned and unnotenable yet he gets there is a quote-unquote
9/11 truth movement that doesn't acknowledge him and if there is it's minimal
and just to compound that the the the American government did something called
an investigation which means when a government says they're going to
investigate something means they're going to do the opposite but anyway the one
of the chair people of the 9/11 commission publicly it's even on the Wikipedia
page for the 9/11 commission stated that the information in that investigation is
not factual or true nor does it reflect what really happened that day okay another
one is I think I've gotten a message to him and he didn't like it was a
fellow named Cody Snaudgris so SNOD GRES he's been making rounds the past two
years giving testimony that he was offered a a million US dollars to blow up the
Murrow building you know as a CIA asset you know not working directly for the CIA
but like a contractor right and his testimony is very valid and very solid
but I had messaged him I said you know your testimony is great but you know you have an
audience of morons basically you know this is whether they're American morons or
worldwide morons no one cares about this is nothing's going to come of it and of
course the response was not positive to that but obviously it's true right so
again it contradicts the government story and which again is is admitted
through investigations that it's not how it's been told so here we have two
quote-unquote whistleblowers let's call them with very good testimony that can be
comparatively analyzed within each subject one being the Alfred R Murrow building
Oklahoma City and the other one being the 9/11 disaster let's call it that and no one really cares
and it's on the internet and it's easy to access right and not only that it's not even being
promoted as a body of work or a testimony that should be looked at or considered
right so I mean there are many more examples on that you know there's a movie called
Vaxed regarding the negative effects of vaccination and even the agencies and authorities that
promote vaccination say we've never really done any substantial scientific tests or that there's
any proof that vaccinations are viable in preventing disease you see but we do know that they're very toxic
so I mean you can go on there's hundreds of subjects you can cover in this way that you know the
the information or testimony that's given through what's called the media is pretty much
rock solid but it's being ignored or not considered hmm I follow what you're saying and a lot of that
does seem to pertain to a more modern landscape of manipulating the public in a certain way
but what you're essentially saying before is that that pertains to an even greater swath of
human history so what I'm trying to see is that if we go back to ancient times why would we presume
that that was the case then I mean obviously what was then has led to what is now so there has to be
a red thread that runs through all of it but are we going to discount you know the philosophical
schools the mystery schools the library societies of ancient times as well you could discount what's
being pervade as what those things are about or those schools are about yes meaning if you were to
pick up any of a Greek philosophy and read it in English it's not being translated accurately
regarding any religious for religious philosophy or religious text scientific text on and on
and on you know Tesla you know just the bounce around you know Tesla never worked with electromagnetism
maybe maybe a little bit when he was asked to build an AC motor but his research did not include
electromagnetism no one brings if you go to any university in the world they'll tell you electricity
is electromagnetic I know it sounds kind of strange to bring that up out of the blue like that but just
think about that for a minute what did he work with right a different form of electricity so when
you hear people talking about Tesla technology it's a bunch of rubbish because they you know because
they don't go and look at what Tesla wrote about hmm well if indeed it is the case that the the
the media is a joke from the ground up then isn't the term fake news and oxymoron meant to deflect
from how observed all the news is in fact or all the media is in fact then not just a certain segment of
it very much like a term they have the legal society has sovereign citizen how could you be a sovereign
in a citizen citizen is essentially a subject or a slave yeah it's it's it's all it's all a
form of dichotomy and paradox if you look at it that way I'm using the word paradox the way the ancient
Greeks did it which is it's not the way people say today it's basically something ridiculous so
George all in the comedian you know fire fighters fight fire and what a freedom fighters fight
that's funny you see yeah so so the essence of it is what do you know about the human society
wholesale and this planet from history on on to today would be the question you know there's
something here we'll just side skirt the media for a moment something called a right of passage right
like you're not considered in certain countries to be of a good standing let's say nationalist or
citizen unless you've served in the military and even better if you've served in a war and killed people
right another right of passage is academia you're not considered to be a viable worker or
respectable in society unless you have a college degree you see so but let's just to take the second one
in terms of right of passage if you let's say you could pick an academic subject astrophysics regular
physics chemistry history 99% of what they teach you in university is on the media and it's fake
what's the difference why do you need to go to university if they're teaching you the same BS that
you learn on the media by watching documentaries well one is the right of passage you have to pay to
get you know the you know the x amount of years and what they call credits and the ceremony
and what they call a diploma in other words if you are in let's say an avid a watcher of television
or on the internet regarding astrophysics right or you have a degree in astrophysics from the best
university you pretty much have the same BS but the person that's sitting at their armchair
can't say he's an astrophysicist because they'll ask him for a degree and but the guy who says he's
an astrophysicist and respected as such because he has a doctorate degree from a Ivy League university
right he knows the same stuff that's on television it's mostly BS you see so there's a difference
here between right of passage that gives you know humans people certain people in human society
the accolades or the respect where everyone kind of knows or has access to the same information
so what's interesting about the media is the BS or the the the falsehood and the fake stuff that's
on the media is exactly the same stuff that's in the universities right but very few very seldom
will you see someone saying well I've watched a thousand hours of astrophysics on television and
though they'll never be respected as someone who has a PhD in it even though it's the same information
and which is fake you see it's low-level garbage really so you know what what what it kind of does is
mix one scratch their head and say that this is basically a level of quality in in other words
humans have are are prefer a low level of quality within their existence and that's why they have
the media that they do or the education that they do or the religious traditions that they do or
on and on and on or the medicine that they think they have so basically the question to ask here is
why are humans so attracted to such a low-level quality existence well I think that part of the answer
would be that there is some kind of a pleasure there that's being offered alongside with the low
quality information or conditions because if it was painful I think people would run from it
well they lack reference for example the painful aspect I find personally many of the things
that people see as being normal is being painful right whether it's the way they eat the way they
keep their their their person the way they perceive things I find that to be very painful I mean
torture for me would be to be transplanted and live with a midwestern white American family
it was very specific Greek well speaking of this idea of the the sort of the masses or the audience
who consume the media there's this idea that the media is a behemoth that manipulates the masses
who are helpless before its influence but I would say that the general sense of reality is created
actually by both groups of people those who produce the media and those who consume it so
the audiences are not as passive as they're made out to be because they are allowing the lies in the
misrepresentation to go unchallenged and I think you've talked before and recently about accommodating
the audience so to speak and that leads me to wonder and to ask which of those two things come first
the media creators with no regard for the masses or the sheeple audience with no regard for their
own well-being well it's very simple here I'll give you an example back in the 80s I knew someone
who was really good at writing you know what's called rap songs hip-hop songs right and we were
standing around one night in the Soho area Manhattan before it was developed and sort of like a
limousine open opens his doors and there's a bunch of older men standing around and the guy is doing
some freestyle rapping and they pull them aside and they said why don't you hang with us and we'll make
a lot of money together these these older you know I would say more Ashkenazi type in their 60s
upper middle class men or wealthy men have no interest in developing rap music
right but they know that if they accommodate those that are interested in that they'll be wealthy
do you see the point yeah yeah so I would suggest that anything that you see in mass is there to
accommodate the masses and this is the beef that I have with what's called the alternative media on
the internet is that they're always putting out this spouting altruistic verbosity about we need to
do this to make America better or the world better or humanity better and they're full of crap
better for who did they ever stop and think that the people actually like that like being this way
take for example the film the matrix where one of the characters the main characters is tied
down to a chair and the one of the agents of the matrix says to him well we had a perfect
environment for you but you you you couldn't prosper in it you needed the the destruction the chaos
the violence the vialness right in order to feel normal more furious I think was tied down yeah
Lawrence Fisprin but anyway I think that ultimately making the world a better place was to do a
reset you have to start all over and this by the way is in all of the ancient rites and prophecies
and philosophies so didn't you want to say that well maybe not on on a stream but I think I've heard
you say that news corporations at their heart you know behind the smoke in the mirrors and if you
go into the actual legal departments and you know the high level parts of the corporation they will
consider themselves as entertainment companies first and if you put your feet to the fire and you
make them sweat they'll say well we're just we're not really trying to educate people but we're
here to provide entertainment but they're hiding behind the plausible deniability of being news
companies can you explain on that a bit sure there are precedent cases in there you know the kangaroo
courts what you call federal courts or state courts or whatever someone had prosecuted fox news
regarding libel and the case outcome was that well they're an entertainment company
right the news is entertainment but yet they take it seriously like for example if if you've got
more than two sharp and pencils in your pocket go back to the 9/11 event you know only the people
on television witnessed airplanes going into the into the buildings and of course they have some
plants on the ground that say they saw airplanes going to the buildings but the public at large
never saw any airplanes I personally had spoken to someone a month later who was crossing
headwalks to work by crossing the Brooklyn bridge and wasn't was doing a project in that area and he
saw the building explode he said there were no airplanes he didn't see an airplane if there was
he didn't see it and there's no way he wouldn't have seen it because he had a vantage of three
sides of the building you see and also there's a lot of testimony on that and if you do a little
bit of research you'll find that there's a company that puts these visual effects in sports games
you know like you know you'll see an advertisement on the field or something it's a video effect
right and this particular company was heavily involved in making sure airplanes were on TV if you
know what I mean and they were granted later on the ability to get big lucrative contracts
with sports you know with television shows that play sports you know if you've ever watched
an American sports game you'll show an advertisement or movement on the field that doesn't exist it's
only a video effect so you know you you have this reality being totally twisted you know
from I don't know something that is tragic and as disastrous as 9/11 as being put together by
entertainment groups I mean think about it right and just for most people if you whether you know it
or not believe it or not or whatever it's irrelevant 9/11 was a nuclear event right it was a
nuclear event so meaning atomic thermonuclear so what I mean by that is being a disaster it is
disastrous to have a nuclear event in a main city like that and have it covered up by entertainment
interests such as the news and investigative reports and other companies that allowed that
visual effect and persuading the public that it was you know whatever I recently came across a
quote about the nature of the media I don't remember who said it but it reads something like this
that exaggeration is every sense as essential to a newspaper writing as the writing itself
because the point is to make as much as possible about any occurrence so that essentially all
that newspaper writers are for the sake of their trade is to be alarmists right and that's their
way of making themselves interesting so when I think about that a bit it leads me to wonder what is
the alternative to landscape driven by commerce as far as the media where being alarmist is sort of
essential well if you're going to write something to simply edify you better try to keep it a secret
because eventually if the subject to matter or the body of work that is written to edify is
broad enough you're going to be stepping on a lot of toes that would want the contrary to being
public view do you see what I mean by that but by doing so who is it exactly that you're making an
enemy of in that situation well you know like I said earlier it's earth ink or the one-world
corporation right let's just bring it down to a national level there's certain countries today
that have in their policy that certain ideologies are to be stamped out and not allowed
so imagine that on a global level it could even be you could even be on a local level certain
municipalities do not allow certain ideologies or actions to take place right at all very strict
against it for example imagine that on a on a global level it's very difficult people to imagine
even though it's a very simple concept that the entire planet is controlled by a small business
interest I mean you could fit them all in a nice size or living room and they pretty much run the
planet but they run it in a subtle way and they've been granted that from cosmic forces until the time
for them not to to do it anymore it comes which is not which is almost around the corner or so
and so in a world where establishment media and technology corporations control the public realm
in the way that you just described I think people end up running into a lot of dead ends when
they're trying to get answers they start to realize that a lot of the promises offered up by
their society are pipe dreams and what you're what they're left with is more of a zombified consumer
existence than anything else and then when they try to escape that by turning to either alternative
media or things like the wellness movement that borrows a lot from eastern traditions they do it
with the same lack of discernment that they apply to the mainstream media and so ultimately when
something like yoga becomes mainstream they're back where they're started being fed a water
down version of something whose true meaning has been cast aside have you been able to discern a
way to escape that kind of dynamic where the media seems to continually encroach on everything
that there is to make it as dumb down as possible well just use a broad brush over anything that's
in the media as a lie let's say you brought up the yoga idea let's say that's in the media for
whatever reason positive or negative if you have an interest a personal interest in yoga then
then you go back and use the standard forms of discernment on the subject which the first thing is
where to learn the history of it where did it start who started it and why go back as far as
you can and and then make sure the information you're getting is somewhat contrary to what's the
what the public perceives and you're probably closer to the truth and just to reexamine that word
probably go back and see how valid and how much verification you could have on the history of the
thing right and any all the subjects are the same so essentially what you see in the media is just
a 180 of what it actually is that's the safest thing to perceive the the there's an old saying in
this in the Soviet Union that people were interested in buying the the newspaper probda which
which means the truth if translated to English and they said well why is everyone so interested in
the newspapers as well because we are interested in what's in the newspaper because whatever the
newspaper says it's a hundred what's really going on is a 180 from it so once you have that
diametric opposition established you you do get the truth from watching the fake news or the
mainstream media right all you have to all you have to do is apply that it's diametric or or
inverse of what they're telling you and you've got the truth it's like the simple but it's not
it's not as simply related here here's a simple way to look at it a baseball and a baseball bat
together cost a dollar ten right and the baseball bat costs a dollar more than the baseball how
much is the baseball cost right together the baseball and the baseball bat or a dollar ten
but the baseball cost a dollar more than the baseball so what's the price of the baseball most people
say ten cents well can't be if it's both a dollar ten because that means the baseball cost zero right
so what is it you have to do a little bit of algebra there again most people will say ten cents
because they take the hole and they subtract this a dollar more no because that means the baseball
then is it is zero no it's not zero see so how do you do that algebra it's very simple
and we don't know i'm not going to give the answer it's not come on just give the answer okay well it's
a simple you know a plus b equal c right and you just plug everything in and the
using common parlance well you'd say well if one is a dollar more than the other the total
is subtracted from that so if the total is a dollar ten and one is a dollar more than the other we
have ten cents left over and we divide that by two which is five cents so the baseball cost five
cents so let's look at it now in in the other way so the the bat is a dollar more than the baseball
which is a dollar five and the baseball cost five cents so a dollar five plus five cents equals a
dollar ten so you're you solved it and this is what you're sort of tying to the media right so it's
not exactly 180 you do have to use a little bit of algebra in other words they're going to give you
let's take 9/11 for example the buildings collapse because airplanes with diesel fuel crashed in it
well okay that's plausible but what buildings was it a chicken coop and outhouse a three-story
you know wood structure that's plot yeah that you know airplane crashing in that and diesel fuel
but not something that is robust as what we're being told and if you look at the aftermath
how can 200,000 tons of steel be reduced to 30-foot pile burning at the melting point of iron
underground so now you're going to have to figure out if both things cost a dollar ten and one is a
dollar more than the other you see this goes into again you can segue into what's the difference
between the media and the alternative media not much you know for example you know what I mean to
lead on here but I call the alternative media in many languages Latin languages papagayo which is
a parrot you know usually when I would be called into comment on things I'm like do you guys want
some crackers you know years ago and I was a little more popular in the alternative media let's see
what the Greek has to say I'm like why can't you make can't you look at the facts yourself you need
to tell me for me to tell you what to think like time magazine you know a lot of the popular American
magazines when you read their articles they're telling you how to think and what to think about it
and if you look today at the alternative media I assure you 99% of the time if not 100% of the time
on the internet they're always following they're trailing behind the mainstream like right now at
this time there's certain investigations with certain officials regarding pedophilia and the
president of the United States still and all this other stuff and all the alternative media is
just latching on to that no discernment on the reality of you know being a human on the planet yet
yeah I mean we're gonna touch a bit on the alt media as we as we go along but just to wrap up with
the mainstream aspect I think that there's something to be said for how useful the media could be
like all humans move from a point of ignorance to a point of understanding by gradually accumulating
more knowledge and understanding and since the world is a big landscape that's far too
Byzantine for any one person to comprehend in a holistic way the media should be a tool for sculpting
a good as good an understanding as you can but the issue is that we have certain people that
you've mentioned running the enterprises who seem hell bent on generating the current state of
affairs and I'm wondering what lies at the heart of media corporations that all seem to coordinate
their efforts towards producing unedifying content and do we like other than generalities do we
have names or histories of what the power base behind the media is the history would lend itself to
the tools that are used or have been garnered through centuries to be used to control society which
is what's called the the law society legal society the military society and the religious society
and academic academic society simple example would be years ago I worked at a television station
doing volunteer work to learn about how that works and I found out that one of the directors of the
TV station this tall thin elderly lady in her early 70s was army intelligence officer
right you'd never guess that you think she was just some grandma or something right
so what the hell is an army intelligence officer doing in a community television as one of the
directors go you know scratch your head on that right and it's the same all around I mean how many
times have you ever heard of someone going to a bible study in a Christian church and they spend a
half hour the priest tells you how important it is to make sure you get your taxes done on time
but he'll never say there is no money to pay taxes with and it's all basically
use of private credit you know of course not he doesn't know either I mean this thing goes on the
media is not simply what people regard as the media it's a level of propaganda that's throughout
every aspect of your life can you mentioned not too long ago in a different conversation about
how the media is not just about enforcing ignorance or lies but there's also fear aspect and
that they control your life by imparting fear can you expand on that well sure there's a lot of
talk about this is a two-part thing here and I'll introduce it as the as a two-part thing
is a lot of talk of quote unquote the dumbing down of America or making people quote unquote
stupid but that's not enough and this is the main thing that's being discussed now in alternative
media regarding the dumbing down well the main aspect of it is the duo the pair of it's in order to
control and keep the society within a certain level of control you you have to keep them stupid
and you have to keep them scared right so the fear aspect won't work unless the population is
quote unquote stupid see when they're stupid they lack the tools a cognitive tools and when
they're scared that's a a disabling factor it's a paralysis so now they're they're paralyzed and
they lack any tools so you've got them pretty much in a pretty well-contained environment
and so the implication is that if you can address the stupidity aspect then people would break free
of the ignorance as a matter of course well yeah well see once they're stupid you know you've heard
that stupid people are dangerous in large groups so they're very dangerous because they know they're
they're got their what comes with being stupid is gallebility in naive-tay and it would be very
easy for a revolutionary or an ideologist that was proactive in activating a crowd to gather
the crowd into doing their bidding right or his bidding or her bidding or the group's bidding
but if they're scared you've disabled them in the they're a fear of doing acting upon anything
even though the the level of action will be considered you know in the stupid with brackets you know
level right so it's very it's the stupidity is not enough you must keep them scared and keeping
them scared is not enough because if they're scared and they have a good cognitive faculties though
they'll want to diminish the fear by acting on their you know cognitive toolbox and saying well
we're smart we can get out of this uh scare tactic you say so you must have them stupid and scared
at the same time one does not work without the other as far as this um idea of making them stupid
and then having them scared do you make any distinction between the different outlets as far as which
one has perhaps been the most damaging in that regard do you consider any particular corporation to
be the most nefarious in what they push content wise no because these corporations are simple franchises
I think I've mentioned on years ago on previous calls any any group quote quote quote corporate entity
once it reaches 150 or 200 million a year earnings they have they're implanted and controlled by
groups again intelligence legal groups a military intelligence on and on and on secret society groups
they always put someone in a position that doesn't have a lot of mobility they pretty much stay there
and report back to home base you know earth ink or one world corporation how to you know the going
on of that company restrictions and things like that so if you for example have a software company
that grows through 150 or 200 million a year earnings the they'll have plants x intelligence
military legal the attorneys or council whatever plants in there that report back to
earth central on the goings on and if they want to shift their policy what the direction of the
of the company to the main agenda it's very easy to do by persuasion and if the those that
are running the corporation are not an agreement then you have what's called scandal whether it's
economic personal scandal or whatever or breaking up the corporation from from people that are
already inside so you know you're looking at the control you know an army of individuals you're
talking probably a million people worldwide that are planted in all of these corporations again
that are in the hundred million to 200 million range and make sure that they're all in step with
the general agenda so they're all pretty much the same just in just different levels of access
no access meaning access to the public what I mean by that is like still you have in any
place that has television broadcasting you have the major channels right and then you have the minor
channels of television or radio right but they all have they all report back to the same central group
and speaking of this central group just to touch on it for one last time do you think that the people
who run the media corporations are as infected or impaired by the cosmic censorship that they
are infecting the masses with more so even more so because because they they're they're they're
they're you know there's the concept of the disinformation and misinformation the disinformer
knows the information is false and the missing form to the receivers that actually believe it
so they're the majority of the people that you see in the media the reporters and anchor people
or even no alternative media are just the they're misinformed but they do know it's it's BS
bovine excrement let's be right but they continue with it and they have to live with it so they
they have a sensory block you know otherwise they won't maintain their sanity for too long
so in other words you're talking about a low-level quality individual and i'm speaking from you know if
you anyone that knows anyone that works in uh government positions as a spokesman or media
positions as a spokesman they're they're not very well-favored uh or looked at uh as being good
quality people even by their own family members so they're very heavily compromised on a person level
which i have to tie it back into cosmic censorship i get you so we're going to continue with
alternative media the greek as somebody who has been around to see the growth of certain underground
radio outlets and sort of fan-driven media enterprises and things like internet radio was
their particular span of years that you would point to that indicated the rise of what would later
be called the alternative media probably uh the first decade middle of the first decade or the
end of the first decade of the two thousands up until about two thousand ten two thousand twelve
then it'll kind of fell apart and again not that it had much of an effect on society in a positive
way it just was there and it was of uh a little more uh you know discerning let's just say but but in
a minimal level not not to uh say that it was those were the heydays of anything there seems to be
a sentiment expressed in a lot of multimedia programs that i think many people pick up on when
they're watching it even if it's not explicitly stated which is that the hosts never really seem to
have could have made it in the mainstream world and so they started their own platforms
not necessarily as a defined expression of entrepreneurship within media to educate people
but as a sort of consolation prize for not being able to be a part of mainstream programming
and so as a result i see a lot of multimedia people commenting as you mentioned on the same things
that the mainstreams talk about but they change the twist to what extent would you say that
multimedia and the mainstream are intertwined based on the fact that so much of the subject matter
overlaps. No they are but it's by a natural default you see like the internet anyone can upload a
content and the problem is anyone can upload content. In other words let me just give you a
a very rightful statistical analysis of the internet if it were i'm all for control of the internet
very like draconian control of it but it's not going to happen because it's tied in with commerce
and even what i'm saying is irrelevant to the world at large so i would not be able to get
on the internet and have you know what we're doing right now or things in the past and that's fine
because it has no effect anyway but having a draconian restriction on the internet like some people
are complaining about censorship with YouTube and things like that i see it as a very good thing
because eventually you're going to get enough computer geeks together to hack their own minds
into figuring out another alternative platform beyond the internet.
So actually a prohibition of sorts would actually be welcome like a just a shutting down of the internet
will not happen like many well it was more popular mean years ago because people aren't thinking
you can't shut down the internet because banking you know so-called banking you know there is no money
it's credit-based economy is tied into it so you know companies like amazon and microsoft and google
and all that would not allow it so there is going to be no shutdown but i'm all for a North
Korea style shutdown of the internet again not just to eliminate the flow of information like the
simple-minded primitives though i would think but what it'll do is it will inspire them through crisis
to create another platform and restart.
One thing that you said a bit before that i've been thinking about there's this idea that people
who are revolutionaries are just disgruntled underdogs who weren't able to benefit off the status quo
and so they seek to overturn it but an actual fact when they get into power they end up doing
many of the things that they were fighting against and to contrast that to alternative media you
have some of the biggest names in the field that seem to offer some of the most questionable
content and i wonder if that speaks to some kind of aberration within the landscape that nobody
seems to remark on how poor character some of the top dogs within the genre are.
Well how could they remark on it because they're not aware of it they just look at the content
that they put up but that's what they call the you know internet stuff content right but
but again to go back to the revolutionary a rival someone that is a revolutionary in an
altruistic way and let's say for a greater good we'll look at society the public at large and
the 99% majority and see them as unusable unusable unworthy of change they just have to go they have
to be eliminated somehow put on another planet or whatever and you can't work with them they're
irreparable you know they're damaged beyond whatever and that is what your first hint is when
you have a quote unquote revolutionary saying we're going to make we're going to make these changes
and everyone will be better now that's not possible if you look at the humans at large
on this planet you can't fix them they got to go sorry they're going to go naturally anyway they
only live to 80 or 90 or 75 but you can't work so so in other words a true revolutionary someone who
does a Messiah of sorts will look at human society and says 99% of them got to go or 95% of them
just can't be here anymore put them on a spaceship send them somewhere else so the the 1% that's
remaining we can work with do you see and that's not the the formula and any a national or social
change ever it's always like put me in power and you'll be better that's not going to happen you
just can't make them better and I know this is really harsh for most people's ears but sorry
that's the truth yeah it does sound a bit harsh to say the least but the fact that they're hopeless
I'm not going to disagree that people are hopeless but is there absolutely no hope well well
from a secular point of view there are absolutely hopeless it's cut in four inches of steel or a
20 feet of concrete that's you moveable of course they're hopeless but from a cosmic point of
you they're not hopeless they all have a chance to be remade and redone so that's you know we're
looking at not a fork in the road but one reality over the other you know from the basement
worms I view absolutely there is hopeless as a granite mountain is as solid but from a cosmic
point of view you know from a divine point of view no there's there's hope for them
well that will give us food for thought and something to talk about later but um
you were mentioning before about content and how the internet sort of has this
blend veneer to it as far as how it treats the information that it puts out with the rise of the
internet I think a lot of people who have no polish to their presentation or the information
that they're presenting were given the chance to be heard on a wide level and I think that there's
a core belief among the bloggers and the multimedia that somehow even though what they're presenting
is qualitatively poor they're still the cutting edge of today's journalism because they're
quote-unquote anti-media in the opposed the establishment so on one hand you can choose between a super
polished product of pristine newscasters and you know the veneer of trustworthyness with whatever
mainstream outlet you want to prefer or you can go with the guy in his basement with a mic who claims
that the system is evil which it is but he's also questionable and he doesn't address that
so where does that really leave people as far as media no leaves them where they are and where
they're going to be in other words there is a you can use that as the defining movement a moment on
how what you just said basically the guy who's saying the system is whatever as defining moment of
how stupid humans are the human that is well aware and perceptive and is in knowledge will see
the current human society whether it's regarding religious aspects academic aspects media aspects
scientific aspects his sort of anything as being unusable in the state that it is right now so it's
basically again just to reiterate you can't make anything that exists right now in human society
better it has to be completely redone so by looking at what is called media that is simply a
reflection of the society there is no better media because you can't have a better media with a
worse society you know so you're going to have all aspects of society reflecting its foulness
and vialness as such so it is not possible so so here's the the the realistic aspect of the media
if you think you have the right stuff to put out to the right humans you do it anyway but don't
expect anything out of it because the humans at large are pretty much crap and this is also known
from a cosmic point of view you know this is a fact from a cosmic fact but them themselves
don't know that they are that the state that they're in they can't discern it you know there's
an old saying you can't take a pig to a debut on ball true i mean one of the things that and i
probably will touch on this for the last time but one of the things that continues to fascinate me
with the media situation is that people are willing to endure things that they can I think most
people can see that they're questionable so like in a world where the truth is something that people
claim to prioritize right if somebody publicly claims that a certain event is going to transpire
or that the future is going to go a certain way and if that doesn't happen usually people are in
trouble and i think that you've talked about that before because that's called being a Charlotton
or being a liar and people like that are generally not treated very well publicly but in our contemporary
times it seems like there's no better time to be a Charlotton or a liar because while it's with the
ultimateia characters have a job and make thousands of dollars a month by subscriptions why do you
think that there's such an endurance for the falsehood that they push well you know what that's been
written about two millennia ago in a certain text believe it or not if your highest level of university
is Charlottons and liars you know here's the thing you can you can corner any university professor not
from a local junior college but from a high world renowned whatever in the reason they're there is
for their salary they don't care about what they're teaching and the ones that do are promptly
removed promptly meet within two weeks to six months so again the central you you're not going to
defeat the central powers that have been granted cosmically the power that they have over the
earth which is they're basically to promote evil and chaos and violence and ignorance to a society
that adheres to such things and not just one society all societies too and the ones that there are
some microcosm type societies of maybe on some island in the Pacific that do not adhere to such principles
or some jungle somewhere that are isolated and they're kept isolated and they're at a minimum
and for good reason you'd want to you know it's called setting yourself apart from it
you know unfortunately we don't have enough knowledge to know the reason why humans are in such a
state that they are but we do know that we can gain the knowledge to know that they are in this such a
state. Well I think we'll wrap up with this last bit here as far as people being in a particular
state that can be observed when we want to talk about getting out of that state you can't turn to
the mainstream media because what they're pushing is outright lies and you can't really use the
multimedia too much because of the quality of people that are running it and what their own personal
agendas are so what has been your own personal experience as far as uncovering the information
that you need. Well you can use it you can use the meat both media again like we said earlier on
whatever the mainstream says it's probably the opposite but not directly like I gave the analogy
of the two the cost of the two items together and how much one is more than the other what is the other
cost right. So for example I've given other analogies in the past regarding the media whatever they're
making a lot of noise about is to cover up where the real stuff is going on so you see so you can
use them if you understand the code that it's being presented in and the alternative media is just
more of the same it's basically an echo chamber they're just an echo chamber of what needs to be viewed
at diametrically opposite or resolved somehow. So for example you could take any story that's being
repeated in the mainstream media you'll see it'll be repeated in the alternative media and that'll
tell you several things it's most likely the opposite of that and it's most likely covering up
for something that shouldn't be noticed. So you can use them. Sure by applying discernment but I
guess I was more talking about you've mentioned being able to make use of other media resources like
libraries for example or ancient text for example or things like that like as far as your own
personal initiative to educate yourself. Sure you can yeah and just use the principle of going
back to the beginning of this thing. Cool well on that note I think that we've covered everything
that I wanted to cover is there anything else that you have on your mind Greek? Not yet I'd say
well maybe we'll pick it up on the next stream. Okay well on that note I think that we'll end
things off and thank you to everybody for listening it's been a good you know hour and some minutes of
talk and we'll see you at the next stream.
(dramatic music)
You