Hello to everyone tuned into this episode of the Greekspeak podcast.
I'm the Archon creator of Greekspeak.com and this is episode 6 of my talks with my co-host
the Greek.
We have yet another hour or so of conversation before us and I hope to make it as engaging
as possible.
If you have yet to catch up to speed with previous episodes you can do that on the podcast
page on Greekspeak.com where there are free downloads as well.
I've decided to retire the live stream chat room so there won't be any further possibility
of posting anything there during streams but feel free to use the general chat if anyone
has any questions about anything Greek speak related and as always Greekspeak.com has
no political religious or commercial affiliations as it's a personal project that's managed
by myself.
And that's it for the introduction.
Please enjoy the rest of the show and thanks again for listening.
Hi there Greek.
Hi greetings.
How have you been faring since the last stream?
Oh fairly well you know you say no political religious or whatever affiliations you want
to run run run away from those things.
Go in the opposite direction.
But anyway.
No I figured that.
I mean it wouldn't.
I wouldn't mind having some financial support but I'll generate that myself.
Yeah well the financial support is interesting because you know it's a credit based economy
people don't know that those that do know get about it get more confused people who don't
know about it are confused nonetheless so yeah food clothing and shelter indeed.
Well at least for this week I mean I think that we'll have ample time to dig into food clothing
and shelter in future episodes but for this week we have the topic of science although
I'm somewhat limited in that field thanks to my useless secondary school education it's
something that I know the Greek to be quite learned in so I'm going to perhaps rely a little
more than usual on the Greeks capacity for explaining things on this episode but I'm
sure you'll carry that load just fine.
So let's start with what the word science actually means and how that word has come to represent
something quite embellished and sometimes misleading given its etymology it comes from the Latin
word ciencia meaning knowledge or expertness but probably had the original meaning of to
separate one thing from another or to distinguish and then by the 18th century we get the modern
sense of the word as referring to knowledge gained from methodical observation of a subject
so Greek what is your studies about the history or origins of science revealed to you about
its evolutions over the centuries or millennia.
Well again how the word is being used like for example there's political science right
whilst people are off degrees in that and you know when you say the word science you think
of state of the art and technology and you know physical know how and we'll get into
why physical know how later but the term science of course just like any term is used very
loosely and to the you know the common pedestrian it means you know usually something they're
either intimidated by have been propagandized to think that they know something about
and also the third part dare I say it's become sort of a religion with its adherence and
priests and altars to be worshipped and you know useless debates and even further more importantly
useless information.
Well certainly that is the modern day landscape of that but if we look historically that did
take its root from somewhere that you know people often uphold this like the golden standard
of the inquisitive mind of people that you know pondered and looked into things that were
hitherto unknown.
We don't know much about that time other than what we have let's say written that's been
allowed to be published and I'll say that as a preface the reason why is you know roughly
and let's say around the 13 to 1500s the idea of having a centralized ruling body over the
entire planet for those for example who live in the West you know so Columbus discovered
America well it's a ridiculous statement on its face and it's a ridiculous even more
ridiculous when you research there was any discovery being done as in terms of finding something
new.
The entire world was always known to let's say those that were interested in the information
was there.
The term discovery is a legal term which means to bring you know jurisdiction over so when
you consider the political aspect or the aspect to control let's say the planet through
from a central location it had its purpose to all control right so not only control the
what they call nations as territories and such but also control the goings on and the
first goings on would be something called industry so you have industry that as we know
today that pretty much only can go back as far as that time period let's say 500 years
ago and what we call science today is based hand in hand to promote that form of industry
which is also part of that control system so what this really means is if we go prior
to that 500 year period we know very little about what was known because it's just not
brought forward so what we do know is you know from a philosophical perspective from an
observational experimental perspective and again it always ties into some form of industry
like for example if you look at someone who was talented in many fields like Da Vinci
90% of his work that we know of other than some art pieces were all basically commissions
by industrialists and bankers so all of his work that we you know glorify him as a scientist
to quote unquote and the term scientist is a very recent one by the way they were natural
philosophers these things were all based around the industry of the time and going back to
500 years or so we can call that a form of cultural censorship you know I would agree that
would be a good pretty accurate term so what we know now about science is stemming from
that industrial cultural censorship that started 500 years ago and the rest of that would
pretty much be going back and pondering what the ancient Egyptians wrote about the Babylonian
Samarians and the Greeks for ancient knowledge of it and it contrasts very starkly to what
people consider to be science today.
I hear what you're saying and yeah I think that provides us with a good platform moving
forward we'll develop some of those points as things go on.
When we talk about science quote unquote I think it's worth distinguishing its methodologies
like the scientific method from the institutions of science which are managed by academia
and oftentimes careerist scientists so on one hand you have an objective mode of inquiry
into the natural world and on the other hand you have a collection of disciplines like
physics and biology and they make very specific assumptions about how the natural world is
constituted which amounts to an ideology really that sometimes gets called scientism what
has been your experience with this quote unquote scientism Greek and what kinds of interactions
of you had with scientists who have a blind devotion to that.
Well it's a sign of the times of culture and society worldwide society and decline these
are basically these quote unquote institutions don't do the scientific method it's all
predetermined to pretty much support all the systems that are in place like for example
people that operate what I call a motorized engine driven wagon or automobile or car you
know why are they still burning gas in it at the almost the same rate of efficiency as
a hundred years ago you know chemical rockets to you know an airplane to go up into the
sky basically medicine that is based on battlefield medicine because you know the worst
thing for an army is an injured injured troop so you know the medicine they have is subpar
also and not changed much all of the fields are like that nutrition you know I mean astrophysics
all this stuff is based on a subpar point of view of maintaining what seems to be progress
and really is not but maintaining the systems that are already in place my experience with
it is the the only scientific method that is being performed is someone in their kitchen
or someone in their garage or a very very small lab of let's say a multitude of just three
people working but once you go beyond that into what's called corporate or a university
study there is no scientific method it's all the predetermined result and experiment structured
to lead to that result it's backwards now that's why a little backup of this is if you actually
take a hint I assure you you go online which is your easiest way to access a lot of current
information and I assure you 99.999999% of all the new research if you look at the authors
and where it's being done it's being done in some undergraduate or graduate college lab
with a bunch of snotty 18 19 or 20 year olds basically don't know anything they still
wet in the crotch right and they don't know anything and this is what they're putting
forward I mean this is ridiculous and when you look at a lot of their experiments it's
a bunch of like acrylic roughly cut and glued together with silicone I mean it's just
they're just mocking society you know so and the people love it you know they that's why
there's no you know Barnum and Bailey circus the circus here in America what no longer exists
because you have these these scientific morons to do it for you but people don't see it
as such and just like any religion the people just do it because it's it's what everyone
else does they don't question it again they're the only site from my experience the only
real science that's being done is on the on the individual level someone who has a discreet
desire in a particular discreet field and does it on their own you're not going to get
anything from any any establishment anymore there what you will get from the establishment
those about done all the grunt work is basically a lot of reference material you know you want
the melting point of this or the boiling point of that or you know what certain you know
basic parameters are and that's it pretty much a reference manuals but the rest of it is pretty
much junk and you know most people are confused about industrialization and miniaturization
as being scientific and it's not you know most of the devices today that seem to do a lot more
than they did years ago or operate in a higher level of efficiency in some cases are is
mistaken as the progress of science and it's not it is actually the implementation of advanced
miniaturization so again it's nothing specific to the field of quote unquote science or learning
what you know things that we associate with science are but it's actually the state of a society
and decline at worldwide society and decline if you're going to view it from a personal you know
experiential perspective I mean there certainly is a lot that one has to reconcile to assimilate
what you just said because people judge with their eyes and when they look around and they look
at the society that seemingly seems to be filled with technological marvels it doesn't compute that
science has not provided that so if you go into any establishment and make the claims that you're
saying they're going to point to the society around you and say well how would you like if we
didn't have all these things well because we do it's a it's it's not a matter of if we didn't have
all these things because we do right so there there's a lot of you know other allegory about that you
know if well what if this and what if that no it's just what is and what we do have is just wasteful
you know at this rate in less than maybe a few two or three or four generations a good portion
of usable land will be landfill because it's still a throwaway planned obsolescence industrial
aspect in the motive again is profit and the in the irony and the paradox here is there is no money
so how can there be a profit so if there is no money and there really is no profit because it's all
private credit it's about just a society in decline sorry simple now when most things go into a state
of decline or right up to the precipice where they will decline are usually at a maximum point
like if you let an inflated balloon out into the room by opening you know a creating an
orifice that the air can come out you'll notice it when it's fully inflated it just buzzes around
the room real slow but as it comes to the point where it's going to be completely deflated and use
and fall to the floor it starts moving faster and faster and it's louder and louder if you look at
any aspect of industry or any industry in the past that has that is no longer around let's say
while when we're recording this podcast you'll see that it reached its peak right before it's
to climb and I'm suggesting here that society is at a certain peak and they are within the system
that exists because if you actually just to go back to you know the topic if you actually look
at what they're putting forward is science it's actually all theory very little of it is purported
to be fact other than reference materials and even a lot of the reference materials are spurious
meaning that they're subject to change but but generally the the the aspect of everything being a
theory and then if you look at the theories they're just a patently ridiculous you know like
everything being a particle you know even magnets have particles that create a quote unquote
attraction and repulsion and light is a particle you know photon which I like to spell FAU X
to in for those that understand the French word FAU X anyway this is patently ridiculous with
their putting in front of as being the science in the scientific community and as much to speak
about there's a lot of criticism and I don't mean for this to be a strictly critical podcast of it
because it's put it this way so what I see as being scientific is so worthless these days that
it's not even worth criticizing just sweep it to the side if you want to learn about how to
criticize what they're putting out is being patently ridiculous and obscene and untrue there's
plenty of stuff on the internet you could research maybe we want might want to lay down a little bit more
of what is really going on that you don't need a special lab or a special training and you could
actually see what you're on eye and prove is being reality as part of what people call science
yes we will certainly look at specific concepts later on in the stream but just to stick with the
historic aspect a little bit I think that through the process of what became known as the scientific
revolution in the 16th and 17th centuries you had science becoming one of the pillars of the
modern age but I'm curious as to how that came to pass given that every movement has its
detractors and I don't think that the these sort of irrationalities that you speak of that are
present in the dogmas of scientism would have gone ignored at that time so on one hand you have the
sort of typical Galileo renaid discartus and Darwin's whose theories about things like empiricism or
evolution became canonized but you also had the romantic poets and the natural philosophers of that
time like William Wood'sworth for example who opposed those things and we don't really hear a lot
about them what do you know about the pushback that the scientific revolution received?
they had no choice I mean there were riots there were small I would say minor and I would say major
riots in many urban environments when things like evolution and particle physics and later on
you know quantum was brought out but that these people who were you know the day card or even
Newton to a certain degree and all the way through let's say the late 19th century Tesla
you know if you look up what Tesla had to say about Einstein and this is I know not the 16th or 17th
century but they you have to realize that their opposition means nothing because they weren't the
ones funding and putting the the power behind the or the drive behind the research once they
those that are funding them let's say or the powers that their political powers are working under
decide that they're going to put in place a ridiculous system you know like evolution or whatever
an evolution is not new that that goes back to ancient Egypt where the pharaohs was written
there's still writings found that the pharaohs told the people they evolved from slime from the
Nile there's nothing new about that it's actually internally known by certain secret societies that's
what you tell the people as a prank but but here's the the interesting aspect about this this whole
thing about science is it and it's not about what I'm going to say now which I started with it's
all political in other words most of the people look for example there are people this is why
their psychology and psychiatry there are people who have made incredible discoveries and were
were stunted and prevented from developing them through quote unquote psychiatry and psychology
and propaganda right there's lots of evidence of that anyone could look up the uh but before I give
references which I don't think that's the point just think of this as a cognitive point of view
that there are more systems put in place under the name of science and which is really
scientism uh to fort development of the field in its natural reality versus its theoretical
aspect so uh going back to the 16th and 17th century we're looking at a mercantile system that was
still uh usually in generally pre-powered driven ship right there was uh very little if none
air travel airship there were airships back then and not just hot air balloons my point here is that
the mercantile system reflected the progress allowed to the scientific community when
when it was time to change the mercantile system it was time to change the scientific community
and when it was time to seriously embed and solidify a certain mercantile system then the science
was changed to the point where no one can apply that new science to produce anything new because
it was so ridiculous and that left a mercantile system or an industrial system as you have today
in place unchanged if you look at what they call the automobile the jet airplane electricity as
it's used this you know in the past hundred years so again you know we're trying to have a podcast
or a discussion about science and you cannot avoid through the ages especially from 500 years on
that it is hand in hand and interlaced and interlinked and controlled by the political interests or
the power interests the oligarchs and you know the secret rulers of the world they're the ones that
decide what's put out just like they decide which religion stays or goes which religion is supported
and so on and so forth right and and it has to also be custom tailored to each culture
so you know you'll have certain cultures that are more advanced technologically like for example
the Japanese and Germans all throughout history have been very advanced in that it was part of
their culture to be advanced in in mechanization and research and things like that and then for
example if you go to the African continent down by the southern part of the continent
the whole grouping of countries there that if you even go there today they're living almost identical
to how they were two thousand years ago so it's also a cultural aspect you have to examine
hmm yeah that's quite interesting I'd never given that too much thought but I see what you mean
right so it's it's it's not it's very difficult to answer a question within the topic about the topic
because there are so many external influences that that pose the direction of science
into a certain posture that no one admits is acting upon what we what is called the body of work
as science but it is notably there you see and that is the political quote unquote money control
power and military and industrial interests always in control what and this is exactly what the
public is showing is what we're discussing we're not discussing specifics now because I can give
like an example anyone can look up there was a NIMS a group NYMCA who is a group of Prussians
Germans let's say from the late 1700s to the late 1890s that worked on aero space in the Sonora region
of California they didn't do it in Europe they came here to do it in America let's say and they
had airships that flew at a hundred to three hundred miles per hour against the wind and they were
not how hot air balloons and this is going on over two hundred years ago right Abraham Lincoln
was given a demonstration of this and he said publicly no publicly so we're we're speaking on
the general cultural science that people understand and then maybe we'll speak on the real science
you know there have been quote unquote inventors developers researchers throughout all time have
developed things that even now would be difficult to imagine for that time and that is another
discussion or maybe we can sort of integrate that into what we're discussing about science and
again why aren't these things you know why aren't we we're told about quote unquote anti-gravity
propulsion from the early 1800s now it it exists it's very easy to evidence this
all right everyone thinks oh hot air balloons and the right brothers you know came later and
let's balloony it's funny that the one of the people in the NIMS a group I've found some notes
from the 1850s in late 1800s or early 19th 20th century they called airplanes sky lubricators I
thought that was really funny and and the reason why they call that I'm presuming is because they're
full of oil you know the airplanes you know they use oil driven petroleum driven so obviously
they're going to be leaking oil and exhaust and they were lubricating the sky that's all they
did they always poked fun if that stuff right so yeah there's you know there's an aspect to
are we going to discuss you know the real physicality of our existence and you know non-physicality
which also affects they're actually predominant and primary to the physical or we can discuss you
know more what people think is science which is absolute rubbish and I see absolute rubbish because
if you don't believe that you're still using inefficient things in your house and in what's
called a car airplane it's all junk rocket science is junk that's a thousand-year-old technology
and you're just you know because it's a culture and decline so let's look at the the idea of
the scientist today's definition of a scientist as you've sort of mentioned was uncommon until
a few hundred years ago you know the 19th century probably prior to that point you had natural
philosophers as the ones who were striving to understand the physical world and if you go back
even further to ancient Greece and Rome I believe the word used is the physicist for someone who
is doing that yeah so you have a book by a guy called Antistheans which is called Physicus and they
translated as natural philosophy accordingly what do you know about the role of that that character
in how they conceptualize the world at that time well they came for it depends on which school I'm
not very familiar with that particular one but there were various schools that were even pre-pigarian
you know if you look at the entire grouping the famous Greek philosophers if you go back to the
the older ones you know they you had the ones that said well everything came from water
then you had other ones that said well everything came from the ether right then you had another
one that said everything came from duality right and then another one that said that everything is a
representation of something in a heavenly realm more platonic let's say right so they're various
schools are they're actually they're all right and they're all wrong see when you say something
like everything came from water which I tend to believe in a very strong sense because when you
start researching with water you'll see that you can create anything in water pretty much and I
mean that and also how water is created during a thunderstorm it doesn't come out of the air or out
of the cloud it's a very easy thing to postulate and lead a good experimentation on but I wouldn't say
that it's strictly so because you know we haven't taken it to to the realm where we could prove that
but I would say that all of them are correct in some aspect then all of them are incorrect in the
aspects that we've been shown I would say that when you say physics or physics the Greek
word is feces not that not as the way it sounds in English word but it means nature and what is
nature I mean again you know we could play around with the need toers the word nature comes from
the need toer which just means god in Egypt in Egyptian ancient Egyptian not the modern Arabic so
I would say that to go back into those days is to see not just from a philosophical standpoint what
they brought what is brought forward to our time now is but what experimental or strictly
directly let's say what directly relates to what we can perceive now because a lot of the
philosophers were making just allegorian points that you know were were analogies and you know ways
to perceive things but did they have anything that is experimental see the experimentation is
paramount in the scientific method right so anyone could look up what the scientific method is and
it it requires experimentation and repeatability and again that because of that it's very easy to
prevent in a society that is in its downward stages for that to take hold right because in other
in other words to do good science now you're going to have to do experiments and have repeatability
and because of the way technology and communication works now that could be nipped in the
bud very easily by restricting access to things to experiment with and also when people communicate
what they're doing it'll be intercepted and of course if any group tries to form it shut down
first they you know ridiculed and shut down so again it's not happy times from that perspective
this was also going on in ancient Greece by the way if you brought up the Greek philosopher there was
a lot of suppression I had seen a document once where there was a it was basically an unfinished
or a partial script about someone who had been arrested by the Athenian authorities because
the markets would not function when he came out and they didn't have refrigeration so if you
were a fisherman or whatever had meat you know it would spoil so the all the merchants got together
and pressed the government there the policing authorities to arrest this man because whenever he
came out he the markets would shut down and all this merchandise had to be thrown away it turns out
that he had a horseless wagon with thunder and lightning and coming out of it and smoke you would
bring out this device which was a horseless carriage and it had a a spiritual kutti which means a
fire box on it where smoke and thunder and lightning came out of it and a lot of smoke and it made
a lot of noise and the people wouldn't leave their homes to go to market so they had to arrest
this guy because the markets were shutting down because of this guy right? Oh so you were scared of
the way yeah he was scaring people away yeah and this is about 150 BC 200 BC.
So curious yeah yeah it's not on the internet this was at a university library it's the frequent and
they said look we got some interesting stuff here we found in a garbage dump in Libya
you know landfills yeah Libya was a it was a Greek and then Italian colony you know people don't
know that Libya was an Italian colony up until 1950s right? So what's interesting is you know it was
found in a landfill you know I was actually having discussion on someone this morning if you have a
landfill and you press something down hard enough and it's anaerobic of instable temperature it will
not decay even if it's paper and it will just will not decay thousands of years will go by so
yeah interesting stuff so in other words what I just gave a story of was a form of suppression
from 200 BC in the Greek society right? And this is a single example of many
yes there is suppression but it's not a suppression for the sake of developing something new in advanced
it's the sake suppression for the sake of it disturbing what's in place. Change is the enemy of the
oligarch in other words the small group of people that own the planet yes you heard me right and they
did it legally just like people say oh that's illegal or illegal who cares if it's legal illegal is
it lawful? Well ultimately you could say it's lawful because once you get someone to legally agree to
be a slave whether they know it or not it doesn't matter well then it becomes lawful so they actually
lawfully hold the planet right now they don't want any change because in order for the people that
run the world and own the world by the way there's no nation states anymore all that's a lie just
like Santa Claus the people that they had to put into motion with great investment a tremendous
amount of radical change to get it this way you see so they don't want any more change once they get
to that position to get back to the topic though I do want to contrast a little bit more this idea of
the modern scientist and the sort of ancient natural philosopher because there exists within academia
this imperative to view science as the vehicle that takes mankind towards quote unquote progress
and the things which belong to the past particularly the pre 17th century traditions are
irrational and so the implication is that ancient man and even middle age man were at best uninformed
or at worst stupid because their methods of comprehending the world were un thorough or superstitious
but when I look at the various disciplines within science and I look at what ancient man accomplished
I don't see a lot of modern equivalents like for example within chemistry there is no equivalent to
the Greek fire if you look at biology a lot of the depictions of ancient man whether it's drawings
or cave paintings or whatever else they always look more robust and physically capable than modern man
with their biological developments so my question is that how should a person's understanding of
ancient man and civilizations be revised in light of that you had a level of independence honor and
other things that were going on back then if you were not a slave like for example if you have a
thousand people in a room thousand men in a room 999 are slave and one is not how many men are in the room
it was only one that 999 are not counted as men they're slaves
do you understand what I mean by that yeah absolutely okay so when they say we the people and let's
say the American side or they say for mankind they you have to specify because if again if you have
one million slaves and two and one million men that are slaves and two that are not there's only two
people in the room you see so this is I just gave up part of the code when you when you look at your
media your science your education when you receive oh that sounds so altruistic for mankind they when
they say they're not talking about you they're talking about maybe a handful of people on the planet
yeah I saw a trailer by the way recently on a movie called the hunt someone sent me a link
and you know they're basically hunting people right because it was you know hunting boars and deer and
you know Africans so far he's got you know it's not interesting enough let's hunt people so they
abducted people and started hunting them was this premise of the story and they said but but you
know you're killing people and then then you know one of the prognosis of caters or whatever she says
they're not people right that went over everyone's head of course because it's not taught how do
you people are not taught how to think that way about reality so when you hear about man advancing man
even in in ancient Greece 99% of the population were slave so yeah I don't know about the number but
yes there was a significant slave population given that there isn't to my knowledge as a singular
corpus of records about ancient inventions or scientific developments what would you say are
some of the individual feats that can be singled out as extraordinary from ancient times oh well
it's the same knowledge we have today they they understood hydraulics they understood electricity
not in the way that we have popularized the understanding now but they everything that we
have access to scientifically is is also was accessed by them based on the their ability to travel
on what they had access to from my understanding of what I've seen it was very rare to be able to
access immediate communication like you know you and I are in different parts of the world right now
we're having a conversation back then to cover a thousand miles you needed four or five hours
you know by either you used signaling all right visual signaling to relay messages across the planet
so you could probably get a message across the planet within a day or two but now it's instant
so within that you creates a lot of inconvenience when you don't have that rapid ability to go from
place to place or communicate from place to place so it kind of limits to what you have within
your own culture or within your own geography but otherwise it's pretty much the same
this thing about as far as the the current day existence I mean in spite of
whatever polemics that you can throw at the current landscape or applications of science and the
teachings of academia like I said before one does have to contend with the physical reality where
we have a fully functioning consumer society that has been erected and it stood pretty robustly
so for the past 70 years or so and so we can talk about fake science and the institutions that
pedal it and then the average person will say well the consumer existence seems to work so well
and yet you're saying that it's trash which implies that far beyond this consumer reality that we've
been put in there is a different manifestation of what things could be do we have any society
throughout history that has given an indication of that of what that could be if it wasn't if we
weren't peddling fake science no there isn't much man man is living in an age the grand age I call it
of a certain level of apathy we're talking about in general sense like I give you an example regarding
that you could speak to any older person now meaning you know white hair and what people consider
to be the grandma grandpa level and when you bring up anything that of concern for future generations
they always say there are very few exceptions I haven't seen much but they'll always say well
it doesn't matter because I'm not going to be alive in 10 years for that right or 10 years or I'm
not going to be alive then so it does I don't care and these are the people you're going to for
wisdom and knowledge right so they're telling you just be apathetic do you see what I mean so one
of the tools of the age is to instill a level of apathy and that's where the consumerism comes in
for example and the the aspect of when I say consumerism by the way I don't use that term independently
when I say consumerism I mean planned obsolescence and waste right just the sign of the age you
let's go back to ancient Greece you know that you could look at statistics a fairly good geological
and agricultural statistics and places like Greece in Italy are 90% deforested over the past 2000
years let me say that again a lot of these great cultural havens of society you know like well
Western Europe or whatever or about 90% deforested I mean don't you think it would be a concern when
you're at about 25% deforested meaning not that it's all forest but you've lost 25% of your forest
and it's not re-growing you see and I'm not talking about urban sprawl or developments for people to
live talking about just wanton destruction you know what point do you are you at 50% deforestation
where you say we have to conserve or re- you know help regrow it you know how do you let it get to 90
percent it just doesn't sound rational right so when you look at anything let's say a
analogous to today this is going off the topic of science but generally includes it as well
if you took the news of the world today and put it in went back a hundred years it would stop the entire
society and everyone would stop no matter who you were and said we have to change right now so these
things don't happen in the future because you have gradualism that takes over and I don't know how
many ways or how many times one can say that you're living if you're hearing this and you're alive
you're living in a society in decline and so it usually takes anywhere between 50 to 100 years
for society to go into decline and then another hundred or so for it to pretty much not resemble
what it ever did before so just to address that point real quick because I think that the layman
would hear what you're saying about people not reacting appropriately to the state of distress
of the environment or the planet and say well isn't that what people are talking about climate
change I mean they're perfectly happy to march in the streets and donate millions of dollars to
questionable charities and pontificate in the media about climate change and we need to do something
in blah blah blah so there is some kind of outcry against what people perceive as being a threat to
the planet no the outcry means nothing if you don't give a proposal of how you're going to do it
and just by simply saying for example eliminating gasoline cars when they say that for example
you know automobiles to fort climate change because the automobiles let's say is a leading cause of it
if you go to the manufacturers let's say and make suggestions on how to increase efficiency they
don't want to listen so whenever you see a problem being posed with a very desperate all or nothing
solution it's BS it's propaganda because nothing works that way you know it's kind of like I'm building
a house I call the lumber company and they're sending over 2,000 pieces of wood and I'm going to
push this button in the house will be erected it doesn't work that way it's a gradual process to build
that house based on a plan see that's what they're basically saying so you know the climate change
is below me or BS bullvine excrement because their solution is bullvine excrement so it's all tied in
it's very it's just how to read the code you see I think I heard you also once say that you made
mention in the past of the role of Walt Disney in spreading certain misinformation about scientific
concepts because he entrenched those things into the popular imagination through his animations and
other media can you talk about that a little bit well it wasn't just Walt Disney there were several film
companies from the 30s all the way through the 1970s there's a whole slew of them actually it's a
short of 50 maybe film companies and production companies to promote everything from you know
how people should get along and to smoking is bad for you to what education what means to be a
patriot or you know yeah it's the propaganda machine you know in place again just to keep things in
place the there hasn't been any real engineering in the scientific field since the 1920s Eric
dollars says that as well and I would find that to be pretty true and the evidence of that is all
all around you just because something is a different color and you're told that it's new and it has
a new shape it's the same um a flescious theory behind that that this is the state of the art
you know and it is the state of the art from an industrial perspective based on the you know
worldview that you know most people have but from from a what's called science and knowledge
no it's rubbish and just to clarify for people Eric dollars is sort of independent and venture type
that is popular for recreating Tesla experiments um what is this where's the evidence for the
Disney thing like where do you just just just go online go to youtube put in Walt Disney in the
atomic model big time lot of videos on him showing you oh this is the atom scientists today use the
atom like this oh yeah that's I mean that's how it was brought I read about it as as a critique on
maybe about 30 years ago and then with the advent of youtube I looked it up and yep there it is
I haven't looked at it in maybe a decade but I'm sure there's something up there about the Walt Disney
promoting it just like you know the big bank theory was promoted and started by a Catholic priest
right not some quote unquote physicist scientist you know the photon was uh coined by a an occult
psychiatrist psychologist not a scientist these people are desperate meaning okay the people
that own the planet are quite happy with the way it is and they're quite happy with with the cycle
of destruction and you know uh some some it's a creek why would they be doesn't it hurt them too well
you ever heard of a crazy person who cuts on themselves right you ever heard of anything like that
it's the same thing so uh the the the interesting aspect here is like I've always said set yourself
apart from it minimize your interaction with the society as much as possible and provide yourself
good food clothing and shelter and then you will really learn what real science is about
yeah I don't think most people are cut out for that but there might be a handful that will take that to heart
but let's move on to the second part of of the podcast um which is that um in order to better
crystallize how certain concepts within the various scientific fields have been ignored I think
we should look at various fields of biology chemistry and physics and pick out some concepts that
if the ruling powers were more honorable and less depraved we'd have been introduced to those
perhaps a bit earlier so let's start with you let me yeah I want to interject uh the reason why they
seem less honorable is because they're accommodating the people who were no longer honorable
they can be honorable even though they're sick and whatever you want to call it you know mentally
deranged from any lawful standard uh you you could say that they do understand the concept of honor
but it's not promoted within the society because society of human livestock which is property or
slave whatever you want to call them chattel livestock citizen whatever you know whatever pick a term
you know their property and can people be property don't be shocked you know the answer is yes
no they they they do know and and they see here's the interest you know the concept of a test right
the test the concept of a test is you pose an individual or someone a problem a question a statement
and um you are requiring them or they agreed to require an answer which is either something they come
up with themselves or a choice of multiple uh other things to to complete what's called the test
you see I just laid out what a test is right and uh the the answer in the reply that's given by the
person who's being tested is then measured against a certain references or proofs or facts to show
how well they did on the test everything I just said is exactly how society's been run by those who own it
they always have given the people you know the livestock that are currently that status of slave or
livestock or citizen or subject or resident or whatever they've always been given multiple tests
over a long period of time and have failed every time miserably not just a little bit
so the state of the condition you have to realize right now might appear dishonorable which it is
it's only because the level of failure sustained by those who are being observed and accommodated has
been so high that you know how many times have you heard me say they're unrealitatable it's not like
someone didn't pass the test go and teach them again so they can pass right or have more favorable
results it's just not possible anymore so and yes there are absolutes in the world and that is one of them
so um continue I mean yeah my attitude to that has always been like which one is the heart and which
one is the horse as far as the people degenerating to a point of not being able to be repaired or the
leaders that are supposed to be stewarding the situation like one of them has to go first as far as
being depraved and it's hard to see how the people millions of people become depraved whilst the
leadership remains honorable and then suddenly the leadership realizes well they're not honorable
anymore so we're not going to either there wouldn't be any leadership if it wasn't accommodating
the mindset that demanded one uh the ultimate society in any any society is one of law where everyone
is well versed in it well known and uh and uh is is uh carries on their their business and their lives
accordingly and of course you're going to have glitches and shortcomings and then there have to be
systems in there to to write the wrongs and all that but the people don't you know throughout history
don't want that right it's very simple you know if you have a thousand page book if you just read
three pages a day which is not much to ask for and if you skip a day it six pages the next day okay
but just read three pages a day consistently you'll go through it in a year right so if you read 10 pages
a day you could do three one thousand page books roughly right so when we're alluding to our various
laws of countries and if this is i'm actually pointing this towards doctors and especially attorneys
shame on the attorneys all of them not some of them they don't know any law at all they know some
some s o m e a little bit of some court procedure but they don't know any law at all other than what
they consider as knowing as law what they see on tv there's university doesn't teach any law never
did never will and shame on them for not knowing the laws right of their of the agent of the particular
corporate body or sovereign state that they supposedly have allegiance to right if you look at the
American codes the French codes of British because none of the attorneys know any of them at all
and they they have the appearance that they do which is another thing the same thing with the scientists
the same thing with the priest to ask them anything out of the bible who'll give you one or two
verses out of context doesn't matter if they're a Jewish rabbi a Catholic priest or a Baptist minister
or an imam or whatever out of islam this is phenomenon that the lead the people demand an ignorant
leadership because if the leadership was an ignorant they wouldn't be their leaders because they
would look at the people and say these people are repugnant why would i want to lead them
so it's a very very interesting situation again from the beginning i said you cannot discern the
difference between the current state of the topic with the political or power nature of so you know
the nature of a culture in the society they go hand in hand i think it's probably going to be
worth dedicating one episode to sort of looking at that dynamic um perhaps the failure of society in
that way um but just so that we don't run out of time let's let's start with the looking at biology um
i think the most talked about biological concept that the greek has elaborated on in the past is
that of the biological vacuum you've talked about before how blood wouldn't be able to flow the way
it does it in the circulatory system without um that vacuum in that conventional physics doesn't
provide an explanation for how 40 liters of bodily fluid doesn't accumulate in the lower extremities
of the body which is what should happen um in a flusky container with liquids um how is it that
a hundred years plus of medical practice doesn't address that and can you break it down a bit more
oh it's the same year same as if any subject how can a hundred years of of political practice religious
practice legal practice uh any practice not show show that it's deficient right uh good religious
practice for example the Christians have been around for over a thousand years and uh not one of
them's uh bothers to check and say uh let's see what the bible says about it right same thing with the
human body right uh go ahead and mimic a model of the human body and put a you're going to need about
1200 horsepower pump to move the body to move uh that amount of fluid uh at that temperature with
dissolved solids and semi dissolved solids through twenty five hundred miles or four thousand
kilometers of blood vessels average millimeter uh millimeter in diameter it is ridiculous uh and
I found out you know the was that the national socialist party gurbals or Hitler the gurbals said
if you make a lie it has to be a big lie because if it's such a big lie no one will question it you see
so they have blood pressure you know I always ask doctors I even have uh private calls with
people that are surgeons with thirty years experience and they ask me the funniest question like
well come on greek I heard you say there's no blood pressure uh you know I can't get that around my
head I said you better not you better not get that around your head you'll be thrown out on your
ass of course there isn't right so well let's let's break that down then so blood pressure is this
positive pressure allegedly that exists with the impossible moves the blood right it's physically
impossible it's right and the more physically impossible and the bigger the lie the more people will
believe it okay so humor me greek why is it impossible because uh you can't move uh the blood at that
temperature with almost 40 percent dissolved solids and semi dissolved solids through um the average
blood vessel at one and a half millimeters in the body of four thousand kilometers long you cannot
move it it's just impossible will not happen ever and any and any experiment whether it's
and here's the interesting thing when they try to view uh how do they view biological uh functioning
through things that are dead that's kind of like having a institute to study uh the development
of automobiles and you only go to scrapyards where they've compacted damaged cars do you see what I mean
yeah in the sense that they they cut open dead bodies and mostly do experimentation yeah
there uh one when the body dies it collapses and it goes into chemical decomposition immediately
immediately once uh the there's the onset of of not clinical death but real death where you don't come
back right so the the everything is a fiction right and it's a fiction overlap just like when you
lay down in bed uh to sleep you you put your put over your body right even in hot weather it you
feel you still want to cover yourself with something right and just because you covered yourself it
doesn't mean you're not there you're still there it's just that you rest a little more comfortably
so what they've done and what is the people of accommodated have been accommodated by is that
everything and anything that they think about is has a layer of fiction over it and that's what they
look at an example someone laying down uh in their sleeping quarters when you walk in you usually
uh look inside the room and you come back out and you say there is sleep well you don't really see
them sleeping you usually see a lump on the bed with a sheet over it typically right you don't go
examined in the person too much that's the most typical viewpoint of someone sleeping and when you
look at people in the society whether it's the scientific field or any field the what you will see
is a layer of fiction covering them and uh in big letters it says whatever that fiction happens to be
science religion politics whatever it's just a layer of fiction covering the reality now here's
the interesting thing just like when you see someone covered in their sleeping quarters on the bed
you don't see them you just see the covering uh what happens is um uh you can you you you don't
define the person by the covering but you sure act and change your behavior because of it
you might be a little quieter right just like for example if you discover that everything in the
medical field is a fiction just like everything in the political or legal or religious field is a
fiction it might be best not to make a lot of noise and wake up the slumber slumbering masses and
because the slumbering masses don't act on themselves they act through third party they're
going to call what they consider an authority figure and complain about you do you see my point
yes so so that layer of that blanket of fiction should not be disturbed um until you understand to
read the signs of a society and even if you did it's not until after they are gone meaning they
are no longer in existence their structures their society their culture then you can come out
and restructure and rebuild there is no such thing as revolution or change that is effective
in this type of society that you're existing in now you know if you said Greek we're going to reduce
the population of the planet down to 10 people or 100 people or 10,000 people and there are no attorneys
no doctors no priests no rabbis no you're right no scientists you might have a chance
right but if you reduce the population down to less than a hundred people and you had an attorney
in there a priest a rabbi your screwed you're gonna be in 200 years you'll be back to a population
of a billion morons or seven billion morons like you have today you cannot bring anything forward
it's called contamination there's a an old book that says you know a small amount of east you know
levens the entire lump right you're not we're talking about all of it being yeast right now
but what we're trying to do or at least what i'm trying to do is to sort of relieve some of the
stink of this bad science by looking at certain particular aspects and if we could accomplish
nothing else but sheds a little bit more light on the biological vacuum that'd be great
it just happens to be that living things are in a container we typically don't we typically
define living things you know insect animal fauna you know plant fauna flora right human you know mammal
reptile you know all the various things that we consider alive down a bacteria they happen to be in
a container of some sort an outer skin of sorts and sometimes that skin acts as a skeleton
structural as well the internal is always slightly internal volume of the container is always in
a slightly less pressure than the environment always so questioning that is not the point
saying why does it have to be the way that way might be a better question why do we have to have an
internal vacuum and that is quickly alluded to once you have the rational several rational answers
to that well because everything else does right so let's just not let's just bypass that
because everything that's something that's common in all things that are alive if everything
that we perceive as being living it has a slightly less pressure internally than externally
and then if you ask why it that is so that that's not necessarily as important as how it's performed
because bypass because they all do anyway you see so now how is the biological vacuum maintained
now there's where your your research starts not that there is a biological vacuum and why it's
there no no it's like how is it maintained because now when you start to look in that from that
posture and you lean on how to create the biological vacuum now you start to get into invariably
directly and positively or negatively affecting all living things regardless right and you will find
that that negative if you continue on this thought that internal vacuum that is maintained by all
things that are living is not a physical there is no physical component to it it is a field manifestation
it is a certain signature that you find in all yes and all living things but it is not a material
component itself yes all the material components experience is let's say that effect but that effect
is not a material is it byproduct of other things so let's just stop the thought right there because
very often people will say well question well prove to me that water you know is wet well then you
might say well you know why is it wet that's not important either is how do things become wet
that you can use you see yes I follow you who I'll just wrap up the vacuum thing who is the most
responsible for furthering research and publications about the biological vacuum for people that
want to look it up no one there hasn't been anything done since victor char burger in the 1930s
because it's too obvious how many books are there about the sky being blue and actually that no
one knows they say they actually had spoken to a graduate student in someone of the scientific
fields that why is this guy blue is well they told me because it's a reflection of the oceans
my professor said right yeah they told me that too yeah it's just the stupidest you know
that you're being pranked as a race as as humans on the point you're being I don't know if people
really understand the gravity or the gravity of what I just said it's all a prank it's all a prank
all the professors are only there because they get a paycheck and they don't even know that there's no
money it's it's it's most ridiculous thing now that it doesn't mean that there isn't any real
research going on in someone's kitchen or backyard or closet or garage or you know a small
a group of people that are you know small meaning less than three that's going on but it doesn't
advance and most people don't know about it even with the internet is because it's quickly nipped at the
bud you you will get if you put a YouTube up of a machine running on its own in a in a way that it
hasn't been already you will have a knock on the door from the FBI and Homeland Security in America
no matter where you are within 24 to 72 hours and they'll send a bunch of guys there with an IQ
of like a door knob and they'll just tell you well you shouldn't be doing this because it's bad for
the financial system of the United States that's what they always say this is detrimental to the
financial system of the United States that's the the pat line hmm well sounds like somebody
knows that for a fact yeah there are plenty of people that know that for a fact but you know it's
not a very well-known fact let's also touch on chemistry so the apex of myth of what's possible
within chemistry broaches on the work of alchemists where transmutation is the most prominent
practice and I think at the lower end of the scale of that lore you have changing metal to gold which
the Greek has said before isn't even that extraordinary and then at the higher level of that scale
I guess might be the ability to make a substance cycle through various elements within the periodic
table can you talk about how transmutation actually works and how it's been sort of ignored sure
just for the sake of time and just familiarity I had a conversation a short conversation with someone
less than an hour ago actually yes I had turned on the television it was a show it was a
recording of something from 40 years ago and there's a discussion of your bones getting calcium
and I just laughed and looked at the other person said well you you taking calcium doesn't does not
mean that you're going to get calcium because you need magnesium for the body to create calcium you
know if you if you are you're told by one of these medical quacks uh that you you're low in potassium
you don't take potassium for the body to be enriched in potassium you take um sodium
based minerals right so if you need iron in your body you don't if you have an iron deficiency you
don't take iron supplements you take calcium supplements because the body transmutes these other
elements into the element that you need and this was the Lewis Kevron kev r a n was left off the
planet when he had proven this so there's your simple chemistry how did he prove that these things
cognitively very simple you know they took you know chickens are known for producing robust
calcium calcium calcium based egg shells you know eggs with that are hard robust calcium high calcium
content is what if we stopped feeding the chickens anything that had calcium in it would they
still produce eggs and yes they did plenty of calcium and they had no bone loss or anything like that
he also did an experiment i had happened to met one of the people that participated in the
experiment from maro uh that the body produces potassium from salt there was a french military was
in maro uh building ref oil wells and refineries and uh the person that i had met that done that he
developed a four-way screw but that's another situation he remembered of the french being there
did an experimentation they had the people eat very little food and uh take no sodium in their
diet and work in the hot desert sweating a lot and they all had potassium deficiencies and once they
started receiving uh uh uh sodium supplements they have potassium went sky high in their body but the
sodium didn't so the body produces potassium when you're working and taking sodium but as many more
experiments you did with plants and animals and people and he was left when he had brought all of his
studies life worked the university they they laughed at him and they gave him a biology 101 textbook
and it's all in the go read that these people uh you cannot in other words there will be no change
as long as you go outside your door and you see people right this is an anomaly all of greek
speak is anomalous to this society it is it is not for this society it is to them but it's not for them
towards them hmm yes i feel like that's probably been the most recurring point of the
stream um just uh to touch lastly on the transmutation thing so you're saying it's something that
actually occurs in the human body but the scientific establishment would profess otherwise and say
that while you get nutrition by digestion and uh absorption there's no such thing either you
get anyone could go look up on the what they call the in-net look up a profile section of the intestine
you have an animal or human don't look gory stuff but the stuff they show in anatomy which is pretty
accurate actually and you'll see there you have the luminal you know the opening in the middle
intestine and the and the hydrophobic completely sealed in or wall how does anything go through that
there's no absorption it's all done by induction you know and this is not the misdirection is so
pathetically obvious again make the lie so big that no one will question it because if you tell a
little lie people will question it you know and if you go to a scientist again these people are
pathetic and the doctors all of them now there there's always i always give uh the the reality of it
because these statements sound absolute which are true but the footnote here is whether you're
talking about a priest an attorney a doctor or a politician they're all ignorant or evil every single
one of them you you what you do is you um you give a leeway of two weeks to six months right that's
your only exception and what i mean by that is let's say you want to be a scientist politician
attorney or priest you altruistic yeah i want to do this field because it helps mankind right
you they don't even know what that means so they go into the field and they see that's all corruption
it's so they're like holy crap what the hell did i get myself into uh i made i wanted to make this
my life's work i just screwed myself so they have two weeks to six months to find something else to do
and they get out of the field whenever you run into someone says i used to be an attorney or
used to be a doctor used to be a priest those are the most interesting people they and they usually
keep their mouth shut because if they ever voice to the higher authorities that they're leaving because
of this situation they're told not to speak about it or else like you know they have a long arm and
they could get to them if they make a fuss about it you see my point yeah so the ones that we that stay in
the legal field the religious fields the scientific fields the medical fields are pretty evil
they know it it's all corruption and they're doing it because they like the control or they're pretty
ignorant they're dumb as a bell or dumb as a doorknob and they don't care right so when we say something
like scientists or lawyer or doctor or priest or whatever you should be thinking of yourself in
that position because those that occupy those positions today are pretty worthless
at least the ones that are stand-ins or have deeply entrenched in other words the the social meaning
to these things that i just mentioned is very high but the actual reality of them is they're doing
the opposite of what they should be doing because of a not it's not only because it's a society that's
controlled by industry or industry controls society but it's because this is a society in decline
severe decline but because of gradualism the existing denizens inhabitants or slaves or cattle however
you want to put it they don't realize it no I understand what you mean all right um so I think
we've talked for quite a bit and it's about time to wrap things up i'm just going to end off with
sort of one last uh thing that i think is good to conclude with perhaps a more metaphysical nature
uh it's a central one to the nature of human existence if you subscribe to the idea that it's all not
just material what can be said about the question of human consciousness and where it originates
because on one hand you have the convention that claims it is generated in the brain but i'm seeing
more and more talk online that that's not the case but no concrete all explanations are being given
well it's it's a field this is there there it's a perturbation in the field a perturbation would be
just like when a drummer hits the skin of the drum with this with his hand or a stick we're dropping
a stone in a still pond these are very fine perturbations and it's just like there there's a
light spectrum the human visible light spectrum is very very small compared to what can be measured
right i mean it goes all the way from infrared to gamma i oath to ultraviolet all the way up to gamma
and x-ray right and there's even beyond that in the in the rays these are waves again the
trapertabations the the the perturbations in let's say the ether or uh that happened that are
is human consciousness have not been uh at least popularly uh known to be measured and uh used
there is plenty of information about how it could be manipulated chemically and a like you know
electromagnetically and other ways but the exactness of it has not been made public and uh you know
anytime there's a thought there's a perturbation in the ether let's say your thoughts are perturbations
of the ether and it's two way three way four way you know there's group you know the perturbations
singular perturbations there's frequencies right you know how each device has its own frequency let's
say you know here's a way to think about consciousness on how it's being minute what what consciousness is
is important but it's even more important than that for anyone hearing this in contemporary times
is how it's being manipulated right so like if someone comes in to your house where you are to threaten
your life and presents a weapon to do so do you say well how did he get here or do you say to yourself
you know i i don't want to be subject to this because you know it doesn't matter how we got
into your house to threaten you let's say with a knife or a gun it's what are you going to do now
that he's here threatening you with the knife and a gun you see so the the real aspect of consciousness
is that's being manipulated and since we spoke about science and before we sign off
you and i perhaps had a conversation about you know how they used to well popular culture shows
that ancients were ignorant right that they were stupid and we're not now but you know they
popular culture is also shown futurism especially more in the past they don't show futurism anymore
for for many reasons which we've gone into but when they did show futurism how society would be in
the future you notice they never said that the people of the future will be more intelligent
that's right never said that is never said because it's all control of your consciousness propaganda
again it's not what something is or where it comes from but what is it doing to you right now
okay um i think that we've given um a good effort to the podcast and um that will conclude our
talks about science and um unless there's any final concluding thoughts then i think we're good
well i think that conclusion can conclude itself thanks all right well um thank you to everybody
for tuning into this episode and we will be back with another one hopefully within a week or two
and uh thanks again for listening
[Music]