I'm going to call this food part one.
So why is it such a big deal?
Everybody's wondering what are we going to eat,
what have we eaten, what should we eat?
Why does it take up so much of
our energy?
I think already we've objectified that we're living
in this body, it's almost like a container.
As a matter of fact, that's how I
call it, the container, the meat suit, you
go on and on the body.
But let's define it, what are we looking
at, you know?
Look at the container, look at your, those
in the military, those that are shooters know
what I'm talking about when I say center
mass, right, your center mass without the limbs.
If you look at the human anatomy, without
even going to the adult side of the
human anatomy, let's go look at the early
stages of human anatomy, when you have fetal
development.
You can, you can on your own pull
up images and you'll see they got all
kinds of stages of fetal anatomy to a
point where you go from cells to something
that looks like what they might call a
fetus, a zygote, and you'll see how the
famous embryonic position that's always been described.
Well, take a look at early stages.
Early stages, what you'll see is that center
mass developing and guess what that is?
That's your center mass, that's your main organs
and mainly the intestines.
Not formed yet, they're mostly outside of the
body, but you know what's interesting about that
is notice how the head is folded over
the abdominal area, right, and when you take
a look at that, you'll see how the
geometric patterns that form the intestines also form
the brain.
Yep, there's a lot of ancient Asian wisdom
on that.
Not used so much now because everything's gotten
so analytical, but part of just rudimentary diagnosis
of people was the face reading and you
won't see the intestines on the face because
I would suggest, as they did for thousands
of years, it correlates to the brain and
you know, once you're made aware of that,
you'll say, oh man, yes it does, it's
just the brain is much tighter, much tighter
wound.
Why?
Because it's up higher and it has to
be tighter wound.
You don't want to slosh, you have it
sloshing around.
That's from a very oversimplified point of view,
but just real quick on face reading because
it does tie in with food.
If you then go by and correlate the
face development or the head development, let's say,
front of the head being the face over
the center abdomen of the body, you'll see
that the lungs correlate to the cheeks.
The nose is the heart and so on
and so forth.
And then as we develop, one of the
last things to develop are the sexual organs.
In the old schools of Asian facial diagnosis,
I would say the chin area between the
chin and the lower lip is the sexual
organs.
But the correlate on the face for the
intestines would be the lower lip is the
lower intestine and the upper lip is the
upper intestine and the bladder is pretty much
the temples around the nose, between the nose
and the upper lip.
There's face reading, there's several, I wouldn't say
corresponding, I haven't looked online that are in
agreement too much, but I just gave you
the basic aspect is the brain or your
intestines, small and large, and lungs are cheeks,
nose is heart.
It's interesting, liver line, liver between the eyes,
between the brows, it's interesting how when caricatures
are drawn when they're angry, there's a contraction
of the brows with a pronounced line between
the vertical line between the brows, I call
that the liver line.
So there is a correspondence for the entire
body and it's also visually checked using face
diagnosis, but I want to get back to
food because all this ties in on how
we spend the food, clothing, shelter meme that
I've been putting out.
Why is food first?
Well, if you look at the developmental stages,
we primarily developed to eat food.
If you go ahead and look it up,
41 days and look, I have a, just
a rudimentary image in front of me, you
know, up until the 50 days or so,
you'll see that the predominant development is in
the abdomen and wow, one has never really
stopped and thought that we are just eating
machines.
Well, not as much as cows, maybe some
are, but yeah, it's a, we're, no matter
how contemplative we are or we think we
are, let's say based on higher things, we
are super attached to this environment to actually
eat.
Now look at the antithesis.
What if we didn't have to eat?
Let's say we're a breatharian.
We wouldn't need all that center mass, all
the intestines wouldn't need to be there.
We would look radically different.
Talking about narrow waistlines, it would be no
waistline and we would be extremely slender and
vertical, kind of like a lot of the
way the Spielberg movies drew some of the
ETs by the way.
Well, so I just wanted to show the
correlation on how the human development, just the
rudimentary, most fundamental formative development is based around
the center abdomen, which is so large because
it houses all of the processing mechanisms, intestines
and all the other corresponding organs to perform
the function of digestion and of course induction,
what we call nutrition and rebuilding of the
body and energizing the body and so on.
What's interesting about this is when we go
over and look at the formation of other
things, let's just leave the animals out of
it for a second.
The formation of vegetables, for example, when you
look at the formation of vegetables you'll see
very similar organic shapes that you'll see in
development of all organic creatures, all natural creatures
have a similar archetype and the archetype is
reinforced or enhanced based on if you're an
animal or vegetable or human, and when I
say animal, four-legged horizontal spine.
So what's interesting about this is there's also
a meme talking about actually an ancient diagnosis
where the look of the vegetable corresponds to
the body in terms of specific organs for
specific vegetables or vice versa, specific vegetables for
specific organs of the body.
Now what's interesting about that is one of
the simplest ones is carrots for eyesight.
What's interesting, you look at a development of
a carrot, it doesn't look like it corresponds
to the eye at all, but if you
lay the carrot horizontally and just cut it
in the middle and then look at the
profile of the carrot or the section, you'll
see that it has concentric rings and circles,
yes, and it would look very close to
an eye.
So what's interesting is the clinical aspect is
trying to seek out what's in carrots that
makes the old, let's say, meme about carrots
being good for eyesight, and this corresponds, let's
say, for cabbage for the brain, not only
by looking at a head of cabbage, but
a cross-section of it, right?
Now I'm always going to make lascivious comments,
so you could figure out what cucumbers and
other things are for, but anyway.
By the way, it's the end of the
fourth month here, it's the end of June,
and I would suggest just a little hint
here.
Cucumbers are very cooling, by the way.
What's interesting, we'll get more into the types
of foods and things, just very quick things
that are easy to remember that you can
use and apply to change your condition, but
if you're having a hard time in the
summer, and it is, let's say, warm, or
you feel like you're uncomfortably warm, cucumbers are
a wonderful food to have, which I suggest
are in the melon family.
If you walk into a room or a
kitchen where a cucumber has been sliced, and
then go to another room where cantaloupe and
other melons, stone fruit, I think they call
it in the upside down world, known as
Australian New Zealand, cantaloupe and things like that,
you'll have a similar smell, a very, very
similar melon-type smell.
So I just wanted to bring up the
points on how we always consider food, food,
food, and I even say food, clothing, shelter,
food being priority, food and water, in a
sense, when I say food intake, food and
liquid, let's say, because you can actually live
without actually drinking water, and we'll get more
into that.
I wouldn't suggest it, but it's possible.
I would suggest, though, that having a more
broader opinion, in other words, approaching the concept
of food, almost like the concept of sex,
which I recently talked about on Rated Y,
it's for procreation and sexes, and the rest
of it is based on what culture you're
raised in.
For example, in some cultures, having sex three
times a week is under-sexed and you're
made fun of.
Other places, having sex just to have children
is totally adequate.
So when I say places, it's a cultural
geographic.
Now what's interesting is we have sort of
this similar thing with the food thing going
on.
What culture are you in?
Let's just say, what have you downloaded?
What rules of the culture that you were
raised in or decided to adapt to or
have allegiance to have you taken on as
your modality?
What I mean by that is it's just
like the sex comparison.
Do you really need to eat the way
you're eating?
I think going back to basics, I felt
like it was very important to bring up
the human development aspect on how that center
section develops.
And we would be examined and say, this
is a being that's being developed to consume
things.
Basically, it needs a lot of input, intake,
I should say.
And it's very important, I've mentioned before also,
if you look at things consumable such as
pharmaceuticals, you're always given side effects.
And they're very elaborate about what they are
and the various organs, but they never give
the side effects on the brain, which would
be your mental condition.
And anyone knows that if you have some
chocolate or wine or whatever, if you're hungry,
you can't think straight, right?
You shouldn't go shopping when you're hungry, right?
Kind of thing, food shopping that is.
So where do we place all these notions?
It's kind of like a reset.
It's almost like understanding like you have feet,
right?
And they're very useful.
It's very useful to have feet.
By the way, to prevent people from running
away in old days, they used to cut
the big toe off.
Yeah, so it's not just the foot.
Big toe is very important, unlike the pinky
on the hand.
I would suggest that once you acknowledge the
importance of your feet, you're always wanting to
seek out good shoes because bad quality shoes
will create distortions in the foot and have
problems in the body.
So when we look, when we consider that
the human body is mostly made in terms
of its center mass and main mass and
the abdomen to accommodate organs for digestion, and
it also correlates directly to the brain geometrically
and also in the ancient ways of diagnosis,
it becomes a kind of a different perspective.
And I'm saying this not because you should
change your perspective from hearing this at all,
because, for example, the Greek enjoys European food,
especially Southern Mediterranean, Levant, food from Asia.
I prefer that over hot dogs and hamburgers.
I've chosen that culture to be, or the
cultures, I should say, Western and Eastern Asia
would be more accurate to say, or just
more broad as my cultural, let's say, imprint
desire more than, let's say, Mexican or American
food.
And I hope you Canadians have some good
I know you do.
Just a joke.
I would suggest that just keeping certain things
in mind that it's a drive that we
have to eat because we're made that way.
And then how does that correlate to what
we've been shown and raised with?
Right.
And then try to seek a balance between
the two.
This is not about changing anything.
One of the biggest things that I've always
been a proponent of is if someone, let's
say, let's say it this way.
For some people, it necessitates that they change
their diet if they want to keep living
or sustain a certain quality of life that
doesn't maintain them as being miserable.
They have to change their diet.
Yes.
In many cases, most people do now.
So what I always suggest is a replacement
regimen, not stop one and start the other.
And I've mentioned this over and over.
So if you are eating junk food all
day long or whatever meals you have, continue
that.
But keep in mind now you're going to
incorporate some things that you have deemed to
be more nutritious, more vital, more vitality and
better for the health that you want to
maintain or develop, because most people won't be
seeking such a change unless they're in pain.
And you know, when you're when does discomfort
become pain?
Well, that's up to the individual.
So I suggest go ahead and do what
you normally do, but develop a style or
develop a source and quantity of what you
know will remedy your condition.
Whole food, let's say, organic food.
Stick with the whole vegetarian, let's say, as
a basic concept and just start incorporating that.
So when you sit down to eat the
junk food that you normally would eat, whatever
serving size you would have, just break it
down.
So eat 70 percent of that and 30
percent of the whole food, right?
And then keep that going until you start
replacing the junk food, whether it's each successive
episode of eating.
You could have a junk food breakfast, a
whole food lunch and a junk food dinner.
And then eventually it'll be a junk food
breakfast, whole food lunch, whole food dinner.
And then eventually a whole food breakfast, whole
food lunch, whole food dinner.
When I say whole food, I mean whole
food and vitality.
And then, of course, just anyone who's ever
done this has noticed radical and rapid changes
in the quality of their life, meaning going
going up with also, let's say, avoiding most
of the adverse effects that people would suffer
going, quote unquote, cold turkey or stopping one
and going into the other.
So I just wanted to bring that up,
that transition, because all these things tie in
very closely together as a balancing, let's say,
a balancing arm or a moment arm to
balance out the culture you were raised in.
Even, you know, what's even more powerful than
that is the family or the child or
the formative years that you've had.
So what I really would like people to
consider is just some of the basic things
that I mentioned just to cover them again.
The human body, just look at how the
fetus even develops.
Look at what develops first.
You could just see it.
And then what what's interesting about that is
that the brain also looks like that area,
right?
The intestines.
So we're basically made to think and consume
food basically from a fetal point of view.
Even if you look at the human anatomy
as an adult, that's the center area of
the body beside the lungs.
You'll see that everything from the mouth down
to the esophagus, throat down to the intestines,
all that is to to consume and digest
and then eliminate.
So we are really, really, I mean, put
all that spiritual guru stuff aside.
I mean, we are basically very base creatures.
We're really tied to the land more than
we like to admit.
That's why, again, take all this information and
contrast it to the culture you've been raised
in.
You'll see that even any culture, let's say
even in American culture, you celebrate things with
food.
What's interesting, I wouldn't suggest celebrating with American
But anyway, I say that.
Take us take a moment and look at
the body, because, you know, why would you
consider these things?
I mean, you have one.
I mean, whatever.
Look at just a basic anatomy cross section.
It has like 70 percent more punch when
you look at it than just talking about
it or feeling it, because what it does
is is it allows you to objectify and
walk away from, let's say, what we consider
to be normal behavior and see where this
is the situation that we're stuck in.
We have to eat food.
And it's very important because it correlates to
the brain based on our development.
So how do we move forward from this?
The whole thing is about finding balance.
And it's not about moving forward or backward,
really, or it's about not being stagnant.
Let's just say it that way.
Stagnation, nature always abhors it.
Even things that that appear to be inert
have what they call a half life and
do age, you know.
So what about the contrast that you can
develop or see if there's a difference in
your life between objectifying what is really going
on?
You know, you're a spirit inside a mind,
inside of a body that is mainly constructed
around consuming and digesting and eliminating.
And how do you contrast that objectiveness with
the subjectiveness of the culture and the family
life or your formative years view on food
and sort of like pull it away a
little bit and see what it's what it's
like.
Like, for example, I'm not a proponent of
this, but if you suck on cigarettes, they're
called smokers.
And some people have a hard time quitting
smoking cigarettes.
What I've always suggested to those people having
a hard time is go into a room
where you know there are people smoking.
And since you've been fighting the impulse all
day of smoking, when you walk into a
smoky room, really, that's where you need to
fight the impulse.
Just sit in a smoky room without a
cigarette and you'll be like, oh, wow, this
really stinks and I really can't breathe in
here.
It doesn't make any sense because that secondhand
smoke has lost its efficacy.
It's not as potent as taking a drag
off of a cigarette directly, right?
You'd think.
But what's interesting is that if you want
to stop smoking and you go into a
smoky room where people are smoking, it will
be very offensive to you if you don't
light up as well.
Right.
It's quite interesting how that works, because clinically,
scientifically using laws of conservation and all that,
you think it wouldn't.
So it's interesting when you take a step
back and look at food like, what are
we doing?
Why are we doing this?
And just start with the body that you're
in, because this is not really about the
mind or the spirit at all at this
point.
It's just that we are constructed this way,
just like if you look at an automobile
and the tires are worn out.
So what?
Well, you know, when an automobile is on
an engine driven wagon is on tires, you
see these big hunking tires, even in a
small car, or smaller hunking tires or whatever.
But you know, it's only a contact patch
the size of the palm of your hand
that's making contact with the ground.
So let's say you fill the car with
people.
The four tires only have the surface area
of contact to the ground of like four
palms on the, that's called the contact patch.
So it becomes much more critical when you
think about that.
So those tires need to be considered.
You need to change them or don't drive
it, right?
So when you start looking at the human
body and how we're constructed around basically to
consume and eat, and the geometric forms, the
archetypes that prevail from, let's say, early development,
as I suggested, look at the brain and
look at the intestines, wow, the geometry there
and the archetype, and how we don't ever
consider these things.
Yes, we do to objectify.
We just go along with the culture.
So I'm just saying again, pull away for
a moment and see what the body's demanding
because of its structure and the culture that
you live in, your family life, how you
were brought up and how you view food.
And see if that makes a difference in
the way you think about it.
Just like the cigarette smoker trying to quit
who finds being in a room with cigarette
smoke more offensive than smoking a cigarette himself.
It's a very interesting phenomenon there.
So I just wanted to bring that up
because I always ponder that.
I always have conversations, especially people come to
me about, not on the cooking side, but
on what I should eat side.
And that's a very big topic which we'll
get into here in the near future.
So before I leave, I just wanted to
suggest several ways to look at things, perhaps.
This is Greek-speak, so I think I
have license to say these things now.
Back when organic food came around, the idea,
let's say, in the late 70s and early
80s, I was made aware of that it
was normal to poison crops and normal for
people to consume that.
There was another food called organic food which
was not toxified or had more vitality.
Even at that point, I watched the industry
as it got to the late 90s, early
2000s when it went mainstream.
I said, oh, that's it for organic.
It's going to be legalized and we'll eventually
have to do even better than that.
So even though something is organic, yes, it
still will be better quality and I would
go for it.
So if you're shopping for, let's say, Dijon
mustard and you see the organic Dijon mustard
next to it, get the organic Dijon mustard
in short.
I just want to leave you off with
that.
If you ever see something that's organic and
you want to afford it, do it because
it still is a better choice.
The other thing I wanted to mention is,
oh, before I get on to that, the
foods that are not organic, by the way,
have no sobriety, meaning the foods that are
not organic are grown being chemically high, like
a crack baby or a heroin baby or
whatever, from the mom all the way to
when it's adult.
It's not going to function very well based
on the structure being distorted from the drugs.
And it's someone, let's say, using a terrible
metaphor to use, but someone who was grown
up from conception being on harmful drugs will
give the appearance of such in many cases
and will not be able to function in
most cases.
This is basically what the chemical food is.
It's food that grows fast because it's high,
just like athletes take performance drugs.
So that's basically what the chemical food is.
And of course, there are things in their
constituents that change the body and that's going
to be another conversation.
But that's not something that I even want
to dwell on, so I may not have
a big conversation on that.
This includes, by the way, a lot of
the hydroponics.
Not that hydroponics is bad, it's just that
it's very convenient.
They don't have to go out and spray
something, but with an airplane in the field,
they just put it in the water that
circulates through the roots because the plants have
no choice.
Again, their feet are in the water versus
their feet are in the soil.
So for meat, I don't have much to
say about that.
People know, I presumed, or if they don't
know, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy.
And what's interesting about the Old Testament, it
indirectly promotes a vegetarian diet.
Well, how does it do that?
What do you mean indirect?
Well, indirect because there's something called being in
a clean state and unclean state.
And when you eat an unclean food or
touch an unclean thing, you're in an unclean
state and you wash, then the afternoon, the
next day, you know, noontime or evening, you're
declared clean.
So what's interesting, there's a mention there that
anything that touches meat or flesh of an
animal, a dead animal, let's say, I'm paraphrasing
here, is unclean.
So this is how I see it.
That's why I say indirectly promotes a vegetarian
diet, doesn't say be vegetarian or eat fruits
and vegetables only.
But here, if anything touches flesh of an
animal, it's unclean.
So let's see, chicken is a clean poultry,
right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Certain fishes, most fishes are, or a hamburger,
right?
That's clean.
It's beef, right?
Or goat roti, right?
That's clean animal, right?
Acceptable, right?
But wait a second, it doesn't qualify what
animal, it says any flesh.
So wait a second.
If I'm eating any of those things, am
I touching the flesh of a dead animal?
The answer is yes.
So that's why I say it's indirectly promoting
it.
It's not a prohibition in any way of
eating meat, but it almost gives the Old
Testament, the Torah observer, lots of choices, by
the way.
So, and also I do recall over three
years ago saying within a year or two,
or I said two years, three years ago,
I said within two years, we'll probably won't
be eating meat.
You wouldn't want to eat meat.
So we're already in that time.
And if you are eating meat, meaning hoof
or surf or wing or any of that,
you'll notice that the changes are here.
The quality has gone down and just the
food tastes differently.
Farmed fish, by the way, I wanted to
bring this up, beware of farmed fish.
They go to scientists, what do the fish
need?
They need a lot of protein.
So, you know, they just feed them dog
food and cat food pellets, right?
Or they make fish food pellets that are
made of things that the fish would not
eat.
And you can taste it in the flesh,
by the way.
I can always, if I'm ever out and
have a farmed fish, whatever, I said, oh,
this is farmed fish.
I can taste the feed, right?
So the other thing before I go, protein
versus carbs, forget about that whole argument.
I had a conversation recently with someone who
I consider a very intelligent individual who's really
into blood pressure and pH of urine and
blood and all that stuff.
All those things go into the category of
calories as a measurement of food energy.
And of course, if you've been around the
Greek for a while, you know that calories
only count for food if you poop charcoal
briquettes, right?
Because look at how calories are determined and
any poop you might have is still burnable
and it's irrelevant.
So all of these things about proteins and
carbs are all quantitative quantities, clinical quantities that
are usually irrelevant to biological functioning.
So again, I think I'm going to get
going, keep this kind of short.
And it's the first one, let's call it
food part one.
And I would like to just leave off
everyone by saying thank you again for all
the time.
If you're here, you're probably not here for
the first time, but if you are, welcome.
And enjoy your traditions, enjoy the things that
you know bring you pleasure and perceive them
as things that are for that.
But if you want to make a change,
you're going to have to be objective and
start doing comparatives to what you're doing and
what you want to do, where you've been,
where you're going.