Greetings and welcome to the Greek Speak Patreon
streams.
I'm the Archon, and as was mentioned on
the last episode, the launch of the solo
streams have coincided with a period of increased
workload for the Greek and I, which served
to stymie a few things progress-wise.
So we've decided that it would help to
return to the previous format with me in
the co-pilot chair.
It's still going to be about the Greek
sharing his insight on certain topics and I
won't be as long-winded with my questions
as in the Greek Speak podcast.
So Greek, I thought we could do a
part two on fitness and health because I
had some follow-up thoughts to some of
the things you said before on the previous
stream.
I was wondering where in the fitness realm
one tends to find the practices that are
most optimal for conditioning strength and form because
if you look at something like bodybuilding, it's
not uncommon for some of the physiques to
take on like an unnatural or overworked form
that's more about pageantry than performance, whereas if
you look at long-distance running, they have
great conditioning but sometimes very brittle, almost sickly
forms.
So where in the fitness world have you
seen that you find this more optimal balance
between aesthetics and performance?
There is none because it's too subjective.
An example with cycling, you mentioned runners and
bodybuilding, I'll cover that, but with cycling you
end up looking like an insect or Mr.
Potato, very thin limbs and an expanded chest
cavity, so your torso is very expanded up
to the shoulders, your lungs go all the
way up to the clavicle to your shoulders
and if you want to see someone as
a natural cyclist, they have a very expanded
chest laterally, not front and back like a
bodybuilder, very wide and the lungs come way
up into the shoulder area.
In terms of runners and bodybuilders, just to
address each one quickly, the bodybuilding aspect should
not be taken on as it's thought of
conventionally with weights until you've exhausted the physique,
development of the physique through calisthenics, which would
be isometrics and push-ups, sit-ups, pull
-ups, basically manipulating your own bodyweight.
That will allow more of a general build
-up in bodybuilding and then you're supposed to
go to the gym with specialized movements with
weights to build up on the areas to
sculpt the body, right?
Literally bodybuilding is, you typically would be building
a specific part of the body to match
the rest.
Really, that was the initial idea when it
came into fruition more in the 60s and
70s, where before the 60s and 70s, it
was just calisthenics and lifting weights and whatever
development the bodybuilder had was their development and
then later on it became sculpting.
So if someone naturally exhausted the calisthenics and
they were very developed in the physique but
they had small calves, let's say, they would
go and just find an application in a
gym that would work on the calves to
make them look slightly more proportionate, right?
A little larger.
That's the concept of bodybuilding and then, of
course, steroids and all that.
In terms of the runner, the runner is
strictly endurance.
They don't expand their chest cavities as much
as the cyclists do because of efficiency, because
of just the tear-down on the body
and the runner can vary in many, many
ways.
There's short-distance runners, which would be sprinters,
very powerful-looking and the long-distance runners
would be very thin and they do not
develop like other sports because it's a different
application.
But the fitness aspect that I wanted to
discuss is not necessarily particular to any particular
sport, actually.
It's just to the fitness mindset.
Yes, you did touch on that quite a
bit on the last one.
I think for the last five, six years,
I've seen a lot of talk about the
role of intensity and reps in people's fitness
practices.
So basically, it consists...
Oh, I'm going to stop you there on
this side because that's information, stock information that
you get from going on to whatever research
out there in the world.
I want to give an example where I'm
going to stop you there.
For years, when I was into cycling, I
noticed that most accidents happened when people mounted
or dismounted at very low speeds.
And it's true.
The insurance statistics for motorcycle accidents was 60
% of motorcycle accidents happen within two days
after they buy a motorcycle, right?
The newbie concept, right?
So I started doing something called a speed
class and safety class for cyclists and basically
how to mount and dismount and how to
lean a bike, how to store a bike,
how to brake properly, how to steer properly,
right?
These are basics.
And anyone who took them, even semi-pro
riders, came back and said, wow, I never
thought of these things.
And when you explain it the way and
bring it forward, I can now technically know
why I'm doing it versus everyone doing it
their own way, right?
Well, very successful with that, very successful with
the speed class, how to be 40, 50
% faster in just 20 minutes of coaching,
right?
Which was a class.
So I had amassed hundreds of techniques regarding
cycling.
And when the internet, this is in the
early to mid to late 90s, internet comes
about and I'm still discussing these things up
until the mid 2000s, right?
Tens, 2010s.
So I started doing research online about the
things that I discussed on the speed class
and the safety class, right?
Absolutely nothing.
Not a word, not a book, not a
class.
Not a course, nothing at all.
Mom, about almost all the points, pretty much
all the points that I discussed for almost
20 years in the classes that I gave.
How can that be?
How is that possible, right?
These are very, very basic things in how
to approach.
So when fitness comes into play, I tend
to have my own spiel about it, right?
And unfortunately, I can create an insurmountable body
of work based on it that is very,
very unique, but works really well, right?
So I want to just stay on that
course, if that's all right.
I just wanted to give that phenomenon a
try on the Sonic here, just to state
that as fact.
The things that I used to expound on
in the classes I did with cycling cannot
be found online or in books anywhere.
And it's phenomenal.
You know, well, the first thing the enterprise
individuals say, well, guess what, then?
You need to do a website, videos or
a book, right?
That would be the first thing people want
to say if it's so unique, right?
And but I'm saying that these things are
so simple that it confounds the mind to
think that we're on a planet with all
these people and it's not being done.
So that's how I also want to approach
fitness.
And the things that you expounded upon in
these classes, were they applicable across various types
of physical activities or was it specifically cycling?
Specifically cycling.
They were so specific to cycling and yet
so simple about cycling and the individual that
it was almost silly and stupid to hear
it because it was so obvious.
And one of the Greek slogans, the Greek
speak slogans, is discovering the obvious one day
at a time, right?
Or no one's paying attention and the last
thing to discover is the obvious.
But, you know, they were they were more
expanded on based on, you know, observation and,
you know, the way Greek speak goes here.
Let me just bring something up about fitness.
It's strictly programming.
It really is.
Other than now, let's put aside natural fitness
abilities, right?
Because, you know, the body types mesomorph that
they classify endomorph, ectomorph, right?
The muscular, the skinny and the fat body
type.
Right.
I don't buy into that.
I buy more into I suggest more there's
a genotype.
But, yeah, those are the types that that
are people are, let's say, blessed or cursed
with.
Right.
Depending on your society.
First thing I want to say about fitness
is there's an element of experience with it.
I'll use cycling again, running or any any
sport.
If you're a newbie in a sport and
you develop a certain fitness level and which
means you're performing better and better and you
reach a certain level and then you want
to expand on that, you increase your fitness
level and technique of the sport and you
do it for years and years.
If you stop doing it and pick that
up again, whatever that fitness, whatever that sport
was, let's say this doesn't have to do
with sports.
It could also be with someone's vocation or
occupation.
Right.
Let's say a carpenter or frame or roofer.
Or UPS driver or something, something physical.
But let's say you stop doing it, something
you've done for years and develop technique and
physique and fitness.
When you go to pick it up again,
it'll only take you 30 to 40 to
50 or 60 days to get back almost
to the level where you were at your
best, where someone who just entered the sport
or that activity would take much longer.
So there's an aspect of memory that one
retains when they gain a level of fitness.
For example, when I stopped bike racing, there
was a bike racer around.
I was talking with, speaking with, he was
in the Pan American Games.
He was older.
And we were looking at these newbie cyclists
coming in trying to get fit.
And you see, you see these guys only
been riding for one or two years.
But you and I get on a bike
and train for two year, two weeks or
three weeks and kick their butts.
Because in two or three weeks, well, right.
We have memory.
We remember what it was like.
So now the thing is, there's a thing
about chalking it up to muscle memory.
Right.
I don't know if you've heard that term.
I don't think it's that.
I think it's more of a a mental
memory, literally memory that you have on how
to apply one's body.
And of course, this can also go into
the emo work.
So when I say fitness is programming, it's
strictly that just like health.
What level of fitness do you want to
have for what you know that you could
be in the health category?
Right.
Just to recap, do you want to have
be comfortable at a sedentary job for eight
hours a day or do you want to
climb Mount Everest?
Those require two different levels of fitness.
And that's where health is basically determined.
We've taken the word health and used it
to bid someone well, good health.
Right.
And it's cheapened it and taken it out
of context on how it can be useful.
And then people just rely on their culture
or their social relationships or education on whatever
topic to manage what they think is, quote
unquote, healthy, which is doesn't work most of
the time.
Actually, it never works because they don't know
why they're doing what they're doing.
Right.
So fitness, just like health, is a program.
What is a program?
It is a deliberate use the computer analogy
in computer as a programmer.
There's someone that sets down a deliberate code
or protocols or language based on a language
for something else to function by.
So in terms of fitness, you would do
the same thing.
Oh, ergo, when you go to the gym
and you get you hire a coach, what
do they give you?
A fitness program.
You know what?
You should do this every day.
Eat this.
Right.
Get this much sleep.
They give you a program.
So let's say you pick a sport, any
sport.
Right.
You find out what that sport requires and
what the general aspects are, and then you
go and see what you can do or
want to do within that sport and apply
what level of fitness you need to achieve
to perform that sport.
Right.
But remember, I mentioned earlier, there's something called
memory that once if you take a pro
that's retired and you put him in a
training regimen of any sport, within a very
short period of time, he'll be better than
the novices that would take years to get
to that point.
So that's where the memory is.
And I'm suggesting that the memory is not
this muscle memory that when I've discussed this
with people, it's actually part of the program
that all the weaknesses and strengths have been
ironed out and you know how to apply
it.
Right.
Just almost like when you download a browser,
it asks you what color do you want
to pay your personal preferences.
So the memory is actually you've already applied
your personal preferences to optimize the program.
And the program is obviously diet, it's rest,
it's what's called fitness conditioning, exercise, working out
and all that.
So in essence, with fitness, the better the
program for you that you apply based on
your what you know about yourself, the more
successful you will be and also try to
get as much information as possible from those
that are highly experienced in that particular field
or sport.
Right.
But there's a problem there.
There's a problem that humans have.
It's called communication.
Like I mentioned earlier, I used to do
two classes, a speed class and a safety
class, and I can't find a stitch of
what I taught in those two classes in
a book, in a video online anywhere, anywhere.
Right now, I haven't sifted through everything on
the planet, but I have been vigorously looking
since then.
I stopped a few years ago for a
long time and asked people.
So let's say so we have a little
bit of a problem here because people are
not communicating.
So if you want to get into a
sport and you read about what people have
written about the sport and how to get
into shape about it, yeah, I hopefully it's
not as bad as the cycling thing that
I mentioned.
Right.
Because those two classes I teach are extremely
effective.
So you're going to have to be very,
very smart about it, literally, because a lot
of that memory that allows you to bounce
back once you've stopped that fitness level is
how smart you were about it to yourself.
And the oh and this is a this
is a big, basic problem.
And it's a communication problem.
The other thing that I've noticed is that
when people do things, they want to enjoy
themselves.
Right.
Oh, my gosh.
What did you what did you just say,
Greg?
Right.
They want to enjoy themselves.
So what does that mean?
They usually practice and engage in things that
they're good at doing more than things that
they're not good at doing.
Right.
That is the biggest mistake anyone can make
when they want to increase their fitness level.
What I mean by that is when I
used to go on training rides and coach
people on cycling, for example.
What will we be doing?
A course that was uphill, downhill turns and
all kinds of, you know, variable course on
the road and the people that were good
at climbing hills, we got to the hill,
they took off and the people that were
good at downhill maneuvers, we got to the
downhill, they took off.
And when it got to the flats and
sprinting, the people who are good at sprinting,
they took off.
So I was like, what is everybody doing?
We're a training ride.
Why are you sure?
Why are you practicing and training what you're
already good at?
You should be practicing what you're not good
at right now, you see.
So when we got to the hill climb,
instead of the hill climbers leading the way
and taking off, we got those that were
not good at hill climbing to lead and
pressure them into seeing how far they can
push themselves and also improve their technique.
So what I find is that people like
to enjoy themselves when they're doing just about
everything and they forget that one of the
things they should do is to train their
weakness and use their strengths for competition or
when they or when they needed to achieve
something.
Right.
They overuse their strengths and they forget about
their weaknesses.
And that leaves a big open weak weakness
in their performance typically, you see.
So in essence, when you're going to increase
your fitness level on anything, find out what
let's say categorically, let's say it's a sport.
It doesn't have to be a sport, by
the way.
But find out what you're not good at
within that context and work on that.
Make sure you dedicate in your program more
time or a more proportionate, disproportionate time on
the things that you're not good at.
Right.
So very much like learning, if you're not
good at math and let's say you have
to do three hours of studying a day,
you're good at language and you're good at,
let's say, science, but you're not good at
math.
I would focus two hours plus on the
math and 45 minutes on the other things
instead.
You see.
No, certainly that makes sense.
Speaking of you've made a few different mentions
of mindset and perhaps that alludes somewhat to
mental ability.
Also, I do wonder in what ways does
fitness influence mental ability?
Because when I look at the intellectuals of
the 16th to 20th centuries, it doesn't appear
that slothfulness or obesity affected their ability to
contemplate or philosophize.
So you can be fat and still be
somewhat intellectually capable.
Yeah.
No, again, it's programming.
It's what, how, you know how I mentioned
the three body types, mesomorph, ectomorph, endomorph.
Are you blessed or cursed with them?
Right.
Depending on what society and culture accepts.
Like, for example, in some cultures, even today,
if women are thin, they're considered to be
unhealthy.
If we're in certain cultures of women are
overweight, they're considered to be unhealthy.
Right.
So, you know, it's a matter of culture.
Yeah.
I think that there's a correlation between certain
senses, like people who lose their eyesight, get
more acute taste and hearing.
And, you know, also people who lose their
hearing, their sight becomes more acute.
Right.
I think with the senses, there is an
acuteness that develops with those that are left
in the senses that are left intact to
compensate in a way.
But with a physical body, I would say
it's very subjective, too subjective.
But in essence, if I were to even
just sum up the sonic right now is
people are spending this.
People could take this the wrong way, but
it's a contemplative thing.
People spend their time wanting to enjoy everything
they do, meaning what's easy for them, the
path of least resistance and what they think
and they know they're good at in performance.
And what I'm trying to say in terms
of fitness is find out what you're weak
at.
And I guess fitness would be mental as
well as you brought up and dedicate an
extra amount of time for that.
Not not because of you might be weak
in something that will never be used.
Also, you have to decide where you want
to dedicate your time.
But that's part of being a well-rounded
individual.
You know, there is an ancient Greek term,
Pan Metron Ariston, which is everything should be
measured to be, you know, Arista, which would
be high, let's say, you know.
No, thank you for that.
All right.
I think we covered quite a few things,
so I'm quite happy with that.
Good.
I think the point the point is was
made in a Greek speak fashion.