Okay, so I want to talk about fitness,
and by the way, it's been a long
time since we've done anything, or I've done
anything, because what makes Greek speak so good
in some ways is that it's extremely focused,
and maybe because I get so extremely focused,
I'm on some extraordinary project, plural.
Stuff that is inappropriate for this society is
lawful.
Some would know it has to do with
water.
Yeah, so again, the apologetics aspect of this
is that I am so focused that time
goes by so fast.
I'll be working on something, even thinking of
something.
Let's say I look at the wind-up
toy known as the clock.
It's 8 a.m. Ten minutes seems to
go by.
I look at the clock, and it's 3
p.m. It's like, how can I have
such a time shift?
So speaking of time shifts, we got together,
perhaps for some adult supervision or Archon supervision,
and you mentioned you wanted to talk about
fitness, and that ties in with a lot
of things that I've said, but I've never
spoken on it directly.
No, certainly.
I think that your previous stream was about
simple health remedies, and I thought a continuation
could be fitness.
The last one, almost a month ago, was
not necessarily just remedies.
It was very specific about things that I
do on the fly, rapid application.
What I wanted to do is just kick
over to the listenership.
Things that I normally do, almost on a
daily basis or recurring basis, based on what
I find works, and I take a lot
for granted.
We all do, and when I share these
with other people, they're automatic to me, and
they're so simple, but when I share them
with others, they've never heard of it, never
even were inclined to think of it.
So I was like, wow.
A simple one is avoid all chemical.
These are not remedies, but the thing about,
I always put in a fluid for cleaning
or application, alcohol, hydrogen peroxide, aqueous argentum.
I always stick a spray bottle on there.
You know, on the plastic bottle you purchase
from a shop.
If you don't have that, your only other
option is to what?
Pour it out, which is very inefficient.
If you have a bottle with a liquid,
you're going to pour it out, other than
a potable wine, water, juice, or whatever.
You're wasting it.
You don't need that much liquid, and in
the meantime, what you do is you end
up replacing all these harsh chemicals and cancer
-causing chemicals with natural things like hydrogen peroxide
and alcohol for around the house for cleaning,
and anyone and everyone that I've ever mentioned
this to, since I've been on this planet,
since I've been doing it, does not do
that, and I take it for granted.
That's like totally normal to me, and I
found that, well, maybe let's nix that part,
normal.
So again, what I shared the last time
were immediate things that I do and have
been doing for decades that other people are
not aware of, and I just wanted to
push it along.
Another example with that, just not to stay
on this for too long, dishwash liquid.
A very domestic thing.
People have dishwash liquid by their kitchen sink,
and they wash dishes, and they find that
they have to replace it every month or
several weeks, and it's not the cost, it's
the efficiency here, but if you dilute that
with water and put it in a spray
bottle and spray your dishes with it, let's
say mostly water, if you have, let's say,
an ounce of 16 ounces of water, a
half an ounce of soap, you're going to
realize you're not buying dish soap for like
six months to eight months now, right?
That's a big savings of $3, right?
No, you're being efficient, and you're actually using
less water on the other end, and I've
never been to anyone's house that does that,
ever, right?
So for me, it's like the most trivial,
non-thinkable, hey, here's a word, non-thinkable,
that I think can help others.
So there you go.
Fitness.
Let me just dive right into that.
You know how many times I've been brought
into a call regarding health, and I just
yell out a bunch of pejoratives and tell
people how stupid they are for the 1500th
time?
There's no such thing as health.
There is no perfect health, as a matter
of fact.
They say that when you're born, you start
dying.
Well, it's not really true.
You have incredible regenerative abilities up until about
three months old.
Most people don't know that if you cut
off the last digit of a baby's finger,
a young baby, it'll grow back, right?
You have incredible regenerative properties, you know, the
eight-day circumcision, you know, massive coagulation abilities.
So yeah, but you start dying pretty, you
know, you don't regenerate as often as one
can.
There's many reasons for that.
So where's the health if you're on a
downward slide since you passed adolescence here?
So the real issue about health is what
fitness level do you want to maintain?
Ah, fitness level.
We just said we wanted to talk about
fitness.
And what fitness level?
So you have various levels of health.
Hey, look, I just bought a bicycle, and
I'm going to ride that bike ride, you
know, that little bike ride called the Tour
de France next week?
You could say that all you want, but
what is the possibility that you're going to
achieve that, even if they let you in?
In like 0.3 seconds after the race
starts, you'll be dropped, right?
Why?
Because you have a bicycle and you decided
to ride in the Tour de France or
because your fitness level isn't up there, right?
So the same thing with extreme sports or
the high end of sport performance is what?
Fitness level.
And it's also mental fitness, right?
So someone says, I want to be healthy.
For what?
Climbing Mount Everest next week or in a
month or in a year, let's say.
Let's be more reasonable.
People don't say I'm going to go climb
Mount Everest anytime soon.
They say in my lifetime, let's say.
And I'll prepare for it over a certain
amount of years.
That would be the more rational cogent statement,
wouldn't it?
So let's say you take someone who is
reasonably, let's say goes to one of these
quacky doctors and they get a clean bill
of health, they call it, right?
Do you think that if you suited him
up and had him trek up Mount Everest,
he would fare well?
Not at all.
It would be farewell, right?
Because there's specific conditioning that's required, specific levels
of fitness, endurance, blood chemistry, respiratory fitness, cardio
fitness, all this stuff that must be focused
on, trained and achieved.
Okay.
Well, anyone listening that says, yeah, Greek, you
know what?
We know that.
But you don't.
This is what you don't know.
What you don't know is that you're taking
it for granted that there's some utopian health
condition that you're going to pursue by eating
something or doing something or thinking something.
And I'm telling you, it does not exist.
It does not exist.
You must entrain the body with the conditions
that you are going to want to follow
through as the ultimate test or performance level
that you want to measure it by.
Very simple.
Okay.
So let's give a typical scenario, an office,
pretty latent individual, not overweight, not quote unquote
latent with, by the way, I was going
to say disease.
Most of these ailments that you hear from
the medical community are fictional.
If not all of them, you've heard of
diabetes, high blood pressure, cancer.
Those are all fictional medical fictions.
They're controlled by the legal system, which is
a presumptive fiction.
How many times have you heard the doctor
says, well, legally, I can't do that.
Well, legally, I can't say that.
I said, damn, are you an attorney now
or what?
So it's all fiction.
There's very few things that in fact harm
the body.
When in fact really harms the body, it's
an inability to recover on many levels.
So let's go back to a latent individual
that has quote unquote an office job.
And they know that if they eat right,
whatever that means, and they exercise, whatever that
means, they'll be healthy, right?
So let's take a short cross section of
that.
Let's say he just does his latent office
job, sedentary office job.
And he doesn't do the other things.
And then he begins doing the other things.
And you ask him, do you feel better?
Yeah, I feel much better eating right and
exercising.
I feel much better.
But you can only quantify that so much.
It's purely qualitative.
So there is a qualitative and quantitative aspect
to this.
For example, you can in all your heart
and mind want to climb Mount Everest.
But quantitatively, if you don't have the quantitative
physical fitness to do so, all the mental
rigors in the world, you could actually drive
yourself into a heart attack, right?
Before you even get two thirds of the
way up.
It's plausible you can make it two thirds
of the way up, by the way.
You know, the last tenth of climbing Mount
Everest is harder than the other nine tenths.
By the way, what's even more difficult than
Mount Everest, I keep bringing that up, is
K2.
It's the mountain next to it.
It's not as tall, but it's much more
treacherous.
So how do I know anyway?
One thing about this, this, oh, I call
it microwave.
Well, I call it out of a can
society.
You know, when people want to eat, they
get a prepared meal, they just open the
end, which they conveniently give a Ziploc reseal
for or they open a can.
And that's it.
You know, you're done, right?
Your dinner's ready, mom, right?
Or, you know, soup's on, right?
I mean, right?
You know, the American white people think, yeah,
eat out of a can.
That's it.
The eat out of a can mentality does
not work.
And what follows through with that eat out
of a can mentality are the pitfalls of
an eat out of a can idea of
health and fitness.
So then Greek, let's just say this on
the third party.
Would you say that there is no such
thing as fitness unless you're specifying fitness for
what level of performance?
And I'm not going to answer that because
the answer is in that question.
No, of course.
I think that perhaps some of the reason
for people's erroneous perception of health is that
we've seen over the last 15 years quite
an upswing in people partaking in fitness culture
as a form of pseudo religion, where it's
really mostly about psychological comfort over biological benefits.
And all kinds of schools of thought have
come from that.
As somebody who was a former cycling athlete,
what sort of things did you learn early
on about fitness that perhaps would have been
unintuitive to the average person?
Adaptability through repetition, repetition.
In other words, you want to get really
good at cycling, spend hours in the saddle,
do a lot of it.
Now, of course, there's why do you reinvent
the wheel?
But you will actually learn things that you
think you came up on your own or
invent things, but were actually done by others.
Why?
Because the bicycle is pretty similar to others
and their body is very similar as well.
So you're of course going to come up
with similar things.
But there's an aspect of coaching and training
where you get the information up front and
then apply it.
But nothing is a substitute for experiential rigor,
meaning hours in the saddle if you're going
to do cycling.
Then, of course, there's personal proclivities.
Some people might be built for power, for
power and might be good sprinters.
Other people have a light frame and good
endurance and good for climbing.
So there's a specialist aspect that is shown
in football, like in American football, right?
You have all the different positions.
The linebackers are very big and bulky and
slow, good for blocking or penetrating a defensive
line.
Then the running backs are very light, fast
and nimble and have good finesse and agility.
Then the quarterback, who's all about timing, has
a good arm and can take a blow
and take a hit and repeat the move
in the next play.
We have lines of scrimmage and just like
the goal, that's inevitable in any of these
games.
It's pretty meaningless.
It's just a score card, isn't it?
To me, all sports, except for cycling and
a few others, are just a bunch of
people in uniforms chasing a ball.
I think most Americans, by the way, won't
get into cycling because it requires a lot
of cerebral concepts of knowing the team and
knowing the characters, kind of like chess in
a way.
You know how each player in chess or
each piece has its own maneuvers.
So cycling is very simple.
You'll see a cyclist, oh, this guy's known
to be a sprinter, watch out at this
part of the race, or this guy's known
to be a climber, watch out for him.
See, I wouldn't fully discount American sports that
much.
Maybe I feel kind of unsympathetic to the
population perhaps.
But anyway, I would say that repetition goes
both ways.
For example, let's take the latent individual that
has an office job and they get into
eating right and exercising.
In the beginning, it's going to feel different
and odd.
But if they do it more and more
and more, their body will build around such
rigors and such behaviors that it will change.
They'll look really fit.
So if you run into them, they'll have
clear skin pretty much and a fit body.
And you wouldn't guess that they sat out
of the office for eight hours a day,
right?
What I'm trying to get to here is
there's more to intent.
There's the qualitative and qualitative aspect to intent.
It's what you're going to do.
You must structure and design based on what
you desire.
But also, here's the thing.
When I gave the example of the latent
office worker who says that I will be
more healthy, quote unquote, if I eat right
and exercise.
I'm using stuff that they say on television,
by the way, deliberately.
If he pursues that, that's by design.
That's by his intent.
Here's the other thing.
You ready for this?
Even if he pursues the conventional stuff they
put out for the NPCs and the normies,
which would what?
What would be eating right?
Less fat, less meat, less processed food, right?
And what would be exercise?
Walking, perhaps going to a gym, swimming, jogging,
stretching, even one of those dummy loads, which
is a treadmill or a Nordic track or
a weightlifting machine, which is a dummy load,
by the way, a dummy load in its
engineering sense.
Even if they just follow the stuff that's
put out by convention, they will fare much
better than someone who does not engineer their
life.
I'm not saying that the conventional route is
right because it's full of traps that they're
not aware of.
Avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its
existence.
So ergo, let's say this, quote unquote, healthy
person goes to a lazy, greedy doctor and
tells him that he has high blood pressure
because he has a fictional imaginary system known
as whatever, you know, blood pressure metrics are.
And they get them on medication, starts damaging
the liver, and now their blood sugar is
out of whack.
So now they have type one diabetes, which
none of these things exist, by the way.
And now further damage to the liver from
pharmaceuticals creates type two diabetes, where they need
to be later on on kidney dialysis and
they die from it.
Right.
So that's a very dangerous protocol to pursue,
where in essence, the man that never had
high blood pressure or diabetes, there's no such
thing as diabetes, by the way, or blood
sugar.
Blood sugar is something where the liver triggers
the pancreas to release insulin because of hydration,
either dehydrated or just hydrated or for foods
that tax the liver into such a modality,
just like I've gone into.
You know, there's no such thing as AIDS.
Only no one has died of HIV except
for those that took the treatment because the
treatment is a epithelial apoptosis suppressor.
It's an enzyme that when they give it
to the body, it tells the body that
cells have been replaced when in fact they
haven't.
So you wither away.
I don't know if people have seen the
movie Marathon Man in the 70s with Dustin
Hoffman, but in the end, it's around a
diamond dealer and he's an ex-Nazi concentration
camp doctor that experimented on the prisoners.
And towards the end of the film, Sir
Lawrence Olivier, I think, towards the end of
the film, he's out in the Diamond District,
which is a very Jewish neighborhood in Manhattan
in the 40s off of 7th Avenue.
And some of his victims are walking the
streets pointing him out.
Now, this is never going to happen in
this society.
You have so many AIDS researchers.
And this is not off topic, by the
way.
So many AIDS researchers and disease and diabetes.
And when the people thank them.
Right.
So you're in really deep trouble as a
society.
Very, very detailed.
It's not going to end up like you
think for that.
And it must be the society must.
And it needs to be reset.
Right.
So the other thing is there's a website
called Soft Underbelly.
And they interviewed this.
The dirtiest cop in history in New York
was in the 90s, was arrested because by
the feds for helping out the drug dealers.
Right.
And he thinks he's still a bad guy.
Oh, my gosh.
And he should.
He was a good guy because he was
a good cop.
He doesn't know.
That when the country went to an unlawful
money system, which it did, you know, fiat
currency.
That the bankers had paper means they own
City Hall and they demand most of the
buildings and cities and they demanded crowd control
for their own private property.
So they developed police forces.
Right.
Police forces developed by the bankers to protect
the prop their properties that they had debt
on.
Right.
Note carried notes on.
And anything that morphed into the legal system.
And he doesn't know that the police are
there to defend an unlawful money system.
And the only reason he got in trouble
with dealing with drug dealers is because he
didn't have a license to do that.
The unlawful money system in the society that
procures that all they do is what's called
the underworld and all the darkest things in
the world, you know.
So how do you get this information out
to them?
You know, I told this lady, you know,
serial numbers today.
I was in commerce on the money comes
from birth certificates and other things.
That's impossible because these serial numbers have been
on for years and there was no Internet
back then.
Oh, my gosh.
You know, so so we get a similar
reaction speaking to the cop or the person
who is diabetes, high blood pressure, by the
way, or AIDS there, you can't get through
to them.
And this misery continues.
You know why?
Because they have children and then they put
that on their children.
Right.
So how does this connect with fitness and
health?
That's the mental fitness part, because look how
simple it is.
OK, again, the office worker, latent guy decides
to eat right and exercise and he will
look better and be healthier following the convention.
Right.
But here there's something waiting for you.
A greedy, incompetent doctor that tells you you
have high blood pressure puts you on medication
as such.
And you decide to take it damages the
liver.
Now you're diabetic, which is no diabetes, by
the way.
You just have liver damage.
And then that further on cause then you.
Right.
You see that.
Oh, then cancer.
Then the body starts to put up roadblocks
to stop the the energies created by all
this chemistry.
And they call it cancer.
You start removing parts of his body.
And then none of those things exist, as
they say.
Right.
So do you see how even though he
wanted to pursue something he says, even though
an office worker who is pretty latent and
decides to, quote unquote, eat right and exercise,
like they say on television, do you see
how how susceptible he is to the second
scenario that I mentioned?
Very susceptible.
So it's a mental discipline.
It's a qualitative discipline.
And what are the chances of all these
conventional people that work in an office that
want to eat right and exercise?
What are the what are the chances that
they will fall for such a scenario?
Very, very high.
Right.
So think about it.
There's there's there's there's a lot that one
has to know to pursue anything.
And hopefully, even though I don't get much
reaction to Greek speak, I think I'm the
only one speaking on these things ever.
I probably will be.
And we just have a very small, partly
people to support it, which I'm grateful for.
And it seems like it's it's that's it's
that's where it's going to stay.
So I would consider it very highly privileged
forms of thought and very highly privileged information,
not because I'm saying it, it's because it's
so simple and so easy to apply.
And it could actually, quote unquote, save more
time on your life.
You know how they say save your life?
No such thing.
Save it where?
Save time.
So you'll have more events to experience, perhaps.
And that's all I have to say for
today.
Thanks.