Greetings and welcome to the Greek Speak Patreon
recordings.
This is a new format that's debuting in
the wake of some podcast appearances that the
Greek and I have done in recent months
on platforms like Hiresite Chats and Mike Adams
Health Ranger.
The reception to those streams were quite favorable
and I've received quite a few emails asking
when we would resume the Godspeak podcast, which
was discontinued at episode 8.
I honestly can't say, because I just haven't
had the time to structure the last few
episodes of that series, so I figured that
setting up a Patreon would be the next
best thing, and so here we are.
Patreon will serve as an archive for past
Greek appearances on streams that are no longer
available online.
I won't be able to include the recordings
that are other people's intellectual property, like the
Ocelli Show or the Freeman Fly podcast, but
for the material that was on American Freedom
Radio, which is a site that no longer
exists, it's probably fair game to make those
available.
So, to give a brief breakdown on what
you'll find on Patreon, there are six tiers,
starting at $2 a month and going up
to $25 a month.
Tier 1 is just the Greek Speak and
Godspeak podcasts, which can be supported for a
low cost if people feel like doing that.
Otherwise, it's already free to hear on Spotify,
iTunes, Google Podcasts, SoundCloud, and wherever else.
Then we have the ascending tiers of American
Freedom Radio archives, starting with the first season
of Ocelli and the Greek in 2015, which
costs $5, followed by season 2 at $10,
the Greek and Seth Michael at $15, and
the Greeks Uncommon Radio is at $20.
The final tier is reserved for the Greeks
present-day solo streams, that'll mostly be ran
by the Greek on his own, with me
handling the uploads and making the occasional guest
appearance here or there, and of course each
higher tier gives access to all the tiers
below.
That's pretty much a breakdown of the Patreon.
I could have added more tiers because there's
hundreds of hours of recordings between the Greek
and other parties, but honestly I don't have
the time to sift through them.
The files are generally between 3 to 10
hours and it would take me weeks to
go through it all, so if I see
the support for the Patreon being enough to
where I can take time away from my
regular occupation, then I might sort through those
files.
So we'll see what happens.
Lastly, I've made it a point to edit
out the overly long intro music and the
ads that appear midway through the American Freedom
Radio episodes.
You will occasionally hear some music in the
middle of season 1, but it's been taken
out of most other places.
So yeah, that completes the Patreon introduction and
now I'll be talking to the Greek about
this new Sonic event of his, so I
hope you enjoy the rest of the stream
and thanks again for listening.
Hello there Greek, how are you faring?
Yes, hello.
Doing well.
Maybe we could just get right into it.
The current event is found at ocelli.com.
It's Ocelli and the Greek, rated Y, and
the theme is the Unculting of Humanity, and
that's the current one.
Constantly stating with Ocelli that, well, we're bringing
up episodes, it's episodic and each episode sort
of is a loose conversation with some subject
matter and context, and we're bringing up the
idea of getting deep into these subjects on
Solos, where I would just have a more
penetrating insight and instruction on various things, whether
it's health, hygiene, legal, lawful, money, weather work,
you know, magnetism, electricity, all these various things.
A deep penetrating insight and those would be
intended to keep them under an hour, and
they're intended to be at fast pace, and
for whoever is listening to use the pause
replay button to go back and reference them.
So that would be the main purpose of
the latest, most latest, meaning the latest is
rated Y, Ocelli and the Greek, found at
ocelli.com, but the latest latest is the
Greek Solo Sonics.
So, there you go.
Okay, and what has prompted you to want
to return to that?
Was there some kind of subject matter that
you felt is more suitable for Solo coverage
than with a co-host?
All of it.
Yep.
There's something about getting into a, how would
you say, it's a state where you just,
without being pedantic, let go and put out
everything you can on the subject, right?
It's kind of like I tell people, if
you want to know what I'm thinking, listen
to what I'm saying, right?
I have no inner monologue, which is a
good thing.
I get into what the inner monologue really
is and various aspects.
When I say what really is, it's in
terms of acute observation and testing.
None of us know anything about everything, but
some of us know a lot of things
about certain things, right?
I don't know if that makes any sense.
So, most of the things that I've ever
discussed ever is about things that anyone can
access.
It doesn't really make sense to do what
the establishment does is, oh, you can't do
this because you're not whatever professional and you
don't have the expensive equipment required and all
that exclusivity.
What I try to do is bring the
human inclusive or the mankind, man, woman inclusive,
where pretty much everything you need is within
arm's reach and slightly beyond that.
I suggest that just a little bit of
hints in what direction to go within that
five feet realm is all most people need
to get pretty much anything and everything they
ever wanted done, done.
Since you're covering these things that are accessible
to everyone, where does the bifurcation go between
say the advanced stuff and the novice stuff
and will you ever cross over into the
prior at any point?
Meaning advanced?
It's all going to be advanced, but advanced
just means that, means further down the line.
Whenever you start anything, whether it's in writing
or in Sonics audio, it's good to give
a little bit of a preface and the
preface will pretty much let you know where
the Sonic is going to be going.
It, all of it will be advanced at
this point.
It's kind of like to the point where,
you know, if you go out in public,
let's say, for example, I'm out in public
and I'm speaking to people on any matter
and people ask a question, well, how about
this?
Or how about that?
I'm like, well, if you're asking that you
haven't done your homework, right?
That's not a sarcastic remark.
So when the Sonics are going to be
topical, let's say if it's on electricity or
magnetism, you're going to have to have a
basic rudimentary, even from the stock academic bullshit
is good enough.
And I could preface all that and then
get into more advanced workings on, on the
subject and it won't take very long.
And just to be humble about it, these
Sonic, these solo Sonics will be like getting
a four year education in one hour.
What the establishment does actually better because you
actually don't get much, you know, in other
words, what the establishment teaches in academia, academia
is about 90, 90 to 98% fiction,
right?
But it's functional fiction, right?
Functional meaning that if you go into a
society that is structured around that, you will
have the appearance, you know, of being real,
just like when children go to Disneyland and
they point to Mickey Mouse.
Yeah, that's Mickey, someone in a Mickey Mouse
costume, right?
But if you say Mickey Mouse, it's fair
enough.
And if you go even further, it's a
fictional character, but if there's someone in there
playing it, so there's, those are like the
different ways to look at the things that
I'm going to be speaking on.
And with you starting this in the near
future, what is the timeline for how long
you think this will continue?
It'll be perpetual.
Okay.
Has there been any impetus for you to
start these from your own personal experiences in
the recent past or the unfolding of circumstances
in the environment or world events?
Has that inclined you to want to speak
more?
Well, they have a term for livestock.
It's called human resources, right?
Because humans have been reduced to like a
livestock status.
They may, those terms are not used, but
if you look at everything, you know, look
at what, not what someone says, but how,
what they do.
So humans have been reduced to livestock pretty
much under the title of human resources.
And I'm going to harken back to that
and say that I'm looking for a human
resource in terms of not as livestock, but
someone to help me further along what I've
been delving in what in any field, someone
that would be more compatible than just a
spectator or someone just listening.
And I think that sometimes you just have
to egg people on with just a little
more information, a little more insight to get
them to flip over and be more of
a workman or more of a participant than
just a listener.
And that's the real impetus.
I think personally, you've heard me say, I'm
looking for people like me, not because I'm
great or good or anything at all.
As a matter of fact, when someone says,
Greek, you don't have much of a legacy.
I said, legacy?
When I die, I want to be thrown
in a garbage dump.
You know, not, I don't even want a
funeral or any good words, because being here
isn't really what people say it is.
So how to have the best time while
you're here and make the most of what
you've got is really what I'd like to
get into and find people that are along
those lines as well.
So it's really a headhunting scheme.
But the notion of going headhunting would imply
that there are worthy candidates out there.
Do you have, have you seen anything in
previous audience response to cause you to suspect
that solo streams and more pointed conversations would
generate a more engaged audience or advanced audience?
Not really.
But I think an act of futility is
still worth trying.
I'm not saying I'm not being sarcastic.
I'm just saying it's I don't think it's
an act of futility is something that might
seem futile is truly futile.
Anyway, I think it's worth trying.
We can certainly hope for the best.
I mean, I think that it could be
that there are people that have been listening
that have been silent this whole time and
maybe solo streams would prompt them to come
forward.
Yeah, I think so.
There's, there's, you know, we live in a
fictitious setup.
In other words, the mental, the mental construct,
what people think about how things are put
out from that, that's pointing towards the mental
construct.
Not like for like a building, when you
approach a building and there's a revolving door,
you have to go through that door or
a sliding door or swinging door, you have
to negotiate that physical aspect of the edifice.
I'm talking about more of the mental aspect,
negotiating the mental aspect, right?
So in terms of finding people that are
able to do that, yeah, that's very, very
difficult.
And I have not been successful to this
point.
In other words, looking for peers, a daunting
task, but surely not insurmountable.
And that's what this is.
These are, this is actually the secret reason
why, and if you want to know what
I'm thinking, why doing the Sonics, I'm telling
you why.
I'm just looking for peers.
I have a joke, by the way, I've
used this before.
In terms of, this is in terms of
mainstream and peer review.
That's the joke.
That's the punchline.
That's all of it.
You've heard of that term, right?
Or a jury of your peers is another
joke.
That's the punchline also and the joke.
So you see what I mean?
It gets very interesting how these terms are
being used and not being considered.
One was, I mean, even if we put
aside the most recent Greek speak activity, when
was the last time that you would say
that you'd come across a peer of yours
in some industry?
I'd say about 15 years ago, 25 years,
my senior.
So most of the people that I have
come across have passed away, but I believe
time works forward and backwards.
So I believe there's some that are much
younger as well that around at this point,
basically to someone who's enthralled about really being
here, not asking too much about why we're
here, but what we're going to do that
we are here.
And what can we do with what we've
been given?
Like in short, I've said before, the establishment
that goes back thousands of years.
And when I say that any criticism on
the current establishment, for example, I'll give you
a quote, everything they teach in the schools
are lies.
Well, guess when that was said and quoted,
that was Socrates 25 or 2300 years ago.
Okay.
So when I say the establishment, it goes
back that far, what they've done is a
lot of grunt work, like digging ditches and
the heavy lifting.
So when you go through it, and you
find out how you're told things are work,
and it's incongruous to what they show, you
know, in terms of the work they've done,
there's a fine line and putting it together
and excelling in any subject.
That does cast somewhat of a shadow for
what people think education is doing for them
in the current day.
Well, well, Gustav Le Bon, he wrote a
book called The Crowd.
And just to simplify, basically, it's a good
read.
A lot of it is pre psychology or
psychology, pre psychology, which was another scam, by
the way, trying to tell people what the
spirit and the soul and the mind are,
you know, redefining it, because pretty much if
you've heard any Greek speak, everything that could
have been known was known by the late
19th century, the 1890s.
And if you're not aware of that, go
start looking back and you'll see there was
a lot of futurism around that time that
showed that we should have been in flying
cars by the 1960s or 70s.
So we're being, you know, kind of shown
things that we where we could have been,
it's not about where we could have been,
because going back to Gustav Le Bon, The
Crowd, and just to oversimplify the book, no
pun intended, is that when you're going to
present a notion, a concept, or an ideology
to the public at large, or large groups
of people, you have to simplify it.
But what happens is it becomes so simplified
that it no longer represents its original meaning.
Right?
So we end up right where we were
with Socrates' quote from 2300 years ago.
So I think there's a fine line where
people are attracted to doing this kind of
stuff online, and people are attracted to what
the Greek has to say.
And then there's another point where once I
get into doing the Solosonics, and I pretty
much share everything I found out about something,
not what I know, but what I found
out about it, because what you know can
change and what you believe definitely can change,
because that's why it's a belief, I think
will be more inspirational and more to the
point for some.
No, that's encouraging to hear.
I guess my last question is just this
sort of general statement that you've made on
the American Freedom Radio streams, and probably elsewhere
that you only share 10% of what
you know.
And now with it being almost a decade
later, what is that at now?
And what can we expect on the solo
streams?
I'd say a lot more, because there's only
so much you can do, but with time
allotted, when you're trying to nurture a conversation,
let's say.
I'd say all of it if it can
be, right?
Because believe it or not, we're beings that
rely on feelings and emotions, which are more
in the ethereal realm.
It has a language of its own, and
the language of that feeling and emotion is
silent, which I have been getting into much
with the inner monologue that people recognize as
themselves, because they actually hear themselves in their
own voice.
And I've gone into how that's not really
you, and who you really are is a
very sober, full of sobriety, and very silent
mechanism that communicates into the inner self.
So, how much of that can be communicated
on a sonic, we'll see.
But I always say, you only share 10
% in public, and you hold, reserve the
rest.
So, lately I've been thinking, I'm in my
sixth decade now in life here on this
planet, surface-dwelling earth inhabitant.
And I think the gap is getting bigger
between those who know what they think they
know, and those who say what they think
they know, and those that know, and those
that don't know.
So, I'd like to just offer a very
simple way, by projecting what I found out
about it in a perspective known as Greek
-speak, and hopefully those that are interested will
be even more interested.
Yes, I agree.
I'm sure that they will be.
There's been a lot of people clamoring for
additional streams, so it'll most likely be appreciated.
Well, I think we've done a good job
of elaborating on the scope of the coming
sonics, and what people can expect.
So, we may as well conclude this introductory
episode, unless there's anything more you want to
add?
Oh, a lot.
Well, what we're going to be adding are
the solo sonics, and I guess hope to
see whoever comes over there.
Yes, it should be a good experience.
Like I said, I'll be jumping in from
time to time to help with stuff, but
you'll be able to find all of these
streams on the Patreon website.
We'll be sending out newsletters to anybody that's
subscribed to Greekspeak.com or Godspeak.com, so
if you haven't done that, make sure to
do that.
And, yeah, we hope that you enjoy the
coming sonics.