Hey everyone, we're going to call these simple
remedies.
Simple remedies meaning the ones I use often.
Where do we start?
Depending on the situation, the easiest one that
I can come up with that I use
the most often is referring back to the
analogy I give for magnets.
What are magnets?
Well, magnets are to electricity what photographic paper
are to light or is to light.
Meaning, as the photographic paper captures a moment
in time when light exposes it, a magnet
captures the electrical field going through basically a
piece of iron or iron alloy.
And when the electrical field is released, you're
left with whatever impression, just like light leaves
an impression on photographic paper.
Well, what does this have to do with
remedies?
The body all day is experiencing many fields
and many situations which imprint upon it.
And usually by the end of the day,
you might say, I'm tired.
I need to re-energize.
I kind of feel like I have everything
that I did today still in me.
I mean, this is a thought that I
come up with.
I just wanted to share.
And what I do for that is the
easiest way to demagnetize the body is water.
Yeah, go take a shower.
All right, so very simple.
Some people I recommend baths and some people
say, I don't like sitting in my own
shit.
I'm like, I never understood that.
But I just want to bring that up
because some people don't like taking baths.
If you feel that way, just like at
the going into a pool or a beach
or whatever, shower first, then bathe or whatever.
But baths tend to be a little bit
better because you're sitting in the water.
Now, what do I mean by demagnetize?
I don't even know if I said that
yet.
But when you wash the body in water,
it's demagnetizing the body, literally, just like a
magnet is imprinted or photographic paper is imprinted
with the effective fields on it.
The rinsing off or the water running over
the body, especially in a bath, when you
have some water trickling in and some water
trickling out, not a stagnant bath.
But let's say just a shower.
I've run into people that very often, infrequently,
that bathe where they don't have a bathroom.
Actually, I shouldn't say I don't have a
bathroom.
Off-the-grid kind of situation, people living
in van life type thing, where they have
to improvise showers and baths or truck stops
and things like that.
It's the same thing.
Running water over the body is essentially what
I mean.
It could be as much as if you
live near a lake or a river or
the beach, taking a dip at the end
of the day.
Again, what I call it is demagnetizing.
People that I know, for example, if someone
says, I really had a hard day.
I'm feeling whatever.
I said, did you demagnetize?
Those that know me know what I mean
by that.
It means go take a shower.
It's fast and easy.
It's not even a washing episode.
It is just a wetting episode.
It could just be 30 seconds or a
minute.
I don't know how much to stress that
or emphasize the positive effects of that.
We usually associate that in most cultures with
just washing because you're unclean.
I mean, you just whatever.
You need to wash.
But in this case, I'm pursuing the idea
that it is a form of demagnetizing the
body.
You can take it however you want in
terms of if you want to look at
it spiritually, meaning Old Testament style, or if
you want to look at it from a
material chemical point of view, or do you
want to look at it from, let's say,
an emo or emotional point of view, which
would be kind of an invigorating feeling, right?
When you think about taking a shower, it's
an invigorating feeling.
Usually, I suggest that there is a demagnetization
process that is occurring.
Why?
Very often when I do feel uncomfortable with
myself physically and others, I always recommend and
I do take a shower and I always
feel different.
When I say different, let's just say I
always feel better, but I'm saying different like,
for example, if you're experiencing a specific discomfort,
a headache, an ache, a soreness, it might
actually, well, it will improve it, right?
I don't know how much more to emphasize.
It sounds almost cliche, but I've never heard
anyone just implying rinsing the body with water
changes the state, and I'm suggesting that it
does.
Just like a magnet is charged and then
demagnetized, the body works very much the same
way.
I don't need to get into a long
idea of expressing how everything that we do
during the day or encounter, and even things
that we don't do, imprints itself, those actions,
activities, objects, other people imprint themselves on the
physical body.
And of course, you know, if the physical
body is not reacting well, the mind and
the spirit will not react very well.
So, when I say these are quick, simple
remedies, I brought this up first, because again,
it's my first suggestion to most when they
say they're not feeling well, did you demagnetize,
did you shower or bathe?
Now, there's the second part in terms of
bathing, there's tremendous amount of, what would you
say, culture built around it, you know, the
bubble bath, the salt bath, the Epsom salt
bath, all that's wonderful, whatever you prefer.
I'm just simply stating that when you have
a sense of tiredness, whatever, discomfort, soreness, a
headache, a toothache, a stomachache, even a heart
attack, rinse off very quickly.
By the way, they call it angina, there's
very technical names, various technical names for a
heart attack.
I have experienced that, by the way, and
I'm not sure if it was a, one
of those vans that drive around with a
little satellite dish pointed at you or whatever,
but I was home alone, it was late
afternoon, I was making a sandwich, as they
say back east, and suddenly I felt my
legs get really stiff, I lost feeling in
my legs, and the heart started beating really,
really fast, and I had trouble breathing.
And from all the information I've ever heard
about a cardiac arrest, I was like, okay,
this is what this is, it's the closest
thing to it.
And there's really no such thing as a
heart attack as explained.
When the heart goes into that state, it
stops acting like a breaking mechanism, it's like
having a failing break, right, because the heart
is not pumping anything, it deceives everyone because
we sense it as a pump, and we're
told since we're young it's a pump.
It's actually a breaking mechanism, it stops the
flow of blood, restricts it, and then lets
it mix in the heart and then releases
it again.
So when this heart attack thing is happening,
it's actually, it's like having breaks that are
not working because it's in the wet, or
failing, or because of fluid, or, yeah, it's
a failing breaking system.
But anyway, back to what happened with me,
is I felt this, and the first thing
I did was ran into the shower, cold
water, I had clothes on, barefoot, but all
my clothes were on, cell phone in the
pocket, wallet in the pocket, change keys, everything,
reading glasses on the head, and just ran
cold water.
It was early spring, so the water was
still pretty cold coming out, and it stiffened
up the body, and I just didn't think
about what was happening, or what I felt
was happening, and I felt fine.
I called the wife about an hour later,
I said, I think I just had a
heart attack, but I treated it, and I
feel better now, and I felt quite sore
and tired for a few days after that
episode.
So I just wanted to share that, uh,
why the cold water and all that, of
course, it's a contractive mechanism, right?
The warm water would increase circulation, cold water
would stop it.
I let my mind run a little wild,
I remember a few days later having sushi,
and I'm pretty friendly with the sushi chef,
just talking about health, I said, you know,
I had a heart attack the other day,
he's like, you're kidding, right?
Anyway, it's a whole other story for someday.
By the way, regarding that episode, later on,
I did catch up with something on the
internet about that, and one of the treatments
that are being used now for that situation,
the heart attack situation, is dipping people in
ice water.
So go figure.
So intuitively, I think I did the right
thing.
This was back, I'd say, around 2016 or
so, and I let my mind run conspiratorial,
you know, figuring there was a van driving
around, you know, with what they call directed
energy weapons, or whatever, because I haven't had
anything recurring since.
Lately, I did have something very similar, but
not as severe.
So I just wanted to share that with
you.
If you are in a situation around someone
that does have that heart attack thing, ice
water, entire body, quick remedy.
I know it sounds kind of severe when
you're talking about quick remedies, I just wandered
off to that end of it.
Water, demagnetization.
So the lingo that I use is demagnetized.
Not your old VCR tapes or cassette tapes,
but the body.
And I'm suggesting that's exactly what's happening.
So we have gotten into other things with
water, and we will get into some in
-depth discussions about water.
But again, what prompted me to do this
is, on simple remedies, is we're in the
middle of a season.
Whether you're on the other side of the
world, you're probably in the middle of winter.
Right here, it's the middle of summer right
now.
And what's interesting, when you get to the
middle of seasons, whether it's the big season,
winter and summer.
And by the way, in the ancient times,
it was winter and summer, and spring and
fall were transition times.
That's when the most happenings are in terms
of the effects of the season on the
body.
And I've been very busy lately, extremely busy,
and I've been finding myself bumping into things,
being clumsy, and getting tired, getting sore, or
doing heavy lifting, all kinds of things, especially
even with the mind.
And I found that the best therapy for
the state that I'm in, particularly recently, is
to just have a good, quick wash.
But we'll get more into water.
We've covered the aqueous argentum.
We'll get into more on how to make
the devices and some more developments on that,
and also water purification at home and wherever
you are.
We'll definitely get into that again.
But if I say it another 20 times,
that demagnetizing the body with a quick shower
will really change the way you feel.
Next thing I wanted to mention, typically for
a quick remedy, most people still experience skin
manifestations.
And this is also going to include a
toothache, an abscess in the mouth, a gum
thing, abscess, swelling, blister in the mouth, anywhere
on the body, I suggest, except for the
very soft areas, the groin, perhaps, or armpit
would be very sensitive.
But for any skin manifestation, including what they
call a pimple, a boil, but not a
rash, not a skin rash, which would be
just a general topical spread on the skin,
dry or red or wet, but basically a
skin manifestation in the mouth in the form
of a blister or a pimple or a
bump, what people call a bump, I would
suggest ginger root for that.
What you do is you crosscut just a
very thin slice of ginger and put it
over the area and wrap it.
I've been one of the people that have
the fate of having mouth problems.
Ever since I was a child, when I
was 12 years old or 11 years old,
I fell off some monkey bars and broke
out the front teeth, and I've had a
bridge ever since then.
But now I have prosthetics, and I got
mad at the dentist for not telling me
that prosthetics work so well, but you couldn't
tell, and I'm quite happy with it.
But I've always had teeth issues and mouth
issues, and ever since I got into macrobiotics
in the 80s, it wasn't suggested, but I
had discovered ginger use, and I would cut
a slice if I had an abscess in
the mouth or a blister or a bump
or something on the skin.
If you have what they call acne or
a boil, sometimes a persistent, a slice of
ginger wrapped or held on there, and when
I say wrapped, you understand it's like a
poultice or a bandage, but even held on
there just for a few minutes.
The other day I felt, because of the
heat here, I got a heat sore, like
a pimple on my forehead forming, and it
was quite tough and it was sore, and
I just cut a piece of ginger and
just held it there.
I sat in front of the computer looking
up some things I wanted to look up
with my left hand, center finger just pushing
the slice of ginger on this bump that
was forming on my head from the heat,
and within 10 minutes or so I took
it off and it was hardly there and
I didn't feel it anymore and it's gone.
So, ginger, ginger root.
If you don't have access to it, I
was going to suggest galangal, which is something
that's found in Asia, but if you don't
have access to ginger, you probably won't have
access to galangal.
It looks exactly like ginger and it has
like a white pepper flavor instead of that
floral flavor that ginger has.
I'm not sure what other kind of root
you would use if you don't have access
to it because, believe it or not, a
lot of the things, we'll put it this
way, I didn't look into other alternatives for
it because I'm in a place and always
been in a place where I could always
get it.
I don't grow it.
It's accessible.
If it's not accessible to where you are,
I don't know what a substitute would be,
and if you're listening to me on a
computer, you could probably look up on the
browser what would be a simple substitute, but
if we look at it, it is a
root.
It grows longitudinally.
It has bulbs, sort of.
If you look at how it grows, something
similar might be similar, and again, always do
a test, but I just wanted to bring
up the ginger because it saved my butt
in so many ways, not literally, but skin
manifestations, bumps, mouth issues, things like that.
It's really like, for example, if I have
a bump forming on my gum or whatever,
like something that's going to be an abscess
or swelling, I would put a piece of
ginger on that and hold it down, or
actually, you could leave it in there like
chewing tobacco, and within 20 minutes to an
hour, seems to relieve most of it, if
not all of it, often.
Instead of something lasting days, it can be
gone within an hour or two using the
ginger.
I can give a quick story.
There's a lady I remember back in the
1980s.
Macrobiotics were big on ginger, poultices, and compresses,
and she was a very petite lady, and
she was diagnosed with breast cancer, and I
was poo-pooing it because most people get
false diagnosis on this thing because they just
want to run them through the system for
the insurance.
When someone says they have cancer or something,
I say, what kind of insurance do you
have?
They say, oh, I have the best corporate
insurance.
Oh, they'll tell you you have cancer.
Of course they do.
Anyway, when I kind of poo-pooed it,
she picked up her shirt, showed me the
side of her breast, and held up her
breast, and you could actually see the lump
through the skin.
I was like, okay.
I suggested doing a ginger compress.
She didn't know what it was.
I explained it to her, which was basically
grating ginger in water and then bringing it
just pre-simmer, making it very hot and
turning it off and having some cheesecloth or
a white cotton from old sheets or T
-shirt, dipping it in there, slightly wringing it
out, and pressing it with a towel against
the area for doing it for about 20
minutes at a time.
Well, it turns out she did it for
about four hours at a time for about
a week, and it developed a very black
and blue, almost black in the center.
Half of her breast turned black and blue,
and she was threatening me like, oh, this
caused this.
It's making it worse.
Well, what happened, I hadn't seen her then
for about another week or so, and I
said how she was.
She said she left the hospital because the
tumor came up to the skin and became
a boil, and they lanced it, and it
all came out.
I was like, wow.
Is that good?
Are you happy?
She goes, that's excellent, because now it went
from what they diagnosed as a cancer to
a boil that had to be lanced and
relieved.
So the therapy for lancing and relieving a
boil is radically different from being treated for
breast cancer.
So this was back in about 1989.
I just wanted to share that, because that's
always one of the strongest memories of using
ginger on the body other than when I
use it, and I've also suggested to other
people, and most people have very good results.
Again, if you don't have access to ginger,
you might look up an alternative and maybe
email me, uncommonsenseradio1 at gmail.com.
That's the number one, and I'll help you
maybe find something if there isn't.
I have not looked into it.
I've been a little lazy on the alternatives
for some of these things.
Okay, in terms of so far remedies, those
are the two major ones that have come
to mind that I've used recently, and I
use very, very often and suggest to people.
It would be the water and the ginger
compress.
Now when we get into more of these
basic remedies, it's just a smattering of depending
on more of a specific situation.
The first one was the most general, just
demagnetizing, and the ginger would be more specific,
but very general, again, because it's the entire
outer skin area of the body and the
mouth.
I don't recommend it for rashes.
I have once I got a rash and
it just made it worse.
It irritated it, and there's a reason for
that.
It's the way the energy flows with the
ginger.
It's very piercing, very penetrating, and a rash
is something that is only topical, and to
put a penetrating energy on something that needs
to be topical will aggravate it.
So the other basic remedy that I encounter
often, and because I'm extremely active with various
things that I'm doing right now, making prototypes
and doing things, is little cuts and bruises
and burns from soldering iron, sharp bits of
metal that cut into your skin when you
least expect it, or when you're rebuilding a
machine or something, a motor, or working with
all kinds of stuff.
You're going to break your skin or bruise
it or burn it, and that is the
classic thing that I've been shouting from the
hilltops is wrap it and wrap it tight,
whatever it is, whether it's a burn, whether
it's a cut, a bruise, a fingernail lift,
or anything like that.
You get your finger caught in one of
these, get it pinched and you get those
crazy blood blisters.
With that, you only have a few seconds
to wrap it really tight because those are
very fast acting, and also the deeper the
cut, the faster you have to act.
That is classic Greek-speak stuff, very important.
What I want to add to that is
when you wrap it, well, when you wrap
it tight, you're preventing the loss of vacuum
so the body doesn't have to go into
emergency mode and start swelling all of the
tissue around it to prevent it.
It already senses that you are restoring the
vacuum very quickly.
The other thing is the interstitial spaces do
not, you know, the spaces that the cells
are pressed in together with do not expand,
again, for the same reason, and rapid, very,
very rapid healing takes place.
Now, of course, we know by now that
everything in the body works by induction.
When you take in anything, it doesn't pass
through any membranes.
It's created on the inside via induction.
What's interesting is when the wound is healing,
if you've ever looked at a wound, first
it drains a clear liquid.
Very rarely do you see blood.
It's a clear liquid, which typically forms a
scab, so it hides what it's really doing
underneath, and then the liquid becomes, that clear
liquid becomes an oily, thicker consistency, not a
pus.
Sometimes that also, there's like 14 different varieties
of what people call pus, and it's not
necessarily white blood cells either.
That is an oily substance, and then forms
into solids that forms the new tissue, and
there's almost like an energetic medium that controls
what is to form.
So, one thing I wanted to add to
the rapid compression, or wrapping it very tight,
is some kind of a salve or an
oil.
Now, the worst, or the bottom, I wouldn't
say that, because it works as well.
The bottom of the tier would be what
they call Vaseline or mineral oils, which is
in most commercial lotions.
I think if you're at this stage right
now where you're listening to Solosonics, you know
that, but I just wanted to bring it
up.
You would have to be a vegetable or
animal based is much better than a petroleum
based oil, but if that's all you have,
you know, what they call baby oil or
Vaseline, that would be at the bottom tier.
The next up from there would be your,
any kind of a cooking oil or coconut
oil or whatever, which is tropical, very thin,
and then up from there would be the
heavier salves.
When I say animal, there was a lanolin
based lotion or salves that were out in
the market.
I think they stopped using those for a
while.
Very hard to get that.
You also want to use a salve that's
made from an endangered species of some kind.
No, I'm just joking.
And up higher from that, by the way,
from the animal, would be the vegetable and
the vegetable pertaining to, of course, the temperate
or the climate that you're in and what
would be the season or climate.
So when you have a shift in climate,
make sure that you don't use tropical stuff.
Well, if you have to, it's better than
nothing.
But one thing I didn't never really got
into with just wrapping it tight is applying
some kind of an oil or a salve.
I want to thank personally Frank for sending
me some wonderful Burdock salve.
It's a, I don't like endorsing stuff, but
I have used it recently.
I've had a dry spot on the ankle
and it's, I'm very impressed with it.
It's a Diamond G Forest Products Healing Pine
Salve, Patterson, Georgia.
Ingredients, olive oil, pine gum, rosin, beeswax, turpentine.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's not the Burdock.
It's pine resin.
Yeah.
So that is a very interesting, I've been
using it.
I have a small dry spot on the
ankle on the left side, by the way.
It's kind of blocking excess yin from going
through into the ground and it's been reoccurring
for about a year or so.
And this year it's been okay.
But I noticed when I'm drying off sometimes,
there's a dried little spot.
It's about the size of a postage stamp.
And I've been keeping this on there for
about a week now and it's disappeared.
So it is quite effective.
And it's the, I just read the ingredients,
olive oil and pine.
So again, the reason why you want to
put some kind of a salve, by the
way, it's very old Testament, by the way,
you'll see that coming up that, you know,
you're not putting salve on stuff.
What's wrong with you, right?
Kind of a comment.
I'm just paraphrasing in the old Testament, but
in order for the skin to rebuild any
tissue to rebuild it, the energy that's induced
is pure energy.
And it starts to materialize into a gas
form first, and then it becomes a liquid
and then it becomes a gel.
And then it becomes the solid form and
tissue.
And what I mean that like your skin
cells are made of solid and gel and
liquid and gas, right?
So having some salve in the area would
definitely promote the healing only because it's what
the body is striving to do anyway.
It's kind of an interesting thing where it
was a very ancient methodology to put salves,
various salves for various ailments and cuts and
things like that.
It's less popularly used today.
There's first aid cream and things like that.
Again, petrochemical, not necessary.
But what I'm suggesting here is when you
wrap it tight, you can just...
Here's the thing about the reality we live
in.
When you do the wrapping tight, it has
to be done immediately or very quickly.
So don't spend time looking for salves and
things like that.
So the most immediate thing, even if it's
like vegetable shortening, put some vegetable shortening on
it.
The top tier stuff is vegetable based that's
temperate, meaning within the climate you're in, within
the region you're in, within the latitude.
And then the second best would be what
they call their products for skin, first aid
cream, whatever, and animal products, which you probably
won't find.
I don't think anyone's going to be putting
lard on there if it's listening to me.
And then the bottom tier would be just
the Vaseline.
But if you don't have anything and you
have access to Vaseline, don't use motor grease.
That's but in other words, keep it moist,
something there.
Now, if you just have hand cream and
hand lotion around, that's fine as well.
But some of the fragrances that they use
there burn.
In other words, if you have an opening
in the skin...
By the way, when you hear of people
getting cancers from using these products that they
put on the market, whether it's soaps or
lotions or whatever, it's actually the fragrance component
that causes the cancers in the body more
than any other of the components, which are
more inert to the body.
So one thing I always tell people, if
you're going to shop consumer grade, mainstream stuff,
get stuff that's fragrance free, because it's the
fragrance component that makes people ill more readily
than any other component.
Unless, of course, there's something just outwardly toxic
in there like dioxin-based bleaches and things
like that.
There's a long list of that, but it's
avoid the fragrances.
So keeping it moist, keeping it wet, and
wrapping it tight.
This goes for cuts and burns.
With burns, it's very popular.
Most people know about this already.
I've gone into the skin a little bit
very quickly.
If it's a dry spot, wet it.
If it's a wet spot, dry it.
With drying a starch, if you have a
wet spot on the body, which I don't
really see many topical things being wet unless
the skin is broken, some kind of a
starch, even cornstarch or flour would be the
best to draw that out.
Don't get into mineral powders.
They will burn.
So again, just to so far where we
are is relax the body, demagnetize the body
with a quick rinse.
And the ginger on skin bumps, a pimple
or acne or a mouth sore, and wrapping
things tight, of course, and using a salve
or wetting it down as well.
Now, one thing I also want to just
recap because I want to make sure people
are doing this correctly.
When you have a cut, for example, and
it just happened and you happen to be
somewhere where there's a napkin or some electrical
tape or something, even a rubber band or
something to wrap it tight, do so immediately
because it's the first 15 minutes that determines
whether it's going to heal in 24 or
36 hours or 72 hours or longer.
You want to make it as tight as
possible without hurting yourself, meaning if it's on
the finger, after 10 minutes, if you look
at your finger, it'll be numb and purple.
Let it out mostly so you get circulation
again and then put it back, but not
as tight.
And then let it out again after a
half an hour or 15 minutes again and
put it on again, not as tight, but
it should always be very firm, firmer than
just like bandages to stay on, even a
bandage should be firm.
In this case, you want it more firm
than is usually considered application of a bandage.
And that's how you would have it dressed
for the first day.
I don't think anyone is actually dense enough
to make it so tight that it's like
a tourniquet, but the idea is the tighter
it is, the more it will prevent signaling
to the body that there's an injury.
There's something that the body does that facilitates
an injury.
It tells, it's kind of like when if
there's a car accident and you call it
in, they're going to send someone, you know,
the police or fire department or whatever to
come check it out, right?
So when you, and then they show up
at the scene, the body does something very
similar.
If you wrap it very tight and say,
it's going to be fine, it doesn't send
that crew out to the injury.
And that crew is basically swelling, right?
Because it will create swelling of the tissue
around the wound to prevent any more loss
to the body.
But that defense mechanism also prevents the cut
or the bruise from healing quickly.
So the entire thing is to not call
the 911 of the body or not allow
that call to take place, right?
That's the whole purpose.
And also, of course, the rudimentary explanation of
the vacuum, maintaining the vacuum in the body.
So those are a few things or things
that I do often, and I don't think
I've ever discussed them in that order or
any order on how I, you know, these
are things that I always consider.
I'm frequently considering when I'm in discomfort or
feel a discomfort or the things that I
mentioned.
It's basically the quick wrapping, the ginger is
always on hand and the washing.
The other thing that I wanted to mention
also, which I do often, but especially when
I'm doing a hard labor kind of thing,
if I have to cut a bunch of
things and fabricate something and whatever, and I
don't do that often, and I get sore
and tired.
Especially if you're doing something where you're standing
up often or do a lot of walking
and you're not used to it, your legs
will be really sore and after a day
or so you don't recover.
Or any part of the body, general, it
might be general body soreness, like general upper
body soreness or general lower body soreness.
What I found works best to relieve that
is elevating the legs and literally like lay
down in bed, in a bed or couch
that's, or the floor that's near a wall
and just put your legs up as high
as possible with your back to the floor
and your legs pointing upward.
Doing that as a therapy for just even
five or 10 minutes twice a day will
relieve any kind of soreness in the lower
body.
What's interesting again, I speak a lot about
energy flow and whenever you feel a soreness
in a certain area, especially if it's going,
if it's the direction, you reverse the direction.
So soreness in the lower body, reverse the
lower body so it points up, right?
And that will relieve that.
And of course there's a very chemical, mechanical
side to that where, well, of course, Greek,
you know, if you lift the legs, the
circulation, all the blood flows out of it
and the lactic acid flows out of it
and all that, yes, that happens to a
degree.
But because remember, it's moving in a vacuum,
right?
It happens to a degree, but it also
creates a potential change where the energy on
the, especially on the left side of the
legs would be directed more towards the ground,
even on the right side is directed towards
the ground, but everything on the right side
wants to go upward.
Directing them upward, the bottoms of the feet
upward and the legs upward, there's things called
inversion tables and all that.
You don't need to get anything like that,
just simply even laying down diagonally on a
couch and putting your legs over the couch.
I found that relieves any kind of lower
body soreness, even lower body back pain, anything
like that from doing heavy lifting or work
that you haven't done or a long walking
that you haven't done in a while, if
you're, let's say, not out of shape or
not done something that you're not fit for
doing normally, inverting the body.
Likewise is true, by the way, if someone
spends a lot of time laying down and
they start to feel miserable because of that,
well, what's the remedy for that?
Stand up and walk around a little bit,
right?
And they usually feel better.
So the inversion principle, I find that I've
been doing that recently.
I've been doing some heavy lifting and things
and rebuilding machines lately.
And I'm like, man, I feel like crap.
So even today, I spent 15 minutes with
my legs up in the office.
I have a small futon.
I just put my legs up against the
wall and in the living room on the
couch, both 15-minute episodes, and I feel
refreshed and it's been hours.
So again, just these are the simple things
that I practice often.
And I wanted to share them in some
order so y'all get a feeling of
what I do and how effective this might
be for you.
And I hope it is.
So again, these are very simple things and
I'm looking forward to doing more of these.
I have tons and tons and tons of
things to say.
If anyone senses any delay, because I feel
like I sense a little bit of delay.
I've just been busier than normal and I
just don't have the energy to sit down
in front of the computer and do a
recording.
So this is an apology.
In other words, an explanation where I would
have liked to do things more frequently, and
I will in the near future.
In the meantime, again, simple remedies, figure mid
-season, peak of the year sort of, bring
this forward and hope everyone and anyone finds
this helpful.