Hey. Got you. All right, cool.
Yep.
Uh, no, we'll just, uh, I mean, yeah, I won't introduce it the way I normally do.
I just, you know, there we go.
Hey, something, something, uh, to consider, Danny, I really want you to keep this in your mind
as if you get the RSS feed when you go through WordPress. All right.
Yeah.
Oh, and we are live on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
This is an unscheduled broadcast. It just is going to emerge like this from time to time.
And in case you don't recognize my voice, this is Chaco Chelly host of the O'Chelly Effect.
So meanwhile, who do I have with me?
Well, and an unusual thing because there is no title for this. It just is as it is.
And, uh, yeah.
Yeah.
There you go. And of course, people consider this, uh, at this time, most notably, because here I go, I always have to tie it back to something that can be related to, right?
Of course, the discussions regarding land grabs, the Bureau of Land Management, G, what are people's rights, what is the process, what are they actually arguing over, where did this all begin, the bundys, the ranch, the ranchers, beneficial use, the government, the lines they cross, you know, I could just blur it all by you and it really doesn't matter.
And it doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Correct. And the other thing is, you know, I refer you to the O'Chelly and the Greek archive and look for something that references the Constitution.
Okay. There you go. And we can dispatch with the discussion of the Constitution by making a reference. There you go. There's your point of reference for that particular document.
Let's move forward.
[ Silence ]
Right.
Well, let me just say something here, too. The fact that you go back to the newspapers of the time, the magazines of the time is always very helpful.
I can tell you that personally, I own a few of the, say, the newspapers that were issued today that, because everybody knows I do a lot of JFK research, right?
So one of the things that I acquired for my own personal collection immediately, of course, were the newspapers from around the country in various cities, the day he was killed, the day after he was killed during that entire weekend to show what the reporting was like to take a look at, not only that, but the context.
Let's just say how much did things cost? What sort of stores were around then? What else was going on in the news that particular day, which, of course, was dominated by the Kennedy assassination?
But what was happening even the day before? All of these things are extremely relevant when considering how something was received by the society, because for a very long time, previous to internet time, guess what?
Dissemination was through these paper artifacts at this point, I could call them artifacts because of what they are now. But I mean, in real time, this was one of the best methods of distribution to the public.
So when you take a look at something and how relative it was and how widely known it may have been and what else was widely known at the time, definitely these articles are perfect for consideration when you want to take that look back and realistically step into the era.
And there you go, that's only 50 years ago, but even so, it does give you a different perspective from that which maybe is produced in a modern documentary on the subject.
And so I tell you that what you've done there is contextual research based on the publicly accessible information that was being distributed among the people.
So perfectly sensible. Anyway, that was just my commentary for that too.
[BANG]
Right.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, that's a problem because anybody who knows anything about what they call Native Americans and what I was quite satisfied to call Indians as children has a child.
You know, it seems to me as though our history tells us, I mean again, guessing a bit because a lot of it has been obviscated, but truthfully I think that our history could easily reveal to us even in part that the majority of the land we now describe as America was actually occupied by individuals who were Native to it.
See how I'm stressing these words here.
And so therefore, doesn't that kind of mean that they should not invade or take over or do anything with what would be considered Indian land?
[BANG]
Right.
Right. Now one thing, just one last commentary from me before we launch into this is this.
I ask you the listener to this, whoever you may be at whatever time it is, to consider the fact that at the time the general population was not aware of the mechanism that was in play was not aware of the real legal consequence of it or of the system that was in place.
What they were being made aware of, why is this relevant? What they were being made aware of is that these very dangerous, savage people who had strange beliefs did not look like the general population.
They in fact were something to be afraid of. So to the general population it was very simple. They could be decimated and far beyond pulverized whatever word it is you want to use.
I don't know what the active verb version of genocide is, but let's just say that this was all justifiable.
Because the other people, and also to the public's mind, the body...
Yes. Well they were acceptable and therefore it's just fine that you know I'm by my count at least a million Iraqis have probably been killed.
I did say a million and countless other just will just be really blunt and nasty about it, but countless other brown people or slightly brown people have been slaughtered, decimated, whatever depending on how you limit the geographical container on the subject have been absolutely beset upon for similar reasons.
In the public's mind mind you, I'm just giving you the whole... yeah.
Well, right. Well I'm just making the commentary because somebody might say, well gee you know that worked that way because all the people that were around at the time who were supposedly benefiting as the individuals who were being represented by the United States and their various entities etc etc.
Well they acquiesced to this because why? Well if you demonize the people and you show that they are different and I'm just pointing out that the technique hasn't changed.
Yeah that's all.
Well right and I also advise you as a companion,
I also advise you as a companion piece in case you're just picking through the archives to check on the Oceleon the Greek episode which I don't remember the number off the top of my head but I do believe it was about Satanism.
Okay so yeah believe it.
Yeah well but it does I'm not telling people just to go listen randomly though am I.
Thank you.
Right.
[silence]
Right and part of the absolute necessity and I do mean absolute necessity of participation in just about any of the ancient goddess religions because there's more than one they all have their roots in the same very same sort of tenants but the truth is that you have to actually you know here we go I'll give it to you very straight and simple.
The concept that it is fully acceptable for you to be lied to is literally based on the fact that you accept it so if you accept a lie the lie therefore becomes perfectly reasonable it's it's a good thing to do in fact so if I can rob you if I can steal from you and get you to say thank you for doing it.
Then I am fully in compliance with my adherence to the ancient goddess religion that's that's the truth.
[silence]
Right.
Okay.
Oh sure.
Well Lewis and Clark for example yeah.
Yeah we're not saying that this is the original you know plan of action that was created in exactly that year as a matter of fact the point being made repeatedly by me in every presentation I do is that guess what the mechanism has not changed the motivation has not changed in fact it is the very same game being played over and over again no matter how many times you take out that monopoly game.
Or whatever let's let's be a little more modern no matter how many times you take out your ps4 and you stick a disc in it and therefore and so on and so forth there's still a controller there's still a game being played there is still something which is being interacted with and guess what you can change the way it's packaged you can change what you call it but fact is the guts of it the idea that it is there for your amusement.
And that there is still some sort of thing to contend with well the principles are effectively the same and that is the way the code there you go the history works this way.
There we go.
Right.
Well in fact even the the name America in some way relates to one of these explorers previous to it there was a guy named America vest buti that was sent out to do similar things of course he did not discover America or anything like that but anyway that's kind of irrelevant to
America.
Much like a surveyor does today when engaging in a legal process right now guys that go out and measure it and say you have this type of property
you have this many trees grass grows on it or doesn't grow on it etc etc right.
There you go.
All right the land in what's on it just like the surveyor there's a home okay there's also a garage there are three flag poles whatever same thing.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay today I'll give you for instance I got a notice from a PayPal which said that they were part of a class action lawsuit right where a bunch of people get together and actually target not a person but a thing which is a corporation okay and they seek damages and actually I have the right to fill out a form and make a claim.
To get a part of this class action lawsuit because I have been recognized as one of the damaged parties okay.
Yeah.
No but you know what it's very very real because I was actually involved in one of the situations once and that's precisely what happens they still collect their fees in some cases as part of the situation somehow or other the person they're suing lines of giving them money you know just to the attorney not to the damage party and and suddenly you have you know a failure to have.
Those damages recognized in the case just disappears and yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Right. No to the list there we are now entering the place where things don't make sense.
Yes literally just to wind it back once more and then I promise I'll let you fly because it's going to get crazy from here on out but here's the thing yeah literally what you just said just to make make make it very perfectly plainly clear is that they created a description they create a piece of paper or they don't create a piece of paper.
They put together a piece of paper which then becomes the representation of something hardly even matters what it is and then they literally because now that thing exists then create an action against that thing which they created did I miss a step here.
Okay.
Right. I just wanted to.
Right.
No.
Yeah. Right.
Right.
Right. Now look. Here's a couple of notes just real quick. First of all if you go to a post office today you will still find legal notices hung on the wall somewhere.
If you look in the back of those things we call newspapers from time to time I do pick one up and guess what I see that there is on occasion something they call legal notices and these are perfectly acceptable menus to post such things.
Okay. Just pointing out that you know just pointing out that this is not you know an ancient mechanism. Yeah. That's all.
Right.
Well yeah that's interesting too because just the word trespass I've often heard it used in other ways and it sounds to me like a singular trespass is something that in a lot of philosophical veins let's you say.
And initial trespass is not a violation necessarily but.
Right.
Right. And so it's to note it to break it down once again just in case that was too fast coming from you the idea is that if someone wants to let's just say theoretically send a legal notice to be applied posted on your property.
Okay. They do because your sign says no trespassing have the ability to go there that first time and do it without being in violation of trespassing so it is a notice it's a proper notice and literally they've left the loophole open for themselves.
Now if the sign did say no trespass or do not trespass this is a bit different because that means that you're not allowed to be there without expressly given permission.
I mean yeah.
Right.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
That's the bottom line there.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Right. Yeah. Good good note there. I was just about to say that. Yes. That's how it's done.
Right.
Oh no no no no look this is this has nothing to do. Yeah. Right. I know. You could note that if you like but I mean we also weren't talking about how Abner Double Day laid down the rules for baseball either.
So what do you know?
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Yeah. No, we all recognize that we're on the same rock and so on and so forth but not everybody's happy about it. Let's put it down.
Well, right. Yeah, that's a whole other thing but I mean that's like trying to tell you the entire backstory for situations that you see emerging now. Nobody, nobody really wants to hear that.
Let's talk about the meat of it and the meat of it is here's the process which is being used so now you can actually understand why it emerges as it does. That's all.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Right. That was going to be my next point is that you know you can take this as a matter of fact because we haven't even bothered to to convlude the situation with the rest of that story.
You can take this and understand that this is applicable to various situations. You know somebody, literally this is why I keep going back to imagine your house and somebody coming to your property.
Right because it works the same way.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[silence]
Hmm, like right now, we still have the territories to this day, two of them most notably
are what Puerto Rico, and I think the Philippines is still our territory.
Right.
[silence]
No, but that's what it is, isn't it? Yeah.
Hmm.
Yeah, it could be tangible, even a coupon that's expired has what, a two tenths of a penny worth of value, or whatever, yeah, it actually has some value, but this actually is just an idea that's observable and doesn't actually have a physical value.
And actually have a physical manifestation behind it, and that's all it is.
[silence]
Organ. Yeah, actually you could have heard in the alternative media from one person who said, "Why did they not attempt to exhaust the legal process?"
And well, there was two of us anyway.
[silence]
Hmm.
No, we only mentioned it in as much as it is not part of the conversation. I think that's about it, yeah.
[silence]
Hmm, but, hmm.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Well, always does.
Hmm.
Yeah, I was going to say you are notified in one form or another.
So, back to the meat of the issue because you really stuck to this really well.
I think we should just leave it there and continue on.
What happens next in the process?
Hmm.
Well, let's finish up with the follow-through on the explanation though, just a bit.
Now, enforcement comes in, this is where we sort of left it and then we talked about, you know.
Right.
Oh yeah.
your head count. Guess what, you could have a head count and quite honestly scalps are impossible
to misrepresent. If you've got that many scalps, then that came from that many heads. It's
pretty definitive. And yeah, you've got an accurate head count and you don't have to actually
carry full bodies around to prove your point. So, go ahead.
[Silence]
You know, kind of like when you're faced with the idea of individuals who were supposed to
be terrorists because they showed up and they blew up people that had nothing to do
with their conflict and they actually did this on a massive scale and struck fear into
a population and therefore they are terrorists and in a lot of cases what you really have is
them responding in like manner to what was done to them initially. Again, I say that
the technique remains the same. Yeah.
[Silence]
Right.
Right. It actually gives a, you know, primary precedence.
That's what I was looking for, precedence is the word I was looking for, to your right to collect on the value of the thing.
You now literally have an interest in it in the same way that the individual who is supposed to be owning it has an interest in it and therefore has to be compensated.
That's all it is, yeah.
[Silence]
Well, well I gotta tell you I am getting a little bit tired but here's the thing maybe it's just me but I think we need to follow through completely on the rest of the process because you got into some other explanations which were very valid and part of the story for sure.
We have lost sight of that initial process we were describing to begin with and you know what? It seems like that's part of the purpose in fact.
[Silence]
I just had somebody teach me how to pull apart code, and then I would look at a Asian look
at the code and then go, oh okay, that's how that's done.
Yeah.
OK.
You take a look at my site look silly now, but you've got to remember it originated in like
these seven.
And I specially, I specially alerted Clever handle to be listening.
So.
Yeah, now she was a little upset about it and I was like, well, you know what, go go
over to AFR at midnight, you'll hear something.
Yeah.
Oops.
Yeah, that's all.
I just gave you the link from, yeah, I just gave you the link from my crappy old website,
but I put it in the wrong place there, but you guys can take a look at it.
You know, I just had text links that you could click on and stuff like that.
And it was mainly just for my poetry and then I had a black Sabbath fan website connected
to it and it still exists, but like I said, it began in the 90s.
So the structure of it though was like written by me code by code.
So, you know, that was my sense of humor, bro.
I mean, I'm a little rough with that kind of stuff.
What can I say?
You got it.
Apparently Daniel wants me to join him tomorrow night, so I'll be back around then.
No, I know.
So, he wants to watch it.
All right, guys.
Talk to you tomorrow.
All right.
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]