[Music]
Hello and welcome to the Free Zone.
Well, it has been one wild ride as we have all been expecting.
But we need to know, are we communicating?
I mean, who wrote your operating system?
Is your head in a vacuum?
We're going to find out as we speak with a natural philosopher today.
I call them that because if I ever felt like I was talking to someone from the future,
it's while talking with the Greek.
And so, after all of the shenanigans that we've been witnessing,
I could think of no one better to come and really give us a heads-up view
of our world as it is, as it has been, and what it will be.
So, please welcome to the show The Greek.
It's great to have you here with us.
Oh, thank you, Freeman. It's, I guess, good to be back.
Any kind of venue that we could come out and display or do a good public report
is always advantageous for the audience.
So, again, thanks for thinking of me.
Yeah, we are hungry for the knowledge we are.
And we're looking at a world in chaos.
We're seeing everybody function on the programming inside of their operating system.
They don't even know that it's happening.
They don't know where this operating system came from.
Now, in February, nine months ago, we were speaking.
And you said, your vote is your vow to accept the electors' choice.
And I think we should open the show with that in that,
nine months ago, you said this. And now, here we are with liberals in the streets
and bloody, violent riots trying to flip the vote.
And it's blowing my mind, honestly.
I didn't think that the Hillary supporters would be out beating up people in the streets.
I thought, but what I do know is that what they, the they want is chaos.
So, let's look at the operating system that would develop into this idea that
you would write in the streets over this.
And the legal and lawful ways that this is also wrong.
Take it from whoever you want.
Sure. Let's look at it real simply.
What is possible, pretty much anything is possible.
And who can ponder all the possibilities?
So, you have to be a good observer to see what's happening.
And what is happening is possible because it's happening.
So, you know, when you talk about the operating system, you know,
let's use the computer as a metaphor.
You have an operating system, then you have programs, and then you have files.
Most people are actually trying to process files and programs, and they have no operating system.
And what I mean about that is your operating system, this might sound dogmatic now, comes from your God,
comes from your deity, someone you look up to.
Like if you're three years old and you're formative years, your parents are your God.
So, what I mean by God is a higher authority, not only in concept but in actual power,
like the unseen world, rules, the seen world, you know, shadow government, anyone, anyway.
So, what we're talking about here is things to come might seem fascinating to people,
or how things work because they really just haven't thought it out,
or they don't have the convention to access this way of thinking or seeing things,
because the operating system comes from your deity and they don't acknowledge that.
For example, every country has a patron or patron deity in the Western world.
Most of the countries have adopted the revived goddess religion.
And when I say operating system, it's where you get your law, not traffic law or tax law,
but when you eat what you wear, how you operate in business, how you raise a family,
how you keep time, that comes from your God.
And they have up the Western world has incorporated the revived goddess religion,
aka known as Justicia or Justice, Statue of a Woman Holding Scales Blindfolded and such.
Right, you'll see Statues. She's also known as Columbia, Britannia, you know,
a lot of other aspects of, you know, let's say smaller societies have their different gods,
right, they've revived various different gods and that's where they get their law form from.
Now, the interesting thing about that is if you are atheistic in any capacity,
you still cannot escape this. Like, for example, discussing, you know, having this discussion
with an atheist, they'll say, well, Greek or Freemony, I don't believe in any God.
Well, that's really simple. You just ask them, do you then follow or believe in the laws of the state?
And they almost always say, yes, well, then there's your God in April 1st is your holiday.
So you see, this is the operating system and it's in place and no one is paying attention to it,
but it doesn't mean that they're not subject to it, right? Let's go back to the Justice aspect.
How many times have you heard in terms of law form? Let's, in this case, it would be legal form.
You'll have to be brought to justice. You serve justice as a miscarriage of justice,
right, and all of these things. So they're using this in front of you. They have the iconography
and statuary to prove it. Now, their agents and the priesthood and the entitled classes that rule
the rest of the people, guess what? They don't even know it in most cases. They are just following along.
So tie that into what's going on. I think you mentioned what the month is called February.
We discussed about what voting actually means. It means to vow that you are supporting the system
and whatever electorate body decides to elect. You are all for it. I'm with you guys.
And this is what's going on, let's say regarding the condition of what is possible.
I guess there's a protest against the electorate. But so these are the possibilities that cannot be
thought of but observed and maybe described. So that could tie into the rest of the discussion
because it's not very narrow and linear. So what do you think? Do you want to maybe perhaps go down
the path of the political path or just still maybe the general aspect of what the operating system is?
I'm really happy to hear your general views of things because I swear that you are from the future
Greek. So I think that you're you are the master of the obvious that no one ever sees.
Oh, thank you. I want to share that with with my audience because you point out things that are
just right in front of our phases and we never stop to think about them. So I really want to
follow your lead. Okay, well, you know, I have like a stock way of speaking and typically it's
metaphorically, you know, the last thing for mankind to discover is what's obvious, right?
And the obvious is just what's right in front of you. Let's not be hypocritical. I mean, people want to go
out and to far away places and far away thinking to discover things but typically their shallow thinking
gets them diving off into the deep end, right? So if you're going to be shallow about things, you know,
take care of business and what's just five feet around you first, you know, and the stock way of
starting off on anything like this is, you know, people don't even know what day it is. Now what I mean
by that, it sounds kind of bizarre whether you care or not, it's the concept of time. You know, you've
heard in the new age movement a lot of loosely thinking people say, well, there's no such thing as time.
Well, that's correct in a sense because time is nothing other than the recordation and memorialization
of events. So when you hear about time travel, you're not really traveling in time. You're either
going to past or future events and time is the recordation of such. So currently, if you ask anyone
what day it is, they're actually not giving you the day, they're giving you the date, they're giving
you something off of what I loosely call the Pope's work schedule, which is anything between January
through December, Monday through Friday. And they usually have this thing called hours and minutes,
which is what I call the wind up toy known as the clock. So typically, you know, just to refresh people,
if you don't even know what day it is, how are you going to navigate because time is important for
navigation. You know, if you're moving 20 miles per hour for one hour, that you've covered 20 miles,
right? Anyone that navigates or plots things understands time is important. How are you going to
navigate the waters of the universe, social aspects and even any cosmological aspect if you don't
know how to reckon time? For example, if you observe a what's called a birthday or anniversary
any year, you'll notice that it's a different day of the year every year, right? If you look at what
day it is today, folks, you look last year and look at next year, it's a few days off. So what day is it?
It's none of it. It's the Pope's work schedule, meaning it is nothing more than is if you worked at
a corporate headquarters and they gave you a chart with different color days and this is when you work.
So no one really knows what day it is. And in that day aspect is not about being usurped by
a schedule, but actually accessing information that anyone can access without buying anything or having
an allegiance or subscribing. So this convention of what's called the Gregorian calendar that's been
accepted by all society is very much considered, you know, the state of society on the planet has been
being pretty pissed poor if you can't navigate using any good timekeeping. And let me just throw in a
quick thing. This is kind of long-winded. See, years ago people settled their debts with the full moon,
which is really the new moon, rises in the east. That's why today you still get a moonfully bill,
don't you? Don't they give you a moonfully bill? It's called moonfully, but you see the moon rules the
month. And the day starts at high noon, right? Not at midnight. If you remember banking before the
electronic convention, if you'd made a deposit afternoon, it was considered the next day in the wild west
type of society in the US, they had court in the morning and they executed sentence the next day.
They hung you when? High noon. So we're having the day beginning at noon. And actually the time-keeping
conventions of the world, which would be Greenwich and the other one I believe is in Colorado Springs,
in Naval Observatory. If you look up, this was, I'm not sure if it's still there, but on their website,
Julian Calendar Day, they clearly tell you that the day starts at solar noon, but for scientific
purposes, I mean, it starts at high noon for scientific and astronomical purposes, but for the people
at civil midnight. That's like how it's kind of a put down sort of how like the dictionaries were
assembled 200 years ago, they weren't sure how to define words. When you looked up the word oats,
it said what they feed horses in England, but the staple of people in Scotland. So this is being
put in front of you and no one is really noticing that there's a shifting of time, meaning the way
you record time. Time doesn't shift because the events are the events. It's just that you cannot
record it. So now if you don't have a way of memorializing time, how are you going to memorialize
or record events? Very loosely. So that's why you have a lot of this false hope in things. Let's go,
keeping it back to the conversation, tying it back to the recent election in the US.
You have a character now under the covenant that I live by, by the way,
any, I don't speak poorly of the leader of any people because they're put there by divine right,
believe it or not. This is where the Asians are correct. But you have a character here who is,
let's say, allegedly the leader of the American society, now North American known as the United States
of America, what made him so popular is a very, very loose statement. Let's make America great again.
And that's all that it took. There's no understanding of that. What do you mean by that?
Just getting people riled up about it, you see? And if you want to understand that concept a little
more, even though this is perhaps a one hour or a one hour or two hour recording,
anyone is interested a little bit more on what's called this crowd mentality. I recommend them to
consider Gustav LeBond's The Crowd. It's on book form, ebook form, audio book form, and start delving
into how the crowd mentality works. And you will see it from a social perspective, how this man
really compiled something really well in the 1895, I believe. And that will give you an understanding on that.
But again, just to go back to maybe leading this conversation, people still have not realized that
they're not able to memorialize timekeeping and will awful timekeeping. Other things are within
their physical reality. You know, you ever notice how heat rises and cold descends, but in all biological
systems, the cold rises and the heat descends, like a cool feat and cool head and warm feet.
Or when you go up into the sky, it's cold and down in the valley, it's hot. All biological systems have
opposite movement. Why aren't people demanding from their technicians and engineers to design
artificial heating equipment to do that? So right now they're just passively ignorant of this
fact. And they have air conditioning and heating in their cars, homes, and boats and places that give
them a hot head and cold feet and no one is paying any attention. You see, you know, the other stock thing
is going back to their deity. Now most people when you bring that up, you know, they're God, they think
of religion and you have the major religions, Islam, Christianity, Buddhism, Hinduism and such and
all the spin-offs. Do you know that none of those religions know or do anything that's in the text
that they alleged to subscribe to? Yes. At all. And I'm not talking about taking it out of context and
it's really easy to start a religion. Like for example, if you look at the, a lot of the Catholic
Christian memes, you know, if you want to start a subgroup in there, it's very simple. Get a
chocolate chip recipe, bake a cookie, bake a set of cookies. And if one of them looks like what's
called the Queen of Heaven, you tell everyone and in about a month, you'll have a thousand people
following you asking you about how that cookie crumbled, right? So this is very, very simple. I mean,
people again, the crowd mentality, but going back to no one knows or does anything that's in the text
that they alleged to subscribe to, meaning in context. And here's the thing, if these texts are
divinely inspired and you are told that no one can understand them or that's your interpretation
indirectly what people are saying is the gods are acting in futility. And I'll tell you for sure
the gods do not act in futility. They might have an IQ of two million and they're giving you baby
talk and you still can't understand it, but that message is not futile. Now here, just to lay
something out. A lot of times I refer to the what's called the biblical text and that's very difficult
to discuss because guess what? All of the versions that you have and all the languages have been
translated in based on King James or other things is not a translation. It is a version. There's
over 27,000 critical mistakes in that document. It's irrelevant in terms of getting the proper
message. Now what you're getting is a general outline of the story, but you will be it is
wrought with error. So you're going to have to go back to the languages of preservation. Sorry,
from that point of view, the same goes with any of the texts in any other language. These texts
are preserved in their original languages and it's not going to be given to you on a silver platter.
You're going to have to do the work. Now when you look at these religions as being the
let's say or as I stated earlier, your god is your law form and such.
And you have now debased it and are going by tradition. For example, Christmas and Easter
bunny and all these other things are not in the biblical text, but the majority is what
Christianity is defined. Public prayer and Islam, mosques and other things about women covering
their bodies and all that is not in the Quran. But they still do it. So these traditions or
let's go back to Buddhism, they have a little statue or Hinduism, you have certain practices.
You will not find that in the Rig Vitas or any of the writings either. So these cultural
traditions, behaviors that the people engage in also have a deity or an entity behind them.
But it is not the one that they think. So they've been kind of winked. So again, we have many,
many layers. Let's go back to the political aspect with this selection. How many times have you
heard of what's called the shadow government? I believe there was even a public speech warning by
Kennedy regarding that. And even Christ. Yeah, and the WikiLeaks. And actually, Woodrow Wilson had
alluded to that about there's a conspiracy so great no man can go against it or something like that
in paraphrasing. There is another entity behind that. So we're talking about a world of the unseen.
Now what I mean by that, it just hasn't been properly identified just like years ago if people
used hot coal to cool to heat their house and they close the doors and windows, they woke up dead and
they didn't know what killed them. It was the ether they called it. But later on they discovered
there's something called carbon monoxide and they had a carbon monoxide detector and now you know
not to do that because you can specifically identify the agent that brought that situation on.
Currently, humanity is in a state where they cannot specifically identify the agents that
bring about their condition, aka known as the gods or unseen beings. Yes, and I'm not really crazy
thinking that I have friends that you can't see. This is just based on what has been memorialized.
Now if you memorialized in texts and information we can access, meaning if you think like most people
that everything came into creation less than a hundred years ago and everyone that wrote anything
prior to you regarding the gods is an idiot or you don't have to believe in it, you are not
examining information that is available to you to explain many of the things that are going on.
Without a doubt, you know exactly what you're saying it's all social norms and none of it
is the documented evidence which again they're only allowed versions and then with this
traditional standpoint and the versions that they're dealing with and I've seen you know,
Christians that disagree with interpretations and get thrown out of their church or whatever
you know back and forth because of interpretation and we're looking at a situation where they
want to rile up the mob and all the fanatics are out there screaming kill all the fanatics.
So, right. Well here's the thing you brought up church and all of these institutions, these temples.
They are just revived a post-flood let's say paganism like the word church comes from Cirque
it actually Latin word for circus the three ring Circus or what's called the Trinity they won't
find that in the text but they memorialize that now let's just get down and dirty about it which is
actually true and clean is that Christianity was started pretty much very much how 9/11 conspiracy
movement was started. No one really knew how those buildings came down in public and mass groups
so they they have all of these people saying oh it was thermite oh it was some space weapon or
whatever but actually what brought them down is quite simple device and it's not what people think
because they don't understand the structure of the building. Now what was going on around the first
century there was a lot of incredible events happening and there was a lot of a rumor mill that was
going and the events were usurped by the typically a fellow named Simon Magus Simon Simon the
magician and he was quite popular and quite wealthy like a Houdini or a David Copperfield with the
budget of let's say Bill Gates or George Soros right and he was at that time period and he didn't
know what was going on either but he was able to promote for his advantage the frenzy
that was going on about the events in the first century then to focus on what he was saying about it
right and he was also a Samaritan descent which the Samaritans are very interesting if you look them
up back in the day they had their pagan gods but they also invited let's say scriptual law so
there were a good mishmash of everything and also when you look at the history of Simon Magus you have
the offshoots of what's called nosticism right and all these other aspects of Christianity but if
anyone studies the biblical text you'll see that everything that they're doing not some of what
Christianity is doing but everything Christianity is doing is either on the abominations list or the
don't do list of the biblical text now the problem with discussing this like this and not making
this a quote unquote religious discussion is I want to just make a comment there's quite a few people
unstudied and unfamiliar with the text that come out and say it was a different god of the new testament
than the Old Testament right many times have you heard that well the thing that they miss out
on that the so-called god of the new and Old Testament is the same one and it's not what people think
it is the Christ himself in the text now this is not as nothing to do with what you believe in
because the Christ was god himself manifest in according to the text so one of the main things that
they bring up is how in the Old Testament the Israelites were told to go and kill every man,
woman, and child in certain cities before they occupied the land and in the New Testament it's
all about love and peace and all this and there couldn't be anything further from the truth they
have not studied the text now I tell people in passing and they find it very shocking but who
is the most hateful character in the biblical text pause they can't answer it's the Christ how do
you know well you just read the text he'll say things like think not I brought here to bring peace
I came to divide with the sword I will bring terror amongst you oh another thing that's stated in
in the in the in what's called the New Testament is that you've been better off been at Sodom and
Gomorrah than what's going to come upon your village or city or how about this one um why do you
speak to the people in parable in riddle it's the truth is not given to them it's given to you
right so you have many of these aspects now what I mean by hateful meaning that hateful of the way
that man operates at this point right and even at that point now let's just jump back to the Old
Testament remember I just mentioned that they were told to go kill every man, woman, and child
in animals as well so it can't be the same god right because they have this concept and I just
showed that he's not about love and peace well why why did they tell the Israelites to go in and kill
everything and everyone that moved you ever wonder why well it's very clear in the text that they
were engaged in pretty abominable acts that are actually represented in parity today hey Freeman
let's go back in time we're gonna walk down an ancient canaanite village you ready I'm gonna let's
uh hold hands and go on a windy walk through let's say ancient canaan right this is we're talking
about the time that the Israelites were told in and go ahead and slaughter everything and everyone so
what we're walking down a public square right now and we're looking in one shop and what do we see
well we see a whole bunch of animals tied down donkeys horses sheep chickens and like you're like well
what's that for I said well this is a sex shop you know people like to get off before they go to
you know into the marketplace down the road this is what they do right so you get all these
animals possibly knocked up with human sperm oh let's go to the next shop what do you see there
oh I see all these little children and cages what's that for oh well you'll see down at the end
of the square there you'll see a seated statue it's made of bronze and it's a glowing red hot
and people are told to make a wish a prosperity by placing a child in its lap and searing it alive
but it's kind of hard to do business when you hear children being burned alive so they ring bells
you know if you've ever heard of a fat red character where a child is placed on his lap and you have
bells involved like jingle bells right that's mullick revived mullick now this is the type of society
that was operating out and open out in public back then so that these people were unreadable
that was so incorporated into their society that they would rather die than let it go and they were
accommodated by that now what you have in this modern society how many times have you said have you
heard let's say people saying oh we have to preserve Christmas you know the actual thing right
you see you see what's going on it is exactly the same society but it's in parity another thing I
bring up is what do cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common right I think I don't know if you
brought this up previously but you see these things all tie in together and we can go into what cannibals
birthdays and dolls maybe have in common in the second hour perhaps because that's a little bit of
a litany on its own so perhaps all of these things and these misunderstandings something is minor of what
religion is and discounting the facts behind it and then having pseudo academics or academics promoting
a dichotomy that doesn't exist for example the Old Testament God is different than the New Testament
God is foolishness right and by the way at this point I'll say this publicly I am embarrassed
to be in a room with anyone who has more than an eighth grade conventional education you know
for example have you ever seen people drive around in the cars of a bumper sticker my child is an
honor student at this school and my child goes to that school and they're so proud of it sure
well I want to make a bumper sticker that says that the only reason I'd said my child to a public
school or university is if I knew there were a complete moron so anyway that is a personal comment
on the current system and everyone's idea that everything is propaganda that this is just a tool
of indoctrination and is that what you mean by this? Well yeah it's indoctrination but either
accommodating the people like for example there's there's a reason why fast food is so crappy
because people want to be accommodated by fast food but and they don't really care about what the
ingredients are so how are you going to make a profit if you use higher quality ingredients so you
keep it at a minimal high profit because the people don't care it's what you get away with it's
with the market will bear you know here there's something that I've always discussed in the past
it's called pranking humankind right now is subject to a cosmic prank and in other words all
of your entitled classes your doctors your attorneys your professors your scientists are pranking
you now what's a prank look it up it means ludicrous trick but the primary prankers are your parents
in most cases meaning like when you're a child you're told about Santa Claus in the tooth fairy
or you told about this or that and one of them is like you can't see ghosts either right there's a
boogie man in the closet no you didn't see anything yes you did okay so you're being pranked by your
own parents who take the seat of God at that time because you're not aware of any higher authority
even the state as a child and at some point the parents tell you oh you're you're too old for that
right now you can't talk about Santa Claus or the Easter Bunny what's wrong with you right they
never apologize see that's why you have a lot of psychological problems with teenagers
in the western world is because the parents never apologize for all the pranking they did here's
another former pranking the parents yeah they have the steep psychological embedded thing that you
all need to do is apologize for lying to the child now here's the other yeah I was just gonna say
that's how Catholics become Satanus well yeah we can get into that no but you know you can't you
can't be a Satanus without being a Christian and I see so often that what happens is is that
disillusionment when the you know the prank is revealed and they're like they become the complete
opposite of what they were you know they're operating but it's but again it's not let's let's hold
the pranking thought for a moment Satan is a character that anyone can research he is only dealing
with major institutions he doesn't deal with each individual at a time he will in the future
with one individual aka known as the anti-Christ he's the only man in history that Satan will actually
possess all of the other ones are demonic possessions there are trillions of demons you can even
have five thousand demons in in in one person in one man or woman right so they're forget about
the seven billion people there's trillions upon trillions of these of these entities in the spiritual
realm you absolutely believe in deities and demons well it's not a matter of believing in them as
I've looked at what's been memorialized about them and I've found it to be validatable and sound
information and if you want to go that's what belief should be based on if I write you a check
for fifty grand and you call the bank and and there's fifty grand in the account to be transferred
to you for example you can go around telling people you just got fifty grand even though you haven't
yet because everything's in place for it to happen believe should be based on things that are in
place that will happen not some obscure abstract insanity that most people are operating on but let's
go back to the satanism well you hear a lot of people in these small occulted movements known as
satanists they're really not and they will tell you when they set up like a satanic temple that
who their entity is like for example the temple of set that is not Satan that is an ancient god
revived from aegypt for example and there are others various bells or balls or lords satan is in
control this this whole entire social construct is his meaning satan doesn't deal with a little
satanic temple that is a revived demon as a minor very very minor impure demon satan is in control
of all the governments of the world all the religions of the world all of your sciences all of your
entertainment very very subtly you see so to say that catholics leave that to become satanic well is
Catholicism one of the major religions of the world yes right so it is also under the control of
that right it's very easy now satan just means adversary now i want to just we're going to go back
to the pranking hopefully because that's very important i believe in some of the disclosure that
i like to give i didn't mean to derail you because we did cover satan pretty good last time yeah
but actually let's cover one one more thing in there when you read in the book of genesis what would
they give you regarding satan and all that is known as a serpent right people they it's been i
in iconography statuary and in legend even in film shown as a as an actual animal a snake right
now if you actually go read the text in in context you will see that is the name of an individual
that is very and very anthropomorphic have you ever heard of a man or a woman's name called robin
or someone called hawk does that mean that they're a bird no it just happens to be their name so when
you go and look at what's in the original language of preservation what is being translated as the
serpent is actually someone's name and this is someone that has taken the form anthropomorphically
spirit being that is engaging primary man and primary woman let's say right you know so there's
there's an aspect to that that needs to be looked at and i mean we can do 500 hours and not repeat one
thing and and give an encyclopedia on this that anyone can access the problem is people just don't
care at this point right but we're going to say it anyway now i want to go back to the pranking
and um you are all subject to a prank which is eluticrous trick
and uh what i mean by that is that if you try to rationalize a prank you cannot it's purely emotional
and if you ask the prankster why are you pranking me they never give a rational answer but the
ultimate answer is because i can and i feel like it that's why i tell people do you know i'd have a
false sense of optimism on this planet if you woke up this morning alive be thankful that you are
because the reality of the violence level of violence spiritual and physical on this earth is
not really comprehended by most people i tell people basically be thankful that while you were sleeping
last night wherever you were that no one came through the door of where you were sleeping and rip the
liver out of your body be thankful that didn't happen this is the potential level of violent side
everyone is living under right now and if you by the way someone did do that or attempted to do that
to you while you were ripping the liver out of your body if you ask them why are you doing that
they say because i feel like it and that is good enough and that's what i mean about the level of
pranking on this planet if you talk to any of the entitled classes the doctors the attorneys the
leaders of the people the academics and all that they're all working on a particular field of
their specialty but none of them know anything about what's been memorialized about that field in
other words there are set memorialized documented rules and how are they are to operate and none of them
know any of these rules are very few of them operate along them at all the giving an example like
what's called law enforcement you know there is no law enforcement that knows any law they're being
directed by the attorney general's office to do things right for example if you get pulled over
what's called pulled over with the flashing lights and the issue with ticket or whatever it
doesn't matter if they're a sheriff a local police or highway patrol or whatever do you know that in
order for them to properly be able to do that they have to have what's called d_o_t_ certification
and they the actual ticket itself has to be signed by the director of the department transportation in
federal office and how many of them do you think have to apartment transportation certification
not one and it doesn't matter because the rest of society will say if you tell an acquaintance a friend
a family member what happens is well you shouldn't have been speeding well you shouldn't have done that
that's what happens here i'm like but it's not according to the rules but does it well that's that's
the society we live in this is how people react so they're subject to the prank and also there's
a sense of voluntary like is him in it who we have has to be voluntary but most people don't know
what they're volunteering in the group of prankster will say here would you like to sit
and uh... you say yes and now he's placed a thumbtack on the seat you sit on it and get
you know damaged or injured from it and you jump up and say why did you do that this is well you know you're
the one who said yes i you wanted to sit you know the pranking part well that was you know that's how i
have fun you see that's how i roll that's how i roll and this is how your professors are this is how
your law enforcement is this is how your legal this is how your religious people are
confront any e-mama priest bishop guru regarding what they're doing and they're saying it doesn't
matter as just need to believe or leave me alone right they don't want to know anything so
we're not saying this because anything is going to change but we're saying it because this is the
rationale behind the irrational that's going on on this planet right now and what is going on on
this planet ultimately in a big sense is that folks time ended almost 18 years ago and you're in
the credits part of the movie right now what i mean by that is if you're going to shoot a two-hour
movie do you get just exactly two hours of film or do you have to get two hours in 10 minutes because
you have to roll the credits the credits started rolling around the fall of 1998 and what's you in
the reason i use that metaphor is simply this the purpose of the credits is to give credit to the
efforts and the people behind it and also it's to show what you didn't see in the in the main feature
and also the order of importance sometimes has changed but you get to see all the things behind the
scenes and the other interesting thing about using this as a metaphor is you ever notice while the film
is running if someone speaks or stands up you're promptly told to be quiet or sit down but when the
credits are rolling the film is still technically rolling but people are talking people are moving
around and there's disturbance in the theater but it doesn't matter because it's the credits that's
why since 1998 when you see all these things happening it just doesn't matter people don't see it
you see so we're talking about all the corruption the child trafficking even spirit cooking all coming
to the surface coming to the light and who cares right it's the movie is over you know it's they're
not going to tell you shut up and sit down and and this is how it's just pretty much you know
metaphors are simple and this is not an oversimplified metaphor it's just another perspective on what is
going on here's another perspective on what's going on i like to use architecture as a metaphor meaning
a thousand years ago structures especially public structures were built to last a thousand years
i remember growing up at the bison teniel in the us around seventy seventy six speaking to some people
in europe and saying two hundred year bison telling you kidding i'm living in a house that's a thousand
years old right so a thousand years ago public structures were built to last a thousand years a hundred
years ago public structures or most structures were last were built to last a hundred years look at
the skyscrapers in new york that were built around the turn of the century or a little after they're
still very robust and structurally sound now structures since nineteen ninety eight structures are
being built to last only twenty years go look at those big towers that are built in aja or in
duba actually go research it a little bit what is the life expectancy of these large towers twenty
years and to put it a little more perspective on the subject i was conveying down what's called a road
one day and i saw what's called a housing subdivision going up and i took a glance at it and i
pointed to someone look the people are so far gone they're putting their building their houses out
of compressed sawdust think about that for a moment you know what i mean by compressed sawdust
you ever see that particle board yeah it's all of a sod folks that's what it does matter the
reason why is why do you why should it be made it doesn't need to be robust because this information
is ingrained in everyone just like a plant knows when to come to seed society is now coming to its
point now it doesn't mean doom and gloom because anytime you preach doom and gloom in human history
you will always sound correct but the problem is whenever doom and gloom is preached they cannot give
you specifics what we're trying to do eventually all these we meaning what the Greek is saying is give
specifics and one of the specifics here is that what everyone is experiencing right now is the
precursor to the precursor of a middle east union that is going to be forming it's a group of
ten nations which only nine exist right now in what's called the middle east area and when this
union comes together it's going to be a very loose union not like the european union all of your
government economics judicial recreational entertainment education religion is going to be
based out of there and then coming out of there you see it's going to be the hub and it's going to
be projected from there through the entire world and if you want to keep it really simple before
getting into more specifics or maybe not you ever hear grandma say what goes around comes around
you ever look at a racetrack where's the starting line okay look at the starting line now where's
the finishing line the same thing even in the rubbish secular education system in academia they tell
you that man society started where messopotamian region well guess where man society is going to end
based out of there as well so it's very very very very simple and by the way this has also been
prophesied in many of your ancient texts but who wants to read the ancient text because those people
are just ignorant you know it doesn't matter why i don't believe in that you see so you know we're
modern now and by the way if you study any of the ancient writings do you know like ancient Babylon
or ancient Greece or even parts of Rome before they fell from their prominence in their writings they
described themselves as being modern yes so so you know let's let's tie this back we kind of like got
more of a narrow aspect here but i believe in going deep in certain aspects but just covering
broad things because you know shallow thinking usually gets people diving off something deep so
you've got to pin yourself down into a thought that's what meditation is by the way meditation is
like re chewing the cut you have a thought and you you keep processing it just like you have a
diamond inspected or they just glance at it and put it back in the in the sack or do they keep
turning it and look at every facet right and how the light goes through it from every direction
and when you hear about meditation by the way they really screwed up the western world on that
because when the body is active the mind is quiet and when the body is quiet the mind is active so
back i think many people that consider themselves contemplate over meditational are trying to keep
their body still and make their mind still that's how you go insane folks meditation happens when the
body is still the mind is fast you know if someone is running a marathon and you want to ask them
technical questions or shoot you to the side they'll say listen let me finish this run and then
we'll talk right because when the body is active the mind is quiet and when the body is quiet the
mind is active so if you're laying down in bed and you find your mind racing that's good you're probably
not used to it and you don't know how to take control of it but once you understand the simple
premise that i just shared with you folks you know you'll have fortune in understanding what meditation is
so that does help because yeah who can stop that you know you're supposed to stop all the thinking
or you know again that is a tradition instead of an actual practice the way that we see things
in the way that this is all going what crazy times okay so we're looking at we're in the uncredits
we've been the revealing everything going on behind the surface we find that our elite are all
bloodline tracking back to ancient lines we find that they are all trafficking in children
every single person that has come up in this last election has been accused of rape and then
we get a middle east union where the laws and the you know the the traditions are quite different
America has been set up as this role of Satan as the evil overlords of the planet
thanks to things like the use of 9/11 truth and all this revelation of how we know try
try pizza parties and hot dogs and things of that nature that are coming to the surface
what happens when as we start to boil into the second hour here we're going to lead into the the
process of enacting these stoning laws in in the west and and how this middle east union will
affect us sure sure and now when you when we say stoning laws and you brought up 9/11 you know I've
got to say this and and many aspects perhaps people have no comprehension or don't want to have
comprehension about the one of the major traditions that goes on is from the secular point of view is
the preeminence or predominance of the Christian era all right if from a secular point of view
this is known as the Christian era right that's why your your years are numbered as such right and
it's all erroneous the the figure of the Christ for example in all that you will not what's shown by
Christianity the crucifix and all that and the continents of the man with long hair wearing a loin
cloth and such is not in the biblical text at all and when you say 9/11 that is also a loose reference
to when let's say the the birth of this biblical character took place so in essence just to tie it
back to what sparked this me to say this is when you said 9/11 two things that are very important
folks to consider about 9/11 one is all of the discussion that is out there regarding it no one
goes back and discusses the type of construction that was used for those buildings and people don't
know that that type of construction was around for decades before or a decade before it was actually
implemented and the reason these buildings were not implemented because no one knew how to take them
down and until the method was developed or procured then they were built and it wasn't just the
World Trade Center it's the UN building Daegharmershade Plaza the Sears Tower this is a specific type of
construction now the reason I'm mentioning this is there's no one is speaking about it the other
thing that almost no one is speaking about is in the in the Christian era you have something
called Christmas the birth of what's called the Christ and no one discusses the accuracy of
the information that is available for that they all take for granted we don't know when it was this
is what how we celebrate it but what's interesting in the biblical text it gives you an astronomical
alignment when that happened very specifically and if you're going to do a cross-cultural cross-era
communication of time you have to use astronomical alignments you can't use ridiculous calendars
right because they change you know so in the biblical text it's very clear a virgin was giving
birth which 12 stars at her head cloaked with the sun and the moon at her feet that is very
specific alignment and we know from secular records that during the time of let's say the biblical
record when the Christ was born there was a census or head counting of the empire by Augustus
and also we know that herod had died about two and a half years after that time according to
secular records that puts you between 2 a.d. or 8bc so if you go look for this alignment that i just
mentioned the constellation Virgo with the tail of draco at her head with the sun in the middle
and the moon at her feet that is in the late afternoon and if you go to a nationalmical observatory
or computer that will show you that happened between 2 and 8bc and that happened on 3bc
on the day of 11 on the month of september around 640 pm so what when you say 9/11 that was what's
called a birthday party right if you get the meaning of that we'll talk about what cannibals
birthdays and dolls have in common as a metaphor to understand this society so i just wanted to throw
that in there as well to give a little more comprehension on what's going on yeah absolutely we
are seeing the birth of a new world and folks it is the year 57777 in the Hebrew calendar or the year
616 anolusius calendar or you know year 2016 and yeah well we we from memorialization it seems to be
there's a new kid on the block known as atom and that was around 618 years ago so when you're
referencing the biblical text you would probably around be around there now what's interesting
about the Hebrew calendar by the way the reason it's losing out a few hundred years is because they
decided to eliminate the years when they didn't have an unrighteous king so for example if you
didn't like George Bush Jr you reset 8 years like never happened right never happened and that's
what the and I don't know is that lawful to do that you see the answer would be no it's not lawful
it's not a lawful time keeping well for the pranksters in the historical system it absolutely as they
have kept us veiled this whole time hood winked as you had said and now they've got us running in
the streets screaming kill all the fanatics yeah and the fanaticism is what you are being shown like
for example back to 9/11 for a moment when 9/11 happened in within 30 seconds they said it was
Muslim terrorists it was loosely accepted because since the 70s 80s and 90s Hollywood had done a
very good job in procuring Muslim terrorists in film right and also news and and also the xenophobia
of how look how different they are kind of thing it's always you know just like with Asia in world
war two it's very easy to pin out an adversary because they look very different because you have
the sports mentality you know people are into sports you know it's about a bunch of people in uniform
chasing a ball and the reason why they're so easy to follow sports is because they look the teams look
very different you don't need to be a genius to figure out what's going on right so without a doubt
and we saw that whole sports mentality come out that's exactly what runs these politics and everybody's
like my team has to win and and now we see the results of what happens with poor losers and and these
in this very thought that you're having here I made me consider this idea of how many bloody murders
would you personally witness without television or Hollywood sure very few but it's kind of difficult
to say because without television or Hollywood there might be fewer distractions and people might
be out actually committing more of them right all right to Shay but so we can see how this has been
melded into the system just slowly and subtly that this has been going on forever and ever and
and that's the thing is that they have they've spawned these reactions when Kathy O'Brien who we
will be having on the show folks very soon you know has been talking about this for 25 years and it's
only now because it's a mob rule situation that they're going to react to this knowledge and
what we hope the Greek and I folks is that we give you data so that the reactions will will
you know be tempered by understanding and knowledge that this is not new it's not time to react they're
forcing you to react at this moment sure and you know the reactionaryness of everything you know
if you were growing up let's say in the 50 60 70s or even 80s when world leaders or captains of
industry would speaking we're speaking you notice how they spoke about multi-generational terms they
wanted to do these big public works projects and social changes you ever notice now how captains
of industry and leaders of people only speak from a reactionary point of view when event happens
they're taken out of wherever just to make a comment there there is no more discussion
about you know multi-generational or long-term thinking at all and that is another clue you need to
look at folks to see how things are falling in place but you have to remember if anyone is familiar
with homeopathy right which is how little of a substance you can give or the subtle energies
it's the subtle energies that actually dictate the things that come later it's the shape of the river
not the water that dictates the flow you see so what's happening now and it's been happening for a while
is a lot of subtleties are being put in place that are allowing people to accept what's happening
and we'll probably get into a little bit more on the current situation like you brought up you know
the pitophilia the human sacrifice let's say you brought up the murders and the stoning and all
this how that people are being let's say indoctrinated or being it's they're being warmed up to these
concepts because these things are going to be very significant in the near future actually in
the next decade let's say the secular decade don't be pranked by the systems folks mob does not rule
the subtleties of your very character will make all the difference necessary don't run around
screaming kill all the fanatics because well that makes you a fanatic so what a wonderful understanding
to to start to bring about the knowledge necessary to to stand on a firm plane as the world just
erupts into chaos around you and know that you're not being pranked by this very same system
if you guys prank yeah yeah I'm gonna ludicrous trick yes yeah it is ludicrous it is all ludicrous
this whole thing that I'm watching right now is ludicrous folks it's insane I mean I mean I wouldn't
pick either one of these people to you know take care of my dog much less be the ruler of my nation I
the the things that have come out that people just don't care is blowing my mind but I don't want
them to really get it all in one punch like they are this idea of child trafficking and MK ultra and
all the true things that are going on behind the scenes in the dark dark occulted world of politics
and global governance so I don't want you to be reacting to that I want you to be knowing that
this information has been here it's it's we've been talking about it and we can change things but
homeopathically with subtlety as we interact with one another I want to conclude this by saying you
can find the Greek very soon at uncommon radio dot com that is uncommon radio dot com and he he gives
you his work in in bits and bites and lets you take that in and I want to announce that next week
we will be talking with Fritz spring Meyer on the beast system because we got such a
wait rave review from last week show we had to we got have to get deeper into this so Fritz
spring Meyer next week on the beast system and tonight I will be live 8 p.m pacific that's 11 p.m
eastern I hope on k b k a b c in Los Angeles so if you're in the LA area 8 p.m. I will be live on
the radio and that should be an amazing show I certainly hope so I'll do my best I promise you
that so we're going to take the Greek over into the members section we're going to look at
birthday cards cannibals and dolls we're going to bring up a little bit more doom and gloom
and then we're going to discover something special about people's tattoos as a matter of fact have
you seen this latest one I'll put it in the artwork for you folks this one blew my mind it's
going to be right there on freeman tv dot com for you it is a woman who had
Donald Trump is not my f.ing president down her entire back in a tattoo this is blowing my mind
because hell Hillary might still be president in the not too distant future it she'll be stuck with
this for the rest of her life we're going to talk to the Greek about tattoos the middle east union
doom and gloom and really look more into our homeopathic status these deities and demons that we're
dealing with so I hope you all will subscribe get over to freeman tv dot com and click subscribe
there are numerous ways to do it and it all helps in getting this media out to a bigger and bigger
audience so that we can really start to affect change in ourselves and then watch that radiator as
it comes up through the plant life around us though those around us all you can do folks is plant
a seed and watch it grow you're never going to beat this stuff in anybody's head and the more you listen
to the Greek the more you realize that they don't care they really don't you can bring out their own
books you can bring out their own data and say here you are completely wrong and they'll say well
that's not my book any final thoughts on that gree oh well you know I think we're going to really
finalize it in the next hour so I encourage anyone to just come on over to the membership area
it's a fantastic time folks it's really been going great and thank you all so much there's been such a great
rave review recently and over the last few months and you know all of this last year honestly
has been just epic so get tuned in and we're all here for you I promise and there's going to come
a time where that river is going to guide us all together so I really look forward to seeing you all
out there until next week we will see you later
and welcome back you wonderful members and all you new members I hope you are figuring everything out
and it is very simple for you of course I guess if it's not you're probably not hearing this portion
of the show I was going to say just write me freeman at freemontv.com if you have any issues at all I
probably should have said that in the live part so that the people I haven't trouble getting in could
hear it but it's wonderful to have this little space here with just us and I really am glad that you
guys have joined this trip and are hopefully enjoying every minute of it like I am because what an
amazing world we live in and what strange times and how bizarre is everyone I mean we got to sit
back and be observers and and realize what's going on look at the long now and really take it in so
that we can then be the Christ or the seed planters of the future to allow other people to come in
and I I I quickly see how I clearly see how quickly people get triggered as in last week show
the name Jesus was brought to the surface and boy boy you bring that name into the puzzle and I get hit
from all sides I'm I'm I'm fanatical Christians are writing me say you know thank God you've come over
and radical anti Christians are writing me what the hell are you doing I can't believe you would
allow the name Jesus on the air and for me I was not raised with the religious system whatsoever
everything that I have gleaned about religion and and dogma has been through my own outsider
adult perspective so I don't have any of these triggers and so when I when someone comes on my show
and they they bring up anything of any religious I mean I've had the high priest of the church
is eight and on here you know I've had text bars and evangelicals I've had every range that you
could possibly imagine on the show and I'm not going to challenge your beliefs because it's futile
and we're going to discuss that with the Greek now because you know it's futile and if if I feel
like you're taking it in a positive light and using the spiritual armor then I say go for it because
we all need more hope and more ability to be able to feel like we can stand up against this evil
in the world so Greek what do you got to say well would it feel good if I gave you a stack of
hundred notes and you were passing them around and buying things that you wanted you know federal
reserve notes hundred dollar bills let's say and by the way when you look at someone calls it a bill
like who's going to pay that bill but anyway if I gave you a stack of hundred dollar bills and you
felt pretty good but all of a sudden you go somewhere and someone scans and says hey man I know
you've been using these all day but they're counterfeit what do you mean they're counterfeit well you
can't counterfeit a hundred dollar bill with a dinner napkin and a crayon you have to take a lot of
time to make it seem very much like the real thing right but it's not under scrutiny now you
brought up the J. E. S. U. S. aspect well when people bring that up with me I say which one because
every aspect of Christianity has a different one meaning one says you could do anything you want
it's all been forgiven the other one says if you don't believe in me you're going to hell the other
one looks like this the other one looks like that okay well you know if you have two people or three
people or ten people coming to you and saying that they have the truth and their story does it
match well the only thing is possible is that they're all wrong or only one is correct because the truth
has to match like two plus two in Swahili equals four will be the same in Japanese or English but if
it's two plus two equals five in one group and two plus two equals nine and another it doesn't work
you know so here's the point I always say this and it's true unfortunately or fortunately for
those that have eyes and ears discussing any biblical character whether it's Adam and Eve Noah
Abraham the Christ the Apostles anyone at all is almost nearly impossible because it's all been
tainted the reason why is because no one goes to the text and what I mean by that let's just say
it's easier to find the nuclear launch codes of a country's arsenal than to accurately discuss
any biblical character period and what I mean by that is very simple just what I just what I said
go read the text very simple give a quick analogy you know you know that Cecil B. De Milgei
did the movie ten commandments with the you know they they cross the red sea the waters open up
and they walk along the bottom you know and they go across the other side you ever you ever walk
on the bottom of a dried out lake bed and all the crap under there you're gonna be knee deep in it
right there's no way practical and also if you read the text it said 600,000 fighting men left
Egypt that means that if they each had two relatives that's 1.8 million people right if they each
had three relatives that's 2.4 million people you don't that doesn't work now if you go to Exodus
15 it says that a cold wind blew all night and the waters were piled up if you go look at the meteorological
report and Sinai in the springtime it goes down to about 20 25 degrees is that cold enough to freeze
water and the reason I mentioned cold enough to freeze water is how do you pile up water
freeman can you pile up water of course you can if it's frozen and if you read very carefully in
the text it says that they all crossed over in and come morning time Farrow tried to cross but he
fell to the bottom he fell to the bottom like lead he fell to the bottom like a stone is what the
text says now let me ask you how can you fall to the bottom if you're ready walking on the bottom
now what they did is they walked on an ice bridge parting the water the etymological
root means to part or separate now let me ask you this have you ever heard anywhere in the
else in the biblical text of walking on water right sure yeah I've walked on water because I've
lived in the northeast once and it was very cold in the winter so now you can't do this because now
we've philosophically did mystified the biblical text we're not taking its power we're not taking its
relevancy or the respect that it garners away we're just being practical also they crossed the
Jordan everyone likes to focus on what Cecil B. Demil is showing now there's a lot of Jesus movies
that show you the depiction of his execution how he was born and how he looked none of that is biblical
sorry folks here's another point of view I ask Christians very simply when Moses was speaking
at the mountain you've heard of the burning bush by the way Moses and the burning bush right
do you know if you read the text there's no burning bush if you read the text it states that
Moses saw an angelic being that was giving off fire and then the angelic being stood behind a bush
and the fire from the angel was not burning the bush was not consuming the bush where do you
get the burning bush out of that well I'm curious as to why we should even take any of this into
our operating system in the first place I mean what gives credence to any of these stories of
because it's a code it's a code and it's also a memorialized information of a very high
ranking database and we'll get into that maybe in the future and you've heard of what's called
the bible code where they open it and they give you a computer code and you final psalm have been
flawed and if you crisscross the letters and all that well that what they don't tell you is that
works and with Emerson's Moby Dick or Melville's Moby Dick also works in any literary work
there is a bible code in there that's very important and it has to do with geometric forms and
that will probably discuss in another time how's that but this is what's important
you ever hear of something any information transfer is not coming through and remember how we
said in the first hour that your law comes from your god so anything that is regarding deific or
spiritual information tends to take a higher order right and people's information base
and if they've got it all mixed up how are they going to study any any any information base how many
times have you heard for example bacteria or viruses cause the cold the common cold in winter time
right well the most people follow that rationale or logic but it's acer nine and stupid why
because if that were true that would render the need for refrigeration useless the reason we have
refrigeration is to retard those little buggers right so it doesn't right so in the winter time
their bacteria and things like that are dormant right so they can't be the cause of cold
what actually is the cause of cold is you're not eating seasonally because if you're in a cold
place you knew you'd food grown in the tropics it changes your body chemistry to the tropics right
so you're gonna freeze or get mucus right now now here's the other point let's go back to viruses
if you study all of the documents regarding virology even that infinite bastion of wisdom called
Wikipedia look up virology and they'll tell you that virology is a branch of toxicology and all
toxicology has to do with the liver function so how the hell are you going to catch a virus if its
viruses originated in the liver as mitochondria no one is paying attention to any of the memorialized
information that's what's important it's not whether it's biblical it's whether it's scientific
academic medical legal right anything yeah i have no idea what is the the crane crane fly effect
in that as i traveled around the u.s. and i think even across the nations or continents
i would find people talking about this mosquito eater or some places they called it a mosquito
hawk and what it was is a giant bug that looks like a one you know it looks like a giant mosquito
and people see them bouncing around the house and they say oh no no don't kill that they eat mosquitoes
and i've found this from east to west coast and the truth is that that bug is actually a crane fly
it's a common ordinary house fly it doesn't eat mosquitoes but everyone knows it does and everybody
believes it and i'm i want to take this and lead this into birthday cards cannibals and dolls greek
i i'm just dying to understand this let's give the perspective on it that i like to this is how
I introduce it let's say you're on a mothership you have intergalactic travel and before you go
down on a planet that give you a short briefing well if you approach earth briefing the shortest
possible brought briefing regarding the society on earth right now would go as such you cannot
understand the society of these people until you understand what cannibals birthdays and dolls
have in common now if that doesn't sound obtuse and weird i don't know what does and let's go let's
roll right into it like you said and this is one of the standard stock explanations that i give
now let's start when you go back even into the trashy secular history that we're given
where do they tell you everything started the Mesopotamian region right between the Tigris and the
Euphrates and all that and this is also in a lot of the ancient texts as well but let's just
just say you know this is where everyone sort of has agreed the origin starts the people in that
culture in that society spoke what's called a caldian Hebrew meaning that is a general classification
of languages just like when you say the latin languages that would be Italian, French, Spanish and so
Portuguese right so let's go back to the language in caldian Hebrew the people remember that you
get your law from your god right then the gods have priests the priests were known as the cahons
and the priests had convinced the people that if they make wishes of prosperity they sacrifice a
young child right and the and to a ball B-A-A-L or a lord all right and when they sacrifice the child
they would each partake in eating a tiny piece of flesh like the size of someone's fingernail and
taste of the blood this was part of the ritual and so the cahons were the cahons are the priests of
the balls so the eating of human flesh is cahon ballism or cannibalism you could look up the route
meaning of the word cannibalism comes from the cahon balls now cahon ball literally means priest
of the lord and you still have priests of the lord today don't you they profess such right you go
to a place that has a priest they say I worship the lord and what are you a priest thank you very
much there's a cannibals etymologically not right okay so this is where you get the what the word
cannibal means just means priest of the lord and it's associated with eating of human flesh now what's
interesting about this wish of prosperity is people were convinced that it would bring prosperity
to them in that culture and when you know what's interesting about the quote unquote family union
a unit and the psychology in the culture is when you have brothers and sisters and the parents take one
away and come back without them and as a child aren't you gonna ask where's our brother where's our
sister right so we have a missing child now in the family unit and the altar boys of these priests
of the lord of the cannibals were able to take care of that or suit that a little bit by making an
effigy of a child a doll they say well when you go back the children are gonna ask where it happened
to the child so why don't you give them this instead to take its place so right now when you look at how
parents give children dolls to play with now you know where that ritual or custom or tradition comes
from whether you are doing it for that or not is irrelevant this is the origin of giving children
dolls okay super creepy yeah and it goes on and on out you know people usually respond by saying well
I had a doll I didn't but it has nothing to do with that it's the gesture okay now when the people
realize that doing this ritual didn't really bring prosperity they usually ran these guys out of town
but before they got run out of town or did get run out of town they figured out well let's do a
parody of this event and I had read this in a book that was published in the 1800s and I'm trying
to remember it's title thing was ancient rites and rituals rights being spelled RITES
of the Hebrew caldians and and I was trying to piece this together because it stated they had done
parody of events by baking a loaf of sweet bread and placing lights in it or around it and the
child would make a wish of prosperity blow out the lights reflecting or meaning blowing out the life
and everyone would eat a piece of this sweet bread which represented the body and to show that the
event brought prosperity anyone attending the ceremony brought a present now this sat in the
mind for a little while and I was like you know what that's the origin of the birthday party
insane yeah and now this is all done in gesture hey Greek we don't we just have a good time
we don't we don't kill children or each other but it's the gesture now this is why the
you see do you see now what kind of understanding you get on this society now the gestures and the
parody and the human sacrifice that is involved in what they do as pleasure and as morally acceptable
is not right now let me just throw a statement in there the gods love human children more than
parents do imagine the most loving parent the gods love your child more than you do now what do you
think whether you do this actual sacrifice or you do a parody of it what's the difference in the
spiritual realm right you see so this is where you're heading so that's why when I have discussions
with people say how a society gonna get better I say wait a second before we get into that I say
are you able to go to a store and buy what's called a birthday cake as such or a doll says yes of
course as it will your societies in the shit as long as that's available because that is a gesture
of human sacrifice that's why I always suggest now the you by the way that was the short explanation
of what cannibal birthdays and dolls have in common do you think well the audience might be satisfied
with enough of that I don't think we need to go into more of it because it's about as it's about as
macabre is can be right yeah yeah absolutely every that pretty much lays it out there that was Santa
clause that we got in her earlier that clause was different was more like but similar human size
so I'm saying just you know just shackles child sacrifice for a parody of this situation that is
just constantly the operating system and I mean okay let's go all the way back there was a time where
you had to be a people of the book and there was a group of characters wandering around and they
were in bright colored dress and they were they were stopped by the lead priest or what would be a
chic and and he he demands you know what people of the book are you and these people of colorful
descent I don't know who they were they went and studied the the law and and came back and said
we are sabians and in this they became the followers of hermys and because hermys was one of the
accepted days in the Quran the sabians were there before then considered a people of the book
so now we're looking at this middle eastern union we got people tattooing Donald Trump is not my
having president across their back and we're all going to be expected to be a people of the book and
I wanted to give some people heads up about the sabians in case maybe that will come into play and we can
announce they actually were sabians and we're we're the followers of hermys because that's about my
favorite character and all of these different saviors so let's get into the Middle East
Assiria the anti-Christ and tattoos okay very important in this order we've all if anyone's heard
the Greek I've always been talking about what's coming around the corner with accuracy what makes
it accurate is that well it happens and it's it's just a good report now as we mentioned in the first
hour there is going to be a Middle East union and when this comes together you're going to have
whether it's popular or unpopular how many times have you heard the concept of the anti-Christ
you're going to have him as the ruler he's going to be surrounded by a council of older people now
why is it that whenever someone is unfavorable they're called an anti-Christ when
if you're going to pluck a concept or a character out of a source document you have to use the
definition in the source document right how many times have you overheard you know a poor leader
being regarded in media as the anti-Christ well if you look at the source document he is not
a poor leader he's actually a very charismatic leader a very powerful leader everyone likes him
right so where is the understanding on this now we're not allowed to make things up everyone has
their own opinion and personal belief but not everyone can have their own truth which has also
been happening so let's get into a little bit more of that now it leads into law form and to tab
twos so we have a Middle East union that's coming that's a prerequisite of ten nations now
and a lot of quote-unquote air quotes here Christian circles they think it's Europe there is no
mention of Europe in the biblical text at all other than all the nations it's very specific about
these nations being in the Middle East the problem is there only nine in existence today the tenth one
would be this country called Assyria it would probably be called the new Assyria and most people don't
know much about the Assyrians but there's several million Assyrians throughout the world there's
less than a quarter of a million in the Middle East now because of all the turmoil they are of Christian
descent meaning orthodox Christian and they cease to exist as a nation around 2300 years ago
and if you actually study the Assyrians let me just make a loose personal opinion statement here which
I rarely do Freeman okay one of the reasons they cease to exist as a society is because if they
didn't I don't think anyone would be here today why what was the Assyrians industry the Assyrians
industry was war straight up if they needed or wanted anything they just went and attacked another
country to get it have you ever heard of medieval torture devices they even have museums will
get teen some screws all these things right the majority of these torture devices and methods
of executions were invented and procured by guess who you got it the Assyrians there were quite an
interesting people in that respect now what what we're going to see is as I've been saying for
over a decade a new Assyria forming in northern Iraq and when it forms its boundaries will go into
Turkey and Syria so back as early as 2000 what they called 2004 I was telling people learn to watch
Syria and Turkey and northern Iraq obviously because when this Assyria comes by its jurisdiction is
going to take some land from Syria and Turkey and when does a political move like that or geographical
mapping happen without a fight or turmoil or chaos hardly ever right so what do you hear about in the
news right now you hear a lot about Turkey and Syria don't you and northern Iraq don't you very
interesting so what you're going to see when this country comes about now the prerequisite for all
these ten nations are in place right and this is what this period is going to start in the spring of
2018 going until what's called 2025 is when the the the prominence or the gain of prominence
and the focus is going to be on the Middle East because of these ten nations and they're going to
have a central hub in Iraq a central three central areas the other one is going to be in what's known
as Israel the other one's going to be in what's known as Lebanon this is going to be like loose
capital cities kind of like in fashion you have London Paris New York right kind of like a tripart
uh... thing like that so this is what's coming folks in by the way let me just interject this is not doom and gloom this is uh...
you've reached the level of humanity right now where when all of these things take place and like i said in
the previous uh... interview we did the kill shots that are going to be administered to the society it's
not the end of the world or the planet it's the end of man's rule and it's the end of the gods or that
society the unseen being imperceptible after this time period when man is toppled his way his system
of doing things is toppled and redone the gods will be overt there will be no more question about
angelic beings and things you'll be able to see them in such right so this is a wonderful time that's
coming for if you see it as such right but uh...
what yeah so but the problem why it has to be done so violently is because people have reached a
point where they're unreadable how many times have you heard people say i will die from my belief
too many
yeah so guess what you're going to be accommodated for that okay so let's be careful what you believe in what you say
what you're willing to lay your life down but there's an ancient Greek saying that says that those that
those that are afraid of dying don't know how to live the reason i brought this up is because one
i do mention these things in public i get a lot of personal contacts that say well how do i do what
do i do to avoid the kill shots you know like the solar event and the asteroids and just the chaos
that man is going to ensue and i'm like what kind of question is that you know we're too far away to
answer give you a solid answer and the thing is why would you be afraid of that you see but we
let's go back to the middle east union in this antichrist character what people don't understand
about the biblical character biblical text and characters besides nothing uh... and how do i
why do i say this is go ahead and speak to your average average believer now the the jewish and
christian faith have hijacked the biblical text and when i mean by hijacked is exactly that taking it
forcefully with and not using it for its appropriate reason and just like few uh... no anyone that has
a sporting goods store ask them how many baseball bats they sell and they'll tell you many but how many
of those baseball bats that are sold are actually used for playing baseball hmm probably a third or
less because baseball bats make inexpensive clubs don't they when you see these religious people walking
around with these ancient text i assure you they don't know anything in them they're using it as a
baseball bat you know here bible fumping they've heard that before right using it as a club now
people that do understand these texts and and uh... there is no such thing as your interpretation
or whatever there is only one interpretation there is many versions for example if you go or an
ambassador and go to the u_n_ you don't bring a version stator with you you bring an interpreter
stator with you right he has to be as accurate as possible now anyone is entitled to a version but
not anyone is entitled to differing interpretation if you have two people saying they have an interpretation
not a belief for a version but an interpretation and if they're not identical the only thing that's
possible is they're both wrong or only one is correct they both cannot be correct so these and to
say that it cannot be understood is by is the same as saying that the gods or those that transmitted
this message act in futility and they don't act in futility they might have an iq of one million
and they're speaking baby talk to you and you still don't get it but it can be comprehended
when you throw in cosmic censorship it makes it all difficult but maybe we'll discuss
the cosmic censorship someday or maybe if we have time but let's go back to the middle east
union the reason why i did this preface within the explanation is because anyone can see what i'm
saying in the text and you can see it manifesting not here to convince anyone i'm here to just give a
good report why because there are there isn't any good reporting on this subject being done it
you know it really sucks what you hear about this subject matter and it behooves anyone that
discovers what is correct to speak so you know just that's why we're speaking hopefully
so so going back to the middle east union one of the most pre preeminent characters that is in the
biblical text and also on the minds and mouths of people is this anti-christ character and seemingly
no one has any details about it well here we go it's very simple the number seven how many times
have you heard the number seven being significant in the biblical text or has to do with spiritual
you're the divine quite a bit okay well what's interesting about the number seven is number four is
in the center isn't it you have three on the left three on the right take out seven objects
the center one is number four and then you have one two three on the left of it and then five six seven
on the right we're given the number seven metaphorically and practically in the biblical text over
and over and over the center figure is the christ figure that means that he was born exactly in
the year four thousand which was around september eleven three bc according to the pope's work
schedule or bit or in lawful time keeping it was around the 15th day of the seventh month by the way
september mean seven october means eight nova means nine and deca or december means ten think about
that for a minute so if the christ was born by the way on the year four thousand because these
essential figure who might have been born hmm under let's say the sixth millennium the sixth right
aspect of that number seven the year six thousand well guess what number six coincides with a number
of man whenever you hear satanic references to six six six that's bullshit folks why because number
six denotes man system right guess what one did man come on the scene when during the creation
story six day you got five fingers on one hand that six you got two legs two arms torso and
head that six six feet under six feet tall anytime anything is written a prominence by man for man
it's divisible by six interesting that's why a lot of the king james versions they tell you there
sixty six books they're telling you in code that's a mocked up version of the biblical text
because the biblical text actually has forty nine books seven times seven but what they did was they
divided some books like first and second kings first and second peter for to get the sixty six
because they're mucking about you get it so number six has to do with man so on the one
did the six millennium come around roughly the fall of nineteen ninety eight so if this man's number is
six meaning six six six six and the reason there are three six is is because it's a number of a man
and you need two witnesses to verify something don't you from the mouth of two or three witnesses
so you have six you're sure it's six yes six and you're sure that yes six that's why you have
the six six six very simple it's a number of a man he was born on the six millennium so he that
would put him roughly around eighteen years old right now also the text is very clear that he is
of us serian descent hey didn't we just finished describing the aserians a little bit preman
interesting right so the anti-Christ folks whether you believe it or not know it or not or
care to know it or not or don't like with it what is being said here if you actually got
objective and studied what I just mentioned you'll find it to be true in the text and you must adhere
to it right so we have an aserian that is roughly eighteen years old that is the anti-Christ figure
right now go figure so what about all this talk about this is the antichrist that's the antichrist
well you know that doesn't really are they aserian are they around eighteen years old now
don't be hoodwinked folks the alternative media in the mainstream literary works religious people
yeah too subjective you're not allowed to make up definitions of things that are extracted
from a source material right you cannot use when you say that uh you know the antichrist would be
known as charismatic and a great leader and and people calling George W. Bush the antichrist is
obviously flawed yes yes and you this you will hate to say it this way but you will get that from
the Christian perspective now here's the thing that I always like to say there are no Christians in
the world that comprehend the bible just like there are no Muslims that comprehend the Quran or any
Hindus that comprehend the Vedas or the Buddhists that comprehend the writings of the Buddha why because
if you adhere to a particular faith or religion institutional conventional like this and you actually
study the text that it was alleged to be subscribed to you would not be part of that group you
you would renounce it very clearly because why this is not my opinion if you made a list of
everything these major religions do and actually went to the text that they allegedly subscribe to
you would find that just about everything these believers do in his corresponding face is in the
don't do list or abominations list of the text that they allegedly subscribe to think about that
for a minute folks now that that leads me to tattoos and why it has become so prolific in the 21st
century yes very simple now how many people are familiar with the biblical text raise your hand
right well you might be think you're familiar with it because you're really just watched a lot of
movies or went to Sunday school or whatever but it's not what we're talking about if you actually
remember what we spoke about earlier that your law form comes from your God you know you ever heard
of the books of Moses it's a little bit of a bit of a kiss or there's a lot of laws in there isn't there
a 616 laws roughly right you've heard of that roughly right now what's interesting these biblical
laws are not religious if you actually study the context of them they're very much like the
constitution of a nation like what's the constitution of a nation the laws and bylaws and how the
government will be set up in function right if you actually look at a lot of the biblical laws which
by the way have not been done away with and I want to just interject one thing here and I do this
often but if you've heard of esop's fables like esop fables was like the the tortoise and the hare
you know fable okay well have you heard of the fox and the grapes just go look it up there's a
little one hour one minute YouTube on it the fox and the grapes is very simple a fox is going down
a path and he's it's hot and hungry and on the trail and it sees a grapevine and the grapes are
up high and it keeps jumping to reach the grapes can't reach them all afternoon and it says you
know what I can't reach those grapes but you know what they're probably sour anyway right so what
happens most people try to comprehend what's in the biblical texts and put it in context and they
can't so they say oh you know what it's done away with right no it doesn't belong it doesn't adhere
to me the fox in the grapes because I don't understand it it's not you know it doesn't exist right
this is how science works right so so here's the point when you look at the biblical laws as being
a constitution or the way that you live your life and set up a country or a town or
what you eat what you wear how you keep time how you do business how you raise a family all these
things are in there right when the Antichrist figure and the Middle East is brought together
there are going to be suggestions made to bring world peace and I'm going to interject something
beyond tattoos here as well Freeman but when he when they are looking for a new law form
just like I used to say if you want really new idea read a really old book they're going to go back
and look at what things are based on and they're going to discover and people are going to discover
that the biblical law form will begin to be re-instilled and for example in the biblical law form
capital punishment the death by stoning and things like that that's why you guys are being prepped
for that kind of stuff little by little but here's the point when you read in the biblical law that
if you for example have a piercing or marking on the skin you're to be put outside the camper
outside of the nation you were exiled if you did certain behaviors or certain things right
let me ask you if the entire planet across the equator or pole to pole takes on a law that
you you're not to mark your skin where are you going to go where are you going to be exiled to if
the entire planet from pole to pole and across the whole world is going to be under this law where
are you going to go you see my point so what I was when I saw and read that one third of humanity
will pretty much be wiped out so for social reasons or lawful reasons by others with the laws being
acted on very harshly I started looking at the proliferation of what's called tattooing back
maybe 12 years ago and I started telling people you know about tattoos and they're like yeah I do
I said you know how they're growing up you're usually for bikers or people in the navy you're
going to see everyone getting them not everyone but good amount of people because they're being set up
right and also when this law is put in place there isn't going to be tattoo police it's going to be
the people are going to be so enthralled in this society in this law form that they're going to
execute laws on their own right so this is why and also when this law takes effect it's not that
easy to remove a tattoo right or cover it you know most people that have them are known by others
right so is it in fact a death sentence loosely yes but conversely no because it's a setup now
here here's the other point that I want to make according to this how are you know I said there
aren't going to be any tattoo police that the people are going to do it themselves how is that
going to be possible because when this middle east union comes together around 2025 2025 2026
and you're going to have world peace prosperity liberty from things that you're attending to do and
you're going to have these charismatic people not only leading the world and setting up the world
in a way but they're also going to be performing miracles and reach a point where their arrogance
is going to lead them where they're actually one of them is going to declare themselves
God on earth right and the way you're going to identify him as such is this anti-craze character will be
in a mortal type of accident either a car accident or assassination attempt and he'll be declared dead
but then he'll be brought back let's say on an operating table and he will no longer have the use
of his right eye or his right arm but I am suggesting here I don't like to do this but I'm going to
go out a little bit or right Freeman that when he's brought back they're not going to certainly hide
that but what might be hidden is his eye in his arm he might have a prosthetic that functions really
well like an arm or an eye that functions like an eye and you may not know and there might be a rumor
that he actually lost his arm in his eye and he might need evidence on that but when this happens
this will be the first person in history to be possessed by Satan himself when I think I gave a
loose definition of Satan he doesn't deal with people he deals with the institutions of people
these demonic possessions and things that people see like ghosts of family and things those are
various minor impson demons that is not Satan himself right so this will be a precedent where the first
time of Satan actually is guiding him so while this is happening and prior to that people on the world
will be convinced that look we have world peace we have charismatic leaders and we have a wonderful
law form that works and this now is the new millennium this is how we are going to be in a wonderful
world for the next thousand years and when the glitches start to happen these very aggressive
application of the biblical law form and what I mean by biblical law form being aggressively applied
like you know we all know water is good without water there is no life right but you know what is
them what is what material is responsible for more property damage and insurance than any other
is water you can drown a grown person face down in three inches of water water is wonderful
it's necessary for life but it's also can be used for destructive purposes right and when this
starts to happen in the world people are still going to be convinced with all the mayhem that's
going around them in chaos it doesn't matter we'll just get over it because we're on a thousand
year golden age that just begun and even on the last interview that we did that I mentioned
there going to be three kill shots a solar kill shot not a solar flare but the so the sun being
extremely hot for a duration of time and to the point where the full moon looks like the
newnday sun to the two asteroids that hit the earth even when those things are happening their
billions dead overnight the people will be so enthralled and propagandized that they'll say it's
okay if that there's a billion dead last night we'll get over it you see this is so imagine the
level of propaganda that's going to be put in the next decade that is going to make people
completely blind to what's going on around them right yeah even so this is with a setup and yeah
so I hope we do you feel satisfied with that or should I go into more depth I mean so far I mean
do you think the audience is is benefited from this at all you know from the cannibals birthdays
and dolls all the way to the explanation of the Middle East Union if there is there anything do
you want me to get more specifics on we can yeah it wouldn't have been long ago that I would have
said oh this is crazy talk but I start looking at things like a stonna where the global world
religion council gathers in a giant pyramid around a sun table and I see the future the futuristic
city that is a stonna in these buildings as you're saying that aren't built to last longer than 20 years
but designed as portals it's a pre-plan city that is the same as a seal of Solomon to channel demons
some of them are ineffective okay let me I don't like to give references in mainstream tv shows
but have you ever heard of a tv show called Pimp My Ride right they take an old car and they
invest you know thousands in the but a tv screen I mean it's just very elaborate right a lot of
this is Pimp My Ride type stuff like Surn is physicist Pimp My Ride look at this crap we built this
huge thing that spins absolutely nothing and it's only to show you guys that we have access to the
banking system and we can get anything we want and you don't because there's no such thing as a
God particle there's no such thing as an atom even it's a construct that was put together by Walt
Disney so the atom as electron and pro tennis such was abandoned by the 1940s but Walt Disney said I
really like it I'm gonna promote it okay just like Simon and Agas yeah yeah exactly he put a lot of
his own money into millions and his own money back then as well to influence scientific community go
along with it just like Einstein Einstein was like an Osama bin Laden character he didn't really
exist as you're being told yes he did exist but not as you're being told so there's many aspects to
this and which aspect do you not touch you have to touch them all because they're you know they're
accessible and they can be discussed and referenced now regarding of what's coming and regarding
religion and what they're doing the thing is that people now what you're going to see coming in
the near future beginning not it's not going to come very in a very stark manner where there's a
total flip but you're going to see people inquiring more and more into the spiritual realm what are
the gods what are what a spirituality what are these religions based on right all these things
they're going to be revisited and the the ridiculousness now here's the thing how many times have
you heard like oh the Catholic Church is satanic or this religion is satanic or this or that or whatever
that will no longer be said they they will be viewed as you cannot make things up or criticism
that is not founded on something that can that it can be based on you have to give if you say
a religion is satanic you have to show me how and you have to be using the terms properly see this
will come into place what you will discover in the future is the world's major religions are
as described in the biblical text not necessarily satanic even though Satan controls all the institutions
on the world but they are worthless meaning they have no value let me give an example if there's a
basilica in Rome and they have iconography right images of let's say this one I'm basing it on what
they call the mother queen of heaven or the virgin Mary and it's a painting and she's carrying the
child and she has this red tunic type scarf overhead with a gold fringe of a gold border on it you
might have seen that image right somewhere right in iconography now this basilica when they painted
these icons they actually had a physical model sit there and they dressed up the model with you
know whatever garments they were going to paint now if you go to this basilica I believe it's
outside of Rome and you look very closely at that icon you will see that she's wearing this red
sheer silk cloth in the image and if you look at the border very very closely you're going to see
Arabic writing in the border and if you read the Arabic writing it states over and over repeatedly
in the border Muhammad is the only true prophet of God and it goes around the border of this icon of
the virgin Mary who is isis when you look at the isis of course so right and isis by the way yeah isis
is the Greek name for that goddess it's not the Egyptian name for that goddess yes it is the queen
of heaven which is also mentioned you know how earlier in the hour we mentioned this is all the
revived goddess religion let's let's get into you want to really get something in that's going to
people can sink their teeth into or maybe not want to hear let's do that let's do have a lot of time
okay the revived goddess religion is as such now is that when I used to speak on this people you
say Greek your anti feminine is this no that's bullshit you know why because if someone
card jacked you with a ski mask and then you found them later let's say the authorities capture them
and you pull the ski mask off and it would happen to be a woman if you say you were card jacked by
woman does that make you anti feminine or is it the card jack or just happened to be a woman it
doesn't make you anti feminine right you see we have this particular goddess religion that is
against mankind not women or goddess is because one of the chief goddesses in that realm is Sophia
wisdom and she is not malevolent she is benevolent now let's piece together a decade worth of
research and I'm going to paraphrase here I'm not going to give a lot of references but anyone
that goes down this path will stumble across this revived goddess religion as you mentioned ISIS
and other things like that you will see now what I have discovered now I'm going to do a big paraphrase
here because I can't even go into the details just too much time the revived goddess religion in
the ancient goddess religion especially around the time of the flood was based on this are you ready
this is what we're going to sink your the audience hopefully will have this sink into their minds
okay here we go the teaching of this goddess religion because most religions have teachings do they
not right the teaching of this goddess religion is that mankind was once in a godlike state
and in that godlike state they were either hemaphroditic or asexual
and the way you promote man to be in a godlike state is that you promote male with male union
and when the males unite they become a feminine and sterile and when the females unite you promote
female with female union they retain their fertility and might even take on masculine traits
and they procreate without the men and when they procreate without the men they will have asexual
or hermaphroditic men or people and that then you know you are going into a godlike state
that's why I stated earlier all of your sciences all of your cultures have repatren or matren deity
now have you ever heard of in vitro fertilization genetic babies right artificial insemination
yeah we actually a Francis christian institute was our topic of the discussion last time we spoke
when they finally announced that it was legal to create genetically modified babies yes have you
ever heard of gender bending chemicals like fafallates or plasticizers where the fish change
sexes and when the swim in water that has plastics in it right yeah all of this on and on and on
now is not as iris just in beaver sorry yeah or so so you know yeah that's fine here's the point
though when you look at this now let me uh mentioned as we did earlier the justice is the matren goddess
of the western world that is used in the legal or the legal court system is it not do the legal
or the attorneys rely on scientific testimony don't they evoke witness testimony from scientists
and don't scientists publish documents only after they pass legal scrutiny so can't we say that
the scientific community is working with the legal community and can we say that the scientific
community is engaging in a religion that is part of this revived goddess religion this is not a
stretch folks this is an explanation not just a description see this is one thing that you do find
in the world in a vacademia which is why i hate it so much i don't you see i hate what they do
and what they do is they provide descriptions explanations are not allowed
you see yeah yeah they do not explain it they just describe it and you don't ask questions so
so the point here is the scientific community the religious community the legal and law
community the government community your entertainment community i can say the entertainment
community also i think on this you might vouch for it for you man is involved in the revived goddess
religion aspect right um i mean are we not battling isis at this very moment in name only yeah yeah
the isis thing is interesting because you know obviously the isis is all funded by western
interests it's not just the us it's france in england very heavily all of those two yodas that
you see them driving the new ones are manufactured in texas and the reason why they use the ones made
in texas is because they have the slightly larger radiators or cooling systems that function better
in the desert how do you know just things yeah when i saw war on isis on the headlines it is
you know it i can't help but say it shocks me you know because i look just please carry on yeah
now this this stuff with isis you know they are radical islam you know well but the thing is
islam is not based on the korean and let's just be respectful you know the noble korean because it
is a noble document and the reason why it's a noble document is it because it refers to the spiritual
realm with accuracy just like the biblical text is the noble document here i want to interject
one more thing here for you mean you're ready this is something else that the audience might find
of great value if you read the korean and do what's in it do you know that there is several syrias
in the korean that state that a muslim or a believer or a faithful one will acknowledge that the
law came from moses and do what moses says so let me repeat that there are syrias in the korean that
state that if you're going to be faithful you're going to acknowledge that moses provided the law
as a prophet and you will do what moses says you get that now how do we how do we know what moses says
where do we get that well would be the first five books in the biblical text right where you find
a lot of the laws well if it's korean tells you to do that or it's written that you do that how many
muslims do the Passover or you know do this or do that that's found in the biblical text none
even though their text says they should right yeah gotta keep this team separated from that
team right now all islam is all christianity is all hinduism is all buddhism is or whatever is a
geographic adherence to whatever pagan deity ancient deity was geographic that's why when you look
at christianity in Rome it's different than christianity in the east eastern orthodox it's different
than christianity in england it's different than christianity in the bible belt is different than
christianity in mexico because all it is is the revival of these local geographic entities with a
christian name on it the same with islam you have over 40 different factions in islam the three or
four major ones and they all do whatever local pagan deity was settled into that geographic area
with a muslim name on it the same with hinduism the same with buddhism now in the eastern text you
know when you look at buddhism for example you will see that they do certain rights and rituals but
that's not what it's based on if you study it's based on living a life with integrity there's a
story i like to throw out there for example where a woman her child was eating too many sweets and
she went to the buddhism for advice and the buddhism for a total of come back in a month and i'll
talk to your child she comes back in a month and they talk to the child about you know not eating
so many sweets and the mother asked why did you tell me to come back in a month and he replied
that at the time when you first came i was eating a lot of sweets myself because i was traveling so i
had a weight a month so the buddhism is about living life with integrity not about what you see out
there right now in the same with hinduism and the same with christianity there is by the way you will
not find christianity in the biblical text it's made up by simon magus right you will not find
judeism as such in the biblical text either that is a post-tomatic post-babalone in adaptation
it goes on and on and on and on that i'm saying this respectfully to honor mankind
when we need to release people from their religious triggers their political triggers and all
of the triggers that are just being unleashed on the world right now and we've made it to the end
of this hour great and i i wanted to get just um these final thoughts in in the idea that
we can see this world that is is creating hermaphroditic reality and again folks that's hermys
and aphrodite and you will find them in almost every nation's capital i mean in every state capital
the hermys aphrodite i've covered this over and over again showing you all the different aspects of the
hermaphroditic goddess worshiping system that is around you at all times this is your obelisk and your
dome this is you know why they put the millennial dome across from big bend this is the hermaphroditic
hermys aphrodite system that is coming to play in this crazy world that we live in that is absolutely
wrapped up in this middle east union the concept of the anti-christ this one world dominated by
i guess a being possessed by Satan any final thoughts on that will be coming and that would be it
and by the way i know that you've done a lot of work with free masonry and you've
looked at free masonry you will see it echoes a lot of the things that we discussed uh... and hopefully
anyone else who has will this will benefit them in their studies of free masonry because it tends to
be the de-juretopic as well you know luminonity free masonry when it went out the same you will this
will sort of clear things up and also uh... if anyone goes to the uncommon radio website right now
it says done for a little while but we will have some things that you could sink your teeth into in the
near future and perhaps even before this is aired uh... so that's pretty much and uh... maybe we'll do
this again and we can get into specifics based on what kind of reaction uh... is garnered from these
presentations right absolutely i will be looking at all of those emails uh... i want to thank you
guys again uh... members for all the kind words you sent me and i think i have written everybody back now
and it's really good to hear from you it really lifts my spirits and it's awesome to to feel all of us out
there i can't wait for that moment where we're all really drawn together whether it takes a catastrophe
or if we just finally decide to turn the tide and walk another way uh... i can't wait for us to all
really come together the whole point of this show really is to not be pranked by the system
to not have this common reaction that's going on from the triggers that are so obviously placed
throughout time to boil up into now and to be secure in your own person so that you don't feel the
need to have to strike and lash out outside of yourself but only deal with what's right in front of
you and around you because there's plenty going on uh... in your life right now and we just need to
reach out and communicate and contact and become closer and closer together i have that's that's my
only hope for humanity but i see how crazy it is and i see how the triggers happen and i can't
believe people are rioting in the streets right now and pulling people out of their cars and beating
them up uh... this to me is is the most bizarre thing and to have you on the before the greek uh... i
had to put the gun there uh...
with you stating that your vote is your vow and that you accept what the electoral college is going to do
obviously nobody cares about that either
perhaps not yet but again uh...
the the only thing i would say to people is if you can objectify what's going on then you will learn how
to set yourself apart from it and deal with it uh... accordingly based on your law and your deity
whatever kind of information that you find is being relative it's very difficult to tell someone
what they should do and one shouldn't because you do have the ability to do that uh... that is the
concept of free will but again uh... free will is not what people think it is uh... if you're on a cruise
ship going from London to new york everyone on that ship is going to from one to new york but you
have free will on where you want to spend time on that ship and this is what life is the things we're
discussing uh... and have discussed is where the society is going as a cruise ship now what you do
within it is up to you but what i feel like i have been parted at least with a little bit of time
that we've spent together is uh... where this how this big ship is being navigated what you expect
to see on the horizon that is a great analogy that is perfect folks were on this boat together and so
uh... let's just sit back objectively watch this but i don't mean sit back but uh...
we know they're triggering our reaction so let's go out there and be the true soul that you are and that's
that's the the cure you are the homeopathy of of planet earth
mm-hmm all right well thank you greek for giving us this time and folks thank you so much for supporting
my efforts and oh we have so much to come next week again we will be speaking with fritt spring
mire that's always a great time oh my god when fritts and i met it for your mind and he realized that i
was also talking about human cloning he was so relieved because he thinks he's so far out there
i'm like now you're not far enough yet my friend uh... but he is in a wonderful guest and uh... in one
hour from now i will be live on k a b c in loss angeles and that's going to be amazing i hope you
all will tune into that if you're in the LA area if i can get a copy of the show i'll put it on free
mtv.com don't know so often these shows that go out on fm you don't get copies of so you got to be
there to get it so that's all there is to that thank you all so much again for being here and i
hope that you are really enjoying everything that we're doing because uh... that's the way we do
it we want your your true soul to be awakened and to feel like there are more of us out here than just
you alone so we will see you all in my team
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]