Beaming out across the galaxy. This is where a conspiracy on the wild side meets the perspective of a lifetime. This is the free zone with your host, Freeman.
The Francis Crick Institute just announced that they are going to begin DNA altering. That's right, this is going to make the UK the very first country to start producing GMO children.
Now, it is currently illegal to implant these genetically modified embryos into women, creating designer babies. But as it is now, legislation has been passed, DNA altering is going to begin occurring in the UK at the Francis Crick Institute.
Now, when you start to tell people things like this, they tell you, well, I think you're watching too many episodes of the X-Files. And people only hear what their own bias will allow them to hear. And they will throw this off into the fringe zone and never accept it into their real world concerns.
Well, today we're going to talk to the Greek. And we're going to offer some practical information, not opinions. We're going to look into all levels of our being and our media. We're going to analyze the flip side coins of Alex Jones versus Fox News.
And the most important part that I want you to take from this, tonight we're talking with the Greek. And the reason he is coming to speak to you now is because if you know something and you say nothing, you are just as guilty. So please, welcome to the show, the Greek, as we lay out for you some of this amazing research that he has been working on. Welcome to the show.
Well, thank you very much for having me, Freeman. It's great to be here with you.
Well, we're going to focus some on how do we change our world today. And we're going to just get into this idea right now. Okay, there's so much information coming out at people. It's just bombarding their senses. Nobody knows what to think about. And we have what now is known as the alternative media.
But I saw that immediately as a flip side of the same coin. Everybody's still focusing on the same issues and the same false reality. And yet they want to say, well, we have this opposing opinion, so therefore it's change. What do you say to that?
Oh, well, you see, people naturally have a desire to learn. That's what separates us from the animals. We require training where we have to dedicate a certain amount of energy to learn and get input about the environment around us and especially how we should think and speak and behave.
And this energy is being dumped or damped out by what I call the dummy load. That's what most of the media is. And if you notice, it's just done on a weekly basis. There's a weekly story. It's like what happened about we were supposed to end society three times already last year with comets and financial collapses. And none of that seems to happen, but people seem to ignore it and go on to the next dummy load.
So we need to get more practical. When I say we, meaning because we're all here together and start really paying attention. I think I mentioned before, the most occulted and the most secret knowledge is actually discovering the obvious. So we need to start looking there, perhaps.
Isn't that the truth? I mean, everything I have ever said to anyone is straight data, resourced, backed up for you to find. And yet I'm constantly bombarded with, oh, my God, I can't believe you think this. And I'm like, well, it's in the news. It is real.
I explained how we sent a Doritos commercial to Ursa Major through using the iSCAT antenna array. And I'm getting messages. Well, you had me with your information until you brought up that we sent a Doritos commercial to Ursa Major. Obviously, you're just full of it.
And I find that people won't even hear things that don't relate to their own personal bias. And then they come back and say, well, you said this. And I'm always like, I never said that. You heard that.
Yeah. And also, I don't think anyone on Ursa Major will really get that commercial because the type of wave provocation they're doing will not make it there. It's another thing about how people consider the state of technology that they're in is another form of deception or delusion.
Because the quality of what's been given or portrayed as high technology or even, like you said, the news is qualitatively very low. And people just accept it.
Okay, so for 20 years, we've had alternative media hosts. Let's use Alex Jones as an example, since I'm friends with him. Well, I know him, and I feel like I can talk about him.
As simply being the flip side of the same coin, when 9-11 occurred, I said, don't freak out. This is all for your reaction. And in a way, I was predicting the Alex Jones type movement in saying that fanatics are going to rise at this time.
And I mean, for 20 years, this guy's been the alarm bell saying it's the end of the world. And people are all taking this into their soul and acting on this planet in a very schizoid manner because of all of this information that's being bombarded on them.
Yeah, and that has to do with things that I discussed, like, for example, what's fit and proper, what's lawful and unlawful.
And if anyone hasn't noticed, the planet right now is under an unlawful society. And this is just to go back to Alex Jones.
If it were a lawful society, people take what others say very seriously. And if someone is going to preach doom and gloom, especially and give a time period when these things should happen, and they do not,
those people won't be walking around too much longer. They're held accountable in these life and death matters. And what's going on is, because it's an unlawful society, people allow this to go on.
Well, let's talk about that then. Let's understand our laws, legal advice, and contracts, and try to figure out where it went wrong. Because if we want to go back to the birth of America, Freemasons coming over with their goddess Columbia and establishing justice on planet Earth, let's start there.
Because, I mean, people don't even know, first of all, that their nation was founded by this secret society. And they don't know that so much of what they're coming comes through this also religious programming.
I mean, I don't want to jump topics too quick, but we're looking at laws, legal advice. We might as well also throw in there the clock. Because, I mean, it was a regulation in the small towns back in the day, in the 1600s, 1300s, 1100s, where the church bell had to be able to be heard by the next town.
And the towns would be determined, the spacing, by being able to hear this chime that sets you to the clock. And folks, if you go around and look right now, you will see on every one of your cathedrals, that's where you get the town clock. This is where time comes from. So if we want to go legal and time-agreeing, let's look at that world.
Yeah, and there's many levels to that as well. Maybe we could squeeze that in enthusiastically, the other levels as well. Like, real quick, the church bell ringing. If you look at the etymology of the word church, it came from cirque, which meant the ancient circus. And it was borrowed and syncretized from various religions. The reason they're ringing these bells in public is because of the human sacrifices that were being done in public.
So that, wow, it's like, what did he just say? Yes. We could tie that back together again. But regarding law and timekeeping and all that, when we say law, I'm not talking about traffic law, tax law, or these things like that. I'm speaking about your basis for operating in the world.
You know, what do you eat? What's fit and proper to eat or lawful to eat? What's fit and proper to wear or lawful to wear? How do you raise a family? How do you do business? You know, all of these things are your laws, like laws of physics describe the natural world. When we say laws for mankind is that it affects or it's the impetus to how he will behave. All of that law comes from your deity. And I know it sounds kind of strange. And many people want to debate me on this. And when they do, for example, someone says, well, I'm an atheist. I don't have a god.
How do you deal with that? I said, that's easy. Do you believe in the laws of the state? And they usually say yes. I said, well, then the state is your god and April 1st is your holiday. Next. It's very simple. It's part of the operating system. Now, the legal aspect that we sense in the Western world today, when I say sense, because it's very convoluted, you can only get a sense of it if you actually put your handle and study the legal system, you'll see it's what they call based on legal fictions, representations.
So when you look at the Western world, especially if you look at the American Constitution and the preamble within the first preamble, it states that the people are to establish something called justice. It's like, wow, what is justice?
It seems to be a statue of a woman blindfolded, carrying scales. And if we do some research on that, we will find that is the revival of the ancient goddess religion. Has nothing to do with law, never did, never will. And essentially, the people from Europe were coming West to escape justice because it was destroying them.
So if you want to know something bad is going to happen, it's very easy to determine that when you see this term called justice arising in society.
Well, let's talk about her for a minute, because I was really the first expert on the goddess Columbia. And it was my second film and I laid it out there and I explained her connections to the pentagram, her connections throughout the different goddesses of Diana, Minerva, Inanna.
And what I found, also the connection with this pentagram, then it was a year later that Dan Brown came forward with the Da Vinci Code and kind of bonded the idea of the pentagram with the goddess, but never gave any explanation, which I had done.
And so, yeah, let's talk about Columbia and this goddess justice. And because I've asked Freemasons and people at the nation's capital, who is that standing on top of the Capitol Dome? And no one knows.
Yeah, the thing is also we have to throw in here, believe it or not, there is a parallel society to this materialistic human animal type, materialistic world that we look at sentient beings. And this is the spiritual realm and it is a multitude.
And here's the thing, if we're going to say that everyone that came before us that memorialized information, what they call the holy writs of the world, and even in the mythological texts, if they're all just a bunch of ignorant savages, and because we have iPhones and we can spin a prop and fly in an airplane, we're more advanced and we should ignore everything that came before us is quite foolish.
If we look at all the information that's been memorialized by what we might call from the ancients, far reaching back, even to the local, let's say, thousand years ago, what's been memorialized about the spiritual realm seemingly has been ignored.
And that there is a mass plurality, and yes, there are many gods, there is a hierarchy of gods, just like in the military there is a hierarchy, from the private, you know, boots on the ground enlisted guy all the way up to the colonels, generals, and the emperor, this is how the spiritual world is set up.
In other words, the military ranking system on the earth is not unique, it was actually conveyed from the spiritual realm.
That's why you'll see almost every country in the world has a very similar ranking system.
Now, within the ranking system of the spiritual realm, especially if we take heed to what's been memorialized, it seems like these lower level, what we call ranking spiritual entities, are interacting with mankind and have been for a very long time.
And it just so happens that one of the predominant inspirational spiritual entities on the earth happens to be female.
It's not that it's because someone might say, well, Greek, that's an anti-female, feminine sentiment, it's not.
It's as if you were, let's say, robbed by someone wearing a ski mask and you caught the assailant an hour later, you pulled the mask off, it's a woman, if you say I was robbed by a woman, does that make you anti-feminine?
No, it just so happens to be a female in this case, you see.
And this is also memorialized in the ancient texts.
Her priesthood is male, and a lot of people have misunderstood it as being a patriarchal system because of the male priesthood that she has.
And when I say she, there's actually more than one goddess as well in name and in attribute.
But this is a long-winded preface before getting into the goddess religion, because you'll see there's the concept of ISIS, Columbia, decay in ancient Greece.
There's the Statue of Liberty, there's justice, Lady Liberty, all these things, they hearken back to this very similar type of system.
Yeah, and it's being carried forth in near secret, but yet at the same time, our capital is the District of Columbia.
Yes.
And there's not a single person I know out there that ever asked the question, well, who is Columbia?
I think I was the first.
Yeah, probably.
And even though it's, well, you know, it's pretty obvious though, wherever you go, you do see it, but no one wants to discuss it, as you would have been probably the first to do it, as you say.
But what needs to be looked at is very simply, when you're brought into, let's say, the paradigm in the law or legal system is justice, for example.
And you ever noticed, it's in the language, if you listen to what's being said, you are brought to justice, you serve justice, there's a miscarriage of justice.
And where is the law in that, you see?
Because when we study the history of it, these goddess religions impart great cruelty to the societies that adopt them.
Now, it sounds kind of harsh, but I'm not making this stuff up.
You know, this is a fact.
Typically, the societies that have adopted these, again, I'll repeat myself, adopted these goddess religions, end up falling into situations of great cruelty and apathy, and a level where humans intuitively sense things shouldn't really be this way.
But yet, your common citizen or plebeian or person will say, or man or woman will say, I want justice, we need to bring him to justice.
Well, if you keep asking for it, you're going to get what you're asking for.
And henceforth, a lot of the complaining and bickering and whining about the justice system, there is nothing wrong with the justice system when they speak about corruption and cruelty and privatization and monetization and all this stuff going on.
That is inherent in that goddess religion, or the revival of it.
Well, so we've made these social contracts with these people.
And really, as you're saying, in our more and more atheistic mindset, I mean, we are controlled by deist, the free masonic order, the orders in charge, you know, you have to accept that, you have to state that you believe in a higher power, a deity.
But yet, when we're looking at a Masonic lodge, you will see the Koran, the Torah, or the Bible, all on their altar.
Yet, Freemasonry has all the trappings of religion.
So this obviously is a keen underpinning of why we have a goddess Columbia in their religious belief system.
But also just the idea that this religious programming, this tradition is idolized.
And, you know, we're like, we're not going to allow somebody in that isn't in the club that believes in religious programming.
And, you know, so let's look at where their mindset comes from in this religious programming.
We already got into the idea of the time, and we'll get deeper into that as well.
Sure. But in terms of the religious programming, it's beyond programming, it's more of the operating system.
And use the computer model, you know, the actual machine we call computers these days.
When you first start one up, you don't install a program, you install an operating system.
And then the program and then the files.
The operating system of, let's say, nation building or nations or groups of people, is that their government has a patron deity.
And you will find this throughout the entire history of mankind.
What's unique and what's going on today is that that concept has been brushed, not only under the rug, but out of the room and into oblivion.
No one is discussing what patron deity this nation has.
And this is the actual part of the operating system that you mentioned.
The Freemasons, they tend to be, you know, like it's said, a secret society and that they hold certain things in knowledge.
They do have this in their structure, the concept that each nation has a patron deity.
But they don't discuss it and they can't cognitively recall it, but they do sense it.
And part of speaking out publicly is that people go to a lot of these secret societies thinking that they actually have some deep knowledge.
And they don't anymore.
And I know this might be like kicking them in between their legs.
But what I mean by that is, you know, someone like Henry Ford, who started a car company on his own.
Do you think you can take his great grandson and give him all the resources and he can start a car company?
Probably not.
The people that originally formed a lot of these secret societies were very unique and very talented in that field.
And the people that come after them are just simply going through the motions, if that makes any sense.
Oh, absolutely.
You know, I don't for a second believe that George W. Bush or even Jeb Bush is a devout Christian.
And, you know, what does that even mean?
Can you get into that?
Sure. Well, this is a general thing, like you mentioned, in the Freemasonic Lodge.
They have the various holy writs of the corresponding religions, let's say.
And I have made this statement and have been making it and have not been proven wrong for years now.
That there is not a religion on the planet, bar none, that does what is allegedly in the text that they subscribe to.
And this is the truth.
And it sounds shocking on its face, but it's true if you look at it.
Now, religion just means something you do regularly.
Like if you brush your teeth and tie your shoes every day, that is a religious act.
It just means something you do regularly.
And because religion tends to tie in with a spiritual side of humanity or the gods, let's say,
that ties in back where you get your law and what you do based from your god.
But people are not acknowledging this.
And this type of discussion is typically not popular because, again, using the computer model,
if you're going to discuss computers, you might discuss this program, how you interface with it,
or the color of the webpage.
But no one wants to discuss the machine code, the C++.
You see, and this is what we're discussing is the machine code or the code behind what we call,
not just modern, but civilization at large.
And this is also probably a good point or very opportune to go into what's called timekeeping
because it is very important.
So with that, maybe we should mention that there's anomalies in people believing that the calendar is a timepiece.
How many times have you heard, you know, ask someone what day it is,
and they emphatically tell you something between January and December
and something between Monday and Friday with a number thrown in,
as if that is actually a timepiece.
It is not.
What we on the planet today are using as a calendar is not a timepiece.
You cannot reckon time with that calendar.
What I mean by that is if, let's say, you celebrate a birthday,
you'll notice that it's on a different day of the week every year.
What that calendar simply is, it is a work schedule for PAPL subjects.
I'll just say it one more time.
It is simply a work schedule.
That's why it's called the work week and the weekend.
You cannot keep time with it.
But just like a multiple choice question and answer test,
they give you four months out of the year that similarly denote
the correct correspondence of timekeeping.
Like, for example, septem means seven.
Octo, like octopus, means eight.
Nova means nine.
And decem means ten.
But everyone's writing December as twelve, November as eleven,
and so on and so forth.
So the way that time is being kept is part of the operating system as well.
And this is a recent phenomenon that the entire world is under this PAPL work schedule,
which is pretty fascinating to see in itself, how they've pulled that off.
Yeah, definitely.
Do you have any thoughts on the fact that we now have a Jesuit pope?
Not much.
Because here's the thing.
What's interesting is if you look at Christianity as you brought up,
and with the modern Catholic system,
and just to make a quick slice of what that really is,
first of all, you will not find Christianity in the biblical text whatsoever.
And second of all, the biblical text,
which is delivered to the world today based on what's called the King James Version,
is not a translation of what is known as the scriptures that are preserved in Hebrew and Greek,
correspondingly meaning Old and New Testament.
What is called the Old and New Testament,
which you will not find that in the text either,
that is, subtitles that have been put in after,
have yet to be translated to this date.
So what they have is a version that has been custom-tailored,
and basically the world still does not know what is held in those scriptures
unless you have done private research on your own.
Now back to the Christianity and the Jesuit pope,
what is called Christianity is actually started by someone called Simon Magus,
around the first century AD,
because there were things going on in the world that no one can explain,
things that were done in secret,
because the reason I'm saying they were done in secret is because they were actually public events.
So, go figure.
And they tried to syncretize, through syncretism,
they tried to explain modern day events in their time
by putting together all of these, let's call them pagan religions
from all over the world in concepts and traditions,
and they formed early Christianity.
Like for example, if anyone does any referencing to texts that are preserved,
these are secular texts about the Christians being thrown to the lions in the Colosseum.
If you go look at the texts that are preserved,
what they were actually doing,
because they would actually announce a decree before the games start,
just like they sing the national anthem before a baseball game,
and in those decrees before they allegedly threw the quote-unquote Christians
into the lions in the Roman Colosseums,
you will see that in the decree it states that
the reason they are thrown into the lions is because they are atheists.
In other words, they have an unidentifiable god.
This is really bizarre, but I'm not making this up.
Anyone who wants to really do the legwork can discover this.
Now what's interesting is that the syncretization
of all of the religions then solidified around the time of Constantine
and up until the first century AD,
and you have what's called the Catholic Church,
which is universal.
It's like we've swept everything that we can
and brought it up into one big pile,
and we've mixed it all together,
and we've syncretized it, and this is what it is.
It has no bearing on the biblical text whatsoever.
Yeah, I don't think many people are reading in Greek or Hebrew in these days.
Well, yeah, and even the thing, you know,
what's interesting when you do read in Hebrew or Greek,
or even in English, to understand the text,
it doesn't say that you need to learn any particular language.
It states that you have to have the ability to perceive with eyes and ears.
Okay, so on that thought,
and to take this to kind of back to the beginning
and on to another level,
when talking about the 9-11 programming
and the idea of the alternative media
then saying it's an inside job, it's an inside job,
you know, I was quickly one of the people saying,
no, you're throwing yourself into the fire.
They are going to use your own homework
to bring America to a war crimes tribunal.
And so, with everyone that is out shouting,
the government did a 9-11,
they are therefore throwing their own nation under the bus
without looking at the whole picture.
And I feel that, you know, it began in the Middle East,
it's going to come to the Middle East,
it's in the Middle East right now,
and with America coming down
and this potential of being called forward for universal war crimes,
what do you see going on in the Middle East?
Why is this such an important time and place right now?
Oh, from a geopolitical and from a large,
let's say, looking at the forest through the trees,
where now we are going above the forest,
looking at the entire forest,
you will see through history,
and I don't mean history like we started off,
alternative media just focusing every week on what happened,
but looking at history in thousand-year chunks,
let's say, or millennial or ages,
even in secular history,
you will see that it is stated
that civilization started in the Middle East.
And there is a lot of preaching and teaching
and all this stuff about we're in the end times.
Well, we're really not, but we are,
because it's not really, it hasn't been defined properly.
But what's interesting about everything starting,
like grandma said, what goes around comes around,
it is established through history
that everything started in the Middle East
and things are going to sort of wrap up in the Middle East.
And what you're seeing right now
is the precursor to the formation of a Middle East union.
Unlike the EU, see, the EU is also a union of nations.
It's going to be very different
than how the EU is operating today,
just to give the EU, meaning European Union, as an example.
Like I said, any time you preach doom and gloom,
you'll be popular.
And when they were preaching doom and gloom
during World War II with all of the bombing
and terror raids that were being done in Europe,
it was very convincing to say it's the end of the world,
and obviously it's not.
When I say world, meaning man's rule on earth, right?
So what had happened during World War II
was like the pulling out of teeth
of nationalistic governments.
Because you can't have, let's say,
ten nations forming a union
if they're independent and nationalistic
and don't want to work with each other.
So what people are witnessing
is that going on in the Middle East at the moment.
So a Middle East union.
In the future, yes.
And there are many, many, many details regarding that.
And it's not very difficult to see,
just as if, for example,
if someone is trained in chemistry,
and you're not,
and you walk in and speak with this individual,
he might say, well, don't touch that,
or don't mix this with that.
And you're like, why?
They're just two perfectly clear liquids.
What could go wrong, right?
So if you're studied in a certain field,
then you can impart that information, you see.
But most people seem to have wanting
to get stuck in this myopic, narrow,
oh, we're modern,
we don't need to look at what was written before us.
By the way, when you look at history
and other languages,
you know that every civilization before its fall,
or when it was in the period of its downfall,
which could have taken decades or a century,
always called themselves modern.
The Babylonians called themselves modern
in their texts at one point before their fall.
So did the Egyptians, so did the Greeks,
so did the Romans.
Interesting parallel.
Absolutely.
Well, in this modern age,
we are taking in tons and tons
of data and you were talking
about this info dump that,
this is one of the biggest problems
I see in our current trying
to change the world,
is that we just don't even know
what to focus on anymore.
And we get data, data, data.
And every day there's another thing
that you can twit and Skype
and chat and Facebook about,
social media all over the place.
And it's just going haywire, Greek.
And so let's talk about that.
Sure.
A real simple way to do that is,
let's just sidetrack here for a minute
and go right back to it.
Let's say we got a job working in the sewer.
It's the only job we could get.
It pays real well.
Do you skinny dip and drink the water
or do you put on a full hazmat suit
with breathing tanks?
Probably the second part.
Okay.
So anyone that does any research in society
will see that it's basically a sewer.
Every aspect, whether it's science,
within that system,
medical, legal, religious,
it's all really bad.
It couldn't be any worse,
like the frog being boiled kind of thing.
Everything is a little bit worse today
than it was yesterday,
but not as bad as it's going to be tomorrow.
It's a very gradual downslide that plateaus.
Okay.
So are we going to drink the water?
Not really, or the Kool-Aid
or whatever you want to call it.
So what that means then,
if you're going into the sewer
wearing protection,
you're actually setting yourself
apart from the medium.
You're creating a buffer zone
or a boundary layer
and you walk away from it.
An example for this,
just to fast track this thought,
is, for example,
during an election season,
people are always bickering
about following political leaders
and how the government is bad
and we can change it or whatever.
But when they do have,
let's say, an election,
and by the way, voters don't elect,
electors elect.
The word vote means that you are vowing
that whatever the electors do,
you'll stand behind it.
That's like a bombshell right there.
But if people want to change,
let's say, the way their government operates,
if no one at all,
this has to be an all or nothing,
if no one showed up to vote,
not a one person at all,
not even the crickets,
all of the government buildings,
local, state, city and federal,
will be empty.
Why?
And then anyone can walk in
and take the position.
Why?
Because they're going to say,
okay, the gig is up,
the next thing is we're in deep trouble
so we better leave now
while we're still alive.
You see, not violent revolution,
not protesting,
not all the stuff you hear,
it's all about the people.
I definitely see that.
I was introduced to
the Celestine Prophecies
by James Redfield
and it really described
what was going on
in my own personal view
as life had swept me up
and presented me
an experience that I could have
never imagined
or thought up on my own.
And at this moment I realized,
oh my God,
to be open to the opportunities and the possibilities that are being given to me.
And I have to be in a happy mindset, friendly and agreeable for miracles and angels to enter
into my life.
And I found that if the world followed these simple insights of connecting with beauty,
therefore finding your inner peace and then projecting this out as an energetic form of
your soul, that that will attract the right energies coming back and you will find miracles
going on in your life where you're like, wow, I would have never thought to do this.
This is perfect.
Wow.
How did this even happen?
Well, what's interesting about that, it sounds wonderful, but we, in order to get to the
manifestation point, we need specifics.
And there's certain generalities that work, like most people that operate what they call
an automobile don't know how to rebuild the engine, but they know if they put the key
here and push this pedal and turn that, they're going to get the job done.
And when we're discussing help from the spiritual side, most people are completely devoid of
it.
Like for example, when people say angels and gods, they are under the misconception that
all of that is benevolent.
And if you are not benevolent, you are always going to show as being benevolent, you see.
It's kind of like if someone's going to counterfeit a note, do you use a crayon and draw a quick
doodle of Ben Franklin and write a hundred in the corner with a crayon, or do you try
to make it look like the original note as close as possible, you see?
So mankind has fallen for a lot of this, and we do need specifics.
And these specifics are part of what's going to be coming in the future regarding the spiritual
realm.
Well, using the concept of the idea of counterfeiting, you know, I would say at this time and space
that money is the deity of most people right now.
Sure.
And you know, most people refuse to research things that they established as things to
be worshipped.
Like, for example, like we mentioned earlier, you will not find anyone that categorizes
themselves as having a particular religious faith as ever researching what that faith
is supposed to be based on.
Because if they do, they retract and say, I can't call myself a Christian or a Muslim
or a Jew or a Buddhist or a Hindu or whatever, because I've researched what this is based
on and I just can't do it.
See people idolize and worship things, and once they get into that realm of worship and
idolization, they no longer want to look at anything about it.
And then it's very easy to have that system debased.
Like for example, all of the religions are debased currently.
All of the money is debased.
If you tell anyone, this is fiat currency, they say, well, I don't care as long as I
go to the store and get something for it, you see.
So there's this worship of things that makes mankind retract from using his cognitive rational
ability and then falls into these debased things.
If you ask people, why do they go to a particular temple or religion, they say, I don't care.
I just like there because I have a good time.
I feel loved or whatever.
So the worship of money is an interesting concept because what is actually being used
as money today is clearly not money, lawful money.
And it is just a means of exchange, unlawful means of exchange, right?
Because if you're going to do barter or exchange, it should be of equal value.
And no one seems to care simply because they worship it.
And anything people worship, for example, even people that go to these better universities,
they don't care what the professor says.
They just want to say, I went to an Ivy League so they can be worshipped, right?
If someone walks into the room and says, I have an Ivy League education, how dare you
question me about anything, you see?
So there's many things that are worshipped in society and money being the base of it.
And money is not the root of all evil.
It's the love of money.
And it's sort of like a joke that the spiritual realm, because they do have a sense of humor
apparently, is playing on humanity.
They probably said, let's take money away from them and watch how much they still want
it just to show that it's the love of money, you see?
So these things are pretty much the money, the religion, all these aspects are debased.
There is nothing backing them up anymore.
And almost everything that mankind is dealing with right now is debased.
It has no basis, whether it's scientific, medical, and so on.
And the money being the root of it, because it's very hard to operate in society without
it.
And by the way, I've also said in the past, you hear a lot of these economic people making
comments on the economy and money.
Not a one of them ever says there's a difference between lawful and unlawful money and what
the money is actually based on.
If it's not based on anything, it is based on something, because you see numbers and
things flying around.
Again, escapes pretty much everyone.
But what I've said is that money just is portable land.
That's all it is, because in a perfect society, you'll be able to garner everything you need
from what's under your feet.
But when you travel and go to someone else's land, you can't bring your land with you.
So you bring precious metals and or something that is based on representation of the land.
So these things are very simple concepts.
But again, once they're thrown into the realm of worship, no one wants to look at it.
Well, this also has brought us to the level of waste and planned obsolescence and the
way that we are trying to make more money than we are, you know, things.
We're making more things than we need so that there's more empty houses than there are
homeless. And we have this built in planned obsolescence, which is only due to money.
I mean, what kind of idiot world would create such a thing?
Sure. Well, the thing about the homes is interesting is let's look at the Western world.
Remember, we said what goes around comes around.
Most of the Western world, meaning this hemisphere, let's call it America.
How did it start? It started with slave labor and stolen land.
Guess how it's going to kind of wrap up slave labor and stolen land.
So it's just these things are very simple.
You know, like what I mean by slave labor is back in the 80s, Ford was a motor company
was hiring line workers for 20 to 28 dollars per hour in the 80s.
Right now they're hiring them for 10 or 12 an hour.
Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. So minimum wage, according to a lawful perspective, should be around 23 bucks an
hour, about twenty two fifty right now.
Okay. So and stolen land.
What I mean by that is there hasn't been a legal or lawful foreclosure in the US in the
past 80 years.
It's all presumptive and people go for it.
So, boy, these are these are topics that people just don't want to look at.
Simple to understand.
You know, simple doesn't mean easy, does it?
Not usually. No.
Usually, as you're saying, the obvious is some of the hardest stuff to take in.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. You know, here's an example.
Throw this in maybe about the obvious.
You ever notice when you heat or cool a room, the heat goes to the ceiling and the cold
goes to the floor all year round.
So you have a hot head and cold feet.
But if you go out in nature, it's hot in the valley.
You go up to the mountain, it gets colder.
And if you go in an airplane towards the sun, which is supposed to be a heat source, it
gets colder and colder and colder.
Because could it be that in all natural biological systems, cold
rises and heat descends?
But in all artificial type situations, you have the opposite.
So where are the people asking their air conditioning and heating engineers?
Why don't you design systems that have an ascending cold and a descending heat like in
nature? Because right now we're getting hot heads and cold feet.
I have never thought of that.
And how obvious is that?
I mean, I am sitting here exactly in that condition.
I've got my slippers on trying to keep my cold feet warm.
And yeah, I got a hot head.
That doesn't make any sense.
So why would it be that way even?
Yeah, well, if you want to just give a quick slice, you know, for those that tend to be
technically or scientifically inclined, let's say whenever you have chemical
decomposition or things being destroyed or exploded, you have the heat that rises and
the cold that descends.
But whenever you have a chemical agglomeration where things come together and build
like natural growth, you have a cold that rises and a heat that descends.
Like, for example, if you called a medical person and said, I'm not feeling well and
they say, well, how do you know?
Well, my head is hot.
My feet are cold.
Oh, you're not feeling well.
But wait a second.
I thought heat supposed to rise and cold supposed to descend.
But you see, in all natural biological systems, whether it's the Earth, the planets, a
dog, a cat, a plant or you, the heat becomes dense and descends and the cold becomes
rarefied and lighter and it rises.
And no one is paying attention.
No one is going to that.
Yeah. Why?
Because it's right in front of us.
Right. The same with the timekeeping schedule.
You know, here's the thing, you know, the for thousands of years, the ancients kept
time using the sun, the moon and the stars.
And they were very precise and very accurate.
Like even today, if you want to convey an accurate time event.
Well, by the way, time is just the recordation of events.
So whenever you hear about time travel or this or time being a dimension, that's all
bunk. If there is time travel, it's traveling to a past event.
It's not time travel.
Now, Greek, that's semantics.
But think about it. All right.
So for thousands of years, people settled their debts with the full moon, which is the new
moon today. Don't you get a monthly bill?
Yeah. And the day starts at high noon, like before the electronic banking conventions,
the banks, if you made a deposit afternoon, it was counted as the next day.
Yeah. Some people say after two o'clock or whatever, but typically that's how it works.
And even this, if you go to your timekeeping authorities in Greenwich or Naval
Observatory in Colorado Springs, I believe in their website, they used to have a since
I've started speaking about this, I think they've taken it down.
But you can still find it under Julian calendar date that define the calendar.
And they tell you in their timekeeping authorities, they tell you that for astronomical and
scientific purposes, the day starts at solar noon.
But for the people, it's civil midnight.
Now, wait a second. That is such a put down.
What I mean by that is when dictionaries in the 19th century were becoming coalesced to
be put out into the public, they didn't quite know how to define words because you see a
dictionary doesn't give you the meaning of the word.
It gives you the diction of the word, how you should pronounce it.
So it seems like you know what you're talking about.
That's why when you look up a word in a dictionary, it always shows you the phonetic
spelling first, you know, like the upside down E means an A and all this other stuff.
But if you want to know what words really mean, you need to look up etymology.
But back to the dictionary, when they first started writing dictionaries, they didn't
know how to define words.
So, like, for example, when you looked up in an old Webster's dictionary, the word oats,
it's what they feed horses in England, but it's the staple of the people in Scotland.
What a put down, right?
So so so the scientific community and what you want to call them Illuminati or secret
societies or the people that are in the know know that the papal work schedule is not a
timepiece. And that's yeah.
Webster was a Freemason and he actually encoded many things into the dictionary like the
Bible. That was one thing should lead you to another, you know, see this reference
that and it would lead you into this code.
So, you know, even the dictionary was written by secret society.
Oh, yeah. And all the high noon, high noon is very important inside of Freemasonry as
well. Yeah. Oh, sure.
Sure. And that's how you know your concept of equinoxes, you know, equal day, equal
night. And that's the St.
John's inside of Freemasonry.
Yeah. But that is also erroneous because the term equinox equi meaning equal knocks,
meaning night means that there's an equal measurement that needs to be taken at night.
We can discuss that later, but the real equinox is and really freak people out.
It's very subtle. So the equinox is erroneous.
And even what they're calling solstices are erroneous, because if you even look in their
own documentations like weather websites, what they're calling the solstice, you'll find
like this year, the day was still what they were calling the solstice was about two
minutes shorter than the previous than the than the day that would come after that.
So they're not acting. But no one's checking right now.
No one wants to look at these things.
So because it's part of tradition.
But, you know, the timekeeping, the secrets and the secret societies, all of these
things are linked together.
And these secret societies, all they all they do, it's kind of like the the sewer analogy.
They kind of look at the behavior of the masses and say, do we really want to share this
information? And they say no.
So they keep it to themselves to a certain degree.
But here's the thing. Then what they've done is they've removed the eyes of the people
and then blame them for being blind.
So it's a catch 22, you see.
So, you know, the information should go to mankind and it will not now because there's a
right time and a place for everything.
Right. And but in the near future, there will be a time where people will start to look
at what things are based on and referencing them more properly.
Absolutely. Etymology is an amazing study.
You know, when you start to realize where things come from, what they mean, your whole
language changes.
You start to understand the legal system in a whole new light.
You know why a human being is classified as monster or things of that nature.
Yeah. Or nice.
You know, you're a nice guy. This is a nice show.
People are nice. You know, if you look up that word and I don't like to give the meaning
of it because for some reason, when people look it up on their own, it has to have like
70 percent more punch to it.
And like they don't want to believe you when you tell them.
But the word nice, if you look it up in an etymological dictionary, it means foolish,
senseless, stupid.
Huh. So, yes, that's just it.
We are we are really ignorant and words are power and we know this.
Well, what they are is the action to it's the preaction to action, just like, for
example, in the military.
And in an analogy, you can have a commander sitting on one continent giving a word to
someone on the ground in another continent and then the action is conducted.
So they are very powerful in that way.
It's communication. And just like the military, before you attack, you make sure that
the opposition cannot communicate amongst themselves.
Now, if you actually look at how society is on Earth, if you think people are
communicating, you're not paying attention because they're not.
One of the first things that has been taken away is people's ability to communicate
effectively. Amen.
Amen. Well, we open this show with the idea that the Francis Crick Institute is now
legally altering DNA and embryos and opening the door to designer babies.
And so I would like to close out this hour with you with the idea of the satanic
view, if you will, the idea of stark materialism.
Sure. How we've gotten there and what that's going to lead to.
Well, there's two aspects to that.
When we say something, let's say the mark of the beast or the end times or Satan or
the Antichrist, we in order to in order to prevent those topics or notions from being
debased, we have to go back to where those things came from.
And obviously they came from what's called the biblical text.
So we have to go and adhere to what is memorialized in the biblical text first before we
start making up porcupines and things like that, because then we are just drifting off
into La La Land.
If we go back to the text where we get the concept of Satan, we will find that the word
Satan just means adversary.
Like if I say black, you say white.
If I say ugly, you say pretty.
That means you're an adversary to me.
This is a cosmic thing.
Now, what's interesting is when we look at the ancient text, and this has nothing to do
with opinion or what you believe in, that the entire world is run by a cosmic adversary.
And for example, Satan just means adversary.
For example, court TV.
If you turned on court TV in Jerusalem, in the modern Hebraic tongue, the prosecutor is
introduced as Ha-Satan.
So it just means the adversary.
So what is interesting when we look at the ancient text regarding Satanism, this cosmic
deity or entity known as the adversary, and he does have a name, by the way, which is
memorialized in many texts, is in control, you're ready for this, of every government,
every major institution that man is involved in.
So all of your religions, all of your sciences, all of your philosophies, all of your
governments, all of your laws are controlled by this satanic cosmic deity.
Wow.
Now, what I want to say about that is when you have these groups calling themselves
Satanists, that is erroneous, because if you look at, for example, these Satanists, that
is not Satan.
Like, for example, the Temple of Set.
Set is not Satan.
Set is like the Lord of Darkness from Egypt.
And you'll have various sects that call themselves Satanists erroneously.
They are reviving these ancient balls or lords or demons of particular geographic locations
of the world. So again, we are not communicating.
But what I mean about the darkness, the second part to this, is that when you read in the
ancient text, beware the workers of darkness, for example, that is not necessarily visible
light and dark, but that as well.
And what I mean by this is, for example, in ancient days, society garnered most of
their behavior and materials from the light.
The day started at high noon.
The full moon was the full month and they used the stars and luminaries to keep time.
All of their materials to make furniture, clothing, foodstuff, buildings were garnered
from the light, surface minerals, trees, plant fibers, plant inks.
See, now this is the time of great darkness because your day is reckoned in the middle
of the night. Your new year is reckoned in the darkest season, in the darkest day, the
darkest month.
Your materials are all garnered from petrochemical products.
Can anyone really say that there is nothing that is petrochemically derived within five
feet of their reach?
All of your food is wrapped in it.
All of your materials are affected by it.
Petrochemicals come from the dark.
It's black crude oil.
And also the light destroys the dark.
If you leave petrochemicals in the light, they're destroyed.
So this is the light and dark and the satanic and, you know, and satanic.
You know, there's contrasts within each one and people fail to understand them still.
Amazing stuff, folks, his name is the Greek, and this is why he's going by getting us out
this information that no one else is sharing.
And so I can't give you a website or anything to share.
But you are now currently on AFR doing a bit of a block there and sneaking your way in
sometimes in the late night shows.
I love Danny. I just want to say that AFR has always been really good to me.
That's American Freedom Radio, folks.
Definitely check out their shows.
And you've got a slot right now you're doing, right?
Sure. And the site that we set up around that slot, it's called Ocelli.
And the Greek dot com.
And because I need adult supervision, Chuck Ocelli, I feel very much indebted to him
showing up two hours a week to be the sonic counterpart to the Greek because I just can't
do it alone. And it's called Ocelli and the Greek.
And it is on AFR.
Yes. And I do appreciate being here as well for these small bit of time.
Well, I knew we were going to have a good talk and folks, I hope you gain some from this
to really just to start to look at the obvious again and take things in deeper.
And members, you know, it always gets stranger on the other side.
So when we get back, we're going to take this thing off this out of the world and get
into advanced energy ideas, our future radioactivity, end of the world, prophecies,
predictions and everything coming for you in the members section right now.
The rest of you, thank you so much for tuning in every week.
And I love seeing you all there at Freeman TV dot com.
And please give us thumbs up shares rates and all that good stuff whenever you're
listening to the show, especially on Stitcher.
I don't know if me bringing this up will make it go down even worse, but it seems that
on Stitcher when you're listening on your phone, you can give a thumbs up and it seems
like only the haters give the thumbs down.
So I would love to rise up in those top 100 ranks so that this show goes out to more and
more and more people because, you know, we're doing this because if you know, you
better share. And that's the last message I want to leave with you all is is share
this information with everyone that you can, because you want to feel like you had a
part in making the change and you don't want to live with the guilt of having done
nothing. So if there's no more else you can do, at least share the information.
And that is at least, you know, the least you could do.
We all have a big job in front of us as we're learning to learn to get this true
information understood and to know what to focus on and what not to focus on.
So I'm so happy we have people like the Greek coming around to hone in our focus a
bit more. So stay tuned, members.
We're coming right back with some really good weirdness.
You're going to really enjoy this show and the rest of you.
We will see you next week.
And, you know, Freeman TV completely under construction.
So don't worry.
It's going to be awesome.
So if it's down, just don't worry.
It's going to be great when it comes back.
It'll only be days.
So don't worry if the website is down.
All right. So thank you all so much for tuning in.
We will see you next.