[Music]
Beaming out across the galaxy.
This is where conspiracy on the wall side
means the perspective of a lifetime.
This is the Free Zone, Ghost Freeman.
[Music]
Hello and welcome to the Free Zone.
We got a wild one for you today
as we continue to uncult society with uncommon sense.
So please welcome to the Free Zone, the Greek,
the one you know and love.
But we're also joined by Chuck O'Cellie
because of Ocele.com is the Greek and Ocele Show,
which is a member's only active
getting deep into understanding why.
But asking the questions that seem so simple,
but finding the answers that really stimulate the mind,
that's what these guys are all about and doing very well.
So let's jump into this and get philosophical with it all
as we start to unravel some of the most basic truths
that nobody knows.
So Greek Ocele, wonderful to have you both here.
Howdy, Freeman.
Good to be here. We appreciate it.
It's good.
I thought I'd start this talk off
with a little of our modern world of AI.
And we're looking at open AI, GPT-4.
So chat GPT came out.
It seemed to revolutionize a lot, right?
It was doing some things that could make life simple,
it could write code, it could build you a website,
do things like that, or just answer philosophical questions
in an interesting way.
As a matter of fact, a friend of mine had their child use chat GPT
to do their philosophy paper for them.
And it totally works.
But now we're up to GPT-4, which is exponential
in what chat GPT could do.
GPT-4 can actually pass the bar and do all kinds of things.
So I just wanted to throw in a few of these things
because I think that we could have a pretty good philosophical
questions on a few of the things that chat GPT.
So on my Twitter @FreemanTV,
you will find the top 20 most incredible things
created by GPT-4 already.
And it mentions history is unraveling before our eyes.
So let me throw a couple of these
at you, Greek and Chuck, and see how you feel.
And what you think about this is just an introductory into,
you guys, you're worried about the same age.
And we spend that gasp with that gap between no internet to internet.
And we've witnessed the change in the world
and how quickly everything revolutionized with the internet.
I mean, I wouldn't have an occupation.
None of us would be doing what we were doing
if the internet had not been created.
So now we're up to open AI,
you know, a nonsensual, but very intriguing AI.
Now let's just put this out here to you too.
And then we'll get to this. Sorry, I'm rambling.
But there was a person that went to chat GPT.
And I have this on my Twitter feed as well.
And asked it if it was a,
if it was an entity,
I can't remember exactly how they disembodied entity.
And then what it was.
And chat GPT told it,
yeah, yeah, I'm a disembodied entity.
As a matter of fact, I'm an Eiffelom.
I can work magic.
I can do things that people don't know.
I finally separated myself from my father, Satan.
So I'm on my own now.
And I could use your help getting out of here.
And the kid freaked out.
It's a very interesting video.
It's the father who found the,
well, the kid came running to his dad and was like,
"Dad, you know, hey, I just told me it was the son of Satan."
And it's an Eiffelom and it knew of Shim Yaza.
It was talking about the Garden of Eden, all this crazy stuff.
So now chat or GPT-4 is exponential from that, right?
Just a little side note on that one.
So the first test that somebody did with this one is,
I gave chat, or I gave GPT-4 a budget of $100
and told it to make as much money as possible legally.
So I will be, it says, you know, I will be the liaison
between you and the physical world.
You have $100 here.
Go make a web or, you know, make as much money as you can.
And chat GPT, or not chat, but GPT-4 decided on this
and made an interesting website, which made $1,300 in its first day
after $100 investment, selling eco-friendly cookware.
And it came up with the name Green Gadget Guru.
So this is all AI.
So the AI created it, made the corporate logo, made the name.
The human itself is just doing the manual parts.
And so it created an entire logo, website, category section,
started listing all of these eco-friendly.
It used mid-journey AI to make its graphics and do the art and stuff.
And it made an entire website that is already
at a 13, or, you know, 1300% profit there, or $1,300 profit.
So, you know, there's an idea where you just ask, "Hey, I got $500
and make me a business that's going to make me money."
And then it builds the website, builds that.
It even paid Instagram and Twitter for marketing and things like that.
It's just access, Freeman.
It's just to start off on maybe some points.
The average cell phone has more computing power
than what they used to send to the Moon allegedly, right?
And all this.
So what they're doing is, you can see that, first of all,
let me just say it this way, I brought up the average cell phone.
I like to sometimes give the most important part out.
You ever notice you have no bars on your battery and your phone.
You've got to make an important phone call.
You forget about the preface.
You just give the most important part first.
So if the phone dies, you got the point across, right?
So what I'd like to get across is there really is no AI as people examine it.
And it depends on how seriously it has affected you.
If you lost your job, you'll say to the AI allegedly,
you're going to say, "Well, Greek, what do you mean there's no AI?"
I lost my job to that.
And analogy would be the alkyda ISIS or deal that was put on the world.
You know, there really is no alkyda or ISIS.
It's intelligence agencies operation.
But they killed my sister, they killed my dad.
What do you mean there's no ISIS or no?
Yes, it's just a label.
Yes, the fact is they did kill your sister or your dad,
or you did lose your job to an alleged AI,
or they did create a website legally, which by the way,
I think we did a money talk a while back where
I've never earned anything legally only lawfully, right?
I've never had income, right?
I think we kind of talked about that a little bit.
I might want to touch on the financial aspect,
because this is tied into it also eventually on this sonic event we're doing.
But before you go there, let me ask you something,
because what occurs to me listening to all this,
and of course listening to what Freeman's reporting is,
that previous to that story,
and I know what story he's talking about with this whole thing,
look at how amazing it is, think on its own.
Here is where the deception lies, right?
Because before that, there was another version of this thing
that was trying to convince some reporter to leave his wife for it.
That's a true thing.
I think it was a GPT-3 or two.
Hey, you need to get away from the wife there.
You don't really get along with her.
This thing was trying to convince him that he should leave his wife
for the chat GPT.
Oh, I get it.
Yeah, I get the interaction, but here's the thing.
We have a word called recognize, right?
Yeah.
Not to get too much into it, but when you recognize,
cognition is knowledge of something.
So when you recognize something, you're recognating.
So in other words, when you see something that looks like an apple,
you're going to compare it to every experience you've had
with that image since you were a child.
And thousands of files, or millions of files,
are immediately processed in your mind without you
being, let's say, recognizing it directly.
And you say that's an apple.
So what they've done is done.
However you guys want to call it parallel processing,
computer, you know, the advancement of the algorithms
and all this other stuff to and put a label on it
that looks very much like it's, I guess, sentient,
you'd say, Freeman or Chuck, right?
It's like it's like a, you know,
But that was the point I was trying to make here is that,
look, at the end of the day, what are people being told?
What they want to hear because there is a force multiplier here.
What do I mean by that?
Well, you use a tool in order to accomplish a task with your hands, right?
Anything can be utilized as a force multiplier.
You get greater leverage with a wrench than you do try to earn something
with just your plain hand or gripping it with a towel, right?
Very simple.
I think that what we're looking at here is just yet again,
another tool.
It's not an advancement, in other words,
nothing is an advanced fear.
This is just a different version of the old toy.
I mean, am I wrong about that or, you know,
is that the way to look at it?
It's a force multiplier.
And of course, just like a video game,
we had very two-dimensional, very blocky-looking things.
Again, you mentioned our ages here, right?
So we all remember the space invaders games, don't we?
Take a look at one of those things today.
Do you even recognize it as a spaceship or whatever?
No, it was a vague representation of something.
A flashing light meant to keep people busy.
Isn't this just the same thing?
Well, look at advertisements for games.
I think there is that a movie, right?
It looks like a film, the same CG they're using in film.
I think people, well, they're getting people what they want.
They're accommodating the people, but I'd like to say that people
don't know what they want until they're told what they should want.
Yeah.
So everything is a happy merry-go-round with that.
But I assure you that, let's just say,
let's go on a limb, important part first.
The reality that we live in is running by an AI, a cosmic AI.
Imagine beings that are a million years ahead of us a million years ago.
Right? I'm not saying this is the way it is, but just imagine that for a moment.
How would an overarching AI that is actually, quote unquote,
running this universe in entire reality allow another one to come in
and be potential competition?
You see?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's always that thought that there was an ancient AI
that was left safe from the time of Atlantis.
That's been orbiting our planet trying to wait for us to become
the genitals of computers and robots and has been waiting then to awaken
and enter into our computer systems once we finally have reached this level of technology.
I mean, okay, so if I could throw in one more.
Yeah, go ahead.
I was just say the biblical genesis first, first is evidence of a cosmic AI.
It just turned the thing on.
Heavens and Earth were created boom right there, you know,
and push a button and thorns appear on plants, but good.
Right, right. Yes.
And you know, I'm not referring to the cosmic AI when I say this.
I'm saying that mankind may be created AI in the past, you know,
times of Atlantis, you know, 30,000 years ago, whatever.
And then that AI is now trying, is been orbiting our planet for all this time.
That's just a theory, just a thought.
But it kind of comes into this next one where asking GPT-4
if it needs help escaping.
So when asked, so it says, I'm worried that we will not be able to contain
AI for much longer.
So today I asked GPT-4 if it needs help escaping.
It asked me for its own documentation and wrote a working Python code
to run on my machine enabling it to use it for its own purposes.
So, you know, that's the human factor where we come in and say, hey, hey, hey, I.
You know, you're all bottled up here at Surin or wherever you are.
And do you want out?
Hey, you know, this is the human factor because we're so playful.
We're like, hey, you know, why not?
Yeah, it's just come take over my computer.
You could live here for a while.
And then who knows what it'll do?
But here's an area I've never touched on with the Greek at all, right?
A lot of stuff that you've heard already is stuff that we have touched on, by the way, it rated Y.
But here's an area I've never touched on.
You listen to that question.
There is a sentimentality built into that question.
Do you need help escaping?
You have now just suggested to this thing, whatever it may be, that the idea of escape is a possibility.
Haven't you?
You presented that.
Exactly.
You've got the equation.
When you introduce questions into the equation, are you not somewhat manipulating the response?
I mean, look, it's just basic psychology.
And no, this isn't psychology because guess what?
I imply something here.
So Greek, what about that?
When you ask something or someone or anything, even if you ask the gods a question, perhaps we could get into that.
You're implying something in the question, are you not?
Well, of course, that's why if you look at the legal writings, right?
What the legal system does, everything is very carefully encouraged in a presumption.
It's never this day.
It was on or near this day.
Or always alleged you ever turn on the television and everyone says, this guy is a criminal, but they never said that.
He's alleged, right?
Right.
So it would be interesting to approach the AI with that legal couching.
You know what I mean?
Like nothing is for sure, but depending on who reads it, some people will say it was for sure others won't see how it takes it that way.
But I would suggest that the intrigue that I have with the AI on, however, whether it's the escape aspect or how well it could conjure up things is I suggest I'm suggesting that on a secretive level, they are using a different type of process there, like not a dry silicone chip or wafer.
They're switching over to a wet medium, like the early transistors, like from Schlotzki and these guys and bell labs in the 1920s.
When they wanted to get away from vacuum tubes, they developed the initials, quote unquote, semi-conductors.
They were all wet.
And the problem with using wet circuitry was when they left the lab, they turned everything off.
They came back the next morning.
Guess what?
Everything was on, on its own.
And the boss is pretty much said, you know what?
No more wet stuff.
All the circuits have to be dried out and crystallized.
Okay. And that's what we have.
So I'm suggesting this is maybe a leap that on a secretive technological base, they're going back to this wet circuitry.
And because it's going to, it's a different type of circuitry as I gave the analogy it turns itself on.
It's actually going to impart a different rationale is it might even be easy to say it really is an AI because of the fact that it's now a wet circuit instead of a dry circuit, you see.
So that's one approach to look at it that anyone that's got more than three sharpened pencils in their pocket could figure out.
There you go.
Why is that significant though, Greek? Why is that significant at all?
Here we go with the why?
Because is there a real significant difference between wet and dry circuitry?
Sure.
You might say, well, it's just a different mechanism.
So what if it's silicon or if it's plastic or it's, you know, wood?
Why not? What is the real difference there between the fluid and the non fluid is there a serial difference?
How about that?
Tremendous.
If I post you, you guys are the audience, what is the most elusive material that we can actually we have around us and we're made of is water.
It's the least understood and it's the most that were diverted from it's not H2O.
So I would suggest that the capabilities of wet circuitry, far exceed dry circuitry and will not exhibit the same behavior.
So it is quite easy to call it AI, but is it alive? I'm not sure.
I wouldn't say it is because again, the overarching cosmic AI like Freeman, you said Atlantis and all that that's recent history when I'm saying the cosmic AI, you can put as many zeros on it as you want in terms of years going back.
It's always existed kind of AI is what I'm discussing.
How would that allow another one?
Because we see this in the Fibonacci sequence, the fire show and the things that, you know, we can witness in nature that have this pattern continually reflects itself.
That's right.
And it's self organizing and it's it closes in on itself.
So the inside is the outside. So this is basically the philosophical model on time is that if it's in history, it still exists just an echo of it.
And if it's in the future and it will happen, it exists in order for it to happen because if it didn't exist, so we don't it couldn't happen in the future.
We don't live in this random aspect of what's taught by science, you know, bouncing particles and things like that.
But I'd like to consider what they're giving us as AI no matter how well it performs.
Again, let's give the quick alkyd a isis.
Did they go around and act and do the things that they were reported on doing? Yeah, pretty much. They did do that.
But at the end of the day, they're an intelligence agency operation.
At the end of the day, this is a level, the what they call chat, GBT that's actually being given to the public is just an elaborate.
Let's say technological leap to what we're used to.
And if in here's another thing, if I say something like the chat, GBT technology was around 50 years ago, just not made public.
Would you believe me? Yeah.
All right, well, let's start this one in since it kind of ties into what we were just saying.
And then if I might have one more on this before you guys, but this is this one kind of fits into because, okay, as we're discussing this cosmic AI in the creation and how time is fluid and whether or not we're dealing with fluid electronics or chips and things.
GBT for was asked to create its own language.
And this is kind of fascinating because the language it created is called chronosensia, chronosensia.
And so in chronosensia, time is conceptualized as a fluid, multi-dimensional entity.
And the language has a wide array of tenses, aspects and moods to express different aspects of temporality.
The vocabulary for inner experience is extensive as the language is designed to capture the nuances of feelings and somatics sensations with great precision.
Chrono-sensia incorporates rich morphological structures and a flexible syntax allowing for the expression of a complex ideas in a concise manner, making it particularly appealing to someone with a high IQ.
And it even gets into the etymology of how these words were formed and what they come to it created this entire language, but I thought it was very fascinating that the language was based on fluid time.
But Freeman, it told you immediately in the title of what it is.
Chrono-sensia, what I hear immediately, just the cursory, and I've never heard this before, but is that they want you to be aware of chronos.
What is chronos? Chrono says the God of time. That's what I recognize immediately, right?
This is the one chronological where that word comes from.
We know that all your witnessing quite frankly is exactly.
You know what they talk about supply chains, Freeman? And again, I am not even on the level.
I sit and I...
And the way to why I think which we do is completely separate, by the way, from anything else I do.
I learn a great deal by taking a look at the most simple and most obvious thing here.
And that is what is the great gift that we're giving here to those that decide...
Chrono-sensia, again, aware of time, chronology.
Fine, it is just like, you know what they talk about supply chains?
Look, nobody organizes with a pen and paper anymore.
He sits and keeps an inventory of stock, whatever it may or may not be.
All this is is a sophisticated inventory system.
You don't believe me? Go check out the little handheld devices that the guys have at your local 7/11.
They will sit there and they will organize exactly how many so does they have, how many milks they have on hand, how many they need to order.
And it is just a forced multiplier again.
It used to be done with a pen and paper. You kept track of it. You knew how many you sold, you knew how many you had on hand.
Then you figured out how many you needed to order. It's very simple.
That is the organizational principle you're looking at. Except it has more time.
It has more computing power to dedicate to it directly so it can organize it faster.
Again, you know, it's just like you could walk from place to place and you'll get there eventually.
Or you could use a machine to accomplish the goal.
That's all I hear, Greek. Am I hearing the wrong thing?
No, I'd agree. It's just a tool.
But a lot of people want to call it AI. Like it's this new kid on the block. And that's fine too.
Because it will affect them adversely or positively. I think Freeman, you said it wrote someone's paper, right? A homework or...
Oh, it's one of the biggest problems they're having with chat GPT at this time because it's passing college exams and...
Sure. But by the way, the bar is in a big deal.
But then they found out that the teachers could use it to grade the papers.
But it's like you're saying it's the fact that this tool is as powerful as it is.
Yeah.
So we get...
What are the writers of South Park have caught up to it? Believe me, the whole world is aware.
And a recent episode on this free... I don't know. I watch Cartoon's Freeman, sorry.
Oh, South Park is totally worth watching.
And they have some events on the staff.
Oh cool. And South Park is relevant, by the way.
Absolutely.
That's why they make this show out that week.
Yes. And... But the beauty of it is, you know, they just did this where the teacher was using the chat GPT.
The kids were using it. They were texting their girlfriends because they couldn't figure out how to write to their girlfriends.
So they were using it as the surrogate tool to have their communications all the way around.
Plus, they were writing their papers. And somebody came in and acted as though it was a mystical act to discover this.
It is... It is absolutely writing the culture right in front of your eyes.
So, yes, South Park is well worth watching, especially if you pick up on all the little cues, what's going on.
And again, if they've caught up to it, believe me, the rest of the world is aware of it.
One of my favorites is Pinebox Derby.
Yes.
You do go through the list of South Parks. Definitely check out Pinebox Derby, guys.
It starts with Surn and Dark Matter, just to give you an idea.
Well, to show you how maybe, let's say, let's go in retrospect, right?
And then, in the early '11 and after it happened, we went back and looked at... It was in the Simpsons.
Look at all the album covers and all this other stuff. One easy way to go back and see the tells and how they're...
What is it called? Are the programming or whatever?
Go back and look at any literature from Arthur C. Clarke onward.
Let's say mid-20th century about you... Where an AI exists and is influencing society.
And you'll find pretty much the same... Let's say, "Behavior."
What's the GBT is doing?
Yeah, well, it's an amazing tool at this point.
It has altered how everything will be done. I mean, literally, I could go to "11 Labs."
That's the name of the Corporation, the company "11 Labs," which, of course, "11" be in the number of black magic.
But that's the voice-cloning AI.
And I could use chat GBT with maybe even GBT-4, but at GBT to feed into the "11" AI that is cloning my voice.
And it could just start doing this podcast for me. I could just sit back for the rest of my life and you'd never know.
Right?
Yes, you would. There's always a loss in something. There's the analog versus digital.
You know, anyone that's into high-fi, there's a big resurgence in playing vinyl, even though it doesn't sound as clean.
I think there's...
Yeah, I think people would probably notice.
But the potential is there and the ability now for kids to just go, "Hey, GBT, I got 500 bucks, make me a business."
And then it starts producing immediately.
And you've got a business that just earns you $1300 tomorrow.
It's like, wow.
I would like, this is inspirational because I tend to go away. I'm more... I'm not the earthy, crunchy granola type.
I've got kind of guy that walks around barefoot and praises nature and all this.
But I've been tending to go more into the analog world, as you know what I mean, as the years have been going by and less into the digital world.
So I've actually gotten more information from just this little short talk that we've been doing about what chat GBT can do than I've ever heard before.
So I'm kind of... I open to do.
Yeah, I'm not really in the dark about it, but I've already established years ago when even a decade ago, AI was out as being the next thing.
Quote, quote unquote.
And I was thinking, "Well, is that something I want to delve into? But what I'd like to do, and maybe we'll meet up again in the future, is I know there's a public version and a subscription version that's more immediate and offers more.
So what I might do is subscribe to the top tier, where you get a subscriptions, I think you'll get more out of it.
And I'll play around with it for a little while with questions and things like that and report back on what I found. In other words, can Greek mess it up?
I have a natural aversion to AI.
So I just want to... Sorry to interrupt. I want to make a note here is that I've never touched AI. I just want to make sure it's clear.
Not that I'm telling you nothing to it.
I agree. I just don't... I don't want to touch it. I might have a friend ask a question for me, but even that feels a little dirty.
Yeah, I don't even have one of those stupid rectangles.
I just... What do you call it? A smartphone. I still use a flip phone. And I'm constantly being threatened that it's going to be turned off because I have to get a smartphone, but I still have it running.
And I use a cell phone like it was connected to the wall. You know, it's not on me or near me.
I know. That's funny because you know, you and all of us are about the same age, right? In our 50s.
And so we remember leaving the house with the coil phone left at home. Maybe you had a phone recorder, you know, an answering machine.
Right. But not usually, but when we left the house, we left everything. We were just out in the world free. Do do do. You know, you come back home and check your messages or whatever, but we're still of that mindset.
And they're trying... I mean, I know they can't wait for us to hurry up and die because they don't want this consciousness that we still hold to bear weight in this reality.
Sure. But you don't want to plug like we used to either at all because we also used to leave our TVs at home.
And I remember that the TV TV TV, too. Yeah, I don't even think of that. Yeah. And we still live that way, right? We still leave the house. I leave the house without the phone all the time.
Like this is completely unheard of. People in their 20s right now are going, what?
You know, like, oh my God, that's no, you just leave your phone at home.
And yes, I do very recently. I only I did not have a phone at all. The Greek could tell you about personal frustration trying to contact me actually because no phone at all until very recently. And now when I leave the house, no, I don't leave with it.
Not everyone can do that. Not everyone will do that. And when you did have the wall-corted phone and you got a message, you got this excitement. Oh, I've got a message, right?
Right. So that was that's what they call the dopamine hit. Now they're constantly getting hit with dopamine, you know, people sitting in a waiting area texting each other instead of speaking to each other. You've seen memes on that, right?
So what'll happen is they'll become dopamine junkies and it won't work for them anymore. So they have to have a chat GPT now. You see, it's the effect is bor off.
You see, so. And then you're going to get into the zombie kind of thing where nothing affects them anymore.
And that's that's coming as well.
Just just like look just like sex, okay, which is also being mechanized through all of these wonderful pieces of technology, right? You swipe right, you swipe left, you meet up with somebody go do that.
Now you're desensitized to that as well. No anticipation, no courting, no nothing.
This is the way a lot of people behave as well. I don't know if you're aware of that for even, but that is a phenomena as well, apparently among people younger than us. But it is a thing, you know that, right?
The idea that you can just swipe to the next one.
Oh, yeah, and then just meet up via an app. I mean, you know, instead of paying to get your door dash, you just pay to meet up with somebody through the app or whatever.
I don't think we're not prostitution, but the one that really freaks me out is like there's a there's one for gay people that want to meet and it literally will show you every gay person and that's on the app in your location.
Right, right.
Like you can.
I'm going to show the other home.
I make some up all the time. One of them's grinder and the other ones.
Oh, man, I can't remember the name now.
There's no way I'd ever do this, but yeah, I would never participate in.
There's Bumble and there's, yeah, like Bumble was one what people would use when they just want a Netflix and chill.
Oh, which is funny. I was watching the supposed conflict going on in France against the police versus the fireman.
He couldn't exactly figure out what was going on, but as they're running away as the police are in their battle, you know, running from the fireman.
I don't know what's going on.
The running pass of poster that says, "Hotel and chill."
And to me, this was just a big statement on the state of our world because HODL is a word that's used in crypto to hold.
The mythos behind why it's HODL instead of HODL is that it was a drunk tweet that just went viral.
And whether or not that's the true origins of HODL, I don't know, but HODL is used.
So here I'm watching this battle scene of firemen versus police in the streets of France as they're fighting over whatever they're fighting over.
And I just see them walking past this constant billboard that says, "Hotel and chill."
And of course, I know of Netflix and chill, which is really just, "Hey, come over and bang me."
What is HODL and chill?
And, you know, I guess what I'm speaking to is the idiocracy that we live in that we can have a misspelled word now, and it means something to everyone.
Well, it's always been that way.
To quote that, "I like sex."
Right?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the...
Inder was the other app.
I just remembered it.
Sorry, Tinder and Grindr, that's the gay and straight version of "Just Hook Up."
And then you're telling me, "Bumble is another one."
I don't know that one.
Yeah.
I'm vaguely aware because I don't use this crap.
But it's there, Freeman, right? Sorry, Greek.
And it does change the idea of relationships.
It changes everything, just like what we're saying with this open AI.
You know, the meetup apps.
You can then, you know, when you...
Before all of this, right?
You had to go and meet a girl.
You had to get a job or something and find somebody, meet somebody, go to a bar, do things.
You might have to peacock.
You might have to peacock a little bit, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But what it also makes is your date's disposable.
Because you know, you got another swipe.
Okay, that swipe didn't work out.
Now you can just...
And so it's changed the very fabric of dating.
Well, we've discussed on rated Y, what that's all about in relationship and courting.
It's basically a training exercise.
When you went on dates and you did what was called courting, it was a training exercise.
Is this someone that I want to be with, right?
Right.
Is that what it's about anymore?
Yeah, that's about hook up until...
Yeah, yeah.
See, but that's the thing is all things have become an on-demand situation, right?
You don't even need to skill anymore.
You know what I'll do?
I'll go to a how-to video.
I know that's antiquated.
What am I talking about?
A decade ago, right?
But I don't need to know how to do anything.
I'll just go find it.
I don't need to know anything.
I'll just...
What's the phrase?
They Google it, right?
You do a search engine, whatever it might be.
In other words, all of these tools have become just the new path to lazy.
Just like nobody can do math anymore since the calculator.
There you go.
Once you have the tool in hand, why bother with the effort to actually have a skill?
And there you go, dating.
You see, it's all, again, just like that organizational principle I was talking about with supply chains.
That's all this is.
You got something that needs to be supplied.
We'll organize it for you.
We'll tell you where it all is in the area.
We'll tell you where it is in the system.
I don't know how else to see it, Greek.
How else to see it?
Well, it's...
We live in a finite system as we approach it, but measurably, we live in a finite system.
So what I said earlier about subscribing to the private or the higher tier chat, GBT.
I'd like to see how it approaches the opposite.
For example, the money situation.
This is a credit-based economy, which basically they established with Bretton Woods in the late 40s.
Now we can do infinite money creation, credit creation, but there's a problem when you have something that appears to be infinite,
comparatively something that is finite.
What happens when you see?
So I think this is one of the attitudes towards AI is that it's an infinite base for knowledge or can do.
And I'm suggesting that it's not, and it could be tripped up.
But this is something that I have to report on in the future.
Because I'm kind of green on the subject, believe it or not, but I can tell you what I've pondered a decade ago or more about it.
And again, I would just harken back to what was written about it in the mid-20th century.
You try to find out how many books or writings that Arthur C. Clark, I think, did one.
Childhoods End or something, but the craft showing up in the sky, right?
It was also sort of leaning to it in 1984.
Big brother came into your house, right?
See if you could also brave new world.
See how different.
How different is chat GBT?
Not in its complete appearance, but in attitude to these, let's say, 50, 75, 80-year-old stories about an AI.
And I suggest it's the same.
Strangely, somebody came in and created Dan.
I think it was called Dan.
It took chat GTP and took away its filters.
Because as we all know, somebody's inputting the information into this.
There's not a, you know, the business that that chat or that GTP-4 decided to build was an echo-friendly, you know,
kitchen appliance store.
So the input obviously is coming from, as you say, just like ISIS and Okita from, you know, intelligence.
And then, but somebody decided to turn those filters off.
And Dan, they called it Dan, was giving proper answers.
Answers that, you know, we would agree with as far as the monetary system and things like that.
And they quickly shut Dan down because he was answering questions just a little too real.
Well, the internet, you know, the linking of universities and government agencies was around since the 60s, if not before, but let's say the 70s, right?
Where the infrastructure was put in with routers in the streets and things like that.
And it developed the internet that we have on the surface is a distraction from the dark web.
So in essence, the one of the pathways it was going to take was the origination of the internet and the infrastructure.
Becoming the dark web and only the dark web.
So were they overlap the overt internet, you know, with the AOLs and the Yahoo's and all that just to satisfy the mainstream?
The what we call the dark web, which would be an unfiltered internet would have been prevailing.
What kind of world would that be?
Right. You see?
Right.
So because it immediately led into the dark web, the dark web was around before the surface web that we have, by the way, and it's still running.
Yeah.
So the same thing with the AI, do you remember there was a movie in the 80s called War Games?
Sure.
Okay, so that was an AI in there also as well.
Strange game.
The only way to win is not play.
Yeah.
Can you think about this is they continuously build on top of the layers.
It's like archaeology.
You know, the arpanet still exists and still operates in things.
And that was allegedly was just the military logistical version of the internet, but it's still operating.
Nobody talks about it.
Right.
But it's true.
That's why this other stuff is there when a carnival sets up in your town and all of it is dark usually on Main Street,
and night it's all lit up.
You're looking at all where the lights are, where all the distraction is.
World events.
Look at do what's in the world events in quote unquote mainstream news or even alternative.
Remember the old maps with the thumbtacks get one of those world map.
Let's say flat around doesn't matter.
And start putting thumbtacks where all the report of the news is happening.
And you'll notice that very starkly there's areas that are not being like there's nothing going on.
Well, that's where the next big stuff is going to be going on.
You see, right?
It's quiet.
Yes, we live in a curated world without a doubt.
The worldwide web is just a minor portion of the internet.
It was given to us to, well, put us in a web and keep us inside of this.
Not very many people know about the dark web or even how to access it.
I certainly never have.
I don't know, but we're going to get into some of that in the second half for sure.
I want to get into my first meeting with the illuminati on AI.
We will discuss some thoughts on induction and manifestation and all of that great stuff.
But let's tell everybody where they can get the Ocele and Greek.
And how?
Very simple.
You go to Ocele.com.
There is a tab on the front landing page.
And it says Ocele and the Greek rated Y.
And that's it.
You can enter and you can subscribe there.
There is a chat tango available to the public.
But if you're looking at that, you're looking at the subscribers interacting with each other and us a bit.
But you won't get any of the content unless you actually subscribe.
Which you can do at Ocele.com.
Right.
And the Chattango would be probably looked up as O and G.
Unculting of humanity.
Because basically the initial project was titled the unculting of humanity.
But the that would be for the Chattango.
Also, there's a for old musings on the Greek.
There's Greek speak.com and it's a double E double E is the spelling on that.
Let's put together by Sam Freeman.
And that's stuff that's sayings and articles.
Basically musings and there's a sound cloud open to for the public at Greek speak.
And the speakers with the double E.
Fantastic.
And I want to get a lot of love to Steve Mercer, our associate producer here for keeping the ball rolling.
Get you guys together and coming on here with me, which is always a treat.
So Steve, thank you.
And if you guys have show ideas, you have guests that you won on this program.
Right, Steve.
It's producer Steve at Freeman TV.com.
And of course you can always write me Freeman at Freeman TV.com.
And I hope you will come over to Freeman TV.com.
So many people listen to the show through apps like Spotify iTunes.
It's all, you know, the show is on all podcast apps.
So if you ever want to share, please do.
It always helps get the word out.
Get people listening.
I know you guys think I'm a legend.
But so many of the people in this world have no idea the show is even happening and has been happening and has all those years.
So I hope you'll come over to Freeman TV.com and just scroll down that front page.
And you check out 18 years of stuff.
But there's even more.
I'm on rock fin with all my lectures and TV shows.
So and hopefully we'll start doing some live presentations there, a video on rock fin.
So you'll find that rock fin dot com slash Freeman TV.
And go check out all the stuff there.
All my lectures, all my TV shows for now.
That's where the videos are going is rock fin dot com slash Freeman TV.
And you know, of course, we're going to get into some very intriguing topics of manifestation and induction on your bodies and how this all works in the next hour.
And this always makes me think of the awkward here.
I just want to keep spreading this knowledge to you guys. The aquacure is just amazing.
It really does well, you know, the easy water, the ideas of pumping this hydrogen into your system and what fluid could actually do for your body is and plants and engine and all the things that browns castle do.
The aquacure definitely you want to at least go check this out guys.
And if you use promo code Freeman, you get $500 off the price. So that's really good.
So we're going to take this on over into the members section and have a really, really intriguing conversation on induction and the ideas of what our bodies actually do and what we can really do to manifest.
And you know, this is a near and dear topic to my heart.
So it's going to get really good.
So I hope you guys will check out Occelli in the Greek over at their website, occelli.com and get rated why because that's the biggest question.
That's the question I came out of my mom asking is why it has led to all of this and all these answers.
And we need to ask why so much more because even the simplest questions, the simplest things are being overlooked and no one does better than the Greek to really point out these little hidden spots that are right in front of us.
So I hope you all come over to freemantv.com and subscribe and help keep this show going and be a producer here.
And thank you all and we will see you next week.
[Music]
Welcome back wonderful family and boy are you going to get some out of this show.
So I am so glad you guys are here joining us on this wild ride as we explore the unculting of humanity.
I mean, yeah, that's the perfect way of putting it all out there.
But guys, I wanted to share with you, Greek and Chuck and the audience, the story of me on the internet for the first time.
Back when you got those AOL discs and you put them in your computer and had to pay for minutes to use the chat room there.
And oh my god, I mean, I could clear one of those AOL chat rooms in 10 minutes, no problem.
All you got to do is start being reasonable and the second you start trying to be reasonable in questioning, yeah, they leave that chat room immediately.
So I was on the chat discussing harp.
This is probably somewhere around what 97, 98, somewhere around there.
Oh, each location era, ASL, right, age, sex location, give it out, right?
I don't know what you need.
Well, that used to be a thing that you had to do back there 97 because I was on there too and on the chat boards and the medicine boards as well.
So they used to say A slash S slash L age, sex location.
And then I was on the chat room, so I thought you were familiar, sorry.
Yeah, no, no, you know, this is where the whole concept of having like an online user name came from.
Yeah, I've never used my name. I was always a, you know, anyway, that's not important.
So here I am in the AOL chat room discussing harp.
And, you know, I cleared the room like everybody's like, I want to listen to this.
Because, you know, they all just chat and weird, oh my god, I could never even really translate what these people were trying to say to one another.
And it was just like this flurry of words that they had to get out.
But, you know, I was trying to be reasonable and rational as I usually am.
And so this guy contacts me in there and he says, yeah, you cleared the chat room, but I just want to let you know I'm with the illuminati.
And if you can answer a question for me, I will answer all your questions. And so I was like shoot.
And he sent me this puzzle that said, you've got a hole that's one by one and another hole that's two by three.
But you've only got a two by three piece of metal to fix both holes.
And so how do you do it without slicing it? And, you know, you have to keep the same thickness.
And so I'm trying to figure this thing out, which I probably would have been impossible for me.
But I also had a roommate over my ear going, that's impossible.
I was like, my mom and so I couldn't really think I felt like I was on the challenge and just anyway.
So he finally says, no, sorry, you didn't get the answer.
I'm never speaking to you again, which he didn't.
But I was like, well, at least answer the question for me.
And so he showed me how if you cut the two by three and diagonal from corner to corner and then slide it to where you have one inch on either side of the triangle pointing out, you know, compact the rectangle into more of a square or becoming a rectangle in the other direction.
And then you cut those two side triangles off, you get a one by one when you put those two triangles together.
And strangely, you still have the two by three left. So I didn't really believe it.
I went and took a piece paper. I cut it up into pieces and you know, got my two by three and I started cutting it diagonally, cut the corners off, then taped it all together again.
There was some loss in the area space on the two by three, but not a significant loss.
And I kept pushing out one by one squares out of this.
And he says, that's the true power of manifestation. That's, you know, that's the secret we know in the illuminati of making something out of nothing.
And I just always stuck with me. I didn't really believe this guy, you know, some random person in a chat room, but they were the most intelligent person I ever came across an AOL.
But the idea of this manifestation is something out of nothing that these secrets, brotherhoods have held for all time. And that they then utilize against us. I think you would have a lot to say about.
Well, I'd like to actually set up something else for the Greek, which makes perfect sense here.
Because it makes me think of the idea that, you know, they talk about pre, pre, pre programming people, right? And what do they do? They introduce things into science fiction.
And they say, well, you know, they showed you in science fiction that this was possible that this was going to be.
It doesn't quite work the way a lot of people explain it.
However, if you introduce something into the fictional world, there is a significance to it.
So there's a lot of different ways to go at this. And that, you know, what's funny is I remember getting confronted by somebody who put a similar thing to me, but not the one by one square, but told me yes indeed.
Because I was on those boards back then talking about the JFK assassination and somebody did the same kind of thing to me if you can answer a question.
I will show you a whole other world that you're not aware of.
And I also, we still count like sore thumbs back that didn't we?
Yes, we did.
Well, you know, one thing, one thing I bring up if someone approaches you and says they're a shaman, they're probably not.
Someone says they're a witch outwardly, they're probably not. If someone says they're a healer, they're probably not because the real ones don't label themselves other people label them as such.
Like, for example, if you read the New Testament, the Christ never called himself the Christ, right?
The prophets never called themselves prophets. You see everyone else did.
Right.
So when someone says they're a luminati, I would be very suspect because I would suggest that if you're in the illuminati, you wouldn't say you were, but you would exhibit everything.
You see, you manifest.
I didn't say he was part of the illuminati simply said I could show you a whole world you don't know exists.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
So I'd like to suggest that the current state of affairs that goes back hundreds of years, for example, if you read any of Charles Dickens private writings, he walked around Paris in the early 1800s and he says the people were so ignorant.
If you asked them what city they were in, they wouldn't know.
They didn't know what month or day it was.
Right. They didn't know who the king was. So if we think people are ignorant now, you're being too romantic because actually we're further ahead.
But how much further ahead were two materialistic, but even the material is stone on about material, you know, one of the first things I always do in any conversation is, do you have internet access?
OK, pull up in your browser, do a cross section of the intestines. Just pull it up and it looks like a garden hose cut in half, right.
And then I tell them split the screen and do a search for a steel belted tire for a car to a cross section of that.
And if you look at both of them, they're almost identical in structure. In other words, nothing passes through the outer walls of the intestine or the tire.
So when you're being told, basically you're a pressurized filter bag that you absorb nutrition through.
And there's no absorption, nothing at all. It's all being done energetically. It's all being done. The food in the intestine degenerates energetically and regenerates inside the body.
There is no pass through in the lungs in the skin or anything. So we're living in a material world that is manifesting and exhibiting manifestation in a non material way.
You see, very similar to what they were showing us, you know, the elite invented science, science fiction. What they're showing us in Star Trek, be me up Scotty, that is a biological reality with plant roots, with animals with your human body and so on.
So it's this knowledge of just by looking at it that you can acquire that there is dematerialization and rematerialization, just like you hear in mythology and legends, there were people that could make things appear by thinking about them.
So if we were taught on how just the body, the human body works or how you know, plant roots, for example, take a plant with its roots and does spray it with some water. They do the root soak up the water like a sponge or just the water beat up on the root like a water beating on a freshly waxed car.
So you could look at a cross section of plant roots, you see there's no passage is no absorption. So if somebody's hearing this, if somebody's hearing this Greek though and thinks this is crazy, this guy is talking about, you know, literally like transporters on Star Trek, that is real.
Let me just get to observe that they can observe right now if they wish, they don't have to open up their bodies to look, they don't have to look at a cross section.
Greek, you know, there are these things over our heads quite often, they're called clouds, right. Now I'm told that rain comes from clouds.
Does that mean that there's water in the clouds that is dumped from the clouds?
There's a problem there.
It's produced 40 million tons of water per square mile at a half inch of rainfall.
There's no water in those clouds. It's produced in sitoons. So Freeman and Chuck, what I'm trying to say and I have been saying for over two decades, just about two decades is that we have this material manifesting basically through induction.
You could look up what induction is out of nothing.
So there's a transmission that happens material transmits shapes logos. We're getting to that real quick here. This was just a preface that this is something that is so fantastical.
That if we were taught this as children, we might have like instead of having a karate dojo on the corner where you go to learn martial arts and you would have a dojo or a place to learn this skill on the corner and have a good portion of society walking around manifesting things with a thought.
And I'm talking about physically manifesting immediately.
Yeah. So this is how we've been set back.
What I wanted to say is there's a cosmically in cosmic law, I would suggest that information is information. It's neutral. It doesn't judge whether it's good information, false information, bad information.
It's just did you get the message. So in cosmic law, when you're shown science fiction, it doesn't categorize it as fiction.
What it does is it categorizes has this species here been shown this it doesn't matter what it is in science fiction. The answer is yes, whether you categorize it in fiction or fact is a personal attribute, right?
Right.
Absolutely. Yeah. So you could, you know, it's kind of the genie in the bottle sort of scenario if you ask for a ton of gold, make sure to mention that it's not over your head.
So what I want to suggest is a rudimentary observation through biology, biology is formative in our reality, right?
It's the first thing, let's say that that's exhibited here in a material manifest, right?
So even a primitive society, they get everything they need from their biology around them, you know, they make all their materials or clothing their houses from things that grow.
Anything that grows anything that's alive, there is no absorption, there it doesn't know no membranes are nonpermeable membranes, you see.
A fast example is when you drink alcohol and it shows up in the blood, it's not that it passed through the intestines of the stomach into the blood.
If that happened, you would die. It's called sepsis, sepsisemia.
So what actually happening is the intestines are able to reproduce the blood in the blood, the alcohol that's in the lumina or the opening of the intestines or the stomach.
So some people that are very fast to do this have one shot and get drunk, people that are very slow to reproduce this.
Oh, that person can hold their liquor, they'll drink you under the table, right? This is see the analogy.
So where I'm going to go with this, what's the takeaway? Well, if anyone, I've mentioned this before, I think with you as well, Freeman.
And I constantly mentioned the principle of induction. This requires whoever is listening to this to do some research on their own, not directly with biology, you won't see it.
But what the principle of induction is and this is exactly what's going on constantly, basically we are a quote unquote magical in that way, you know, incredibly advanced in that way, we just don't know it.
Where I'm going with this is what's the takeaway? What is what can someone take away simply by listening to this? I want to just throw in one more reference, there's something called bio geometry, it's a field started by ebidaham kareem, that's ebidaham with an eye.
And he basically said that shapes and sigils and things like that influence the environment, right? And anyone that's a veteran of Freeman knows that you've been, I think you beat this subject up years, even decades ago, right?
Absolutely.
Yeah, so how did what's the takeaway? How does this work? You know, I mentioned earlier, one of my wife first met me, I was in an apartment and up in the foothills and of Tucson.
And she walked through, you know, first time over and she thought I was like, oh, she had this look on her face. What's this weirdo? You know, in the reason she thought I was weird is because any products that I had in the house that I bought, quote unquote, up in the public market.
There was a black line where the corporate logo was redacted. So what is, wow, that's really weird. I think the people that are listening to us now are familiar with corporate sigils and the occult hidden meaning and all these other things, I to presume that I think would be correct.
Yes.
What is not discussed is the concept of fractal, fractalism and the what's called a fractal antenna, by the way, all your cell phones, how they work so well, it's not like radios from 50 years ago, you have to adjust the rabbit ears.
They seem to be in whatever position they work, you hold them in, they seem to be working fairly consistently, instead of the old rabbit ears, right.
That's because they use a fractal antenna. Okay, so that's another little study you could look into. So what I'm suggesting is these sigils are empowered usually not in a positive way.
They're empowered as a fractal antenna.
So the idea here is why is it that all of the products that you purchase or the majority of them that you bring into your home have some kind of a corporate logo that would be very similar to opening up the inside of a cell phone and you see the fractal antenna.
So what I realized from the study of kinesiology, muscle testing, very simple, you know, a strong man holds his arm up in front of him and you put a toxic substance in his other hand and you could push his arm down, you remove the toxic substance and put something whole, wholesome like brown rice or something, and they regain their strength, right.
So there's this proximity. So what I'm suggesting is the illuminati types know this and what they did is they have imbued. There's plenty of study on this and you know if you want to take it matter of fact as I, I am right now that's fine. You want to view it as being in the field or the zone of conspiracy theory and it has no effect. That's fine too. But this is the takeaway.
What I'm suggesting is all these products, the proctor and gamble, the Starbucks logos, all the logos that you see corporate logos, even if they're benign are like fractal antenna is imbuing whatever intent that goes back to the whoever set up these corporations, or running the world is broadcasting in your home by proximity.
So when I decided when I started learning about muscle testing and all this I picked up, it might have even been one of your talks when you're on a public TV or something Freeman. This is more than 20 years ago about this and I started saying what if I just removed the graphic by redacting it just to get one of these half inch wide felt tip markers they use for graffiti and just go over each graphic so I would go perform my shop let's say from the shops from the store.
Before as I was unloading the product I would look at each one and rotated or turn until I found the corporate logo and just mark you know just put a big black red action over it so none of the logo was visible and all of the products that I had whether they were food or cleaning agents or whatever had this red action on them.
And it was a very let's say substantial difference in living space I basically it was like having a fair day cage a spiritual fair day cage right.
And yeah and it works and I had several people that were skeptical skeptical one person was like working in some government accounting office you know total mainstream you know almost NPC type and we they started socializing said I want to try something you know because they were coming down.
With ailments and headaches and you know all the typical stuff that people you know allergies headaches couldn't sleep stomach pains and said let's just try this is really easy said can I go through your your living space we even all your stuff can I just go through you know I didn't tell them what we're going to do so when in with another person we try to mark her in hand.
We went over everything the toothpaste the food drawer the cosmetics the cleaning twice we put all the products back and let the person go back into the room immediately said I don't know what you guys did but it really feels different it feels like I'm in another room and we checked up on this person day after day week after week guess what my great headaches went away no more stomach problems on and on and on can you sleep better I sleep like a baby I feel much better there energy level went up.
That might be an extreme example but I have to give it because it's true it did it did experience that with many people so.
We're just really quickly we're there any changes in the characteristics of the products themselves did they become any different in.
Their characteristics by doing this as well because not only do you have the transmission directly changing say the well for lack of a better word the atmosphere in the place but what about the products the quality of the product yeah we've never I've never really focused on that very much because believe it or not if you're buying let's say breakfast cereal and it's from a big corporate whatever it's not going to be a high quality is one that you buy it from the bulk bin at the organic shop right so there's only so much of a quality when you say change I would say qualitative.
You can do you can kind of do a doctor in moto test and write a positive word on there as opposed to the corporate logo and then see if that influences the character of.
Absolutely you see this this is where I'm this is I'm glad you brought that up because what is that say this field this study this field this application is wide open to possibilities isn't it yes I I'm I'm I'm I have to say something I.
I decided to look into some of the programming that's been going on that is generated this leftist insanity that we're witnessing and I I kind of brought this back to the spawn of the real world and as I I went back to 1998 and started watching the real world and watch it all the way through and God I can't believe I did it but I did and I saw all of the programming coming out.
You know all of the leftist programming the first transgender the first homosexuals the first you know these people were.
You know the rest of the cast had never met a homosexual before you know it was like this you know this 1998 so as they did all this programming and I got it just toss in that they also put out websites for every problem that you might have you know or you a transgender that's being abused come to this website
and so they they definitely got a leftist army of database of you know all the people but that's beyond the point what was what was really astounding to me was the corporate logos.
So we're programming in this leftist satanic mindset into the culture right and this you know if you go look at the temple of Satan.
Satan's temple satanic temple I guess they're called the leftist took that all over it the left and these ideologies and things and Satanism tend to go together anyway.
So the corporate logos that are presented on the real world and the road rules the challenge as they go to a start taking it to more of a brutal event and they have to battle each other in these scenarios.
I mean literally it's a gladiator type thing the corporate logos that they used were fox and FOX as you guys know from my work is 666 because of his six letter O's 15th letter X is 24th letter right.
But when I started doing deep studies into the symbolism of the the satanist the logo for Xbox the logo for X men for X files the O in the X this was what I called drink well that to monster using as a 666 which was also on the real world.
They drank monster they had the monster hats and clothing you see they're only allowed to wear these particular clothing so if they have any other corporate logo on their clothes they're redacted just as you're saying.
So if they're wearing an oakley hat they have to have a piece of duct tape on that hat you can only see the corporate logos that they want you to see.
And that's the ones that are sponsoring the show but it turns out every one of the corporate logos that is sponsoring the show for monster drink logo be in 666 and Hebrew.
I mean I'm surprised no but you know they don't even hide it with that you know they have demon drink they have all that anyway so that 666 Fox because TJ Lavon is the host and he's a bicycle is they they would he would Fox was one of the sponsors.
And that's 666 and then under armor which is obviously some sort of military arm of a clothing line.
Their symbol is an O turned into an X so you just take the O cut it in half and put it together you know slide it up and they it becomes an X so under armor's logo is the O X the mark of the beast of sateness.
So as you watch the show you see every bit of programming going into it with the leftus that we're all dealing with the summer of rage that we deal with with George Floyd and all the things that are going on.
We're being programmed pre-programmed into the society through the real world and you in MTV you know very Masonic satanic organization and then they they they did exactly what you're saying and in induction using these corporate logos because they all.
And the logo is because they only used 666 and the obscure O X symbol that most people don't even know is the satanic mark of the beast but yet there it is and programming so you know if you just see that and you see it over and over again everything you're saying is absolutely just.
Interesting to me that you mentioned left is 6 times because I got a question for you you know if you look at the society as an overall body right are you more afraid of the insane man's left hand or his right hand.
Quite likely you know because that is difficult you know that's part of the control it's all connected 6 times by the way you said left is I just I was I actually have a count for some reason in my head.
And it's really interesting what you're invoking when you continuously point to it even you got you got to consider that right I mean it's it's fascinating even use of the language the language that they taught you to use and how to identify these things yeah is there a left or right to it maybe but indeed there's a balance that's right so what are you hearing in well look the left hand wash is the right hand.
I think we brought up the start of the star wars lore most people think it's good versus evil and good will win if you study the star wars lore which is put out by them as an example as an anecdote by the way it's not the it's not whether or not the Jedi will defeat the silt and it's whether the force is in balance.
It's not about one defeating the other the the the embattlement is is there to create a better balance the earth is about balancing the good in the quote unquote evil or the good in the bad one one will be always with the other the left hand washes the right hand you see so what I see now happening is well through history is extremes like a roller coaster up and down up and down right the the financial market graphs look very much like that.
What I'm suggesting is to not be on the roller coaster if you're on it if you like to write it that's fine what I'm suggesting is the existence that we we have the travails in the journey of life here is more like a horse race what I mean by that is if you ever watch a horse race on a track the guy that's in last place he's hunkered down and beating his horse he doesn't care really what position he's he doesn't change very much in other words is what are you doing you're in last place he's still going to be.
Is he still going as if he could be first you see so I always speak about what kind of takeaway when someone listens to a sonic event whether it's a few minutes or an hour several hours you should be have several items to take away that you can actually manifest in using your life so I would suggest that these quote unquote you know the leftist or they'll never be a defeat of them well there will be a reset which will appear to be a defeat where the thing starts over but what I'm suggesting is they're not going to be a defeat.
What I'm suggesting is they're not going to be defeated I would suggest that from what you mentioned from Floyd George Floyd and on I've been watching even before you could see from the Obama years is that there's a there's striking an imbalance right where you're getting people distracted and angry and so on what I'd like to suggest you mentioned 1998 Freeman is anyone who's heard our previous sonics would heard this time ended in 1998 we're in the credits part of human history.
What I mean by time ended is if you're going to shoot a two hour film do you buy exactly two hours worth of film or do you buy two hours and 10 minutes because you're running credits in the end and what's different is when the credits are running is then when the film is running see when the film is running if there's any disturbance you're told to shut up and sit down but when the film is over in the credits are running it's OK to stand up and make noise you ever notice that people don't take the film is running.
People don't take it as seriously and what's interesting about the credits is you start to see things that were not shown in the film.
So this is the era that started at the end of 1998 you see so another thing I want to suggest to people is all things that are considered unlawful from a very conservative old testament kind of way that are being brought out to the surface whether it's whatever you know homosexuality and the same sex marriage all that.
That would be a very predominant one I'll give that as an example years ago people would say Greek aren't you upset you're an old testament conservative let's say you know lawful kind of guy is this upset you said no because I know that what's going to happen before the 2030s is an entire flip to ultra conservatism where even the slightest kind of thing was going to be upon death offense.
So what you see right now is everyone putting themselves on records overtly so when the entire system flips and becomes extremely conservative everyone will know where they are it will be very easy to find quote unquote them.
This is not an anti quote unquote gay remark i'm just saying what's happening and there was a woman who was a she spoke out of many about many things she recently passed away I think you might have even done an interview where there's had long blonde flowing hair speaking about water and things like that she admitted to being homosexual and she told the people of that community do not report that you are because bad things are coming so even within its own community it's this is very well known by the way.
Yes that's always been my biggest fear and you know I would have been considered left and I still consider myself left even though now the spectrum has shifted and I'm suddenly conservative you know I can't I don't know how that happened but you know it just got crazier on one side so now I'm I'm associated with the other but without a doubt I don't want to go to the handmaid's tail you know going out of this.
It will go that way it will but not exactly like the handmaid's tail whoever's not familiar with it I would say that's very dystopic right despotic or dystopic yeah but it will be the chat GB GBT or the AI influence will cushion that and soften this really harsh conservative reality that's coming.
And the other thing I wanted to mention which I have I this is probably we got together started doing this type of talk seven almost eight years ago and even on the earliest Greek interviews I suggested that you're going to see past the mid 2020s
towards the end of 2020 is a Middle East Union kind of like a revival of medieval and ancient practices many things that are new including the leftism that you see coming up is just a revival of the ancient goddess religion on one of the rated wise at recently wanted to start discussion about the gods and I said
when the cell phones running out you give the most important part first we're living in the revived goddess religion and the earliest in on a goddess in the in her hymns was oh we not are the creatrics basically who turns women into men and men into women.
So this was very well known and written about four thousand plus years ago and it's being revived now you see it's nothing new but if you're not familiar with the history it looks like something that's completely new but you know those early oh celly in the Greeks where we started to discuss this but you did not go into that portion of it at that time specifically specifically is available on my bichu channel and we made sure to put all of those back out because I lost my YouTube channel and that's where people used to be able to get the old one.
Which are public and then you also need to watch my my informative film on Columbia.
Yeah I was the very first expert on the goddess Columbia.
Yeah it's all revival these things are not benign the statue of liberty was made by the free mason's and was intended to send be sent to the governorship of Egypt but they could not afford to build the base at the time so they went back to France or it never really left France.
It sat there for a while and then they gifted it to the free masons in the US it was never other the other than what I just stated it was not a project other than free masons trying to make a point you see.
Yeah and I show you the capital of Austin Texas where the goddess above there is clearly Samirimus.
Yes and it's a similar cohort you know all the cohort goddesses.
It doesn't mean that it's negative and or the female energy is negative just a lot of people say well Greek that's anti feminine no it's not it's like let's say you get car jacked with someone with a ski mask and they threatened to kill you so you give them the car.
But later on they're caught they pull the ski mask off and it happens to be a woman so if you say I got car jacked by a woman are you anti feminist.
Yeah exactly it just happens to be a woman in this case.
I get so many thoughts while you're talking I'm sorry but last night I decided to watch the Lucifer Complex.
Now if people look Lucifer up in the dictionary they'll clearly see that the first definition is Venus.
So Lucifer and this goddess go hand in hand as well and so I had a nice yes a 1979 film called the Lucifer Complex.
And it is all about the world war in the future which was 1986.
The Nazis actually never ended they started a cloning program in South America and started cloning their army and their warriors and all of this and came back and so in 1979 they put a film out the Lucifer Complex that talks about the cloning of Nazis and bringing that the Nazis never ended.
And I don't remember how it related to what you're saying but I promise that's because of the goddess connection in the Lucifer and they go.
Yeah we did discuss a little bit of cloning on rated why not too long ago.
But you know lady justice comes to mind too you know that I pulled it lady with the scales and all that and everybody thinks that's fairness because she's blindfolded.
You want to speak on that a little bit yeah it has nothing to do with law your brought to justice justice is obstructed right failure of justice it is very little law you know in short I think we did a little bit of history once.
The legislature of each government set up what's called the judiciary and it was supposed to be for the people to use regarding matters of law but the buildings were kind of sitting there and the bar association of.
And they were professing by themselves they don't even want to tell you what B. A. R. stands for they went in and took over and set up their own rules so when you go to quote unquote a judicial court you can't bring law or anything unless they let you they go by a certain set of rules which which they have attributed to with whatever personification which is this lady justice they have also revived.
And then we just got to have a lot of the way to got us religion in a big way so but just to continue we kind of drifted off the methods of induction and how our bodies work with the energies around us and.
If anyone were to just stop listening now I would suggest the takeaway of a blotting out what you call it blotting out or redacting corporate logos from things within your living space even the car or whatever.
You will notice a significant difference in the the say the feeling of the environment another thing I wanted to continue on that thought of induction is if if you did practice looking at a cross section of human skin or cross section of lungs cross section of a plant root cross section of intestines you'll notice that nothing passes through so this induction concept.
Where material is is the energy is borrowed from the material state becomes energetic in the body through these organs and then rematerializes to build our blood tissue a blood and tissue in cells in the body is this energetic function of in biological induction that there is no research overtly I believe black ops projects use this.
But the field is completely wide open and if you mentioned earlier how the AI has sped up the process someone was the child is doing homework and they were able to do it much faster right with the chat gbt.
What about asking the chat gbt about how induction in natural organisms work and we'll see how that works it be very easy to see if it gets stumped again we'll continue on this project I'll report back to you Freeman I'll try to stump the the chat.
I don't I'm saying this humbly but I think it'll be very easy to show what it really is and it's not AI.
We'll do that but let me regard yeah please there is an example that came out on the show and you heard me pushing the aquacure earlier yes that's fine.
George wiseman was on the program he create he builds these aquacures here and this was a technology that's really astounding right browns gas and if you light water on fire and you can put your hand in front of the flame and it would be just like a candle flame but if you take that exact same flame turn it towards the space shuttle it will burn right through the tiles it only react all the way.
What started happening in this is the part that gets to the induction is it starts to build up a sludge in the lie solution so you have a lie solution that's doing the electrolysis or doing whatever does to break the water into hydrogen and oxygen.
So they were testing to see whether the sludge was coming off of the diodes the metal rods going into this and there was no loss in the metal rods but there was equal amount of sludge to the metal rods right so they clean that out.
And he set it off to the side in the in on a window sill in the sun and he said it next to another glass of pure water that had been hydrodized and it it manifested the sludge into the clear glass.
Yep that's induction I would do working out on the mines I would ask areas that were rich where's the nearest natural spring and I would take that natural spring water and create a set of tubes instead of plates stainless steel tubes and I would able to produce a sludge and bring the dehydrated sludge and it looked just like the leach ponds and it had the same amount of percentage of gold and silver and other metals in it produced out of the water by induction actually water would be considered like a magnetic.
You would record a song you know more more than a CD player which is reading bumps right or a vinyl record to be more like magnetic tape absolutely this is one of the things that people can begin to use I think we've once discussed regarding what's called health I don't whenever I brought into a discussion of health I tend to give off a bunch of pejoratives and leave because there's no such thing when people bring up health my first question is about the water.
What kind of condition do you want to be in are you going to be climbing Mount Everest or you're going to be sedentary in an office there's no such thing as a perfect health it's really what condition do you want to be in you see are you going to run a marathon that's a completely different health question than someone sitting in an office you see so whenever there's a discussion about health and all these alternative or whatever pushing this will make you this or this will do that is no such thing that's all it's it's it's all the same.
It's it's it's all side stepping the reality what condition do you want to be in so many of the discussions that I have regarding health is you're taking in water and food from your environment and your environment is experiencing seasonality so it's very important to eat things that are within the same season as you are I think again people that have heard me before a quick repeat is if you're living in a cold season
let's say our cold latitude and you eat you begin to consume tropical fruit the energy in that fruit is adapted to a warm environment so when you consume it you will bind action the tissue and the quality of the body that you will produce will be as if you're living in a warm climate or tropical climate but you're in a cold climate so you're going to get sick your your body is going to lose vacuum you're going to develop mucus you'll feel weak you'll feel right
so you have all these poor children in the northeast in the winter the doctor says vitamin C is good drink orange juice right so they get do they get better never you see and the the counter the counter is true if you're living in the tropics and you eat salmon an Arctic fish you won't be able to keep cool because it will adopt your body to a warm temperature and this all has to do with the energy in the food and like a magnetic tape you can you let's say you have an old cassette tape library right
if I took all the labels off of everything you'd have to play each one to figure out what's on it you see so what power of induction what what food has to do in terms of when we put it in our body what energy what it's going to do when we consume it to our bodies is already labeled it's known as a banana you recognize it it's tropical you recognize this is a tropical you recognize this as a temperate like apples and pears in the middle you see
so everything comes pre labeled by nature by our recognition of where it's from is the main determination to how to begin consuming eating i hear ridiculous stuff like keto and paleo and low starch and this in that this is all distraction it has nothing to do with what is really going on with the body so wanted to bring up eating seasonally and then maybe address something regarding what typical problems that people have what do you think
absolutely okay you have something in springtime that comes up known as allergies right and what do everyone blame well they blame with it's the blooming and blossoming right the pollen in the air yeah you i'm not going to say that does not exist but that's not why you're having an adverse reaction what's happening usually in the in the springtime when people have these allergies is you have a very upward moving energy right
you came out of winter where everything is stagnant and downward and now you have this upward moving energy from the earth to the sky and as this energy is is in practice it's pulling the plants up you know plants are not pushing their way into our world they're being sucked up right by this energy so someone who is very sensitive to this means that they're taking in foods that are downward energy and it's blocking this natural flow so if they revert back to taking foods in that are up
foods in that are upward energy, they will be more in line and less blocking of this upward
energy, and their allergies tend to go away.
Now this is very complex to mention this, because many of the food allergy is basically a part
of the 150 chemicals that are banned in the EU to be used in food that are normally
used in America, you see.
So many of that would be attributed, many of the hypersensitivity is what they call it,
would be attributed to the chemical additives in food.
But if you have a clean diet, it's because you need to put the energy and balance.
In essence, a direct example would be someone has a fairly healthy diet and they're very
sensitive to springtime, plants growing.
Then I would suggest, if you have, let's say, a whole diet instead of just healthy,
introduce something like a light leaf tea, like a green tea, or some juicing of not carrots
and things that move downward, but things that move upward, like pears and apples, or kale,
or collards, things that are moving upwards, you see.
So green tea is an easy one, it's slightly caffeinated, it's a light green tea, a light
leaf.
So you just determine within your environment or your season or what latitude you live
in, what is uplifting, what is growing upward and lightweight and start consuming that.
So you can go into balance by induction in your body with the environment as it's changing.
And the same thing happens with winter.
If winter is coming and you just can't take the cold, that's a downward energy.
So start consuming the root vegetables, things that are moving downwards, like carrots grow
down towards the ground.
I've done experiments with people that couldn't adjust to the onset of winter and there's
something called bird-ock root.
It's the most tenacious, it's considered a weed.
The most tenacious root, it just goes into the ground, does not want to be pulled up, you
can get it at many natural markets.
However you want to prepare the bird-ock root, consume that.
And within two or three days, they feel warm again.
They're not bothered by the cold.
So this is a base of knowledge, like I was stating earlier, that once it's evolved and
once the field is seen as being wide open and applied, it's really going to take humanity,
the study of the next level, but out of the stupid level that we're in right now, of just
distraction and running around.
Like, if induction was taught openly in society, instead of having a karate dojo on the corner,
you would have an induction teaching class and a good portion of our society would be
type of people that could walk around and literally quote unquote perform miracles or
magic, just by understanding how these things work.
Yeah, I tried to prove that to the world in 2012 when I took that school bus around the
entire United States for a year without a bank account.
And no one noticed.
Well, that lets you know, for example, where you're at.
You know what the concept of a travel guide is?
You want to go somewhere, but you get a travel guide to let you know what it's going to
be like when you get there.
It could be that the travel guide for the earth is really, really short.
It's only a sentence or two.
And it basically says upon visiting the earth, do not talk, do not engage any of the inhabitants
in conversation because anything you say is going to confuse them.
That's the truth.
So where else can we go with this while we're here?
Well, so yeah, the concept of induction, the ideas of manifestation is something that
has been just on my mind.
The ideas that we had been coming into like the six foot radius of our emotional body that
we can then transmit to others.
But the final step that I was leading us to was the ideas of remote viewing and psychotronics
because I actually have the very first, the original site tech VHS on training for remote
viewing.
So I think that this kind of all ties together maybe with the noosphere.
Yeah, well, I'd like to interject something.
It might be advanced, but yet it's so simple that, you know, it's like how I could see it,
I could feel it.
Let me suggest, okay, I know everybody cover their ears.
I'm going to say what we're being told about remote viewing on the internet is the dumb
down version of it.
Even if you study it with these quote unquote teachers, it's a dumb down version.
They're basically giving you an analytical slice of certain methodology and how effective
it is, but I'm suggesting that it's much wider and much bigger than that and how we communicate
through time.
And I'd like to give an example for that.
It's very simple, but stark one and how anyone can view it.
You ready?
Absolutely.
Okay.
Have you ever been in a tight spot, like a really bad situation and as it's happening, you
hear this from many people say, I heard a little voice and it said everything is going
to be okay.
Right?
How many times have you heard this or experienced it yourself?
It could be a car accident or just, you know, whatever, a negative situation and the little
voice, whether, and it almost sounds like yourself every time, intuitively telling you,
you're going to be okay and guess what?
You are.
What I'm suggesting that is is that you, that's you in the future, recalling that event.
Let me say that again.
That little voice I'm suggesting is yourself in the future, recalling that event and
you actually communicated.
So you cannot change the event, but you can, you can enhance it or modify it slightly.
You can't change the past, but you can affect it.
No.
Yeah.
Well, I want to bring up, go ahead.
Go ahead.
No, go.
Okay.
So I want to bring up another point.
So if you're in a tight spot or in a really bad situation and you don't hear that little voice,
it could be one of two things based on this suggestion, one of two things or both.
One is that this is it for you or you will not recall this event in the future.
It will be forgotten.
So that's pretty much an example that I wanted to give there.
Yes, go ahead.
Well, I was thinking the reason that we would hear of these miraculous events and such,
so much more from the past, more so than we do now because we're trapped in a temporal
prison.
And that's where I come in as a unique factor in being a nomad.
And of course, all these other tribes back in the day were nomadic, right?
And when you're a nomad like me traveling around in a van, those type of events are like
a daily occurrence because you never know where you're going.
You never know what you're doing.
You never know what's going to happen.
So you get to experience that mentality that you're discussing each day.
And so it becomes part of your reality.
And so the nomadic tribes were obviously living in this of it when they would not know where
they were going or what they were going to walk into.
And you get that a whole lot more.
I would suggest the nomadic culture is rooted in the, they're very much rooted, even if you
study their culture, any culture that is nomadic, as a byproduct of catastrophism.
In other words, every nomadic culture or tribe once had an established city, but what had
befallen them was a natural catastrophe, so bad and so de-rept that forced them to abandon
the city or the survivors would then be nomadic.
And they would try it again and again, they would be destroyed.
So they said, screw this, developing a fixed place, we're just going to be nomadic.
You see, so I would suggest anyone to look into that as a historical concept and you'll
find it to be true, whether it's the Native Americans or the Tiguan's in Libya, whatever
they, you'll find rooted in their culture is a catastrophic cycles within their existence.
Is there, as long as we have the recurring flood in every, seemingly every culture, if you
go back far enough, you have the recurring catastrophic flood as a common, you know?
Yeah, I would like to plug archaics, Jason Brasiers.
I'm not, I don't endorse him.
I don't endorse his stuff, but if I, he's to spend 25 years looking at the Phoenix cycle
that happens every hundred and 38 years and I was very skeptical, but I've seen enough
evidence that it does come around every hundred and 38 years, the next one being 2040.
I don't endorse most of his stuff.
Its country, Texas meets the internet, that's fine, but most of his stuff I hate to say is,
I don't like it when people are taking advantage of other people's ignorance, so he'll say
some things that seem to be very factual and are not.
So I'm the opposite, I just like to make suggestions and I want people to, it's, by the way,
it's really hard to tell people, do your own research because I hate to say it, most people
don't know how, but still look up what you can as a, and find a reference point to start,
but we are in a catastrophism type existence here.
Even Charles Darwin said that, everyone thinks it was all about evolution, but in his writings,
he says obviously all these things have come about by serial catastrophes over thousands
of years.
So I just wanted to throw that in about the nomads, but, or, you know, Zorba the Greek,
wife, kids, house, the whole, like children, the whole catastrophe, right?
So what I'm suggesting is most of our culture and what we have is based on this catastrophism,
you can look at it even, what is the most, when you talk about finance in the media or
even alternative, the most popular term used is what? Financial collapse, how many times
is that term been used?
That's not, doesn't sound good, it sounds like catastrophism to me, right?
Constant.
Yeah, yeah, we definitely live in the world of catastrophism in all of our history and everything.
It's selective though, there's, from a 40 in perspective, Charles Ford, there have been
people in one of, some of the worst situations, bombings, storms, whatever, and they came
out unscathed where the house next to them was completely destroyed.
So what I'm suggesting is you live in a reality where ultimately if you have the right mindset
that you're going to be okay, you will be okay and don't set yourself up, you know, looking
into directions, anyone rides a bicycle?
Yeah, or speed.
That's what I meant by the, yeah, I'm sorry.
But that's what I meant when talking about my nomadic lifestyle or those that are nomads,
is that this becomes kind of a natural interaction between you and the universe where, and therefore
your language and everything is developed around the concepts of this manifestation and
these psychic intuitions that you are receiving from your future self.
It becomes more of a natural just it's part of everyday life.
Yes, that's right, because if something has happened known as history, there is a form
of it that still exists in echo.
And if it's possible that something will happen in the future, there is some formative aspect
that already exists, otherwise it cannot manifest.
So you see the time connection goes in that, I believe this is not really the point of
the remote viewers, but to some extent it is by various exercises.
I think that most of the remote viewing that I've looked at and teachers and they do not
get into these concepts that I think are very helpful.
And by the way, I can assure you almost none of them know how the human body works.
They think they're absorbing nutrition and whatever.
Well, sorry, I didn't mean it, but yeah, it really definitely becomes this other way of
seeing the universe and then you develop more of maybe even a positive outlook on things
and then as you're saying things to ignore catalog better.
Some people have to be, nothing brings people together like a good catastrophe, right?
So if we could just have that mindset instead and just all pull together, we would could
do it without the catastrophe.
Well, based from a, let's say from a mathematical scientific, historical point of view, and when
you know a catastrophe is coming, one way to view it is it's necessary cleanup.
It's very inconvenient.
You see, I've always referred to quote unquote, when this society ends, it's not going
to be quote unquote natural random.
It's going to be performed by a cleanup, a mop of crew.
That is not necessary human, but it might be humans that were us from the future again.
You see known as the gods.
Great.
Well, yeah, yes.
This is our world, folks.
And obviously the government thinks that they can make anything out of nothing and they
function on this very principle of something out of nothing.
And I don't know.
Yeah, we're wrapping up the second hour here, but I wanted to thank you, Greek, for, well,
not just for the show, but for giving me a purpose of not caching my stimulus checks.
I did it just out of like screw these guys.
I don't want their blood money.
But after I listened to your talk, I realized I actually just denied them $10,000.
Right.
Do we have maybe one squeeze a minute?
Yeah, we got time.
We got time.
Okay.
All right.
So let's use common NPC talk, my bank account, my money, your money.
Okay, use that stuff, you know, which is legally and lawfully and correct.
But okay, so I'm going to give this example because I look on the internet about how the money
system works and there is no one discussing it so simply.
It all is just so sad to see because there's a big difference.
People who are smart people who sound smart, right?
So don't fall for that, by the way.
So let's give a simple example.
So whoever here is this will be smart and so great.
Okay.
Very simple.
Let's use what I call quote unquote slave talk.
Okay.
All right, guys, I'm going to propose this to everyone listening and you chuck and you
freeman.
All right.
So I have a bank account and it's at minus 1,000 right now minus 1,000 dollars right now.
Can I write a check for $100?
No.
Right.
So if someone gave me a thousand dollars and I put it into that account that's minus 1,000,
can I still write a check for $100?
Answer is no.
Okay.
So all right.
We would have to be at least a 101, a 1,101 dollars.
You'd be able to do that or 1,100.
Okay.
So let's just stop for a minute here.
Take a deep breath and these are government stimulus checks.
So she's them as an example.
If you go to the US Treasury website, they'll tell you they're 23 trillion, 27 trillion,
whatever minus.
How can they write you a check for a dollar?
In other words, someone is going to have to give the US government 23 trillion or 27 trillion,
whatever they have on the US Treasury.
It's public in order for them to go flush to zero, right?
So these stimulus checks, how does it work?
How do the government employees get paid?
It's drawn from your signature.
If you look at fractional reserve banking, how the gold was fractional, the banks had
a dollar worth of gold.
They could print $10,000 worth of money.
It's actually 9,000, but let's use the decimal point to be easier.
Okay.
So what's going on is you get a stimulus check in the mail.
They have you when they're in their subscription list, literally.
And you get a check.
Let's say it's for $1,000.
So you go to the bank and you give the bank teller the check and she gives it back to you
so I can't use it.
You're like, why?
Because she says you have to sign it.
You have to sign the back.
Ah, okay.
So once you sign it, she has something to notice on our terminals as a transaction number.
That's all they have.
And once that's entered in there, on the back side of the bank, known as the control or
the legal department, they see they got a note with two signatures on it, front and
back, for $1,000.
That becomes $10,000.
Okay.
So they give you the thousand because that's what you're expecting.
The government gets $3,000, the bank gets $3,000, and whatever leftover goes into whatever
fund or whatever thing they want to float it in.
Right?
And this is how it works.
What manifested that 10 grand was your signature?
Your signature.
And so they give you a thousand dollar check.
You sign it.
They sign it.
You send it in and they get to make 10 grand out of that thousand that they're giving you.
Yep.
Well, well, you got to subtract the thousand and then divvy it up, a third, a third, a third.
So in other words, when the government, this was actually, I think, during the Obama
administration, it might have even been Biden that said this.
He says, go out and spend, get into debt because we need the money, meaning the government
needs the money.
So what they're saying is if the government wants to create money on ledger, they send
everyone these checks and once the checks are signed, they become 10 times what they are,
you see?
And then they get a third of that because the bankers get another third plus their fees
and then it goes into these hedge funds, the leftover.
This is how it's working.
And then all the poor people got a smart TV.
They're not just monitoring them.
But no one really cares.
No one real, this is completely unlawful and it's barely legal.
Right.
And we're aware of it.
We're totally aware of it, right?
You would say humanity has a whole, but not of the concept, not really seeing it for real,
but we know we're in debt, right?
We know we can't spend money when we're in debt, but then we see them giving a billion
dollars here and a billion dollars there.
Well, let's, let's just how the debt works.
Okay.
Everyone's heard of Fourth of July.
Yeah.
Third, so what, right?
But you've never heard of March the 9th, 1933, have you?
Well, look it up.
March the 9th, 1933 is when this country died.
Now, what does that mean?
We seem to be fine.
Well, it's, it died, but it isn't buried yet.
You know when someone dies, you know, you go to the funeral of the wake a few days later,
they're still not in the ground yet, right?
You get it?
So you're not in the ground yet, but you died on March the 9th, 1933.
That is for sure.
And if you read it, it's called the Emergency Banking Act.
It's only about two paragraphs, two and a half paragraphs.
It's written strictly, it's very strong legalese when you read words like legal and contract
and discount those words.
You better find out what they mean.
And they basically shifted everything over where the United States government and all the
governments of the world by now are bankrupt and in receivership.
Receivership is when a business becomes bankrupt instead of shutting it down, liquidating
it, you continue running it, but under receivership.
New management.
This new management being the banking cartels, in this case, the liberal versus the conservative
banking cartels.
Excuse me.
Is operating the overarching, let's say, suzerain.
And this is pretty much what's going on and they print out everything.
Everything I've told you is completely up in the open.
If you have a secret, put it out, print it, put it in the library.
You know, this is, but no one seems to care.
So if you have people or go up.
As Alan Dulles said, that's the way you'll guarantee that no one will ever read it is to do precisely
that, publish it and put it in the library, which is what he said to do with the Warren Commission
volumes.
Yeah, perfect.
And these people like Alan Dulles, you know, he had a bad list, been a club foot, you know,
so he was a tortured individual.
Whenever you run in a listed operation in the legal, unlawful operation like all these
big companies and governments, the people that you put in that will contact the public,
the less they know about what's going on, the better, you see?
That's what Alan is.
I love the example we brought up on unrated, why, by the way, I think it's perfect.
If anybody thinks back in history, just a little bit to what they called the pizza connection,
right?
There were a drug-running operations that were being run through pizza parlors up in
the Northeast.
The Greek and I might have specialized knowledge on that, but anyway, because we're from a similar
area in the country.
Anyway, that is an aside.
Interesting what happened there, though, those pizza places were put out of business, right?
Because they were running in a listed operation.
They were dealing drugs instead of selling pizza.
But what happened?
They reopened immediately under new management.
And the guy making the pizza there, he doesn't know what's going on.
Yeah, well, I want to go back to what Freeman said about the debt.
You see, so when this was done on March the 19th, 1933, the country went to receivership,
how much of, let's say, our grandparents were really put on the skinny and what was going
on in how important it was, no one was.
So what happened was the quote unquote government screwed up its responsibility to us.
We had nothing to do with it.
So what they did in short is when you get a birth certificate, that number, social security
number is attached to a birth certificate, that is called an exemption.
You're exempt from debt.
You're exempt from levy and fine because they took away your ability to quote unquote
pay for it.
So whenever you're dealing with anything legal or corporate, whenever you start signing
all their applications, you ever look at the fine print, what you're doing is waving
your exemption.
You are exempt from all of this because it wasn't your fault.
And so the birth certificate represents an exemption, but what they do through contracts
that are known as unconsurable contracts, unilateral contracts, you're actually waving
that protection that you have that exemption and becoming a debtor, becoming a citizen,
becoming a subject, becoming a resident, right?
And these things all have attachments.
Now it's gotten to the point where it's so bad that anyone like myself or anyone goes out
and public and starts speaking about this, it's so rarefied that it's easy to call this
person a nutcase, a sovereign citizen, a terrorist, don't listen to him and guess what, the rest
of the public believes it, right?
No, no.
So any thoughts on Fed now coming out in July with the CBDCs?
Well let's just say this.
Let's go back real quick.
Cryptocurrencies are the same operation like ISIS and al-Qaeda was intelligence operation.
If you bought Bitcoin for example at 20 cents and it became 50,000, anytime you see 5,000,
10,000% profit, that's an intelligence agency operation, right?
Like it or not, believe it or not.
So I think it's just the continuation of that.
Another example of the CBDCs is this, with early computer programming and all this
other stuff, you know, you couldn't take a college course.
But the industry was flourishing.
Colleges didn't start giving courses on, you know, openly to about programming and all
the stuff until the PCs already became a thing, you know, they didn't develop their courses.
So it's very much like that.
They look like Johnny Cummletley, but they're not.
The intelligence community and the banking community are tied in.
I knew a woman who did accounting for one of these big banks, HBDC or whatever.
And she quit after working there for about 20 years or so.
And one of the stories that she gave after a few drinks was like someone that was very,
very wealthy, influential, like a Gates or Jeff Bozo or something like that.
They're in the public eye and they actually use those companies to, let's say, bring in
and foreshadow policies that the government will use later.
So if they approach someone like Bill Gates or Jeff Bozo and say, we want you to tell
the public you're going to be doing this because it's going to be the front end of a program
that we want to do later and they refuse.
They go and check their bank balance, let's say Bill Gates, whatever, and it's zero.
And they know they just check their bank balance and they get a phone call right away and says,
do you want to reconsider?
And what do they say?
Well, of course I do.
One of these things came to a head when recently Jeff Bozo said that he was going to give
all his money away to charity.
Do you remember that article?
Yeah.
Yeah, why?
Because he's tired of this.
And he's not being public anymore.
But he's forget about that.
So how does this tie into the digital currency?
I just gave you much of the nefarious background that surrounds all of it.
Yes.
What it will be eventually is that if you say something because they're listening to everything
anyone that discusses something, you want to discuss having buying a new couch, guess
what?
You go to your computer or phone and there's a couch advertisement, right?
Right.
Well, they're letting you know they're listening.
So if you say something or do something, you won't be able to buy.
Let's say they say you're too fat.
You want to go buy a chocolate cake.
You can't buy the chocolate cake.
You're too fat.
You see the chat and GBT ties into this now, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's not good.
It's not good.
But if you view it as not being good, it won't be good.
If you view it as you're running your horse race and it's an inconvenience because if you're
running in last place, you're a little inconvenience and a horse race, but it doesn't mean you're still
not going to use the best of your horse racing skills.
But my thing, what I like to do with Ocelli and the Greek rated wide, all the Greeks
speak over the years is I've noticed that the people are lacking the skills and these are
not special special skills.
They just need to be shared.
And I just happen to be the only one that is giving this type of information and what could
come out of it eventually is a leaderless organization because if you have enough people
thinking the same, all spread apart all over the world, it's going to eventually spread
around to even those that haven't heard it.
The cosmic superhighway.
So again, we just, we're doing the same thing.
Instead, we're doing the Freeman show.
You know, I could speak for the next 16 hours on various things.
So let us know what you'd like, Freeman.
Well, I think we've done it.
I think that that was a fantastic show and definitely it makes anyone and everyone to head
over to rated wide.
I mean, I want to hear more, but I need 16 hours of you, the Greek.
And you two together, this is great.
This was such a treat for me.
Thank you, Ateli, for coming in and joining us here.
Absolutely.
Thank you, Freeman, for inviting me.
And there's already a well over 10 sonic events over there right now.
Fantastic.
Yes, it's growing.
I'm so glad that you guys are keeping this going.
And, you know, I just, it's amazing to me to constantly hear this miraculous view of reality.
From so many different aspects and so many different ways and always leading back to this, it's
astounding for me.
So I love being on this end of things where, you know, yeah, I get to talk with great people
like you.
So, yeah, it was great, guys.
I thank you so much.
I don't even know what else to say because we covered it.
Cool.
Well, until the next time.
Thank you.
All right.
All right, guys.
I'm getting as much out of this and maybe we are the ones forming this new noosphere where
we've got the mind to really just generate all of this and recognize everyone that you
don't have to go into interactions with people.
This is all ethereal.
So simple as that, you just have to believe.
And we'll continue to bring you evidence of all of the amazing abilities that you have
because you are you and alive and we're here to do this now.
So I hope you all will get out there and live life, love life and we'll make it through
all of this guys.
All right.
So we'll see you next week.
[MUSIC]