[Music]
Hello and welcome to the Free Zone!
Well folks it was bound to happen.
Aliens from Hell has been banned worldwide.
I hope you got a chance to get to see that lecture of mine.
They have banned 28 of my lectures folks.
28 of my shows have been banned on YouTube.
Many of them banned worldwide and it seems they don't want me teaching you this stuff.
So if you're going to look at Aliens from Hell, well you can't.
And I'll tell you it is so important right now for you to get that lecture.
So the best way to get it of course is to go to freemantv.com and buy the DVD.
I'm going to have to get it out to you, get it to the members or whatever I...
[Music]
Currently it is.
So you can not want Aliens from Hell.
And this is kind of bummer for me at this moment because of this new Obama Presidential Center that's coming up.
It is scheduled for the year 2021, excuse me.
While the reason the Obama Presidential Center made me laugh on Twitter.
And if you're not following me on Twitter, it's freemantv.
I highly recommend it.
I was laughing when I saw the architectural design for the Obama Presidential Center which will be in South City, Chicago.
You know where Obama calls home. Well folks, this is an ancient Egyptian architecture.
Now as they're building this thing and they got the designs out there in the plans for you to see.
It is an ancient Egyptian architecture.
Now what really struck me is as you guys know I went to university for ancient architecture.
And there was this thing that they taught us about there when I was learning about Egypt.
And it was called a "Mastaba." And a "Mastaba" according to the professor at the university is an unknown building.
It is a building that they say is a faux building.
Right? Look it up. "Mastaba" - M-A-S-T-A-B-A.
And you will see that the archaeologists, the architects, they all classify this as a faux building
because they don't know what its purpose is.
And so they said, "Well they built these giant "Mastaba." I mean they're almost as tall as pyramid some of them.
And well maybe not that tall but they're pretty big.
And they don't know what their purpose is.
So they say, "Well it's just a fake front."
So that raiders would attack that thinking that that was what they needed to attack.
So anyway, Barack Obama's Presidential Center coming 2021 is there...
...as a massive Egyptian structure.
And what they're telling you, you can learn there if you're a good Chicago citizen is how...
What it means to be a good citizen.
What does it mean to be a good citizen?
Well we're going to talk about this today with our very special guest, the Greek.
And he is from UncommonRadio.com.
You definitely want to get in there and check this guy out.
Now all of you wrote to me and said, "We love the Greek."
You guys did.
They were like, "Who is this guy? How can I find him?"
And I'm like, "Well he doesn't really exist. He's a guerrilla journalist."
I mean he's not out there for your...
for you to...
You know he's there for you, all right?
He's there not to make a name for himself, not to be known,
not to have millions of people going to his website
because the Greek has come into you as a guerrilla journalist
to bring you this information that you need.
And this is going to toss everything on its head
as you have been trying to understand how our world works
and what it means to be a good citizen.
You're going to learn a lot more on this show.
And the Greek has something good to say about all of you.
I've been telling you you're the best audience.
Well you're about to find out why.
So please welcome to the show, The Greek.
Hey Freeman, great to be back.
I know and I'll tell you, I'm not wanting to give compliments
and let's just say this objectively.
I've been speaking publicly and semi-publicly for over a decade
and recently did a little website so people can get in touch
and this is probably the third sonic event that you and I are doing.
And people have reached out a few five six or so.
The number is not important but I would say that
90% of the people that I have been in touch with
or have reached out that have given commentary
that is objective, discerning and just downright well educated
have come from this audience.
Now don't take this as a compliment, it's a fact.
So somehow some way the crop of listeners
that you have garnered tend to be in the top 10,
if not top 10, 1% of what I consider to be surface dwelling
earth inhabited free thinkers and intelligent thinkers.
So I just wanted, I was sort of astounded
but I shouldn't be because it's a fact.
So if we're going to be objective just state the fact.
And again most of the people that have had the best commentary
and the most perceptive discerning and objective
have come from Freeman's audience.
So whatever you guys want to take that,
that's what I've experienced so far.
I told you folks, I told you.
Yeah, that's so awesome.
I love it because we are an intelligent group here
that are really seeking answers.
We are not out there in a witch hunt.
We are trying to sort things out.
So you're not going to hear a lot of politics
and things of that nature unless it's very important
because we see that as the theater.
I mean one of the things that we can look at
like we're going to discuss what it means
to be a good citizen a little bit.
When we're looking towards our elections
and towards the world's elections
and we'll get to the Middle East Union
and how these things are forming.
I mean it was reported that 28% of France voted.
28%.
You know?
I mean are we starting to move away from this whole charade
or is there something more nefarious going on
in this malevolent structure we have set up?
Well yeah, interestingly enough
if let's say a group of people conspiratorial or not
but are going to hatch a plan to broadcast
or instill upon society that is malevolent or bad
it has to be presented as being good.
You know like rat poison is 98% good stuff
or whatever.
There is going to be something that is in the presentation
whether it's skin deep or not
that is going to be taken as the whole also being.
You see so the presentation has to be good
and the intent has to be shown as being good
even though the slightest examination you see it's not.
You know one good analogy for that
Freeman might be packaged food.
How many people might enjoy a brand or a type of food
and someone walks into the room and says
have you read the ingredients?
Well no I haven't.
Let's go see what's in this.
Maybe I shouldn't be eating this so much right?
So this is one of the aspects of maybe tying it back into citizenship
or citizen of what?
You see?
Yes.
There's much discussion about that.
Let's just, you know we've let's just say both sides
and the both sides of meaning information that people are getting.
You know you're getting the central party line
let's say the official line and then you have what's called
the alternative fringe commentary
and on the what I can comment on what can be seen
objectively on the fringe or the alternative is that the government's a
corporation and that makes it bad.
Let's think about that for a minute folks.
There is no discussion on whether or not it is a benevolent corporation
or a malevolent corporation and what is the status of that corporation?
No discussion.
Corporations folks are not bad unless they're bad corporations.
Right?
Now typically we've seen that theme being brought about over and over and over
what's called the legal fiction, the corporation and such.
But let's just take a moment from the whole thing Freeman.
I said listen Freeman we're going to start a corporation
and we're going to get all these billionaires to give us let's say
fun so we can help anyone in need
and when we've helped everyone in need then we fold it
and we go about our way.
What's so bad about that corporation?
That's all we do.
Yeah nothing.
That's fine.
But the problem is typically people don't understand because
this is it's not because they don't understand it's because what they're looking at
and it's usually skin deep.
The corporation is very simple it just shares liability so
instead of one person taking 100% liability they spread it amongst five people
so they each get 20% that's one way to look at it
or it's a representative body a corp oh meaning body you know even though it is
in the legal fiction.
So let's go back to the government aspect and the citizen aspect that
shows a form of maybe patriotism or allegiance doesn't it when you say
citizen which is fine.
Let's just go look at what the classified don't
hold me to this figure anyone could look it up is it 186 or 194 countries in the
world today somehow maybe more some states up to 300.
Let's just put it this way.
Most of the countries that you have heard about have gone bankrupt.
Now this sounds pretty okay now let's just say now that we've taken for granted their
corporations let's move on from this they have gone into some form of bankruptcy
between the 1930s and later and now if anyone understands what bankruptcy is
well you know you owe money and you can't pay it so you
you're shut down and when you just discuss bankruptcy basically people that you
owe money to they call them creditors come in
and like vultures they just divide the the the organization the store the whatever
the fixtures or assets on paper or not and to satisfy the outstanding debts
and they and they liquidate it it's gone right that's typically what's
thought about and they're very various chapters in bankruptcy
but let's say an institution like a large department store or an old
true store or hardware store or or something that has become a fixture in
society or community and offers it's better to keep it around than to liquidate
it well even though it goes into bankruptcy they put it in what's called
receivership you ever see certain institutions say under new
management right that's sometimes denotes a receivership so all it means is
that the proprietors and those that originated the business or the fixture in
society have lost all control of it to another group of people that they
had previous debts to simple isn't it now most corporations that exist today
that are in the government entity category are in receivership to what's called
the private banking institutions you want to call them federal reserves and
whatever that's fine and because they are in receivership
and they can they have no ability to pay for anything you they have put in
what's called credit systems every country has a credit system or it is a
credit based economy not a debt based economy a credit based economy
and that would be the foundation for perhaps presenting certain things so what
do you think up to this point Freeman I'm I'm I'm wondering the
difference between a debt and a credit based system okay let's just say let's
just put the debt side aside because that's all you hear about and no one can
explain it because if you're in debt how are you gonna and all you have is debt
and money is debt how are you gonna pay a debt with a debt right okay how can you
right so you so that is called you know an anti-maxim or it's an
impossibility in law let's just examine what is really going on
because these things in your people's wallets they're there either notes or
credit cards they're not debt cards they're either credit or debit or they're
notes right they're not not money cards and they're not debt cards right
right so the only evidence of any of that is secondary and we'll just get into
it a little bit you know for example when you go to a casino or one of these
closed loop organizations right that deal with what's called money when you sit
down at the black chip black check table the roulette table or whatever can you
just go into the pocket and pull out some notes or coins already have to go
and get chips from the cashier that are particular to that casino yeah
got to trade them in that's right it's the latter so when when anyone is born into
one of these government institutions that have gone into receivership
you are given what's called a credit line not a line of credit a credit line
and that credit line is so you can function in that society and that's usually
a number known as a social security number or it's issued by via the birth
certificate no no matter how nefarious or malevolent
you might think or presume it is i'm giving you the basic format in the template
for what this is okay so but what's going on is you have something called
human nature because this credit line is being issued to people is it not
it's not being issued to machines or dogs or cats at this point actually
these can be so so what's going on basically is that human nature is such a way
that if you told people essentially well you see you don't really need a job
because all you have to do is sign your name and you get food clothing
shelter cars or whatever you need utilities and all that and you don't need a
job you just need to find what your natural talent is and pursue that because
we have all these things that need to be maintained in society you need to
still work it's going to really confuse them right because most people have
the for thousands of years that if i don't work i die you know if i don't have
money i you know or grow what i need i die i need access to funds
so one of the analogies i give is imagine that if people were told at this point
just overnight or even 30 or 70 years ago you don't need to work for money all you
need to do is go if you need water gas electric food clothing a
Ferrari a you go if you're old enough to remember those little cars or a house or
rent or anything that you normally use what's called money for all you have to do
is provide the credit line number that you have and sign the name and you get it
now let me just give you this is not for everyone but this is enough people imagine in the
west typically you would you know you you go down the street and you see someone and they've
got the air conditioning on the windows open the water running and the stove on and they're
leaving the house and you're like how about conserving a little bit you know and turning off
you know all that stuff you know and it's like well screw you man it's already paid for
right that's you know you're going to get enough of that in human society at this point
that's yeah so let's go back to the receivership you know the something called a trustee you
know someone you trust to run the organization like a manager in a store as a trustee he doesn't
own it or whatever but he's running it and he's like the represents an authority the legal society
has been tasked as being trustees now even that little attorney that has a little office
down main street you know he is in the position where he has you know more access to the legal
society and these things and you do now when i see the legal society i'm not just talking about
attorneys and attorneys are not lawyers by the way you could look up the difference
i'm talking about this it's an entire society meaning there are judges there are attorneys
there are clerks there are police there is you see it's the entire society there are buildings
and institutions around them it's the entire society has been tasked to keep the rest of the people
in check now i think what we've just said is very simply i would say slightly contradicting
to what you hear in a lot of the alternative information avenues you know about let's say the
straw man and the debt based and and you really can't blame people for following their perception
and and even though it's skin deep or paper thin in most cases you can't blame them for following
it but we're not here to discuss who's right or who's wrong we're just maybe here to lay out
what is really going on that anyone can look at so it's really i can say Freeman it's
there's an aspect of human nature that is at the root cause of a lot of these quote-unquote
financial problems and not what we've been told right you see and and until this changes because
you know when you say you mentioned aliens from hell or whatever or earlier uh where do these
attorneys come from do they come from like alpha centurally through a wormhole or something or they
or are they people just you see are they from earth you see yeah so there's some strange inspiration by
the way folks if you read any the ancient texts you know you hear like Satan or you know the malevolent
forces in the world when you translate that into the language i'm not talking about the Hollywood
type stuff now what it actually means these malevolent forces are known as adversarial to you they're
adversaries so what that means if you say ugly they say pretty if they say hot they say cold just the
opposite of what you right so the attorneys actually represent that force boots on the ground
it's kind of like uh what was that a couple of alien movies like that where the aliens came in and
they looked like humans or whatever right right but spiritually right and this is not um and you
know societies and trouble when you the parents i think they stopped doing this a while back but
they said i want my child to grow up to be a doctor and a lawyer and essentially so you don't do
much and get paid a lot right you know they i don't think they do that very much anymore but i don't
think anyone knows what to say anymore other than still i think they're still pranking the children
though which we've discussed before now this is the planet of the prank right so so i wanted to
bring up that a little bit because how does that connect you with citizenship because you know it's
let's just keep this straight there's a lot of biblical clichés that are being used inaccurately
it's it's not money that's the root of all evil it's the love of money is a difference right yes
so absence of can there be love of money even though there's absence of money
sure because it we're not requiring the substance to love it do we right right so what what's
interesting this is from the humor or irony from the gods is that they because the gods by the way
don't speak well of humans by the way in case you haven't noticed so interesting uh they took the money
away and no one's noticed and just to prove the point aren't there still people putting on let's say
ski masks with guns holding up bank clerks for notes that are not money yeah are they still doing
it it's the love of money yeah you know you it's real easy to shut down a public thoroughfare just full
of get a thousand bucks worth of dollar bills in a bag and let them out the window at highway speed
watch what happens why why isn't it more important to properly navigate a five thousand pound vehicle
made of glass and and steal down the road then chase a piece of paper you know anyway yeah no it's a spell
it's a spell without a doubt oh yeah yeah it's also it's part of the cosmic censorship that i've
discussed and this is one thing that the listeners uh you you know would appreciate the high
weirdness aspect because i want to bring this up folks i i really want to get into the high
weirdness aspect of everything that is real yes it's real because not because i say so is because
you can say so once you're made aware of it very simple um and the high weirdness of all this is
is important to bring up because otherwise it's like oh the Greek is lecturing us again on he sounds
pedantic and you know he's talking about stuff we've heard of but i don't agree with it oh forget
about that i'm saying that listen this goes into the high weirdness category i mean this is beyond
you know the truth is stranger than fiction the truth is a lot weirder than fiction you know so this
is perhaps what we might want to go down and also talk about some obvious things but do you remember
Freeman if you ever have me on i discuss what's called cosmic censorship and i mean it means just that
it's you know what is censorship and what is cosmic meaning the world being affected you know from a
higher vantage point let's say right the the people i want to give to a metaphor in an old person
story if i may one of the metaphors on how cosmic censorship has been working on humanity now for
2500 years is this is an ancient metaphor let's say the censoring cosmically would be taking certain
critical information whether it is historical scientific cultural or or about the gods or whatever
and sealing it so people can't see it right so imagine a book or a scroll that's been sealed
and when you present that to someone and they say well i can't read it because it's sealed
right but then you present it to someone else and they say well i can't read that because see i'm
illiterate and then you present it to someone else and they say well i can't read it because i'm blind
so it's not just one simple thing the information is shut up you also have to consider the variety of
the people that are on the earth right now so what is what i want to get into perhaps is what's coming
in the future which is important to know and i'll say that because what is coming starting next
spring time because year goes from spring to spring by the way and the winter is an interim period
is that what you will start seeing in the next seven years or so is the blind are going to begin to
see more and the illiterate are going to be more literate and then the seal will open a little bit
you see so the cosmic censorship really affects now if i let me just explain what i just said
it affects those mostly that notice the seal don't they right Freeman because if you're
illiterate it didn't matter if it was sealed or not did it and if you're blind did it matter if it
was sealed or not so you see that you see the irony of this parable it's very it gets even deeper now
so but before these things are really open from a cosmic level the blind are going to get more vision
metaphorically and those that are illiterate are going to be more literate meaning you're going to
learn a little bit more about how to convey the the the the sea of information so this is what i'm
getting at for the next seven years that that's going to begin and what this is going to lead to is a
new paradigm on the earth which is going to appear very good but it won't be ultimately but it
will be because it goes back and forth you know right the the other story i want to give is an old
Persian parable or story this goes back to the days of zoraster let's say mythra back in the day
about the the waters that made people crazy have you heard this one no okay well back in ancient times
this certain angelic being came to a man and said you should go and stockpile with cisterns and
vases and containers the water that you know is good because soon all the water will be pulled away
from the earth and no one will have water to drink and when the water is brought back this new water
whoever drinks it will make them crazy so the man followed the advice and gathered all the good
spring water and he just drank from that so what happened the waters went away and then the waters
came back and whoever drank those new waters went crazy and when that was going on they all called
the man who was drinking from the water he had saved the good water let's say crazy they called him crazy
and he was really feeling abused and under you know under a lot of pressures he said maybe i'm
going to go drink some of the water that everyone else is drinking and he did and it made him crazy too
and now everybody was okay with him right i know it has more meaning and farcy but but but you get
the point yeah yeah it's a very simple way of showing and illustrating what is going on yeah we see
that constantly yes and that's why there is no real change and why we can't get people you know the
Hopi prophecy basically said you know rejoice at all of those that are flowing in the flood with you
and and you know share with them enjoy the fact that you are all being washed down this river together
and you know so we have these cycles and we have knowledge that i mean right now we look at the internet
and we feel like we're getting every little tidbit of information and everybody's all stressed out as
they're worried about the russian trump you know they're worried about the the french election they're
worried about this that and the other and you know this level of stress will never allow people to
start to find their true path right and also how efficient is it to stress for things that will
never really happen is that that's like dummy loading that's just waste that's for sure yeah and also
I think we mentioned before we started with if you're physically stressed you recover much easier
than if you're emotionally stressed so definitely definitely definitely you're much better off
working yourself down to the bone and and and feel it all good and and falling into your bed and just
out but if you're stressed you're gonna go to bed and you're gonna toss in turn and you're awake up in
the same condition tomorrow so they're putting you through a spiritual labor camp right
they're working your mind and spirit i think we've defined mind and soul or spirit and soul
which is a mind and breath and up before that people can seek what what those things really mean
because at this point many people are still quote-unquote stuck in the convention they're drinking
the water or or i think the cool eight is another more of a western apropos matter for and i think
that was after that thing that happened central america but i would suggest that the reason the
main reason you're you would want to listen to what's being said is so you live a life of efficiency
or more efficient and i think i've given examples about that and other times that we you and i've
gotten together and there's over a hundred hours of archives on uncommon radio and and that's
all you're gonna get there is just archives but in the future there'll be a new project probably a
podcast or something because i think i was mentioning to you freeman when you speak in public you
get to a saturation point of what can be said at open uh and then you you want to go to the next
level like you know i tell people i never share more than 10 percent it's not because i'm holding back
deliberately it just doesn't seem like it could be done in good taste like i think you and i had a
discussion you know when you were in in a public setting even a conference room you can address to
a certain point and when it gets kind of critical so you say hey freeman how can i speak to you
over here for a minute you know you want to speak more privately and more private more things will
come out and and more elaboration more of the same but it'll be you'll get if you think you've
ever gotten a haw moment listening to greek speak you're gonna get like a double triple a ha moment
and and of course that you know this is just the way things are more is always said in private you know
but what i want to just suggest is that you know we brought up pranking we brought up the dummy
load we brought up cosmic censorship but the thing is uh whenever you're going to convey information
you know it has to be useful what's the opposite of useful useless so i've ever heard of useless
information right oh let's have you ever heard of useful information i got to think about that
for a minute right why right it's got to be that way now in other words if whatever you're investing
you know i used to tell people by the way a long time ago you know if they hired someone or me you know
i'd say you know you don't ever have to be concerned about firing me because if i ever find out
i'm talking to the boss now if i ever find out that i am not making you money i will quit
you see how many people work and they're like oh i don't care as long as i get my hours you owe me
my hours right this is what's going on with information as well unfortunately people know that
they tune into stuff i need it on the background or whatever i like listening to this what do you like
listening about you know the particular host your show i don't know i just like it oh boy you know
how useful is that so let's get into a few things that might be fairly useful and one of the things
that affects everyone if your boots on the ground surface to our earth inhabitants is geopolitical
events but not as discussed normally and uh what does that mean uh that means that one has to know
the future and unfortunately freeman many people have when you say knowing the future it's some weird
nocturitumus or kc or psychic profit type stuff or misinterpretation of uh pro by the way a prophecy
cannot be changed because if it could be changed then it's not a prophecy you see but i'm not
discussing just the profism discussing about you must know the future on a practical level let's
get get more practical like for example if you speak to a civil engineer who builds bridges he knows
the future he has to know enough about the future combined with his studies uh in other words he knows
about how to design steel structures and he knows that once this is drawn up the construction clue
crews can follow it in the future and build it and it'll work and not only that that he has to
draw up a future maintenance schedule like how many years have to go by before it's painted and all
of these things not only should take place but they actually do take place for that bridge to stand
right and to get it even more simply than that uh you go walk into a room and um
grandma has got a chocolate chip uh chocolate chip cookie recipe out do you expect in an hour you
gonna come in and there's gonna be um a roast turkey in the oven or chocolate chip cookies
you see yeah so so we are actually engaging contemplating on information about the future that is
downright useful and practical but yet when you say what is coming on the future geopolitically
oh no one knows that or we can't know that why what's wrong why can't we are certain things
scalable yeah i would say most things are scalable right so why don't we start scaling you know
because typically i would suggest that i find that political discussions are in bad taste usually
they tend to get emotional and they don't talk about the ingredients on the box right right exactly
yeah just the brand just the brand and whatever i mean it's always a party what about the laws of the
nation what laws you know how many politicians or anyone come out say this in the countries in
receivership we're under a credit-based economy how many say that not even actually if you start
pushing the opposite fringe information well it's a fiction it's a straw man all that i think
you kind of get in trouble for a reason right and one of the things uh is that i think we mentioned
a lot of dictators typically send out people that speak out against them to find out who will agree
with them so now they know who is out there against them right so like Stalin's just sending people
out their bitch and about Stalin and then anyone that agrees with them then they know
yep exactly so when you see a lot of the discussion about what is being discussed about a debt-based
economy again that is being put out by the legal society because the last thing they want you to do
is everything know as everything is paid for now now by the way but a lot of people have gotten to
me said greek this sounds i've looked up everything you said it happens to be true how do i get stuff
for free oh boy yeah well yeah yeah great i just want to say out loud folks my name is freeman i
existed long before freeman on the land i have never been a partial to the freeman on the land
tactics and i hope you all know that it was quite of a a cluster for me when they took my name
because everybody suddenly started thinking i was trying to tell you how to get out of your straw man
but me in the greek we're gonna get into money we're gonna discuss a bit more like are you authorized to
use your money right so uh yeah please carry on i just had to make that note oh please yeah i mean there's
so many notes that could be made i mean it just looks like one of those crazy quark boards and where they
tack everything up that's how it could be you know but i just want to go into the efficiency aspect
of useful information because knowing how the money system works by not because listening to you and
i today let's say freeman in the greek but actually doing research on there i will show you where to look
it up and how it's contrary to all the fringe information you're getting and also what the mainstream
is giving you but the the reason why i believe that the most useful information is going to be is
whether whatever you're studying whether it's how the human body works which it doesn't the way you've
been told by the way i think we covered a little bit of that yes we might a little bit again but
how money works what the religions really are all these other things that is not is that that's
all very good but what you're going to get caught up into as a surface dwelling earth and habit is
certain geopolitical events that you will either come across on the as what you know this show they
call the news or internet websites or it'll just be shoved down your throat you know whether you're
out in public or a family member someone say oh no look what's going on here yeah and now what are
you going to do are you going to be able to rationalize this or are you going to fall into that
emotional esoteric vortex of worrying you see because that's what worrying i believe is it's a
strange esoteric feeling that because if you if it was if worrying wasn't so esoteric you wouldn't
be worried would you right so i'm not talking about being subject to liability or bad things just
the act of worrying you know special forces by the way are trained to be confronted with really
bad stuff and immediately adapt with a cool head and react or or you know basically you know
take it on right yeah i constantly find myself full of stress uh and and i'm sitting around asking
myself why why do i feel this this worry and i i take account of everything around me and say you
know okay i've got food i got shelter i've got you know i'm okay why am i so worried all this it's an
esoteric feeling i do it's it's and just like love you know as an esoteric feeling you know people
that you'll be hard pressed to meet anyone who really knows what love is and the definition of love
could be very simple it's doing the right thing even though you don't feel like doing it i like that
yeah most people don't know what love is because again it's a esoteric feeling oh i really feel
hot for this person or i fell in love hey uh smells the last time someone said they fell into anything
and it sounded good right it just doesn't happen and by the way when you fall in love or you go
through infatuation you start out really high on the curve and then it what happens entropy kicks in
and what it just cools down doesn't it yeah it's much better to learn how to love and come together
and say i will learn how to love you you know the only place you kind of see stuff like this and
say don't massacre's tollywood movies you're gonna learn to love this you know it's like well you
know they're actually giving a little bit of truth in this stupidity but but the learning how to love
that's why for example in non-western cultures where they have arranged marriages they have a
percent success rate in the west where they meet through infatuation what's the divorce rate
i think it's 50% isn't it conservatively yeah and sorry the percentage of the first one cut out
oh it's over 90% success right on fixed marriages because they have no choice that we have to
learn to love each other right you know where when you who seems like when you have a choice
and by the way lawfully i just want to get into a proposal so we're all over the place but that's okay
it's like i'm being on an ice skating rink as you know as long as the blade is sharp we're fine
you ever notice how people proposed a men proposes to the woman in western culture
and then that poses problems because you know lawfully you're supposed to propose to the
patriarch in the family that's why when in a western marriage it isn't a patriarch either the
father or someone else giving the white the bride away yeah if the bride was in his how can he
give her away right why are you proposing to the women how many times can you propose to a woman
and she accepts but the father doesn't want it what kind of lifestyle is that you pro ask the father
first or the patriarch or the matriarch and once they grant you their blessing then you can pursue
right why why is that stronger well let's say you propose to the lady and she wants it but the
family doesn't want to be with you you what kind of a life are you going to lead now let's go the
antithesis of that you you ask the parents or the authority of the family and they give you the
blessing but the lady doesn't want well now they're gonna help help coaxering aren't they
absolutely so you're gonna have a much more successful and pleasant i'm not saying that this
should be done this is just a rational scenario do you see that Freeman how simple it is so
so anyway guys stop proposing to the lady and propose to the matriarch
to the father yeah and then you will get the support and even though she's not sure she'll come around
so i'm not saying this is not in trapment i'm just saying this is a interesting lawful
way of perceiving things that why isn't this discussed by the way anyway let's get to it i mean we're
you know the question is are you ready for the next level yeah i was hoping you would explain a little
bit the levels the cycles the seven years and how that is is playing out for us right now let's do
that there's there's a time period that is ended by the way i think we discussed being in the credit
part of human the human epic meaning that time ended roughly around 1999 1998 and there are four
seven-year cycles that are preceded by a five-year cycle and succeeded roughly by two and a half
years oh boy what did he just say just hit the rewind and you'll get it where does that come from okay
that comes from ancient rich ancient scripture there is a seven thousand year plan in place or
six thousand year plan in place and it's really hard to avoid that cognizantly or rationally for
example i recently had a discussion with someone who went to a Damascus tour a few years ago
and the tour bus person said Damascus is the longest occupied city for 10,000 years and you asked
the guy who's just said that when was the catastrophic flood historically that you know it was 45
hundred years ago well so how could Damascus be continuously occupied for 10,000 years one the flood
was 45 hundred years ago anyway people just don't listen to what they're saying you see they're not
paying attention so there's an aspect to this by the way carbon dating and DNA testing and all that
is not as valid as you've been told are you you're aware of that i guess that could be determined in
other places the inaccuracy of all that but let's just say this Freeman if you're going to shoot a two
hour movie do you get exactly two hours with the film or do you get two hours and 10 minutes because
you're going to run credits in the end a lot yeah yeah so what's been going on since 1998 is the
credits portion what's interesting about the credits is that you get to see things that weren't
shown in the film and also you know people that are behind the scenes and all that and there's a much
bigger crew than you then you than you were aware of just seeing the actual show but what's also
interesting about the credits using this metaphor is you notice that during the film if you make a
disturbance stand up or talk people tell you to shut up and sit down but during the credits if you
if you stand up and talk does anyone really tell you shut up the credits are running no it seems to be
okay to be noisy actually i worked at the movie theater this is just a weird little quirk uh and the
movie uh uh uh buckaroo bonsai i worked at the movie theater as a kid and for some reason i i don't
know why i got to mention this but for some reason in buckaroo bonsai no one left they all stayed there
for the entire credits and this as a person that cleaned the theaters after that this was completely
unusual and i still have yet to figure out why buckaroo bonsai keeps everybody there till the very
last word scrolls up the screen it's the weirdest phenomenon just thought i'd throw it out there
sorry oh yeah well they're probably got some serious juju going on in that film you know it put frames
between frames you know yeah uh uh or it could just yeah it's a cosmic thing that that that might
require quite a bit of investigation i'm gonna have to watch it again but okay so we're at the credits
now what's happening now let's say like buck uh like that movie if you if you remain seated it
it's the last show for for the theater for that particular epoch or day what happens the lights
come on the screen gets pulled up and you got this really ugly brick wall don't you know the sudden
the illusion is it was like countered like even tenfold again right so and then you start noticing
you know it's interesting how you don't notice how sticky the floor is from all the gum and soda
until the credits come on yeah during the movie it's not this doesn't bother you as much so this is
the metaphor that i'm using in human society is in right now what you're going into right now
starting next spring and this is not a date folks this is a the the world doesn't work on the
Pope's work schedule which is the Gregorian calendar we've mentioned this before you know the the
moon rules the month and the sun rules the day and when the sun and the moon pass through the same
ecliptic or the same path in the sky it's the equinox or it is the new year right and then they
reverse places again equinox by the way doesn't mean equal day equal night because if it did it
would be called equineum nox it's equinox which means a measurement to measure at night well that's
i think we got into that again prior so what is coming now is going to be very different than the past
seven years of tension that you've had or transition because you've noticed what what are the major
headlines geopolitically and nationally that people have been getting for the past less than a decade
let's see stories about corrupt politicians and political corruption missing airplanes and impending
financial doom how much how much have has that been repeated in the past seven years i'd say with
very fervent cycles and i just got thrown one more rape and and right right okay yes certain social
ills that are coming upon society yes and because i saw each of these discussed in the debates each time
i i even outlined it before the debates occurred i said you know we're looking at voter fraud we're
looking at political corruption and and uh you know manipulation we're looking at uh sexual
offensors which you know was bill Clinton you know they had the rape victims there at the they
brought it all up to the point of even britt talked discussing Barack Obama's birth certificate
for a good ten minutes of the debate which was between Hillary and Trump you know how did what did
this and so uh we didn't see the reinforcement of these uh these programs you know and and also to
bar from the gladio a period of tension these terrorist events you know the bus is the trucks the
buildings the shootings you know the glatio style you know tension yeah because the glatio was about
they called it a period of tension that's what they called it so this this period of tension now is
ending and you're going to be going into another cycle you in other words we're discussing what
the headlines that you're going to be getting are different now you say well Greek uh well they're
always different no they're not because we just brought up how they're all the very similar
this mindset is going to change and and i want to get into a little bit more definitive um from a
secular perspective meaning what's uh access historically about this middle east union because it's
not going to be like the european union whenever we talk about a union we think of the EU right uh
and common currency and all this other stuff and they almost have a common religion they're
particularly christian right uh so i want to give some similarities because it's always good to show
the parallels now if you if you go back uh before the this is before there was a european union
even though it was sort of discussed uh when you look at the cultural centers technological and
cultural centers of europe around what's called world world war one or world war two that was usually
the austrian hungarian empire around germany and places like that and those places were initially
gutted in world war one and world war two now when i say cultural and technological centers i mean
where does strouse come from where does bak betoven uh where do a lot of the um philosophers come from
where where does the the the school of psychiatry where did it come from Freud and all those guys you
see where do a lot of the technological and all from the that part of europe and it got
gutted um now if you look at for example the middle east where where's the cultural and technological
and financial center of the middle east throughout history while you've ever heard of babelon where's
babelon you're acting around you know uh that yeah and have you ever heard of damascus right it's
mentioned all throughout it was a very serious cultural religious and financial hub and uh
intellectual hub you know uh you have to include a little bit parts of lebanon in there as well
where what's being what's been gutted or being gutted at the moment you can you answer
where in the middle east do you see it yeah it's gone after the cultural and technological hub now
right this is this is this is what's going on now the other thing to remember about forming a union
let's go back to the europeans for example um how can you have an EU free men if all of the bordering
nations are extremely nationalistic how can you have an union you can't because each overly
nationalistic leader or government is going to be very persnickety and maybe to the point of refusal
of cooperating with its neighbors to form anything that even vaguely resembles a union think about it
you can't happen so so all of their teeth were pulled out right during the after the war you see
so they can't bite now what you see in the middle east how many uh nationalistic precepts and let's
say just conflicting ideologies you see in neighboring countries in the middle east quite a bit even still
and now combine that with the concept of the cultural and technological centers being gutted
and i mean literally right the Iraq war and now what's going on with Syria yeah and even ISIS blowing
up all the ancient monuments yes and that not even that let's just uh i want to go back to this one
thing with yes yes that but not even that but think what freeman what defines a world war
is it the casualties or the number of armies or is it the number of countries involved yeah that's
what i'd rather yeah now if you know any boots on the ground or people that live in that area that
have encountered ISIS they will give you along in a short list of ISIS is comprised of malaysians
Filipinos Pakistanis Chinese Vietnamese um uh some malays some people from the middle east that
of that origin that came out of europe now how many countries that i mentioned there about half a
dozen or more this is a world war based on that definition right ISIS is predominantly non they're
not from that area they're not from Syria they're not from Iraq they're from everywhere else
there might even be some south americans and australians thrown in there too oh we know the americans are
in there right right so okay technically it's a world war right uh you know ISIS represents a world
organization whether it's overt or as you you've been told is irrelevant because by the way if you
do a little bit of research on what was going on in world war two and why they had to be fought you'll
find it's completely false also what the way the people were dummy loaded i should say and i just
want to interject something which is frightening for the american population this is just take this
and as an objective comment if you have a political leader come out and just say something simple like make
great whatever and you get one third of the country to ban behind such a simple empty comment
it's pretty dangerous to think forward and say what if they wanted to say something else
if it's so simple to get a group of people to ban behind you with such an empty just because it makes
you feel good remember the esoteric feeling yeah so this is what you know also gets people
into ISIS so so again when you look at the european aspect right now it parallels very often
what's going on in the middle east uh mean because there's more to happen there still are countries
in the middle east that are overtly nationalistic and non-cooperative right so what you're going to
see if there's going to be a loose middle east union those countries will lose the ability to do so
now who they are you can figure it out on your own because right now if you look at the middle east who
are the two superpowers in the middle east well it would be Persia or Iran and Israel yeah you can say
Saudi Arabia but Saudi Arabia is a very loosely defined place you know how let's say draconian
so the Saudis are in terms of Islam do you know that on their own governmental website i hope it's
still up or might be may not they stated that they were actually Jewish a hundred years ago but they
can be converted to Islam the Saudis profess that right so so this is like you know this is again
going into the the bad taste or the poor character of politics i we don't want to get into that
religion and all that stuff because then i've discussed what religion is before as well we might
recap a little bit but right now if you look at the scene what the reason i brought up the superpowers
is superpowers do two things they either ally or they or they fight each other right they typically
even if they try to remain neutral to each other there's satellite influence is overlap at some point
which will either be a fight or an ally again right so what you're going to be seeing in the future this
i should i didn't want to really say this in public i'm going to say before more private
discussion but let's just say look for a loose economic alliance between if not loose even more
than loose between israel and iran coming okay the other thing that you're going to notice is there
is a couple of countries that have not been talked about like jordan lebanon how about have you
ever heard of we've discussed this before freeman assyria not syria assyria where is a syria you know have
you heard of the israel the israelite diaspora you know they left palestine and they were scattered
through the whole world you're right you hear that right very often no one ever talks about the
the assyrian diaspora which they had lost their nation or their state 2300 years ago they're all
over the place germany australia the us you know well guess what they're going to go back and form
their nation where is assyria ancient assyria to northern iraq but if you actually look at proper
terminal borders it actually went into parts of syria and turkey that's why over 10 years ago i was
sending out information saying there's going to be conflict between or involving syria and turkey
in the near future as well as iraq you know which already had been since the early 90s and like
reek why do you say that is it well because since when is a new country formed and it takes a swath
of land from two other countries without a fight or without turmoil of some sort right is so so
isn't syria and turkey been in the news for at least the past four or five years in that way or at
least three years dominantly without that why was i able to send out messages about this more than 10
years ago because i know what's coming and now you do too and i'm not asking you anyone to believe
any of this because can i talk about the word belief real quick of you okay like for example
someone says do you believe in god just walk away don't even answer that question to ridiculous
question why because the term belief is usually based on that you have knowledge of something that
has not occurred yet and that belief is based on that knowledge that you've received and you hold
it as a belief until what's in that knowledge based manifest so if you have belief that something
is going to happen in the next hour or the next month or the next year and it happens based on
the information you got guess what that was what a good belief wasn't it now if you get a certain
knowledge base of something that is going to happen and it doesn't happen guess what freeman
was that a good belief or not no that was a really bad belief you see so the term belief is actually a
very dynamic term again it's not we're bringing up this it's not an esoteric feeling you see it's
something that is rational and should be based on something you even hear that in conversation
i believe this will happen right right or whatever so asking someone to believe something on blind
faith or esoteric emotion like touching yourself or something is ridiculous or do you believe in
that something exists is ridiculous well it does it exist and can we find out that it does just
simply saying this is what i believe and i'm happy with it you need to walk away i mean you don't
need to walk away but it's advisable yeah yeah just at least change subject yeah change such a
hand i'm a plastic broom and reflect the vest anyway so at this point the majority of the people
still gone that down that primrose path and i i don't know who was old enough to remember what the
primrose path means but anyway the the the entire thing here is about are we conveying information
yes we are we are actually stringing letters and words together that people understand and they could
form a body of knowledge on that's what knowledge is you know it's very difficult to get knowledge
unless you're getting a divine download for example like an inventor or something
knowledge is conveyed through the meaning of letters and the meanings of words where they form
thoughts and images and ideas so that is basically what the purpose of let's say Greek speak or having
me on with Freeman is about is just to not to be convincing not i'm not selling i'm telling and not
for you to believe unless you find it to be valid or unless unless you find it to be substantial
then it would make a good belief you see at the moment because when these things manifest you
can say yeah there was this really obscure guy called the Greek that said about these things i
really didn't like the way he talked he's really rougher on the edges but unfortunately what he said
is true you see right so this is this is the aspect of sharing you see there's many levels and i'm
giving it in a way that is just with no attachments it's unconditional like do what you want with it
i'm not here to argue or debate or whatever this is just what is going on you do what you want with it
and and what i suggest is that of many of these rationals are put together whether they're historical
scriptural or however even intuitive because you you can also get information that is counterintuitive
you know but if you find it even intuitive you will leave live a life of more efficiency and this
is also a tie-in because we're going to get a little bit more into the money hopefully maybe on the
side of the way we are getting there so we're getting near the the end of this first hour so i hope
yeah summarize this for everyone and yeah so what's coming folks because you know this is
you know how a year ends you know let's say what they call the pagan calendar they start talking
you know the best of the previous year and all this right you haven't had the best of the past seven
years it's just a period of tension what you're going to see because the year goes from spring to fall
spring to fall winter is an interim period this is the last spring to fall cycle or winter to spring
cycle for the folks that are upside down right yeah on the other side of the world this is going to be
the last part of this seven years where you're going to see the mindset changing a little bit of the
cosmic censorship is going to be lifted and the this is the summing up of this rationale you've heard
of time is cyclical things repeat right and you have the small cycles and the grand cycles right
um not to get mystic but just people have heard of these terms uh when you look at something cyclical
let's look at the structure of it like let's say a racetrack or a track of some sort you know
Freeman can you can you envision where the let's say a starting line on a racetrack Freeman you see
it where it is right right now where is the finish line at the start right exactly now even if you
go back to the base let's just use the term bullshit education system that exists uh don't they
tell you that mankind started the messetapetamean region of the world right that all the scriptures
sort of go back there um and and even if you go to the hope again they tell you it happened on the
world at a far away place where it all happened at the same time um because by the way going from
two people to seven billion people in a thousand years is not that hard to do uh if you look at the
world population in the mid 1800s it was barely a billion it i think it was it was barely five
billion in the eighties or seventies wasn't it it's very easy to start doubling the population quickly
but anyway when you look at this cycle of the middle east uh when man society starts to get wrapped up
and it's going to be at a height it's going back to where it started it's very very simple and it's
not being noticed as such and one of the other things that i want to bring up is that in the next seven
years and i was telling the freeman off air i kind of want to stay away from what's called the internet
and media because there's going to be a lot of ugliness uh coming to that area a level of carnage that
people have are not used to seeing and um like you know how many people really discuss objectively for
example uh freeman the bombing of dresden what really happened there very few but they know
it was bad do you know how many hundreds of thousands of people if not almost that died directly in one
night from that you know fire bombing you know you've heard like for example how many people you hear
about the atomic firecrackers that they dropped on japan uh how many you know it was roughly a hundred
thousand or so how many people do you know how many you know it was almost twice that much that died
with the fire bombing of tokyo and but that doesn't really it's not impressive though because it
wasn't a new right but the numbers are still there you see so that's what i mean there's going to be
um massinations and movements in the middle east that westerners are going to show that look
there's genocide going on or whatever but look let me just let me just reflect back to the
ingredients on the box on the hypocrisy of the western world do you know that they're um
in just in the united states alone there are almost a million people a year which is roughly
three thousand a day that are killed by doctors when i killed by doc i say killed by doctors i mean
by negligent practices overt and overdoses and just bad drugs do you know that eighty five or let's
say seventy five percent of all the pharmaceuticals that are legal now will be illegal in ten years
because of you know the warnings you know or so so the do you know that the how many millions of
people in this country or thousands per day died from just bad food and toxins that are you willingly
use you see so you you're actually uh but because you're not paying attention to what is going on
you you're thrown with a few uh really sad events and you think it's the end of the world where
if you're going to have the end of his society it's going to come from what's on the side of a cereal
box not some army you know so this is a hot pot level if hypocrisy i just wanted to bring up in people's
minds that maybe they might want to think about like you know when you say brainwashing it doesn't
sound good then how about just washing your brain but uh let's let's get real is is the idea so hopefully
that was sort of useful to show what goes around comes around and people to get ready for the the
precursor to the formation of the middle east union that's going to be starting in about a year there's
going to be more talk and more centralization and another thing freeman just to throw in perhaps to
sum it up only i'm going to even just list you and i rhetorically get into this for a second if you will
how many times if you heard people preaching doom and gloom coming upon the united states emp
attack starvation grab a government crackdown or whatever god for decades yeah okay well the
past eight years specifically we've gotten hit pretty hard with certain things i say we whoever
we as okay let me ask you now profetically this when this middle east union comes around that all
the world's nations are going to support it morally and with material support how can the us offer
material support to the middle east and moral support if they are in complete catastrophe they can't
so that means if they are going to offer material and moral support to the middle east there is no
catastrophe coming to the us folks all right all the way through until until not until like the early
twenty thirties and at that point you want to be at least three days walking distance from anywhere
and that's another idea which will only be understood by those right now who know the scroll is sealed
not those that are illiterate or are blind and that's another not a put down folks that's just the
different levels of humanity let's be honest folks sometimes the biggest resistant you you find when
you get new information is not from someone on the street or someone on a black with a black robe
sitting up in a court building but it could be from your own family members or loved one sometimes
that make your life the hardest when it comes to new ideas so I just want to say that yeah and in
the second hour you brought up how america had had fallen into creditorship and that
we're we're around because we're useful so I definitely want to get into that second hour
the idea of are you authorized to use your money you you guys are going to you're really going to
jump on this this is going to amaze you as you look at the laws as the greek and i start to uncover this
and get get much deeper into all of that story plus I want to jump a little bit into space folks
because the x thirty seven b is just returned after seven hundred and eighteen days in space record
shattering orbit around our planet sorry flat earthers why do I always feel like I have to defend
myself against flat earthers uh... what do you think about that oh it's an esoteric attack we're
using that word a lot today yes yeah there there's many uh here's the thing about the flat the
the earth is neither flat nor around just like both creationists and evolutionists are both
wrong if that mean but let's just you want to get really simple in the dummy load both democrats
and republicans are wrong right right there you go i don't like baseball so people should choose
your own team and leave me alone yeah i personally feel the critical thing you should take away from
that debate is that you don't know and if you can't admit that you got to look at something there folks
because uh... you don't know until you are in space until you're on your virgin space flight orbiting
the planet you don't know so right and whether the sun in and honestly it would knowledge should be
lead to what's called master ship you know from apprentice to master right if you want to be a master
full surface dwelling earth inhabitant you know the sun rises in the east and sets in the west and it
affects your orientation and architecture it affects the way you grow crops it affects many things
so you need to master that movement and is there mastery of those movements in agriculture architecture
and the rest i would say no so master the movements right right otherwise the rest of it is just
another movement called the bowel movement but anyway so we're definitely going to get into all
this in the second hour i can't wait and i hope that you guys will subscribe over there at freeman tv
dot com and and get all these bonus hours of it helps support this effort it keeps everything going
and you know it's necessary it is right now it's necessary it's less than a buck 50 a week you know
it for two hours you can you can shell out less than a dollar fifty and it just you know this this
cost money to do so anyway there you go subscribe to freeva tv dot com because it's awesome and it shows
shows that were going somewhere and please share this everywhere because we see constantly i mean my
numbers on youtube went from twenty thousand views a month to five thousand views all right this is
not due to lack of content this is due to algorithms and in the fact that they are crushing us right
now so it is really important that you share the information that is important and get this stuff
out there because honestly we we feel like low man on the totem pole over here because as greek was
saying there is already this mindset that has been crafted for everyone and if you don't fall
into that and let me tell you guys i'm contrary to almost every conspiracy theory out there and
people don't realize that and it's because there's so much more to look at and people are just taking
the surface and and going with it and so if you're not digging deeper and deeper into these topics of
the occult the esoteric or even politics uh and seeing you know the the real hidden truth behind
this and the message that is being planted into your brain uh then you are just stuck again in this
cycle cyclical situation which we are seeing happens uh over and over again in these seven year
cycles and now we're at the end credits and we are going to watch as this really starts to unfold and
and you know to ask the question what are you going to be when you grow up is almost impossible
in in the 21st century because everything is shifting and changing right now so fast and as as
greek shows there are cyclical sections to this and that's what the master magicians truly understand
you know the sun rises in the east this is something they can use and they use it all right and they
leave us in the dark so we're going to get deep deep into this into the second hour i also want to
dimension to you guys that uh pv roasters the perump valley roasters the coffee that are loving the
free zone honestly they're just listeners they're the good local home brood company that is brewing
and and and creating the most awesome coffee it really is good that's why i break it up
i just wanted to mention that if you go to pv roasters dot com and order coffee from them get four pounds
because you're gonna want it and second it costs the same in shipping if you get one pound or four
pounds so you will save on shipping by getting four pounds uh same goes for their teas uh get you
know get get four pounds of that get four four sets of that so if you go over to pv roasters dot com
make sure to get four pounds of coffee because you're gonna love it and you're gonna want more so
you might as well just get the shipping all done in one boost so i had to throw that out there and
alanzo pachardo dot com he is thanking all of you for getting in and communications with him
great online marketing and you know he's the guy who helped me rebuild free man tv dot com so you
can see how good he is and then finally uncommon radio dot com home of the greek at this point as
he's about to go a bit more covert but there are our list and list of archives and he's gonna start
formally producing a podcast so get over to uncommon radio dot com if you really want to get into deep
deep deep topics with the with the the greek because uh you know obviously you can't cover this
stuff in an hour it takes years folks for us to get this all so also remember this there is no such
thing as an old show there isn't everything that has been said over the last 12 years on free man tv
dot com is still relevant right now everything that you need to learn and let me tell you folks i've
forgotten half of what i've taught you okay because it comes in and it goes out our brains can't contain
all that data so that's what these archives are for so that you can go back so don't think these are
old news stories this is an education that starts at the beginning so if you really want to
get into this go all the way to the bottom of the archives and start there with me start with the
freeman perspective which you can only watch a number of them because of the fact that they are all
band world wide so i'm gonna work on getting this information more to you but right now the only
way to get really the deep information that i have to share is to come over to freeman tv dot com
and purchase the DVDs because uh it is band world wide all over the internet folks and that's the way
it is even though everything i use is fair use i make sure of it uh i i can't stop youtube from just
banning it worldwide and that is what has happened so if you want aliens from hell you know get over
to freeman tv dot com and get that so we're gonna take this over to the next uh level into the next
side we're gonna join in with the members and discuss are you authorized to use your money and i
think you'll find this very intriguing and well well beyond the freeman on the land so we will see
you all on the other side in the rest of you uh please write me freeman at freeman tv dot com tell
me what you want tell me what you need and members if you have any issues or troubles or anything
at all just write me freeman at freeman tv dot com and i will take care of your problems instantly i
promise uh so that is what we got for you guys be looking out for this middle east union understand
that we are in the the end credits and we are at the the end or the beginning of this next cycle
and we're gonna get more and more into that on the other side
and welcome back you wonderful members thank you so much always for supporting
of my efforts and keep in me going and uh i did forget to mention that if you do uh i want to get some
of that coffee you got to put the freeman in the freeman code so that some of the money comes back
to the show it's a little bit the eatout of the guys this isn't like they're paying me to say this so
i just uh you know i don't know they got good coffee and i forgot to mention that you should put
freeman in the code so there you have it uh wow wow i really feel my brain is churning Greek it's
just churning so many things are going through my mind and i keep thinking b bold and mighty forces will
come to your aid and that that is like the critical statement for all that we're discussing but let's
get a little bit into high strangeness real quick because as we went off the air i was discussing the
air forces x37 b now this is a robotic uh space plane uh it's a it's a
it's you know it's completely automated there's no pilot it's it's a robotic space plane a drone
that orbits our planet doing god knows what and they're always so excited to discuss
how they don't know what the x37 b is like almost every or what it's doing almost every
news source is just gleeful about the fact that well we don't know what it's doing you know but we
of course know it's out there so this is a telepresence robotic space plane that orbits the planet for years
and uh the latest theories that were going on around this thing was that they were testing the new
electromagnetic uh propulsion systems which are noted as the impossible drive is what it's been called
but so they're testing this is one of the main things that has come forward from people
hypothesizing on what the secret mission of the x37 b is but this thing has been orbiting there's
two of them right and they have been orbiting our planet for years and years nonstop and and no one
knows why what or what they're doing so now when we see pictures of the x37 b it just landed
and the sonic boom uh i'll tell you when the space shuttle used to land in Orlando it would knock
our garage door off its tracks with the sonic boom and so and people would be running not knowing
what the hex going on this happened again with the landing of the x37 b now when it comes down into
that runway and it gets uh you see and i've shown you pictures of this and we'll we'll include it if you
want uh these guys come up to the the x37 b and they are in full gear i mean they have their full
radiation burn suits on they have and all they're doing is coming up to this thing with like a giant
vacuum so greek what do you know about this the situation with this x37 b and and why these guys
are showing up in this they're they're full gear uh you know masks the oxygen tanks and everything
when it's on the ground it's not only the x37 b it's all the other stuff that you could witness uh you
know from back the early apparel stuff we're not talking about going to the moon we're just talking
about just going into what's called space there is this quote unquote uh hazmat decantamination
precaution that's being taken and and of course it's a minor detail but you know there's it's
all details need to be looked at don't they and i think you and i brought this up or i brought it up
and and and it's it's something that uh everyone will now know once we discuss it a little bit and i
think it's again like i profess this is a show it's just not take this as just being information
but the truth is not only stranger than fiction but it's a lot weirder too right so what is
weird about this how come there's no talk about why they're in decantamination or they just pass it
off like oh yeah that's just what they do well they do it for a reason right so what's interesting
about this is uh i think i let's just bring it up like uh to the listeners like i brought it up to you
and let's say we go into space you know we pass through the atmosphere and now all the blue is
below you and it's all black above and now you're clearly in what's called outer space and first
thing it's not a vacuum it's full of rarefied gases which i think i might have mentioned a little
bit but hydrogen tends to take around the 20 of position there are many other gases lighter than
hydrogen but that's another story the story here about the decantamination is very interesting
freeman uh do you know that if um you and i were in space let's say one of those spacesuits and we
opened up the visor and uh and took a shallow breath it was was what i brought up to you
and now to the listeners uh and you actually tasted or smelled space what you would get is probably
the most accurate taste feeling or smell and it would smell just as burning flesh would and i'm not
talking about a barbecue steak on the barbecue and the flames or something i'm talking about throwing
an entire living creature mammal or such with hair and skin and a bone and everything all set on fire
it is a very very stinky acrid condition that would probably bring the um
dag reflex i would say to most people now if you notice what the the this thing that came down on
the uh youtube you'll notice that they pull up with a few trucks and they pull out something that
looks like one of these ventilation ducks and they start sucking whatever gases or things might be
in there right and uh this is just a precaution now uh i just want to state that if you are aware of
anyone that's been into space or even have heard of any training that nasa does you know for example
uh in the military they put you through training and uh you know eventually they do what's called
live round fire testing you know or range you know you could actually there are many people in the
military that get killed every year you don't hear about that just from live train fire training drills
live rounds uh in certain nasa applications when they do a as close as possible as space suit
testing as possible uh occasionally an astronaut will breach the suit and will throw up because of that
nasa knows to i don't know if they're burning gerbils or pigeons or dogs or cats
to pump that really acrid nasty burning flesh smell into the chamber where they're doing their testing
so i just want to bring up freeman do you think if this thing spends a year in space do you think there's
going to be a residue of this stench on there you see in space no one can smell your funeral pyre
yeah all right oh boy now think about funeral pyres is that they're so hot you don't smell any
right just talking about a direct burning of flesh which a people in the fire department and
stuff like that sometimes again you know it's the partial burning that gives you the dirt right not
the complete burn yeah wow but this is and out let's just say how you know how i often talk about
scripture or biblical text being of a higher vantage point and of high science for example like
you know circumcision let's say was done on the eighth day why because it science in the 30s
figured out medics that the the highest coagulative ability of the human male is at eight days old wow
that accounts for something scientific doesn't it yes and also by the way the scripture the biblical
text if you read in certain passages in Isaiah it says that the the the light part of the earth and
the dark part of the earth is separated by a circle meaning the on the line so he can only see
that from outer space you know when the earth is round kind of deal right when you light a
sphere on one side so you'll get very high levels of science in there but one all things aside you'll
have descriptions that are passed over in a lot of descriptions that you see in ancient text
texts are like going down the road you see a speed limit 15 miles per hour and to enforce the speed
limit they put a speed bump so if you didn't see the sign the car will be jarred that you know
you should go slow and everyone seems to want to speed through these speed bumps in ancient texts
right right and and one of the speed bumps is if you read in the ancient text that when burnt
offerings were being done the the residue or the smoke coming off of the burnt offering was what
was a pleasing odor to the gods now where are the gods are they up there like the birds or are they
way out there like in space right yeah now tie the now tie that together what's in the ancient
writ with at people that have been in space discussing how space smells like burning flesh
boy oh boy oh boy think about that for a minute now this is a minor detail but I'm sure you haven't
heard this before and I shouldn't say I'm sure but if you haven't heard this before now you did
do what you want with the information but it certainly explains a lot more than just in passing
off a bunch of guys and decontamination suits with air vents around space capsules I think it lends
a little bit more of insight on what's really going on and how practical this reality can be
what do you think Freeman yeah yeah and you got me thinking about that stumbling block because in
Hebrew the mastima is the angel persecutes evil in the Jewish belief system or is known as the
adversary Satan so mastima's the stumbling block was put there like in the story of the talking
donkey you know in the Bible that the stumbling block is there too as a speed bump and to make
you want to change direction and a bomb in the talking donkey as the donkey is trying to tell him
look there's a mastima in front of us a stumbling block we need to turn and he just keeps whipping the
donkey saying go forward because that's the direction I want to go right well in ghetto it's called
slowdown before you fall down right so it would be that but actually also the stumbling block is the
Christ also because it just a not even getting into a discussion but he was adherent to a lot of
Moses and what's called the not Judaism but you know that Old Testament stuff he didn't come if he
came to start a new religion that undoes him being the Messiah so it you see what I mean right right
right because he's not he's here to fulfill not to start a new religion so this J.E.S. U.S. character
is actually an invention of Simon Magus and others through the ages which what a Santa Claus in
Easter have to do Easter Bunny have to do with it anyway we're not we don't want to attach this
a document you know the let's go back to the little spacecraft there I just find it that if someone
had let's say read the scripture or the Bible and had come across the passage that a burning sacrifice
was a pleasing odor where out there to the gods right and you heard that space smelled like
acrid burning flesh you you most likely if you could rub two brains all together you could you could
connect that piece of information that space smells like burning flesh with that passage you read
whether recently or a long time ago you could connect the two and say wow yeah yeah yeah and you
the folks this is what we have I've been learning through this last few decades is that very fact that
as we start to develop our scientific understanding of the world around us we consistently find
platforms within these ancient scripts that are describing the exact same thing you can look at
the Tao of physics and how all of physics was somewhat described in the Hindu belief system then
you when you get into that you're into shamanas and and and flying off the planet and Ezekiel and
you know the descriptions finally meet the the science that we now understand now I had no idea
that space smelled like acrid death and and burning bodies and how would you yeah exactly just like
I don't know whether the earth is flat or out you know well it has to be communicated again you know
can mean knowledge is communication communication is the meaning of words and letters and stringing
them together just like code on a computer and what you do with it is up to you the user now there's
nothing you could really do about knowing that say having two accounts one ancient one modern
the and actually would be from the Greek and Freeman right now that space smells like burning flesh
what can you do with that in your in your lives not much but it leads you into as efficiency when you
do watch the YouTube after this thing lands and you see the guys with the hazmat suits pumping air out
you'll be the only guy in the room that's going to annoy everyone saying they're doing that because
space smells like burning flesh and they want to just clean it up and then they'll say what
right yeah yeah and it makes complete sense you know I've never thought about the smell of space I've
never thought about that oh no if you do a lot of thinking you know you'll get in trouble so
well yeah try to be a lawyer and practice law right right right you'll you'll be a use car dealer
in no time but but here's the thing about this this is something that is just beyond thinking it's
based on good communication are you taking in what can be taken in and I figured we'd bring this
up you brought up the the craft and I said well by the way do you remember the decontamination and here
we are now conveying and imparting let's say a minor but major detail right and I think that
hopefully the the listenership will walk at least even just from that walk away and say wow
it doesn't help me be more efficient or whatever through my life but the next time I see that I know
why they're doing it and it's just piece by piece this is how we figure things out exactly and you
won't even remember then well where you picked that up yeah I know that's from somewhere yeah the
little red flashy thing on the screen yeah now I have brought up just to clarify for the audience
in these two hours I brought up a mastima and I brought up a mastaba so I think I just real
quickly will define these two things for everybody so they don't get confused about you know
thinking Satan is connected to Obama's presidential center okay so a mastima M.A.S.T.E.M.A. is the
adversary within the Bible in the ancient Hebrew mysticism Satan was an emissary of God he was an
angel and there were multiple adversaries there was not a single Satan this was a later concept through
Christianity but in Hebrew an adversary a Satan was there as what mastima literally means is
stumbling block to stop you from making bad choices so that God would said a Satan and a mastima to
your path to try and direct you onto the right path so there was no red devil with horns in a
pitchfork at this time Satan the adversaries meant multitude were there as as emissaries of God
and then I also brought up the mastaba which is M.A.S.T.A. B.A. right and this is an ancient Egyptian
structure that archaeology or texts have zero knowledge of what they're built for and they're
massive buildings that sit in front of the main center you basically they're opening gates into
the city center and they don't know what they're built therefore they don't know their purpose their
big empty buildings and here we start to learn as we learn that space smells like like burning flesh
and we understand that there was a biblical equivalent to this we start to understand that there was
way much more going on in the ancient past than people are willing to accept and this is one of the
biggest biggest biggest things that we must take away from all the information that we've been
gathering is that there is cyclical events on planet earth and humans according to Michael Krammo
you know go back millions and millions of years and so we're seeing civilizations rise and fall
cyclical catastrophes that have been noted documented in keptin secrecy so that those in the know of
these cycles can can respond before these things occur and that's how they end up with the the
situation that we're in so I wanted to clarify the mastama and the mastaba to make sure that we
understand why I find it so funny that obama's presidential center is a massive unknown Egyptian
structure and then the mastama on the idea that we have a positive satanism in this puzzle until it
became this negative narrative and boy the narrative is everything folks yeah and also remember that
the the term satanism is not really used very well just like I think we did discuss it to a certain point
that this character or characters by the way are in this is their world at this time it's been
handed to them humanity is just like you know when before something industrial goes into manufacturing
they create a torture zone for it you know like cars or planes or whatever to put them artificially
through five years of wear and tear in a few weeks you know right these these beings are set up to
basically be a testament to the robustness of the human spirit if that makes any sense just like in
Job do what you will but don't kill them right right it's a torture test or a you know you've seen it
where they wash cars and you know wiper blades you know can they go for a million times and all
this stuff so this is what we're being put under there's nothing to fear about it but there is
many much to overcome yes I highly recommend folks that you go into the member sections growl down
to are you a satanist by Mark Pascio where we discussed the tenants of satanism and you will find
that you agree with most of them right and all the all the world's major religions and institutions
are under that authority and of course for them to present something malevolent it has to be
presented as good so when people talk to me about satanism I'm always like well which satanist because
we we use it as a catch all phrase you know are you talking about the baby eaters which I consider
our elite or are you talking about the church of satan you know which is is more of a charade you know
but there's many levels to it it's not checkers or tic tic toe it's a level of chess but the thing is
you always have to remember in chess you know the pawn can take a king right really rarely does because
people are not that asleep at the wheel or at the chess board but I'm telling you humanity right now
is asleep where their their kings are being taken by pawns constantly so all right speaking of which
the the kings and all that you know we're talking about the mid the coming middle east union and
of course what gets people's attention is nothing more than what's called money and you know how
many times that subject comes up and just like time well it doesn't exist it's just an illusion or
it's dead or anything like that that's that's kind of like not what we're going down we're trying
to be a little more rational and definitive and practical but I think we once brought up a
Freeman what money what money is and have you do you remember should we just recap I think this is
a members area so I think giving them more specifics is probably where it's at yes you know humankind
being agriculturally based and of course people will laugh you know a computer programmer says we're
not but go ahead and lock that joker up in a room with nothing agricultural not including the pants
that he's wearing and how is he going to do meaning he needs food and water and even the clothing is
agriculturally based even if it's petroleum it's a form of mining you see so because we are
agriculturally based on that respect a perfect society would be that let's say a level of
distribution where people live on the land and everything they need they get from the land food, water,
shelter, minerals you get the point it all comes from the earth you know now when it comes time to
traveling and doing barter you can't take the land with you it's not portable so what you do is you
take the absolute best from the land the most precious substance that has agreed on especially
lawfully as a representation so money especially as it was gold and silver is what portable land
think about that for a minute just just this is not for debate or argument this is just a contribution
to the rationale of what money is we're not talking about the system that's in place right now
talking about an old empirical thing you know like like anything it could be go down to its primary
level does that make sense that money in the add the tally stick and you know the methods I've shown
in but yes absolutely that makes complete sense because if you don't eat you die right and also
the gold and silver is mined and it's also extracted and it also represents you know the most precious
what you know aspect of what comes out of the earth so no matter how you slice it it's a money
is portable isn't it even even today well where it's virtual or based on credit it's there's an
essence of portability that is always considered to be you know the most convenient the more portable
the more virtual the more convenient you see all right so I bit coins up to eighteen hundred bucks
a piece sorry you know here's the thing whether it's Bitcoin the thing is is it lawful and lawful
has to be something that's referenceable and measurable a lot of people say well Greek what do you
mean by lawful means it's measurable right if you can't measure it it's not there I mean it's not
lawful and if you can't measure it guess what you can't manage it can you how can you manage
something that's not measurable you can measure exactly yeah so we're we're going down you know if
you start going into the world of the unlawful which the entire world is right now believe it or not
and if you don't believe it go look at the ingredients on a cereal box is that even resemble what
should be in there but you see yeah what's measurable about most of the food people eats is what
is what is on the ingredients is that sound palatable I would say no in most cases not all cases but
most now regarding the the money thing most people that are listening if not I should say well
most I'm presuming are under in a country that has a credit-based economy now how do I why do I
keep saying it's credit-based well because I'm just reading it off the treasury websites now any
treasury any government any financial institution talks about credit like if you go to a credit
rating agency or credit card company look at their contract and what it says is that we we can
report our credit experience with you it doesn't say we're going to report whether you paid for it or
not or didn't pay says our credit experience go read the contracts yeah it's very simple they're
telling you but you know I don't know what that means yeah well let's let's get into it what what
is credit mean you ever heard of years ago well I'm going to give you credit for it Freeman yeah yeah
that would mean that I did something good yeah it means you did something good or basically if
you're seeking some form of gain it's due to you right right yeah okay you you're owed credit for
that that's why in college they give you credits right you know there's nothing there or the little
you get a gold star or something it's just basically a feeling of perception of belief the core
belief of most of the credit system is that when you are born and you are given a credit line meaning
it's measurable you know like the social security number that you have is different than the guy next
you it's measurably different right right so in that sense it's lawful but the way it's being used
and touted as money is not lawful now I think on the first hour I did mention this is almost like the
Star Trek future remember when they brought someone from the past and said what do you guys use for
money and they explain to them we don't use money anymore because everyone is in agreement that
they have to do things and we don't need it okay this was actually this reality was really put in
place in America in the 30s but look at the the mindset of humanity whether it doesn't matter
where you are whether it's Russia America Columbia you know anywhere you get the picture Japan that
the people just don't want to grasp this kind of radical paradigm shift because before the credit
system was put in and you had substance-based money you had to do you had to buy things with gold
or silver or a note that represented that you get it and now doing a paradigm shift like that
was too shocking so they said why don't we put the the law merchants or the attorneys in charge of
it we beef up their paramilitary society known as the police because that they're paramilitary
and to make sure that everything and everyone is held in line and we'll keep the plausible
deniability going that if you borrow you have to pay back and if there's a debt you have to pay it
or you're in trouble kind of thing right right or or you have to put up collateral so
they're still keeping this plausible deniability up which you will also see with every field right
any field you look at right now it's based on plausible deniability with something someone
came up that they are propping up and enforcing as the norm which is false so before getting into more
of this you know most you have some international listeners I'm sure I shouldn't say I'm sure but I'm
presuming that there are people that not only that are in America and Freeman if you would pull up
that law it's an American law is USC 12 United States Code Title 12 section 411 and read it it's
very simple and the reason I brought up the foreign listeners is because they have similar
codes in every country you see right would you be able to read it I think it'll have without it out
if it'll have like 70% more punch if you read it because if I read it it's just the Greek being
pedantic but if you let me share this yeah please remedy of law for federal reserve notes so
US Code 12-411 which is interesting in getting the information right and also the 12 doing
to anyway getting all less so tarot on you issuance to reserve banks the nature of obligation redemption
okay so here we go folks US Code 12 federal reserve notes to be issued at the discretion of the board
of governors of the federal reserve system for the purpose of making advances to the federal reserve
banks through the federal reserve agents as here and after set forth and for no other purpose
are authorized all right stop yeah stop it basically in short it's still very simple but it's
basically there are private notes internal currency between banks that can be moved around only
by bank agents or federal reserve agents and then it says no other uses authorized now do I need
someone to interpret what no other use is authorized means do you know okay and we're looking at this
kind of like the poker chips at the casino right where it's basically an internal system yes
and only for the federal reserve banks through federal reserve agents and you're out it's beyond
the poker chip system because imagine the poker chip system only being by casino employees and
not the patrons right right right in other words imagine going as a patron to a casino and they
hit you over the head because you have a casino chip which should only be held by the employee it
would be like going as a patron to the casino and grabbing a uniform and a name tag that you work
for the casino and you don't right that's the import of this well now I'm really confused
great I mean if I'm not authorized to use my federal notes then what am I doing you
I'm not just you're participating and now what what do you call something in your possession
that you're not supposed to have is it called contraband yes right have you ever heard of people
getting cash seized by the authorities before for sure and why do they always tell you that it's
drug money if you have a large amount of cash they presume that across the board because they're
not going to sit there and explain it to the people because drugs are supposedly contraband also
so they just throw it lump it into the contraband right so that large stack of cash is contraband wow
that's right because you're not supposed to use it now now keep reading because sometimes people
will read this and they're going to run into someone in the legal society which is going to try
to twist it around and keep keep reading and I might have you pause and stop but go go ahead please
yeah sure absolutely okay so for no other purpose or authorized was last of that said just say
you know okay so the said note shall be obligations of the united states and shall be receivable by all
national and member banks and federal reserve banks and for all taxes customs and other public
dues all right stop now on the surface that looks like oh it seems like we can use it for customs
and public dues and taxes right it's on surface but no yes and no yes meaning it can be used for
customs public dues and taxes but by who the federal reserve agents only again you get it
don't get twisted or wrapped around the axle on this you ever ride a bicycle with your shoelaces
untied so don't let this happen to you here because an attorney will try to twist that in saying
see where you could pay you can't it's only again remember if you take that first sentence yeah
yeah if you take the first sentence and apply it to the second just because it sounds different
does it mean the first sentence is washed away exactly so continue okay so I you know the said
notes shall be obligations of the united states yeah that's a very interesting statement right on
its own yes because you don't need money because it's a credit-based economy you're just supposed
to sign your name and use the credit line the number that was given to you right the social
security number to buy anything you need food clothing and shelter it's considered public funds by
the way and if you have a note that you're using that's a bank note a private bank note you're using
it as an extra because you don't really need that and what it really represents is that it's a debt
from the united states and we're going to get into once we let's go okay one more sentence and
I'll tell you how they got into that pickle real quick all right so the last sentence of this
code folks and I just know you know it's three sentences right the us code of 12
4.11 yeah is three sentences that outlines your money and the lawful use of it they shall be
redeemed in lawful money on demand at the treasury department of the united states in the city of
Washington district of Columbia or any federal reserve bank right now what does that mean you
you have that bill you know people say here's a bill a dollar bill ten dollar bill five you know
what I asked people I said who's going to pay that bill right right right right right all right
20 dollar bill and they call them bills yeah who's going to pay that bill well it just tells you
the united states is going to pay it's you're supposed to take those notes with the dead presidents
on there and bring them to the bank to get lawful money now if you try doing that they're going to
ignore you or arrest you or think you're mad remember first hour we're talking about the drinking of
the water that made you crazy yeah so so at this point here maybe we'll talk about what you would
be like if you saved your own water right let's just go back yeah so so what's interesting here as
the best they can do and this is not advice or whatever I could just speak from experience it from
others that when you always ask for lawful money you make a little note on any financial transaction
or whatever you no longer have a tax liability now not saying you cannot volunteer into one or have
one but they it cannot be imposed on you as such because you're how are you going to pay taxes or
anything with money you're not supposed to be using now let me just retract what I just said to
a degree what they call taxes not one penny of taxes collected in the past oh half century has even
paid for a stick of bubble gum or a sign on a politician's door it is under what's called economic
theory and contract law now obviously the water that people are drinking have made everyone insane so
the people that are enforcing this are insane to a certain degree just as those that are using it
are insane meaning the whole world has gone crazy this is a very dangerous path to go down but the
reason we're bringing it up now is because it's rational it's easily comprehended and just like the
smell of burning flesh and space how can you use it well I don't know that's up to you but at least
now you know you see right and if you're if you're well skilled and you want to achieve
master'ship you can go to the next level with it of course but I just want to mention here this
code is written on an eighth grade level which is unlike a lot of legal ease and it also explains a lot
why cash is viewed as a bad thing now let me just get into a little technical aspect before I get
into a little history which is important is that you notice how there are serial numbers on the
cash and on and on transactions and on checks you have noticed that Freeman there are serial numbers
on there oh without that yeah whenever you look for a serial number that's for record purposes only
you ever buy a toaster or blow dryer or a TV and on the warranty card it tells you to put the serial
number yeah warranty it right the serial number is a is it identifier well what I would suggest this is
what's been done and also IRS offices do this by the way when you bring them cash is they keep what's
they do what's called competent record keeping where every time you get a note you have a little book
or however ledger could be done electronically you could scan it where you write the the bill the
the nomination and the serial number and you file it away because all those numbers that you're
accruing are at the end of the year you supposed to send it to the treasury to get lawful money for
it well the serial numbers and all that and that's why if you go to a government office where they
tell you we don't accept cash if you push the issue what they do let's say you give them 150 and
notes 350s they pull out a ledger and they write down on each line well 150 note this is the serial
number another 50 note that's the serial number and I once asked one of the clerks at the office that
did I said if you don't do this you've just created a tax liability for this office as she looked at
me and almost dropped dead she was like how do you know that well I read 12 section title 12 section
411 now title 12 section 401 doesn't tell you to keep competent records and serial numbers in
that but that is the only other reason you start piecing together in Sherlock Holmes fashion what's
going on here to be clear because the federal reserve notes are not lawful money for them to use they
have to then create something else out of it well no what they do is they keep a record that they
came across one with someone intending to use it but they no one can use it so once you have the
record of all of them you go to the treasury to get real money and they can't give you real money
so the whole thing kind of controversy kind of goes away doesn't it yeah so so the the other aspect is
are you going to get lawful money no you're not because you're kind of this is a cosmic joke on
humanity by the way you know but I just want to look we're going to revisit this again and I'm going
to give some more practical examples but can we get into the history of how the US was bankrupted
in simple without the crazy patriot mysticism and all that stuff that you hear online I think that
would be helpful yes okay how you got into receivership what happened was the US was had lawful
money gold and silver back currency basically silver back currency and of course you know since the
time of jackson you know they had the original bank and then it went to a private bank and then
they got rid of it and then they try to bring it back with a federal reserve and by the way there's
a book about some island creature or whatever and that that's that's not what I'm talking about yes
I don't want to say anything bad about it but it's not there's nothing good I can't say it's
wrong but it sure ain't right what you're reading there okay now this is very simple uh
enough you look into the history because there's a lot of this stuff out there now I'm not going to say
these people are shills or putting out misinformation but they're definitely putting out misinformation
because disinformation can only be put out by the one who knows it's wrong and is doing it deliberately
to twist everything the misinformation is those that are innocently doing it they just fell for it
you see right is it disinformed is different than a misinformer or disinformed or is you know you can only
if you're subject to a disinformer you're going to be misinformed it doesn't make it that's not
good say yeah exactly yeah those that are subject to the disinformer become the misinform but I
can very much speculate that everyone that's producing right now anything about the economic
economy out there on your internet fringe level or mainstream whatever is subject to misinformation
right I'm not going to point a finger who's the disinformed because really I don't know
who and it doesn't matter at this point just give it to a straight great yeah so straight what's
going on is the the the American government let's say the US government and other governments got
into contracts with the private banks to produce their notes and their money at a rate of 6%
you get it the interest it doesn't sound too low it should be less but it doesn't sound too
less and sound too high right 6% so what happened was the the government started giving all of their
substance you know contracts title gold silver to the private bankers and when they brought it in
they inventory it and printed notes in return but once the government gave everything of value to
the private bankers and they converted it all to notes well guess what they still owed the 6%
didn't they so how are they going to pay the 6% to the bankers when they already took everything so
the bankers came back and put them in bankruptcy for the interest that was owed simple is this I
mean this can be understood like 12 year old you know eight year old can understand this right very
simple we have an agreement at 6% we'll print all your money we've gotten everything from you to
turn it into printable money and now you still owe us a 6% how are you going to pay we are out of
money to pay you now well what happens when any organization is completely out of money and has
no chance of getting anymore they become what bankrupted bankrupt now should they have been now in
bankruptcy you have a choice either a completely liquidate and dissolve it no longer exists or if
it's a useful fixture in society you put it in receivership you keep keep it going so what do you
think they did with the u.s. government did they liquidate it and disappear it or did they say let's
keep it around because it could be useful and put it in receivership the latter yes and this is why
America still stands yes otherwise you wouldn't have you would have gone into whatever futile
city state war lord stuff right you know right that wouldn't be allowed to happen because the
temples that are in Washington DC needed they didn't want to tear those down and by the way when
you look at those buildings go look at the Lincoln Memorial what's inscripted it's what it's a temple
that says it right there are you familiar with the inscription in this temple is those are considered
temples in architecture it's not because I say so it's not a theory it's actually inscribed on the
building this is a temple are you familiar with that so you know that about Lincoln but yeah I am
very and you know every time they put out the high terrorist alerts and they're worried about
Mount Rushmore or the Washington monument or you know I'm always thinking how are these even worry
some objects you know what about the people the cities you know it's always these national monuments
which are temples oh yeah they are they are temples here I'm going to do just we're kind of maybe
going for time or here but for time I'm just going to open this Lincoln Memorial inscription stock
photos if you can go to that I can just drop it in and maybe have you read it real quick this is on
the Lincoln Memorial this is just to not being pedantic but just just I think it has about 70% more
kick-freeman when you read it I just dropped the Lincoln right there would you read that if you can
open it this is the Lincoln Memorial all right give me just a second here as we I anyone can search
Lincoln Memorial inscription right this is what you will read what does it say in this temple thank you
first words right it's all centered so that every day that is and is sure enshrined forever
right so in this temple as in the hearts of the people for whom he saved the union the memory of
Abraham Lincoln is enshrined forever so yes very first thing you see in this temple and then you
will find that in all of their building not all of their buildings but enough to say to walk away that
you saw a bunch of temples there today yes so so are we I know I know when you're too informative
you sound pedantic like your election but I want to distress the high weirdness of this stuff right
so that's how you're going to remember it you know real memory comes in how it affects your heart
like if you get really good news it affects the heart if you get really bad news it affects the heart
that's why you remember things it affects the heart trivial stuff it's in the mind you forget you see
yeah that's why yeah yeah so it's the heart that that is being directed and misdirected in this case
in every case I should say let's just continue now we we kind of brought up the code that let's say
legally and lawfully proves that we shouldn't you know society shouldn't be using those notes right so
if you ever wonder they're fighting against cash you know is there a debate over who this should
there be cash or not no because the law clearly says it's illegal you see so but what are we to do
well it shows you what kind of a pickle you're in and I don't mean that literally because you're not
really inside of a pickle but you're in a bind and you're not really in a bind there's nothing tying
you down but you are been dictive directed down a path of utter and complete ignorance lawfully and
legal about the leak what's really going on is the purpose of showing this ultimately right right
so so so let's we spoke about the law that shows that we're not authorized to use that we also showed
very quickly and basically how the US got into this condition and let's just go to the future
very quickly you're going to get out of it no you're not because there's no demand for it change right
that's why have you heard of Ron Paul discussing audit the Fed why why because all of the followers of
Ron Paul are fully endorsing the Fed how many followers of Ron Paul or himself came out and said we're
not supposed to be using the Federal Reserve notes at all how many zero right and himself also so
the whole thing is a show the whole thing is a show but this is not about the show this is about
what's going on behind not just the curtain but the guts inside the wizard really is what we're talking
about so let's say now so we've got the history we've got the code in front of us now what is one to do
well there's not much you can do about it but now that you know about it what is this whole thing
based on well obviously it's credit it's based on faith now well it's a really bad religion because
a lot of people are being hurt by it if you know what I mean yeah right now the other thing is there's
a couple of people about they're talking about respa and ftcpa which is federal trade and consumer
protection acts and all they basically said if anyone says you owe them money all you have to do is
deny it well you just say they have to validate it not verify and there's quite a few people there's
a group call I think what lies in your debt I don't want to sort of promote I don't know if
they're still around but only did was say if anyone says you owe them money doesn't matter who they are
forget about how much is it whatever it's like prove it and the only way they can prove it is
whether a sworn affidavit no one's gonna swear to them that you owe them anything in a credit
based economy so that these guys have had quite a bit of success but the thing is people don't contact
myself I might even speak for freeman on how you can get stuff for quote unquote free because there's
no such thing because ultimately free is that an acronym standing for from revenue emanated elsewhere
I'm just putting that out think about it it's all credit now the purpose of the credit system is
that you have a jurisdiction which is also a spiritual one when you see maps geographical
political maps it's just not people spring ink at the printing press there's a spirit behind that
and every country has a matron or patron deity in the world right now it tends to be the goddess
religion and I'm gonna bring this back when you live in a certain jurisdiction like we were talking
about making good citizens that's defining a certain political subdivision or political group by
border and culture right so what what the credit system is based on is that anyone participating in
that system is in agreement that they've donated their body their labor their mind and all their
possessions and their children to make the system work right very simple the full faith and credit
of the United States is what they're talking about but at the same time what the nefarious act here is
of what they've put out for you to use has been deemed contraband now if that's not crazy I don't
know what is now you want to get into really high weirdness now okay when you and let's just do what
I call slave talk oh well go over it again and how the banking really works on a practical level
because most people say I don't understand this and because they've decided they don't want to
understand it how many times if you brought up math and people say well I'm not good at math well since
when did you decide that because people watch other people in the pranking and they're growing up
and they're like oh auntie says she's not good at math and she's getting away with it so I'll go I'll
spend my life saying that that's this is the deep rooted spiritual side of things children copy
so you want to keep people that are if you have children keep the people away that say well I'm
not good at this and that's all because then the children learn that bad behavior right you see
what I mean the how many times you have people say I don't I don't understand I'm not into scientific
stuff I'm not into math I'm not into finance you know what that's a crop a crop a crop a crop of
crap folks that's a cop out the spiritual cop out now that doesn't mean that you don't that these
things work against you as such because you deemed that you don't like it but they're things you can
work and exercise and get better at just like if you're not good at playing golf or tennis you can take
lessons and you may not be a pro at it but you'll be better than if you didn't try to exercise a
discipline in it so I just want to preface this simple story of how the money system really works
and you're ready Freeman we're going to do some slave talk here and just to illustrate to the
listener what their banks are doing bring it on okay now Freeman I write a check from my bank I'm
using slave talk now I take out the book I write a check to Freeman a hundred dollars paid
of the order of and and I put it in an envelope and I send it to you in the mail you get to the mailbox
and you see all the Greeks sent me a hundred dollars and you take the envelope and you go to the
bank you open the envelope and you hand it to the clerk she looks at it all puzzled and she
hands it back to you and says I can't use it why oh you need to sign the back right okay so now you
endorse the back and she you hand it back to the clerk and now she can use it well okay it wasn't
good before no it wasn't good before because you need two signatures on an instrument to make it
valid how do how can we show this otherwise take out a bill one five ten twenty or a note from
anywhere typically you will see two signatures on it right okay so so now we're going down to show
how this thing is formed we're not going to explain all of it but it's a witnessing thing okay
so now you hand the check that you signed the back of to the clerk and she's at the monitor
before they say you used ledgers and she pulls up the only thing that banks have in their inventory
which is transaction numbers so the next transaction number shows up and she starts filling in the details
Freeman and all of a sudden a hundred dollars is created from those two signatures based on the
credit system that we all agree on and debited to your account or actually credited to your account
and you get a receipt that you now have a hundred dollars where you didn't before in the account
you with me so far yes now if i were to really quick quickly check the account that i have especially
in the old days before they had the digital stuff they like i see the hundred dollars is still there
so they didn't really send it over to you just like they couldn't email a tuna fish sandwich
right right it just doesn't happen that's why when you hear people today's that i'm waiting for
money to be wired i mean you're you're waiting to you i mean you're you're being played they're just
playing with you okay so go back to the story now my bank now your bank now that you've got the
the hundred dollars in all the sudden sees that my bank that because the information is there
and they immediately notify or not so immediately notify my bank that this transaction has taken place
so my bank now is like hmm we need to keep plausible deniability up with the Greek because
if Freeman calls him up and says he just got the hundred dollars and the Greek checks the balance
and sees that he still has the hundred dollars we got a little bit of a problem so we need to rapidly
take the money out of the Greek's account so he's under the plausible deniability the plausibility
that it got transferred to Freeman you see so what the bank what the my bank then does is
takes the hundred dollars out of the account that i see and puts it in the comptroller section of the
bank under my name let's say the Greek and stores it there for a few days and under the
paperwork reduction act i think of after 30 days it can be declared as abandoned so they file
certain paperwork let's say at 1099 a is an example on that hundred dollars that it's been abandoned
just like you file an abandoned been paperwork for an abandoned car or funds or anything you
you folks can get the picture very easily now after it's been abandoned because obviously i'm not
doing anything with it then they file paperwork to claim it and now the bank takes it from you legally
and the whole time it was just sitting there it there was no reason for it to be taken out because it
wasn't transferred over to Freeman you see so this has been going on for years and years and years
and no one is noticing so when you start hearing oh the federal reserve all this and that oh wow
wow wow no it's the little branch office the way they work is how they're operating now i want to ask
so if you were to able to file claim on the abandonment before the bank does yes can you just
keep spending that money the well the thing is what happens is what you're supposed to do legally
is uh uh what to a certain degree is yeah claim it once it goes into abandonment or before it goes
into abandonment or if it goes into abandonment then counter that with a claim and take it back out
deposit spend it and then claim it again and so you just need let's say 10,000 bucks or a thousand bucks
for your whole life every time you spend it you put it back in and recycle it right because because
the whenever you're writing a checker using a card nothing is being transferred out of your account
to them it's being created on the other side in real time okay so the form you would need to claim
this abandonment and then what would happen to you okay what happens to you when you try to do this
is they send you a letter saying that there are certain consumer laws because we are a retail level
we could refuse service to you goodbye oh okay so the bank just just says all right uh you figured out
the game so you can't play anymore right and if you do this enough you try to open a bank out some
of them they'll have you sit there for hours and not tell you why you're black called yeah not because
what you're doing is wrong because what you're doing is right right makes sense so a lot of people
say to me am I doing this is this wrong Greek and I'm like well I don't know about it being long but
I'll tell you for sure it ain't right right right now I still can't figure out how to come about
lawful money I mean it just doesn't exist it's gone no anything is there was a story years ago about
a guy at a hockey game one of these Patriot types and Buffalo or something he tried to pay for a hot dog
in a beer with a silver coin yeah and he didn't they didn't know what to do with it so they called the
treasury and they arrested him for that so oh wow yeah yeah this is a sci-fi planet now yeah at the
free-your-mind conference people were trying to pay for their hotel with cash and they were not
allowed to stay there that's different yeah we're talking about silver now lawful money but cash is
not lawful money by far what it really what cash really is it's when you take a dollar bill or
five bill or ten bill hold it up with the president's side folded in half the left half is the front
the right half is the back you have the issuing signature on the front and the endorsement signature
on the back you know left and right of the president don't think of the front of the bill in the
back of the bill those are two separate pages stuck together right the front is both front and
back where the president is the left side shows you the issuing signature in the account or the
evidence of some account to issue and the rear the back of it the right is the account is repeated
we know the account is closed and it's endorsed so when you hold a bill of one five ten twenty or
from anywhere in the world what that represents legally is a canceled check on the closed account
about it this is insanity now if you try to pass a cancel check on a closed account at a store they're
going to call the authorities how come they're not calling the authorities with this because they
are under a spell right they all believe in the system that they've been taught into believe as
we were saying in the beginning of this and then we can't really see the future yes you can but
but carry that belief forward but that would be to try to substantiate what that belief is based
on and you're going to see it's something very negative I just showed you the law the code which
shows if you read title 12 section 401 do you walk away with a good feeling or a bad feeling because
you have federal reserve notes the pretty bad feeling don't you yeah and be using them contraband
that's why for example when these truckers get stopped with cash you know when people get pulled
over by an authoritative figure they usually ask for ID lives since registration insurance all that
when they find the cash they walk away and they come back and they ask you for ID all over again
as if nothing happened like you're my in the twilight zone I gave it to you raise it well
let me see your ID again and why because now they know they have to produce a federal reserve agent
ID and how many of them do none right right so the person the trucker with all that cash needs to be
a federal reserve agent to own it so now he's being charged with contraband so they're coming back
to reintroduce reintroduce the topic and see if he'll produce the proper credentials for owning
unlawful money holding right right right you can't own it right yeah so now you know what what you
that's why you'll notice before cash is taken they go through these weird steps it's like this is
we just did this already why are you doing it again now the people that are enforcing this the guy
the beat on the street or whatever they don't know what's going on they're just called a legal
department you know and even the guys in legal department don't know what they're going on
it's going on either because they're subject to the same thing yeah and like we said earlier if
you're a lawyer practicing actual law you'd be disbard you mean selling selling car used automobiles
yeah and I'm not joking about that I've heard of several attorneys that have been disbard and
they always end up as selling cars either user knew right there's something mystical about that I
don't know but but yeah so this is an interesting part now one way to do it like for example you know
you walk you talk and talk you walk let's just say personally what I do whenever I do commerce
with a note let's say they ring up you know 26 dollars and 11 cents well I'll pull out a 20 a 5
into one and I'll say here's some coin the dime in the penny and I'll say here are three notes I hope
you get money for it someday I never acknowledge it it's a 20 I never acknowledge it's a five or
a one because it's a 26 11 let's say so I'll give them the 20 the five in the one I'll say here are
three notes I hope you get money for it someday and they're like you know what the best is go to a bank
and give them a check and say I'd like to exchange these for federal reserve notes and the clerk gets
nervous like I don't know what that is I'll be right back and she goes in the back and says this guy
wants federal reserve notes for this check and the manager comes back with a stern face no eye contact
counts all the money out and then reams out the clerk tells him take the rest of the day off because
the clerk is sitting there counting these for decades and they don't even know what they are right
because they're remember we talked about the cosmic censorship earlier how the information is
sealed and you bring it to someone who can read and they say well it's sealed I can't read it but then
you bring it to someone who's illiterate and they say it doesn't matter if it's sealed or not because
I'm illiterate and then you bring it to the blind and it doesn't matter what's written because
they're blind so you have three levels that infirmate you see right so right now the majority of
the planet is blind and or illiterate and you don't have a chance because they're all drinking the
water remember the Persian and meanwhile they're just saying well I'm not good at math right so
basically all goes down to food clothing and shelter now personally I played around with this a
little bit without any success and I understand why because you ever hear people say fight for your
rights and all that I said well it or stand up for your rights you've heard of that right
what's okay to stand up for your rights but they're fixing on cracking heads and arresting people
might be good to stay seated for that day I completely agree with you there it's all in our minds it's
all in the narrative it's all in the spell and you need to you know walk away we need to find our day
dream and start to understand where we want to go and to bring in a little bit of high strangeness
we brought in star-track money and we're winding up this hour now Greek so okay we brought up the idea
of star-track money and how they had you know a system that just supplied everything for everyone
they're like we don't have cash anymore that's old school Gene Roddenberry actually is
reputed to have been involved in communication with the extraterrestrial source known as the nine
and they used Erie Geller as one of the psychics to channel the nine and Gene Roddenberry happened
to be one of the people that was that sat in on these say-ons as if you will excuse me
and you know then came forward with with whole new lines to star-track this was after star-track
creation but then you'll see in things like generations where the story of the nine starts to really
come and play a more so there's one just high strangeness with money star-track money and
extraterrestrial source is living in acrid death smelling burning body space and then another one
I wanted to recommend even as strange as it is and I swear guys I think the creators of South Park
really listen to the free zone I they cover so much that I used to and I believe it's true and I've
heard it's true but the episode Pinebox Derby which starts with a particle from CERN gets into
the idea of money and space money and these aliens come down and they give all the space money
and next thing you know Mexico's got water parks everywhere and they're all just using the space
money but I don't want to ruin the end for you but it ends in a cube so definitely check out Pinebox
Derby on South Park I can't believe I recommend South Park now but it's true man and then the ideas
that we really do have this weird extraterrestrial say on type connection to our temples that are
there and and this is where the spell of money comes from and then the rest is the narrative
and the narrative is what we believe and don't believe and what we're willing to learn and not
learn and whether we see that scroll sealed blind or otherwise so yeah final statements Greg oh man I
don't know there's there's the final statement is every statement basically because you can take
anything we've discussed and spin off and spend the rest of your life studying it the only thing I'd
say is I appreciate you for having me again on the another sonic event and I really appreciate the
listeners I'm saying this objectively I'm sending you guys flowers maybe that you have given me a
little bit more hope meaning the listeners that there are people out there that are really
objective discerning and more than just intelligent but are perceptive and it's given me a little bit
more of let's say a breath of fresh air that when I get emails and comments that are just really on
point and I ask them where did they find out about the Greek they said on Freeman I'm like this is
just too uncanny why is it that anyone and everyone that is making sense is coming from Freeman so
I just want to thank the audience yeah and this is the truth folks so thank you guys and thank you
for having me on and also uncommon radio www.uncommonradio you'll just it's just a courtesy site where you have
over a hundred hours of of archives and bring your popcorn and bring your aspirin because you're
going to be entertained and you're going to get a headache and of course yeah there'll be more to
come and thank you for plugging in there's probably going to be a pod bean in the future it'll be
more and more information and experiences and things like that that will hopefully be helpful
because if we're not helping people and remember folks when people talk about problems in the world
if if if just half the people in the world helped one person that takes care of the other half
doesn't it absolutely without a doubt folks be bold and mighty forces will come to your aid
and help you to quit your job and save the world it's all in our say say don't say save the world sorry
I'm just saying as a foot okay go ahead now you've got now you could say it but you're going to get
the benevolent and the malevolent forces against you because the malevolent forces never wanted
the world to be saved during a better place but the benevolent forces are now coming to a time where
they're going to come down here and mop up just like you ever see a mop someone mopping up there
like don't stand here be careful it's slippery so so either way you can do all the things that
require to make everything better but don't say that you're doing it for that reason I'm just
okay this is maybe a satiric advice but you could do it but don't say you're doing it save the world
because now you're voiced and witnessed that you're going to have all the cosmic forces against you
I just I know this is controversial yeah I got you I got you it's all in the in the terminology folks
it really is it's funny because I didn't even think of because you know world like God has so many
different meanings inside of our minds and when I say it the world is the narrative that's going
along inside of our minds and I want you to recognize that you can be driven by a beneficial
force that is unknown to us that we call God that we call whatever that you don't even need a
name for that because you'll experience it and so when I say to save the world from my mind it is
saying to save the narrative to rewrite the narrative into a human structure into a a a
a beautific structure that we all know that we all see in perfection yeah keep in mind the good
advice is this is not doom and gloom and this will be understood better later within the 15 years
that are as left with as you things as you know it a lot of parents yes this is sober people this is
not the new age types of love and light and all that stuff because remember most of the love and
light that's in the world today is really malevolent because they have to package it as such
or ignorant or whatever but the practical reasoning behind it is a lot of parents come to me and say
Greek I have a two-year-old which should I do very simple add 15 to two that gives them a life
span of 17 what would you do different in your life if you knew you're only going to live to 17
doesn't mean that that child has to do that but boy you wouldn't go to school would you you'd have
more fun wouldn't you wouldn't you be more daring wouldn't you exactly some people say well what if
nothing that this doesn't happen in 17 years or 15 years well still fine because now you have a very
unique individual but you have to be careful because you're on the planet of the insane and I'll
bring up maybe as a closing comment here the words of goita which I thought I came up with this on my
own but someone pointed out he had said this 300 years ago is that you need not visit an insane
asylum to meet disordered spirits for the earth is the insane asylum of the universe so be very very
careful and just that's why I always encourage people if they have visitors date an insane asylum
you know where they let the the ones that are safe let's say out and people friends and family
come to visit there's always a group of them that don't have any visitors and just sit down and talk
to someone there and within the first few minutes you'll be like this person seems totally fine I
don't know why they're in here and then within the next minute you're like okay I know why you're
in I got it and this is what happens when you go out in public everyone seems fairly normal but
you start discussing things that we even barely discussed here and you will see how insane the
world is like like the Persian parable so again if this is the end of the hour I just want to thank
you Freeman and especially listenership for showing me the better side of humanity thank you so
much yeah that really really means a lot because that is our goal and guys I got some great shows they're
going to follow this up just perfectly we got Tim Freak coming your way check him out and Jimmy
Church oh yeah straight from coast to coast coming to give you the dark side the things that he can't
talk about while hosting coast to coast he's coming on the free zone and giving us the dark and dirty
on space so we're gonna get deeper into that we're gonna get into Tim Freak and we're gonna understand
more and more about this consciousness that we're dealing with in the evolution of imagination I
can't wait it's gonna be awesome so looking for the spirituality in the 21st century and what I'm
finding right now as my computer is telling me I am about to run out of hard drive space okay so I
guess I need to wrap this up and clean some stuff off of this Mac you know I've had this Macintosh
I bought this thing at Occupy Wall Street at a Starbucks while everybody else was out protesting
in Wall Street I was in a Starbucks buying this Macintosh and I have had this thing I bought it used
in 2012 and this is all I got folks because I have never made money at this show ever and you know
I'm only now starting to accrue a sense of stability thanks to you and feeling like I have got a platform
to stand on because I've been running on a treadmill this whole time and nine years running and so just
let you know I'm still working on this this thing's older than 2012 and that's that's how this is
of my system goes folks so thank you for allowing me to to start to maybe up my game a little bit
because I'm telling you guys this has been grass roots as grass roots as you can get thank god this
computer was under warranty when I bought it because I bought it off somebody ripped me off so anyway
I better sign off here because it's gonna shut down on me thank you so much get over to
uncommon radio dot com and check out all the works from the Greek because there's so much that is
necessary we only get to skim the surface here so that you guys can know where to dig deeper and I
love this information that you're bringing great because it's you know it's it's it rings true there
you go my into it of intuitive hearts is this rings true and remember love is doing the right thing we
didn't we don't feel like doing it so wouldn't feel like doing it so that's I would say a suggestion of
wow it's not enough to take feelings I appreciate that thank you all right all right great
words then don't thank you guys we will see you next week with more and more great stuff
yeah
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]