All right, so it looks like we're recording and today let's say it's what they call a Sunday
the 21st of January, 2024 on the Pope's work schedule and you recognize the voice as
the Greek and whoever is here is here and whoever will hear it later or will hear it later.
This is the inertial domain group.
The reason we call it the inertial domain group is one of the aspects of water treatment
that we're going to be discussing and I put out a call or notice of something like a sonar
because I wanted to do it for several reasons to catch up with everyone, what I've been doing,
what the state of affairs is and what your interest and how your interest could be used in
it, right?
And if you're here you're probably interested and you'll find out if by listening as time
goes on whether you want to be interested or not.
So let's just say I'm going to do this backwards, the questions first, if whoever is here,
if anyone want to ask a question just chime in, just go ahead, raise your voice, unmute
or whatever and before we start let's see if there's anything anyone wants to know.
Okay.
Lots of crooked noise there.
That's fine.
No, I'm used to it.
Am I hurt?
Yes, you're hurt?
Go ahead.
Okay.
The planetary bodies, earth, Jupiter, etc.
You discuss earth being ascentiate being these large creations being beings and last time I
heard you and Chuck discuss gods if you will, Elohim or humanoids.
Yeah.
So what am I trying to ask is Jupiter or these large heavenly bodies?
I don't know how to finish the question.
I'll finish the question.
Are they gods or humans?
They're human, right?
That's a simple like if the if the apple is red and the car is red, the apple must be
a car, right?
Because they're both red.
No.
What's going on is we're living in a state of confusion.
So if your mind could physically go back more than two weeks or memory and remember something,
it's going to be 10% foggy, 10% confusion and another 10%.
Should I ask this question?
That's just a human condition.
That's just how it might sound like a total asshole by saying that.
But that's just the way we are.
So the question you brought up is also in a modern context that anything we hear about, even
for me, the Greek in a modern context is still tainted by the society that we live in.
The type of society we live in.
And what I mean by tainted is that we were brought up now for more than 150 years that the
ancients were ignorance.
And we're the only ones that are smart, the current people, right?
So we're coming from a tainted point of view.
We have a flawed human perception of things.
So all of these things come together.
Now when I say that gods were human, it's because they all have human traits in the text
that they give us unmistakably, right?
And the planets who knows what's up there, who knows and how it's up there.
I've been looking at the planets and all this stuff for very deeply since the 1980s.
I kind of laid off the past decade or two.
But what I found out from old books and things like that is that no one is in agreement to
how many planets there are, how big they are, how far away they are, right?
And all the stuff they put out to the public about how big Jupiter is, how far it is, none
of it's substantiated, none of it, none of it at all.
So where do we go with this kind of stuff?
Well, we know what we know, which is not a lot, and we have to be happy with it until time
goes on and something else, be some knowledge breaks forward.
And I'm happy with that.
But thanks for the question, anything else?
Yeah, somebody joined with a slightly noisy mic and was just saying, check, check a few
minutes ago or a few maybe a minute ago.
We're here and you and you're making noise now.
So did you have something you wanted to ask?
I got a chuck, it's all right, man, chill, it's all right.
Okay, I'm just trying to be, it's, I think, no, I got it, it's a public forum, it gets messy.
Okay, so let's, so if that was just that on the water, what I want to get into is if those
that were subs most likely and those that have had personal calls on Skype and other things
with me, know that I've been up to something since around April of last year on the Pope's
work schedule.
And that's something is I've put photographs up on this chat group.
You will see a photograph, the first photo is almost like a very graphic kind of image,
a high concept image of what I call the scalerator.
It's a water device.
It's a large series of magnets in the middle and pipe goes around the magnets and it's full
disclosure and how it's made.
And the water runs through the pipe, but the key to it working and doing what it does is
that what you normally call magnetism, you and everybody else, yes you, which is, hey,
how do I get this piece of paper to stick on the refrigerator?
You got a magnet?
Well, you put the paper between the magnet and the refrigerator door and it sticks, right?
That's how you think about magnets working or when you see them pick up junk cars, right?
You hit a switch, like your magnet picks up a junk car, turns off the power, drops the
car.
Okay, it's not you, the moment you apply that type of magnetism to the water flow, it stops
working and nothing happens at all.
So going back to the inertial domain, if you look at that first, if you scroll up, first
image, this is going to be very image sensitive, by the way.
So if you listen to recordings, I think when Bruce, thank you, Bruce, for setting this
up in the link in the Skype chat.
I know it's not a lot, but I really don't want to do anything like that.
And Bruce, I want to thank Bruce for setting up this group call, technically.
You will be relying on photos and I will be numbering the photos.
So there will be no ambiguity.
The top very top photo is a picture of the device that you would see like in an ad or a
promotional piece or what's called a cut sheet in industry.
Number two, now I used a typed in number two on the lower left.
I put an X through that image, which is typically what they show you, magnetic water treatment
is, because that's not what we're going to be discussing.
You don't want to do that.
That is the normal accepted way.
So and then there'll be pictures three, four, five, and on and on and on.
And I'll be probably be using a free hand pen on the photo to put a much larger number
to be even more visual.
But if you go to picture number one, that's the device.
I call the scalerator mark one.
And I call it a mark one because it's a one inch.
So two inch would be mark two, the three quarter inches, the mark, point seven, five.
Yes, and it did come up all this on my own, all of it.
So if we go to number picture number two, I'm posting what conventional thought of magnetic
water treatment of fluids is.
Now you see a picture there with the north south, south, north, red magnets.
I put an X through it and it's number two.
I'll make the numbers on another photographs more prominent.
And I put an X through it because that is not what we want.
It should be done because it has no effect, very little effect.
When I tell people in the water industry that do sell products that are magnetized, they're
like, what do you mean it has no effect?
Department of energy wrote a paper that if you don't do that, you're an idiot.
I'm like, okay.
All right.
I'll get into the water industry here too.
Because when you hear me talk about the water industry, sorry, I really, am I the only one
who doesn't have the access to the pictures because I don't see them.
I would ask if you scroll all the way to the top Bruce and someone joins in later.
Can they also get the photographs that were posted first?
Is there a way to alter the call?
It depends.
It depends on where you're posting them, Greek.
I haven't seen anything come up on my end.
I thought it would, are you sharing screen on your own?
No, I'm on a journal domain.
I could take a screenshot of what I see.
Well, you know the other, you know, I see the pictures in the screen.
Yeah, you know, you know, the other one that you're using a record with, Greek, you can
use that and share screen from that computer.
And that way we would see it.
I don't want to do that.
What I'm going to be doing is I'm going to be just putting pictures up in this Skype conversation,
this, this actual call.
And if you get this is, I don't want to start complicating it.
Okay, then you want to repost them into this chat now so that they can be seen because
not everybody can see it.
So what if someone joins in a week?
They won't be able to see them.
They should.
So now that we haven't established call where you're doing this, yeah.
Yeah, they should be able to see it.
All right, I'm going to forward it again, the picture number one should see it now.
Now I do.
Yes, there we go.
Yep.
Sorry, just want to make sure everybody.
I'm not going to keep by the way I've had the reason I have to prove because I'm not going
to keep doing this.
I'm not going to keep roasting, roasting, presenting, representing pictures every time.
So I want to make sure that if someone joins in a week and they listen to the recording,
they could scroll off from a week.
They don't see the first pictures in the second pictures, right?
And that only I don't want to get tough because if they say they can't see it, I'll say
to you bad and it'll be Bruce's fault.
Okay.
Thank you for not setting it up with you.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
I am not, you know, I can get into all this by the way until I could be like the best
computer tech you've ever seen, one of the best, but I chose not to because it's not
where I was.
Look, any geek or any nerd can do this stuff.
This is cookie cutter.
That's why when you're going to hear me talk about the people in the water industry and say,
oh man, Greek sounds like he's really hating on them.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to give you the perspective and I'm going to show you things that you normally
wouldn't see about them as if I just came to this planet and I saw what's going on.
I can give you such a clear point of view.
And when I bring up certain companies, I'm not going to mention names like natural action
technologies or green field, but anyway, I'll drop links and then I'll show you stuff and
then you'll be okay.
What am I looking for?
And then I'll bring up the points.
You know, be like holy crap.
Right?
So does that make them bad?
No.
Does it make them good?
Definitely not either.
And I'm going to show you what's going on with them.
And there's just those are just two examples because they're the dominant ones on the internet.
And I brought them up because that's more the airy, fairy alternative side of water treatment.
The mainstream academic side of water treatment is dead and it's stupid.
It's so dumb that you might as well put Fisher price or romper room on the label, right?
I'm talking Harvard University MIT also.
By the way, you know, this is not the first time here Greeks speak, but I dare anyone
to not notice what I'm about to say.
But go do a YouTube search on new technologies and you'll see a whole slew of videos from MIT
students bringing forward these new technologies and it's a bunch of pimply, snotty, eighteen
year olds with popsicle sticks and silicone glued together talking about this is some new
technology and you got to laugh your ass out.
People look at this and you should see the comments.
Oh, wow.
They're making fun of you.
Meaning society.
That's what they're putting in front.
And what I just said, you cannot unsee it once you see it.
Go look at all the new technology videos.
They showing you 18 or 19 year old pimply, snotty, MIT students with popsicle sticks.
Third grade science crap.
And telling you, this is how they're doing the new nano stuff and whatever.
They're making fun of you.
There is nothing.
You're not getting anything.
You're not getting any new technology at all.
Give me an example.
I like to make fun of people who still have hard drives because you shouldn't because
you should be made fun of if you have something with a hard drive because back in 1983, I
went out and bought an 18T answering machine because it didn't have a cassette.
It had a solid state drive.
I don't know.
Bruce, you probably remember that and you had answering machines instead of the cassette
getting messed up.
It was solid state.
No cassette.
OK.
That means that solid state drives existed for the public to buy even though it was $40
or an answering machine of $400 in today's money.
It was still available in 1982.
40 years later, plus you're still using a hard drive, you should be made fun of because that
technology was around 40 years ago.
Why are you making it demand for it?
Do you know that spinning a hard drive in any device is tantamount to 1950s technology?
It's not any different than watching a 1950s sci-fi when they show you a computer and they
show you the big reels of tape go back and forth, it spits out a piece of paper with holes in
it.
It's ridiculous.
So you're being made fun of and I hate that because why?
I'm not the type of person when I was younger or older, got kicks out of making fun of stupid
people.
I hate that.
You know, I saw people pick on other people that were dumb.
I said, don't do that.
You think they want to be dumb?
Right?
So when I see that happening today in industry and society all around that really pisses me off.
There's a text question in the chat.
I don't know if you saw it.
All right, I'll get to it.
No, I'll get to it.
Thanks.
So let's see.
So what I want to get into, first of course, is any questions.
And the second thing I want to get into is why I wanted to get the seminar together to
put out because I'm ready to put out an effort.
And before you do something, if you think you might want to work with other people, it's
good to figure that out before you start and then look for them, right?
But if you put out a statement or a desire and then with other people and they don't fulfill
it, well, now you know, there's no question.
You have to do it on your own, right?
So if you say, listen, there's this dragon coming to eat our children next week.
Who's going to join me to go fight it?
Well, a whole bunch of people say, let's go.
Well, you have a scenario because you've got five people.
Okay, so we need five swords, five, right?
Axes, right?
Whatever, whatever.
But if no one comes and you're the only one that's going to go fight it, you're like, fuck.
Okay, now I need an axe.
I need a sword.
I can't take, I don't have to take five of them.
Right?
I can only wield one or two at this one time.
What do I, now I have to, you know, I got nobody.
Watch my back.
So what if this dragon whips his tail around me?
What do I do?
So now that's the whole scenario, it changes, right?
So that's why I'm doing this now because it's always good to pick something in life that
you're going to focus on.
Not the only thing you're going to do.
And then put a little bit of an effort and I haven't done something like that in over
20 years, the last actually 25 years.
Last time I did something like this was when I started a bike shop in New York City.
I really put all of my effort and all of my consciousness and everything just fell into place.
It was great.
And with this, this is even more noteworthy because this is not only something that has to
do with water treatment.
It has to do with physics.
It is a new physics.
It's not like Greeks getting into the water business.
No, we're in the physics business now, baby, because there's not a physics, I assure you,
there's not a physicist spell that F-I-Z-Z-Y-S-I-S-T.
They're very busy.
If they're academic physicists forget it, they're just having to stand by the door.
That's about...
By the way, the academic physicists is how they operate their whole lives.
Once they get a degree, they have to find a place working in a corporation.
And the corporations accommodate the academics.
They have a little area where the number of employees depends on how big the corporation,
some corporations could hire a thousand of them.
And they sit in the corporation, I do various tasks, you know, review this, whatever, whatever,
whatever, in their own little contained self-contained environment.
And the only other contact they have is with other academics physicists that are sitting
in a similar environment in another corporation or a government.
So they have this little self-contained society within a corporation or a government, and
they're very safe.
They all pat each other on the back.
They know absolutely nothing at all.
As a matter of fact, they've never built anything, they can't build anything, they have no creativity,
how it can back to, can you name anything that was built by someone with an academic that
you're as useful, no, you cannot.
It's not possible because it's the way that it is.
So am I hating on them?
No.
Am I giving you the objective truth about it?
Absolutely.
Right?
And this is across the board.
Look, I've even tried this scenario out in the pizza parlor today.
Everybody was laughing.
Yeah, we can't think of a damn thing any academic ever came up with.
So all right.
So I wanted to just bring this up again.
It's a long introduction that this is something very important.
But to say that it's more important in physics is irrelevant because now we're going to be
leaning towards the academic moronic side and that doesn't help people at all.
So let's just see what, I don't know.
See, do I have something in the chat, a question?
What size magnet and photo number one?
Oh, OK, that's a five and a quarter inch.
I will drop a link.
Let me show you the exact, let's do this.
What I will do, George, is I'm going to open a file here and I'm going to do a screenshot
of the exact magnet where you can get it and how much it costs and everything.
Is that all right?
Yeah, this is all about full disclosure.
Yeah, it's great.
So I'll show you exact supplier, everything about it.
OK, the model number and how much I pay for it and everything.
Here we go.
Oh, there we go.
Now, the thing here is about, I think also in the last Sonic I talked about how disgusting
truth 3D printed things are to me.
It would be like giving a rabbi a piece of pork.
You don't do, you know, just out of courtesy.
So you know how I feel about it.
But everybody loves pork, right?
But not a rabbi, right?
So I'm not a rabbi, but I know I don't need pork, but here's the idea.
You show me anything 3D printed and it's like showing a rabbi or vampire a garlic order.
It's garbage to me.
There is some aspects of 3D printing that are good.
I said some aspects, but not in this.
If you have to 3D print this, you got problems.
This is totally, it's like saying, I don't know if you guys are familiar with the watch industry.
People are very much still up on collecting old sacoes, tag cures, patek philips.
That's not more of a collection item.
That's more of a status symbol or Rolex is more of a status symbol again.
But imagine saying someone, you could go do a, by the way, a browser search and go to
images, a patek philip watch, go browser search and look what the inside of that watch looks
like.
How exciting do you think it would be to someone who develops those watches that you're going
to 3D print one?
You'll throw up right in your lap.
You'll be like, get out of here, disgusting human.
Look at the workmanship and all that.
So this is again the academics do that.
Everything 3D printed.
By the way, everyone that I've worked with so far was touting 3D printing.
So, does that make them bad?
No, but does it make them good?
Definitely not, not for this.
All right, so before I go on, I know there's a question about the magnet.
I'm just going to go on which direction?
Anybody want to plug in?
Do you want to hear first my experience with the water industry and what they're all
about?
You can, if you presume that it's shit, you've presumed well, so maybe we could bypass
the whole thing.
So, we can get into details from experience for six months.
We can bypass it or we can get into how this started and how we discovered.
We have a fork in the road, so anybody want to give some feedback on that?
I'd be glad to take it.
I was just going to ask, when you say those images are escalated, Mark 1, is that in, are
you referring to the diameter of the tube?
Yes, of the pipe, the conduit.
Okay.
Yeah, so that is what we call a 1 inch or 25.4 millimeter, 2.5 centimeter metric.
If you were a 2 inch, you know, a 50 mil pipe, it would be the Mark 2.
The Mark 3 would be a 3 inch pipe.
Yeah, and we can make them that large.
We can make them that large.
It's not a big deal.
The magnet size becomes a big deal, but I figured that out.
We'll get into that, that's very advanced.
We'll get into that later.
What I want to get into more now is by experiencing the past six months with the water industry
or how it all started and how it can transfer that information to you to answer any questions
that you might have or bypass one, bypass the other, not talk about one or not talk about
both, whatever.
But the important thing here is what I want to keep, and I will keep referring to, the
only way I see this going down, down the line and being developed is with people that are
workmen and true workmanship.
This is more in the line of a device that you would reckon as a fine set of golf clubs,
a fine racing bicycle, a fine umbrella, a fine watch, right?
Now I went and bought a fine set of golf clubs and they're 3D printed.
Would you lay them down here so my dog could take a crap bottom?
How does that sound?
None of that stuff applies here.
If you have an inkling that this thing has to be 3D printed somewhere or another, you're
going to piss me off to leave the call.
It's not that it's bad, but it's definitely not good.
I keep saying that is a Greek so judgmental, is 3D printing bad?
You know, there is some 3D printing that can be done that is nest and necessities, but
once people start going like geeks, like Eric Dollar says, to the computer to 3D print
everything that they could actually improve their human quality by actually practicing some
skills and developing a pipe bending skill, jumping to a 3D printer for that, I have no
respect for you as a human anymore.
You can be replaced by the machine that you're going to.
Why do I need you?
I should just go directly to the 3D printing machine.
You see what I'm saying?
If people that you meet are constantly giving up, progressing their own talents for having
a machine do it, why do I even need them?
Bypass them.
They go right to the machine that they're using.
I don't need them at all.
You see?
So this is more of a human thing that I'd like to maintain.
Again, imagine someone that collects fine watches and you say, "Oh, yeah, I have a 3D
printed version of your Patek Philippe."
By the way, if anyone doesn't know what Patek Philippe is, put in Patek P-A-T-E-K Philippe
and go to images.
Could you imagine someone who is an enthusiastic collector of these is presented with someone
that says I want a 3D print that?
You put it on the floor so I could take a crap on it.
I'd document it, a crap on it too.
Now, this is the level of humanity that we're at right now.
I want to avoid that, like the plague, completely.
Stay go the opposite direction.
And Vandy, you just asked about the Mark I and all that.
And I want to commend you also for making efforts on bending Pipe and all that.
And we will get into that.
I have developed several techniques on how to be masterful in bending pipes and having
them stay thermally stable and how to bend them with precision.
And there's nothing online about it at all.
I mean, the fine points that I will discuss.
I'm the only one that's able to do that seemingly.
There's some other monkey somewhere, I'm sure, but he's not talking like I am.
So this I would like to stay and see, define more of a high level handcraft.
To me, I'm beginning to sound like I'm I harken back from the 70s and 80s and a lot of musicians
were complaining about drum machines.
Now we didn't need all the machines in the synthesizers.
Now we don't have musicians anymore, right?
But that didn't work out that way because if you look at new movies, film scores, they still
use 100 piece orchestras, right?
If you asked me in the 80s, 40 years from now, would people still be using hiring, you know,
like John Williams making a film score for a new sci-fi cowboy movie?
Would he be employing 120 piece orchestra?
I would say definitely not 40 years ago, but guess what?
40 years later, they still are, right?
So there's no reason to get my panties in a twist about everybody around me wanting a 3D
print stuff because that will go away.
But right now it's, I see it as an obstruction and an annoyance.
So I don't know if I think I'll leave that subject alone.
But thank you for putting that up.
If you go to, actually, I'll do a quick, and feel free anyone to post an image, and I do
have some texts here.
Okay, I assume there is a particular number of magnets are in the array.
Yes, we'll get into that water industry first, please.
A bit of history also.
Find like a musical instrument.
Yes.
Now if you go to the images in a protect fleet, you could look at the back of one and
I'll put an image in just to satisfy what my desire and my was to say about it.
I put a link in also Greek.
Yeah, I'd rather just do images than links, by the way.
I would just suggest that because links get really messy and take you away from the page,
right?
But when you have an image, you could click on it and it expands and still keeps you
on the Skype group.
Yeah, I want to avoid links.
I even though I do put them up, just too many links and we start, that's fine.
Protect fleet, okay, and if you go to images.
On the back inside, I'll just put in, protect fleet inside, and I'll post an image to give
you an idea of what I'm talking about.
So, the water industry, we do have someone up for the water industry.
Great.
I want to get into it.
I said, I wouldn't have going to mention names like natural action technologies or Greenfield.
You know, I'm famous for doing that, right?
So I'll mention, they're both the same.
Okay, I'll start off with this.
They're not bad people, but are they good people?
No, they're not good people.
In my opinion, some other people's opinion.
I could tell you what's going on.
You could look them up.
You could find out what they're doing and they're exactly the same, but they're very different.
They're both try to be honorable and I'll get to the last part first.
This is more of the airy, fairly structured water side of the water industry.
Not the mainstream water industry, which is all chemicals and just big filtration and
RO.
I brought them up because they're more of the alternative side where they're not going
to run and ask you directly, where is your degree from?
We are you an engineer, like a company like Pentech or Haliburton would or other companies
that are into big water treatment, right?
So I brought up the two airy, fairly side ones where there's this thing called structure
water that was made more popular.
You guys probably heard of it.
What they do is they both run 2013.
There's this character, I call them a character because I can't watch more than 30 seconds
of his mug.
Clayton Nolte.
I never met the guy, I'm nothing against them.
I just basically he took a bunch of golf balls through him in a TPC pipe, ran water through
and say this is natural action for water, right?
And it was a big craze, everyone jumped on it.
These people started companies, these two people, two companies that I mentioned.
Nothing special.
Both people with some corporate background, cookie cutter, corporate cutouts, very easy.
If any, you want to start a company, you could be 40, 50, 30 years old, nine years old or
18 years old, doesn't matter.
The world, the fractional reserve banking system is ready for you.
There's ready.
Tell someone I want to start a company.
Oh, you got to get a lawyer.
And you got to get an accountant and they're both set up that way, cookie cutter, corporate
cutout, they're enslaved to the fractional banking system.
They don't know anything about money.
They don't know anything about business, anything about, you know, whatever they do, whatever
the account and say, whatever the lawyer says, they think they're good lawyers and they
think they're are good accountants.
They don't know.
There's no such thing.
There's competent lawyers and incompetent ones, but there's no such thing as a good lawyer.
And there's competent accountants and incompetent accountants.
There's no such thing as a good accountant.
Okay, so that's the more of the Greek speak side by being harsh yet.
No, being accurate, extremely so.
What they do though is they sell devices.
You can go on their websites, both of them, which I think are very tacky and I've worked
with both.
And you will find out that they offer these area ferry devices that, you know, air may
not work.
Basically, it's tubes in a golf balls in a tube and the water flows over these flow
forms, supposed to in live in the water.
Now, depends on which way the wind is blowing that day, that device might make the water
better or not.
Right?
And I'm laughing because that's true.
Now, one of the, they have two things that, they keep them in business, both of these companies.
Two things that keep them in business is one, the perception of good customer service,
meaning like if the, if you get the device and 99% of the time that you'll notice no
difference, they will give you all your money back.
No questions asked and take the device back.
Right?
So, do they get 99% of the devices returned?
No, about maybe 30% or more because most people don't care.
Even though some of them are $3,000 or $4,000.
The other thing that keeps them in business is that they sell water filters because they
have to sell something that actually does something.
Right?
A water filter is a screen.
It is a mechanical filter.
It will do something.
Right?
Every time.
It's to, based on its specifications.
It doesn't mean the water is going to taste better though.
I have had water run through various filtration types, media systems, whatever, you name it.
And they tout these filters as cleaning the water down to .1 micron without our row or this
or that treatment and that.
And the water tastes like crap.
It really does.
In other words, I've gone through places in the East Coast and just turned on the tap.
I can clean New York or upstate New York, just turned on the regular tap and the water tastes
better than these going through these filters because I, through long discussion, one day
I will get into water does not like to be micro filtered and it doesn't like to be
steam distilled.
Right?
So, we will let you know by tasting like crap.
So these companies, what they do is this is the alternative water business, the airy fairy,
the alternative.
They sell water filters to keep them in and they hope they want to sell the water filters
because it either works or it doesn't.
They sell these basically flow form things that don't work most of the time.
Actually, it's very subjective.
Some people say they work other people don't.
Now the irony when I came in is the scalerator, the Mark one, compared to what they're doing
even the filters is like a baseball bat across the head.
Does it work?
Are you fucking kidding me?
This is like your house is built near a mountain side and you come home one day and the
boulder just went through your roof and it's in your living room.
Obviously, does it work?
Crazy, does it work?
The thing about the scalerator that they've tried is that it must follow certain directions
in installation and I'm going to bounce around here.
This is again the experience with the water industry.
Now one lab, this is the non airy fairy side, they took the thing and tested it.
They put it on the end of a water source like a nozzle just like you would have a nozzle
on a garden hose and it showed absolutely no change in the water.
But guess what?
It's not supposed to be used that way.
By the way, when I dreamt this up before any of them were even built or a pipe was ever
wrapped around, I had seen that it will reduce the TDS extremely.
It will change the water quality in many, many ways and it would be, before I even built
a unit.
So by the way, when I told people build this and it will reduce the TDS, I had not yet
take any TDS measurements but I was so confident that it would.
How could I do that?
But anyway, the lab showed, I'll post a screenshot, no change in the water, all these parameters.
And I said, well that's not, it's supposed to have at least 10 to 50 feet of runner length
in front of the unit.
If you don't know what that means, if you have a 100 foot length of hose, the device should
go in the middle of the hose, you have 50 feet behind it, 50 feet in front of it, or you
could put the whole 100 feet in front of it.
But don't put the device on the end of the 100 foot hose like a nozzle and water your
garden.
It will not do anything.
It needs runner length in order to work.
This is very anti-material, anti-mechanical thinking, right?
Because if I have a filter or one of these airy, fairy flow form things, you know, you put
it on the end like a nozzle.
It's going to work.
If you put a filter on the end of a hose or at the beginning of the hose, it doesn't matter.
It's going to filter wherever it is, right?
This is very, very, very location sensitive.
It reminds me very much of the Joseph Newman machine where he was able to do 800%, you know,
eight times more energy output.
And whoever tested it, he said, do not ground the device.
Because if you ground the device, that extra 700% goes under this into the ground.
And what did they do?
Oh, your device doesn't work.
Did you ground it?
Did I told you not to ground it?
Right?
So we have to, you know, you could still ground it.
You can still do safety parameters without grounding.
But anyway, they just didn't want to do it.
So whoever takes this device, I had another academic and an engineer do say, it doesn't do
anything.
I built it, it doesn't do anything.
I said, show me a picture.
You didn't.
You just see it on the end of a hose like a nozzle.
You know, it's not supposed to work that way.
I spent past month discussing whether it's not supposed to go that way.
What are you doing?
Oh, but I thought, I thought it would go right.
I'm like, okay, all right.
So, okay.
So, you know, while all this was going on in the back of my mind months ago, I'm thinking,
you know, one day, probably in late winter, you know, or early spring, I'm going to do a seminar
and talk about all this.
Right?
This is about us thinking six months ago.
Here we are.
Right?
So I'm so glad it's very important.
So I'm going to take a pause right there.
Now, I can get a, by the way, I can get it.
So I can get into more of the conventional water industry, but what I just told you about
them using it, they will not follow directions.
They say, we test devices.
We bring the water source to the device and we do not add anything after the device.
That's how we test things.
Fuck you if you don't like it.
And they refuse to do it any other way.
And that's the, that's the regular water engineer.
Right?
So there's not much to talk about them.
They're just as useless as the rest, but in another way.
Now, let me get a little more on how the, the airy fairy side, the structured water ones
are not useful either, a little bit more.
They don't follow directions either.
I'll put in some photographs of installations that were done by one of them and they're both
incorrect.
They did not follow protocol.
But guess what?
It still worked, not as well, but it still worked.
And one of them, both of them, were not the right application.
And one of the applications, I was so upset when I found out what they were trying to do
with the device.
I said, if I knew that, I wouldn't be talking to you.
I would go out to San Diego and decelinate the entire fucking Pacific Ocean.
Right?
This is how ridiculous it gets, right?
So in other words, they thought for some reason they could decelinate, salinated, well water
with it.
I never made such a claim.
And it did not have any runner length in front of it.
It was right in the utility, a remote drop of photo.
And the unit was spent a month in the back of a pickup truck being kicked around in the
support tabs that fall off and I wasn't told about it.
So this is the type of, so are these people bad?
No, but are they good?
I'll let you answer that.
See?
So again, this was months ago and I said one day, pretty soon, a few months, I'm going
to organize a Skype seminar group and talk about this.
Right?
So this is where we are so far with that.
I'm going to take a pause and have some coffee if anybody wants to ask anything.
Is it scalable, Greek, the runner length and the size of the magnet?
Mm-hmm.
It is.
It's very scalable.
But I can't say, it's like cooking rice.
You know when you get a rice recipe, it's usually for someone making it for themselves or
a family.
But if you go to a mess where you're going to cook for a thousand sailors on a ship, you
don't use a pot that you would use for cooking for five.
We use a big bat, right?
For a thousand P50 rice, a thousand cups of rice, right?
At least.
Well, what happens then is it's scalable, yes, but the proportions changed, don't they?
It's no more one to one.
Of course.
Yeah, you have to change it because something takes place, something takes hold, even the
same rice.
When you get to a certain scale, certain things change.
So is it scalable?
Yes, I've scaled them not too much larger because the liability, for me to go, I would rather
do the one inch ones right now, the smaller ones in the three quarter, then go to some
place that has a two inch line and, right, the liability because if you build a two inch
diameter one, which is four times the one inch in volume and rate, and you install
it somewhere and there's a problem where it's ineffective.
That's a lot invested because the two inch lines are not some, you know, they're much more
serious than a one inch line, right?
So I'd rather keep, I'd like to see at least a hundred of them out there in the three quarter
one inch models gathered data.
They have to be properly installed.
Now that's what I'm doing now is I've halted sending these out to anyone.
Whether it's a mainstream lab people, the airy, fairy structured water people or someone
that wants one, no, no, all of them from now on, at least for the next six months or a year,
are going to be done by me here locally within driving distance.
Driving distance is, I'll drive a few hours to you.
I'll drive even four hours to you, 200 mile radius from Tucson.
That's all, that's the only one.
And I'll put in some testimonials of one and one last one that went in last week.
The woman just can't stop mentioning how she had problems with her hair and skin and
water filter is in immediately.
As soon as we put the device in immediately, a minute later, everything she just went and
washed everything was sparkling.
The water tasted better right out of the tap.
Her hair and skin the same day started improving.
Now it's been less than a week and it's way better.
She's like, this is magic.
This is not a scalerator.
This is magical, right?
Because this is Tucson, hard water, right?
Now Vandy, he's been doing stuff.
He's been putting pictures and all that.
And it's rainwater tanks, right?
And if you're still on, you could chime in.
And that water is not hard water.
And if you want to just tell us a little bit of the improvements of quality or maybe not
noticeable because your water is pretty clean other than some algae in the tank, right?
Yes, but I have been using the scalerator on the mains in my house because I don't have,
I've got pretty good rainwater and TDS on the rainwater was about 59 and I made a single
magnet set up with the three magnets like in the pictures that you posted.
I've got 16mm feed line.
It's a high pressure poly line.
And I have, it's approximately, I'm trying to think in feed.
It's about five meters from my mains tap and then I've got another 10 or 15 meters to my
house.
And I haven't tasted it because I don't drink tap water.
But I've noticed that it makes the water feel very slippery like a wash is better.
Yes, it washes better, but also like I do, I do biodynamic gardening and you stir your water,
you vortex your water.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can put little droppings from a horn that you store in a horn and all
the other two, yeah.
Exactly.
But when you stir your water, you'll notice that after a couple of minutes, the texture
of the water becomes silky on your skin.
Yeah, it's more friendly as opposed to angry water.
Yeah, and so the water out of my tap feels very much silky like the vortex water and that's
the one thing that I noticed as well as the TDS dropped from before I put the, before
I put the on the mains line, it was coming out of my tap between like 79 and 95 and now it
comes out pretty much consistently at about between between 60 and 70.
But I did notice, I noted down how you said it needs running length.
Yeah, after the unit.
Actually, more after, more after, but you're good, but you don't have to consider that much
before the unit because the water is coming from somewhere either a container or another
line and the container will suffice.
But after the unit is important, the more runner length after the unit, even a kilometer
would make it even more effective.
I found that I'm not taking it to that limit though.
So, well, I noticed, I've got a, I've got a, a garden tap that is, um,
it's only about two feet from the, the scale orator and the water comes out of that at,
at, at a higher TDS than it does in my house, which is, you know, how much is that?
How much should the reduction?
How much reduction?
Yeah, it's about, it's about 74 out of the tap that's close to the scale orator and it's
usually between 60 and 70 out of my kitchen sink.
Okay.
Yeah, so it is considerable because what I've noticed with the TDS, now there's a question
here from Andrew.
I heard the Hunza have lived, have, have longer healthier lives than use glacier melt water,
which minerals also, the deterian depleted.
This is affect the block wall change, okay, and get some material stuff here.
Mineral infused.
Is there general health? Yes, there are. What this is before we get into the material aspects,
thank you, Vandy.
The material aspects of it or anything like that.
This is not a, right now we're going to be talking about the inertial domain, the energetic
parts.
What we've done here is discovered, I say we, right in the collective, that if we go
back to the first photo and below the second photo that's marked number two, I show that's
a typical scientific or promotional picture of how you should impose the center part of a
magnet on a water flow, whether you alternate them, it doesn't matter if it's the same North Pole,
North Pole, or alternating or South Pole, South Pole, that convection is wrong.
It will not yield, yields mixed results.
I've had good results with just facing a magnet to the water.
If it's constantly recirculating in a tank, it will reduce the scale, but it will not improve
the water quality or anything.
The point that I'm making here and have been making for almost a year now since April
of last year is that I'm the first one to wrap the pipe or the fluid flow around the part
of the magnet that everyone is ignoring.
It's like I'm the first guy to date the ugly chick in the class, right?
Nobody wants to date her, so I ask her out for the problem.
What balls the Greek has, right?
So the best looking guy in the class asks out the worst looking girl.
Go figure, right?
This is exactly what's going on with the scalerator.
There is nothing written about the block wall, the domain wall, the needle wall, as a matter
of fact, it is a stepchild kind of part of science.
It is completely ignored.
Whereas this poor bastard Felix Block in 1946 wrote a paper about nuclear, I could post
it here.
It's a PDF, nuclear resonance, basically.
It's here, I won't post it.
1946, nuclear induction, F block, Felix Block.
So the block wall, the section of a magnet, where one field stops and the other one ends
which is the equilibrium part of the magnet.
You want to know more about that, by the way, Ken Wheeler, the fat ugly monkey guy, you
call it, I think he says so, the ugly monkey podcast or live stream, he does.
There's a video on there that he's put in Ken Wheeler through theory, papacis, block wall.
He has a video and he makes fun of how dumb humans are and all that.
And he mentions what the block wall is according to his findings.
But there is a paper by Felix Block, it's called nuclear induction.
You could look it up, July 19, 1946, very pedantic, whatever talks about, you know, because they
name that part of the magnet after him.
Now there's also the Neal wall, but neither one is true because it's not a wall, the block
domain, the center part of the magnet, you could look it up on your own, folks, whoever
wants to.
What is the block wall on a magnet?
It's not a wall because if you put two magnets together, that shifts to between
the two magnets, if you break a magnet, it shifts.
So it's not a wall in any way at all.
It's a domain that shifts.
It's a neutral point, right?
So this poor bastard Felix Block, they used his name on this thing and they tend to ignore
it completely in industry and the uses are immense.
Now we're talking about just the water here.
The reason why we're talking about the water is because it's unprecedented, the change in
water quality that it does.
And you're not using the part of the magnet that everyone is focused on.
And if you put in magnetic water treatment and go to images, magnetic water treatment devices,
go to images on your browser, you will see these poor bastards, thousands of companies,
hundreds and thousands have invested in selling these things to people that do nothing, almost
nothing.
When I say nothing, they're not consistent.
And I've tried them.
Right.
So when we go around the block wall, the water quality changes intensely, intense changes.
The TDS measurements that you're measuring are actually false.
It is a way for the, what I say false, is there a TDS drop?
Well, the water behaves as if there are.
It is.
And right here, I could drop in photos of my shower, which hasn't been cleaned in six months
and then you could see it's told sparkly.
It's acting better as if I was using our, our own water.
No mineral distilled water, but it's not.
What's happening is the water is being charged so much by the block wall, not discriminate
charging by the north or south only, which we can get into the north or south, you know,
the north or south pole of a magnet has a black hole in the middle of it, you can see it.
And that flips the pole.
That's the counter space part.
Well, we can get into that when we talk more about magnets.
Again, today is just to introduce the concepts here.
And to give a little bit of history of where I've been through the past six months with it.
And how happy I am that we have some, at least 40 participants here, I see in the group
that would listen to this.
But yeah, so can the, can the scalerator be attached under the sink?
I live in a condo and I can't modify the water.
I mean, yes, it can.
But what I would say under the sink is put it as far away from the mixing valve, you know,
where it actually connects to the sink with a, get yourself, what would be practical
if the sink, whether it has a cabinet underneath it or not, at least a 10 or 15 foot piece of
tubing, coiled up, not a small coil, but a wide coil go around the cabinet several times.
Doesn't matter which direction before it goes into the sink faucet.
Yeah, I would do a minimum of six feet and it will work quite well.
Yeah, not as well as if it's on the main.
This is the part where they are indeed more research and development.
Remember, this is only, thank you, Michael, in the text.
This has only been in existence since April, the last year and I'm the only poor sap that's
talking about it.
This could be, this could be an existence for thousands of years, but I tell you it's
not on the surface as far as we know and it's not on the internet as far as we can tell.
And this is one thing also.
I don't think anyone's going to figure their side unless you have direct experience and
direct knowledge in this group or what I've been talking about because it's counterintuitive.
What I mean by that is if someone wants to copy this and they go to a computer like console
and they type in what the scalerator looks like or recreate it and they hit the button to
show me what influences the magnetic fields have on the water.
It will show nothing.
It will show, it doesn't even show a block wall and I have engineers saying, yeah, the computer
dish will block wall.
No, it doesn't.
They don't show anything.
Are you that hopelessly brainwashed?
Doesn't show anything, any effect of the block wall at all.
There is no way that anyone working in an engineering firm that wants to imitate this
will be given any funding if the super computer shows that such an arrangement does absolutely
nothing.
So the chances of this being copied by industry or whatever is next to nothing is zero
to nil, right?
And you won't get a patent on this either.
They'll let look at you and laugh.
But they'll put you through the saw once you know, I know someone who's gotten patent several
people and one thing they do allow is when you meet them, the patent reviewer, you can bring
in and do a demonstration.
You bring in the device.
It's a water device bringing some water tanks.
They give you a room to set it up and all that.
You demonstrate it, right?
The moment you demonstrate it and it works, they're going to put you through the saw.
I don't know if you guys are familiar about the saw system in the patent.
Yeah, just like it sounds, SAW stands for special application withdrawal system.
They withdraw your application.
They send you a letter.
We found that what you are applying for is matter of national security.
So they call it the saw.
So how do I know that?
Anyway, 35.
In accordance with the out one of them and yeah, that's one of them.
Yeah, but they call it internal.
They have an internal mechanism to flag them.
So this is a very rare opportunity for anyone here or whatever that is ingenious is good
with building things.
Don't say you're going to 3D print.
If you want a 3D print, anything, just don't tell me, please.
I don't want to know.
Just like saying you like to cook, but you reheat frozen dinners.
That's your version of cooking.
By the way, they have said on sonics.
Most people that say, tell me they like to cook.
I watch them and they don't know how to cook.
They're reheating stuff.
They don't know.
Big difference again.
So yeah, this is very, very exciting in terms of the water quality.
Now, this is so early.
I'm the only one that's really been pressing forward and working with this since April
of last year.
So let's say nine months or so.
And I've had at the same time in paralleling experiences with both conventional industry and
the airy ferries.
The airy ferries meaning the structured water.
By the way, there's no such thing as structured water.
It's a gimmick.
If anyone tells you there's such a thing as a water molecule with even Ken Wheeler with
hydrogen up here and oxygen in the brew it.
If it's so prominent and dominant, show me a picture, show me how that imposes itself or
fractals itself, even in crystal formation.
Show me.
You know what?
It doesn't because there is no molecular structure to water.
Water is one molecule.
All the water on the planet is represents one molecule of water.
I've been trying to give this analogy for 20 years, even with O'Chelle when we talk about
water.
We have an Olympic size swimming pool between us.
You're on one end, which is 660,000 gallons.
Might even be Olympic size swimming pool might be 666,000 gallons as bastards, right?
But so, okay, I tell truck, you know, you're on one end of the swimming pool and I'm on
the other.
When you drop a glass of water, a one drop of water on your end of the swimming pool and
I take simultaneously one drop of water out of my end or an hour later, it doesn't matter.
Is it the same drop of water or a different drop of water?
Now some people think they're slick and they'll say, well, I put red dye in it and I could
see the water.
No, you see the red dye, you don't see the water when you drop it in.
Ah, gotcha, you see?
That's the first irrational logic person say, well, I'll put dye in the water so we can see
it.
So when you drop the water in, you see the dye, not the water at it.
So I'm telling you, it's the same exact drop of water.
The same water that was used to fill that pool wherever it came from is still the same water.
And I've backed this up many times with people that I've talked to in neurosurgery.
Oh my gosh, what is neurosurgery?
You have to do with it.
So there is a miracle going on here that's been going on under our noses for thousands
of years that we tend to lean on the subject matter as being miraculous water.
But no one's talking about it this way at all.
I hate seeing like the presumption, there's a whole bunch of people out there.
You'll find them on YouTube.
They got, I don't know, easy water in this water.
That water, the water molecule for stage of water, prove it.
Show me.
The irrational and their logic falls very, very quickly.
It falls apart even Vita Austin, who I revere as doing with the hydro glyphs.
Sooner she freezes water next to photographs and thoughts and the water frost patterns
revealed, you know, hydro glyph with what the photo or the thought was.
When she starts a conversation, she says, we all know that water came from outer space,
from meteorites and all that.
I'm like, oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
Does that mean that her rest of her work is invalid?
No.
Is she allowed to say really stupid things?
I mean like really stupid things and still be right about the hydro glyphs?
Of course.
Aren't we all right?
So this approach on the scalerator, running the water line or the fluid, by the way, you
know, sometimes I'll interchange water with fluid because guess what?
Have you tried fuel in that?
By the way, when I mentioned look up magnetic water treatment devices, when you're doing
that.
There's some rascals in there that want to sell you devices to run your fuel, right?
Your gas line with magnets also and they start telling you to get better in PG.
You know that bullshit, you're not because they're doing the same exact thing that the
water people are.
And in the water people, the airy ferries, they use cone, we use a cone magnet, very expensive
cone magnet.
And this doesn't matter.
If you're facing either the north or the south or both or in parallel or opposing,
doesn't matter.
It doesn't work.
Well, if Guineemann Greek, it doesn't work.
Of course it works.
The Department of Energy wrote a paper on there that if you're an industry and don't use
magnets or water, you're an idiot.
Yeah, but it doesn't work like this and you're still going to get scale, right?
So what is this?
Running any fluid along that part of the magnet.
Now unfortunately, so far, not with much experimentation, but more like thought experiments, the best
way to do this is by looping, it's called a spool, by the way, in industry.
If you wanted to go make that pipe made out of titanium, which I like, titanium is a wonderful
material for water treatment, by the way.
It's extremely paramagnetic.
It's not magnetic.
It has some properties that are very unique as a metal.
Otherwise, they wouldn't say they're stargates are made out of pure titanium.
Remember, these stargates series?
It was, again, people were taking advantage of the ignorance of the people.
They closed the stargate and the general said, no one could go through that.
It's pure titanium.
Like, oh my gosh, pure titanium is soft.
You could cut it with regular steel hacks off or, you know, dollar store hacks all cut
right plate.
That's again, taking advantage of the ignorant people.
You tell people this in previous is pure titanium.
Most people think it is, right?
It has to be alloyed.
So if I go to a fab shop to make me a titanium two inch spool, a real mean-ass scale
reader, a mark two, and they want $20,000 to just bend the pipe and weld and polish it internally,
externally for titanium, when you refer to that bend, it's called a spool, right?
And the magnet, we're not going to call a magnet, we're going to call it a magnetic reactor.
And the reason we call it a magnetic reactor is because I don't care at all about the magnetism
of that magnet, you know, basically you care about magnetism of a magnet when you want
to stick something to your refrigerator or you pick up a junk car or whatever, or use it
in a relay.
By the way, not necessarily true because this can also be used in relays in a way that
below your mind.
But we're not interested in the magnetism of the magnet at all, what's what the north and
south pole are doing.
We just, you know, give them their pay for the day and tell the north and south pole,
go home, leave, we don't need you at all.
We just want the block wall.
As a matter of fact, all of the magnetic flux line diagrams that you see online are incorrect,
except for the ones that Ken Wheeler has drawn up and people that I've studied with him.
Now I also put up some photographs of what I've discovered with magnetic field lines, Vandy
put one up the other day, the south pole and the north pole is a north pole and a south
pole.
There's a variation between the north pole and the south pole.
They're not identical.
What is not the opposite of the other?
They're very different.
And that needs to be explored and worked.
I have done some mild experimentation with success, but I'm not going to go down the road
and get a knock on my door one day and they're going to say, "Greek, if this works, you're
a dead man, you know, I don't need another call like that.
I've had those before."
So this is something for someone else or when we get to a point where we can hide a little
better, I can discuss more and what's going on with that.
Vandy did post a picture in the chat of the magnetic field and I will post that again.
We are not interested in water treatment.
I am not.
The scalarator has nothing to do with magnetism, but it does employ a magnetic reactor in a way
that, for example, in a nuclear reactor, a nuclear reactor's purpose is to heat water,
not to put radiation into the water.
Thus it's called a nuclear reactor.
A reactor is, it means it's initial purpose is being used in a secondary form.
So you do need magnets.
You can even use an electromagnet, by the way, but why?
Why would you be pumping electricity into something, you know, voltage and currents where
you can, unless being very light weight is an issue, but then you have the weight of what's
providing the electricity.
So we are using the magnets just to capture and create that block wall.
And you could look up a block wall, needle wall, ridiculous.
This is the stuff they are putting out to the children.
By the way, when you look at science books, physics and all that, keep in mind that no matter
how complex it looks, the goal and the intent behind all that is to fool ignorant children.
Right?
To not show what's going on, but to satisfy their curiosity with gibberish.
I'm one of those people that whenever they show a movie like Goodwill Hunting or something,
even like Felix the cat where they have all the equations on the blackboard, I would
pause it and tell everyone in the room, those are Hollywood bullshit equations.
They don't make any sense in why they don't make any sense and no one cares.
No one in the room.
You shut up, play the movie, you're ruining it for me, shut up.
Right?
It's like, I don't care about the equations.
They look, they're fooling you even here just like they do and whatever.
So I just wanted to bring that up.
So yeah, I think maybe we've been kicking this now for an hour and a half.
So if anyone comes on for the first time, they're going to be how long is this Greek with
another 14 hour thing or whatever.
Let's see if there's any other question.
Yeah, can it be done a burky?
Yes.
As a matter of fact, what I will do, how about I post, I'll try to sanitize the name because
I have to ask the person if they want to be public or not.
Someone asked about the burky if that was Bruce, right?
Who saw you?
Yes, sir.
I got a surprise for you then.
Here you go.
I will sanitize this and I will send it to right now.
I want you to read this comment here.
I just sent this is from last week.
Thank you so much for selling me on the scalerator.
It's magic.
This is not sent to me.
This is sent to the person who recommended the scalerator and then forwarded the message
to me.
So this is a third party, right?
I can't stop cleaning everywhere, sparkles and the water tastes amazing out of my burky.
I saved some of the old and yuck, meaning the old water out of a burky filtered, right?
Tasted like yuck.
So.
All right.
Yeah, so yeah, it does.
And burkeys, by the way, are great on paper.
They're wonderful filters on paper.
They do what they say they do, but I've never tasted water come out of a burky that tasted
good and there's one reason for it.
It's because of that stainless steel.
The stainless steel holds the memory.
Yes.
Yeah, you have to know how to clean the stainless steel, not physically, electrically, and I
could get into that in the future.
It's very simple actually if you just get an AC power cord, interrupt the power cord and
where the power cord is interrupted, you put your stainless steel there for five minutes,
let AC run through it.
Right?
Just take one of those cheap lamp cords and cut one leg of the lamp cord.
Yeah.
And so you expose the wire, right?
Make sure it's unplugged first and then attach it with magnets or whatever to the stainless.
I think it's not magnetic with some tape and make sure there's a light bulb on the end.
There's a load.
So when you plug it in, it doesn't matter positive or negative.
It's AC.
When you plug in the cord with the lamp on the end of it, one of the legs that are broken
on the extension cord goes through the burkeys.
The burkeys making the stainless steel becomes the conductor.
Don't touch it.
Make sure you don't have any pets or children around.
While this is going on, some people say 10 seconds is enough.
I like to do more than five minutes.
But even 10 seconds will help.
And then once you do that, do it dry, dump it out and then clean it with baking soda.
Never use anything to clean a burkey that you wouldn't ingest.
So you don't use like CLR Lyman scale.
So I was like, "Can I use CLR Lyman scale?"
I've been though, I finished saying that.
All right.
Would you drink CLR Lyman scale remover to your food?
No.
I just mentioned.
Do not use anything that you wouldn't eat.
So you would use vinegar?
Yes.
You would use lemon juice?
You baking soda?
Yes.
All right.
See?
So stop using industrial chemicals and you'll notice how things will taste better.
Look, you ever go to something that will help you?
So help us.
Yeah.
Use regular tools.
So help us.
Yeah.
So help us runner length, size of magnet length afterwards.
How would that work in on the burkey when you're scaling it down?
Is my curiosity here?
Oh, no, no, the burkey, no, no, no, no.
This, the comments that I just put here is a scalarator, a 700 degree one, a custom one,
was put on the water main outside with a plumber because it was an HOA, got a license plumber
to install it.
All right.
It was put in outside the house, plenty of runner length.
Okay.
The pipe goes through the garage first and then it goes through back around the kitchen and
it's got plenty of elbows.
Every 90 degree elbow represents about 20 feet of runner length, by the way, anywhere
between 10 and 20 feet.
So let's say you have 10 feet of runner length with 290 degree elbows, you count it as
30 feet, 40 feet.
Each time you put a 90 degree elbow in a plumbing situation, it's like adding 10 feet of pipe.
Energetically and mechanically.
Yeah, that's terrible.
They shouldn't be, it's not friendly to flow.
They should always be using sweeps.
But I found that they work to my advantage.
As a matter of fact, if I build a scalarator with an extra wrap, like a 540 degree one,
instead of a 380, right?
If I make it a 700 degree and I put two 90s on the end where it just blocks the flow, it
almost as if water is in the scalarator, it sees those 90 degrees and it's like looking
down an alley, you don't see it way up.
But when you get down the alley, you can see you go right, you know what I mean?
That's how those 90 degrees work.
When the water sees down to that fitting, it doesn't see a way out.
But it knows if it turns right or left, it'll get out, right?
Terrible.
It seems to work really well.
It's kind of like, you know, all right.
You want to run down an alley or like, there's no way I could get out of here.
You're trusting that there's an opening on the right or the left, right?
You don't want to get caught in a fight in here.
So the water gets a little antsy when it sees these 90 degree bends and it tends to work
better, a little excitement in your life once in a while, right?
You know, shopperger said, yeah, for the water.
In other words, shopperger says that the water has a consciousness, by the way.
His consciousness was overtaken by the water consciousness several times when he was by a
very lively, healthy river during moonlight.
So you know, you can allow it's better than having the TV take over your consciousness.
But absolutely.
Yeah.
So the burky here is just a burky.
It's just a poor man's canister filter, you know?
It's basically whatever water source you got.
Like, if you go camping, you take a burky with you, right?
You should.
You just put it, you know, you go camping with enough people.
Why are we bringing him, honey?
Oh, because he's going to carry the water filter.
That's why we're bringing him.
Right?
So, yeah.
And whatever you dump in there, yeah.
But I appreciate that.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
I appreciate the heads up on that, though.
That's a good information.
Yeah.
We'll be going into a lot of other water stuff that I've discovered.
But generally, just to recap, and we will end it soon here.
The O'Celi, there's a classic O'Celi.
I think it was only for the O'Celi subs, not the rated Y subs, that I did about four years
ago, five years ago, with him on how to treat water.
It was basically pre-chilling the water, using $10, picture filters and buying some magnetite.
And if you can't get that zeal light adding into it, whatever, pre-chilling, certain techniques
and what to do and how to handle water.
Whoever listened to it and did it, found the water quality was exceptional, better than
Fiji, better than anything bottled, whatever, whatever, whatever.
That was a classic call.
We'll recap on some of those things again in case people here have not heard that.
But basically, keep it cool, keep it out of the light, contrary.
By the way, all these are these airy, fairy-structured water people and maintenance.
You go to their websites.
No where does it say, keep your water cooler out of the dark at all.
No one does that service.
And I don't even feel like I'm giving a service by saying that.
But anyone who does that will find an increase in water quality.
But we'll get into a lot of little tips and tricks because I have developed quite a few
things because again, years ago I said, I'm no longer working with water.
I found it to be a dead end thing just because it's the wrong planet for improving things.
This planet has a course.
So if you see any technological improvement, it's not out of happenstance.
It was planned a long time ago and as part of the course, you're supposed to go down.
This is not the right place to start finding things that need to be improved and start
improving them.
If you think you can do that, you're making a big mistake.
And I discovered that a long time ago.
So I said, no more water work for me.
And I had to do something about the scale.
Came up with the scale rate or nine months ago.
And that's pretty much my focus has been because, and again, I had not been talking about
it for a while on the sonics because I had started intermingling with some of the groups that
I mentioned here, both mainstream and non-mainstream water people.
And they get scared.
They're afraid.
They also do what's called delay tactics.
They capture, they kind of like get your attention.
Oh, we're going to be really wealthy with this, but you got to wait like three months,
okay?
Don't tell me how many people have you told about this?
Can you wait another two months and then three months go by.
Can you give it a few more months, maybe told July and so you know what?
Why don't you go like fuck yourself?
Did I say that politely enough?
So because delay tactics is a psychological thing.
They did that to OJ Simpson.
By the way, if you guys don't know the truth behind that, it's very well known amongst many
circles.
OJ Simpson is wife and Mark, whatever.
They were involved in a very big human trafficking and drug trafficking network that was
put together by judges in California, attorneys, generals, ex-military, ex-police.
One of the guys went a little crazy, killed OJ's wife and whatever.
And OJ was like, I can't stand this anymore.
I couldn't stand it while I was going on.
This is too much.
I got to talk about it.
And they're like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you might get into a little
trouble, but you got to, well, you can talk about it in about three months or so.
I know you're a really upset.
Can you just hold it?
Can you promise this?
You won't say anything for three months later?
Come again.
Oh, three months is over.
Oh, OJ, you can't.
You know how many people's lives are at stake?
Don't talk about it.
I've seen these delay tactics over and over and over and over and over and over and many,
many aspects of life and it really messes people up.
Look at how OJ Simpson is now, right?
I'm not OJ's, but I'm just saying I like to give that sterile, like to throw in these pieces
of information.
It's kind of like kicking the powers that be in the shins a little bit, you know?
If you ever listen to me talk, I always try to bring up how 9/11 was a textbook nuclear event,
not because I know better.
Yeah, I do know better, but it's kicking the authorities a little bit in the shins.
Don't you want to kick them in the shins at least once before you go?
Maybe kick them in a thousand little ways, you know?
So yeah, delay tactics.
So anyway, this I'll be opening up more and more as we go on and I hope you guys find it
of benefit.
And like I mentioned the end from the beginning, what I would like to see, I'm going to be
dedicating as much as I can to it.
But at the same time, if my noodle, my brain breaks and I say I'm not doing this anymore,
please excuse me.
But what I would like to see is everybody in this call say we're going to mortgage everything
we own and we're going to convince our grandmother to give her life savings so we can
get at least a million dollars together and open a factory and all of us will be shareholders.
That would then we wouldn't have to keep talking right then we'll say okay, why don't you
say that in the beginning and why we don't need to continue these calls in the Skype group
and let's get to work, right?
So I just want to put that out there too.
So with that said, we'll end the recording right here and we'll schedule another one
real soon.
(bell chimes)