Okay.
How's my sound quality, by the way?
I'm on a different machine, different headset, everything.
Yeah, you sound much better.
More like a shirt on radio.
Absolutely. There's more bottom end to your sound now.
And no crackle and the consonants come through clearly, right?
Absolutely.
Absolutely. So, here's the thing.
I'm just going to provide a quick little thing for the...
Actually, I won't even provide a quick little thing for the listeners, because...
I already set the recording for automated, so it's going right now.
Well, excellent.
Okay.
Are you going to probably do whatever you have to do, right, edit or whatever?
Yeah, well, I won't edit very much.
But what we'll do is just take it from here.
I mean, obviously, we talked about doing this on the show.
And this will go into the Ocele.com member section.
So, there you go.
And I'll let people know that it's there.
And we'll see what happens from there.
Obviously, this is content, which is not normally heard on the air.
And therefore, kind of exclusive to the website, because...
Well, it's not a show that's been done publicly, so...
Right. There we go.
Yeah.
And I don't think I need to edit this at all.
Hell, let it run as it is.
And since it's in this private arena, and we can really open up and discuss what's going on,
that might sound truly fantastic or truly ridiculous to some.
It depends on how much training you have, formal training, you know?
Because this does not...
Well, we're going to be discussing, doesn't go along with academia,
but it goes along with what anyone can perceive.
That's what makes some of the comments might sound ridiculous, right?
Well, you know, that's the thing is that a lot of fans...
A lot of fantastic claims are made by individuals, you know, well ahead of when it becomes acceptable to what they call academia.
Right? And quite often, it's really amazing to me when some of those things become part of the reality without ever being part of academic structure.
They can't, because by definition, academics are supposed to be impractical, theoretical, and non-conclusive.
Exactly. Never coming to a conclusion. That sticks with me when you pass along that...
That hetomological breakdown of the word "academic" not coming to a conclusion is just...
And you know what? For me, those words sum it all up right there, because regardless of the exercise, they don't seem to come to a conclusion.
Ah!
You know, the thing is, people are afraid of absolute... how many times have you heard people shy away from discussions that mention things in an absolute fashion?
And everyone likes to stay in that presumption or presumptive or opinionated realm. And people one day will find out that there are absolutes.
And one absolute that can be made as in fields of legal society, academia, the medical society, all of the people.
Not some of the people in there are not contributing to the benefit of mankind. They're all on the agenda.
This is because of the time period we're speaking in, right? And the agenda is not that they're gonna get you and they want us all dead or this sort of that or the other.
You know, you know, the illuminati or whatever. That's not the agenda. The agenda is they all provide very, very low qualitative work.
The quality of what they do is so low at this point that it's not even worth revisiting the entire institution. The whole thing needs to be scrapped and restarted as if there was no wheel.
You see, right?
So, you know, in a practical sense, to be honest with you, starting with this particular subject for the consumption of the members' only section.
And by the way, in case you're listening to this and not sure what's going on, of course this is my partner on the Ocele in the Greek show, The Greek with me.
Of course, I am always on this website. But this is the other end of the sonic entity known as Ocele in the Greek.
And we're gonna have a rare discussion about something that really does bring us back to the beginning, the bare minimum, the basics of life itself.
Water. That's great.
Water.
Yeah.
Like quite appropriate and how about we start with, you know, an interesting observation, which I find, you know, it seems like it's one of those relative discussions that's not necessarily.
Essentially, when talking about what water is and the fact that it is one of those essentials of life, I'm sure you wouldn't dispute that, right?
It's more than essential of life. It's a mother's love sense as we'll get into it.
Right.
And so let's start off with an interesting kind of question, which is what does the bucket of why, excuse me, why does the bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air?
Right. It sounds like a ridiculous question, doesn't it?
Yeah, it seems really innocuous.
Right.
Because I've got a bucket of water and a bucket that's empty, right? But it's not really empty. There's air in it.
It's open to the atmosphere. So I clearly, if I lift the bucket full of water, it's going to, to me, weigh more than the bucket of air.
But it shouldn't. If the periodic table of elements is accurate and if water is called H2O, a bucket of air should be about 40% heavier than a bucket of liquid water.
Now listen to this carefully. If water is H2O and the periodic table of elements is accurate, then let's go back to the question. Then why does a bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air?
Let's take that apart for a moment. And this is a twofold answer and a twofold question.
Well, right. Because part of it, you'd have to, in order to qualify that statement, to really make it, you know, scientifically replicatable, why is it?
You have to understand both substance is also a little bit. So air is actually made up of what versus the water exactly.
And hold on to it when you look at it. And remember, the part of the question is not only why does a bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air being the, you know, let's say a proverbial question or a rhetorical question.
Typically you'll have academic scientists, people in the industry, anyone with any form of training laugh or even no training in the field of science or physics or materials also laugh, right?
Now, if, now that's the first part, the second part is if water is H2O because that's what everyone assumes it is. And the periodic table of elements is accurate. Now let's look at that point.
I've been on conference calls with, because I've been working with water for over 10 years and I'm known in that industry as the go to go to person for covert type of cleanup projects.
Let's just leave it at that and because not using conventional means. And whenever we, whenever you get thrusted into a new group, you have these things called conference calls and meetings and video skyves and things like that.
And typically there's scientists, engineers, people in the water, cleanup industry from the fracking industry, nuclear, drinking, municipality, all these kinds of, you know, anything that water.
And then you have a lot of people who are bottling and bottling, and they run into them all MIT professors, Stanford professors. Now typically when you get into a meeting they like to go across the table and they each introduce themselves with their names and what their education was, what university they want to, what level of degree they have. And their work experience. And then they go to the next guy in the table.
So it's like I'm Dr Smith and I have a PhD in, you know, XYZ field and I have also been someone who's been employed under that awesomeness, you know, via XYZ industry and blah, blah.
They know the ones, potentials, yeah, they're credentials. So they get around to me and I say, well, I've known as the Greek and I'm just visiting this planet taking notes. And by the way, why does the bucket of water way more than a bucket of air? And they all start laughing.
Right.
Right. Well, you know, and then you know, we get over I'm just visiting taking notes for but they all start laughing about why does the bucket of water way more than a bucket of air.
Let's say if water is H2O in the periodic table of elements is accurate, that shouldn't be true. And then they start tuckling a little bit more and I say, well, let's look at it.
If water is H2O on the periodic table, hydrogen has an elemental weight of one and oxygen has an elemental weight of running running, rounding off these numbers here.
16. So a mole or a molecular weight of water, if it were H2O would be H2, which would be 2 plus 16 in one oxygen would have a weight of 18, a molecular weight of 18.
Right.
Now, if we look at air, we look at all the major, the major five, let's say major nine constituents in air, a couple of them being noble gases.
If you, I was thinking of pulling it up on a, for you to see it, but I can just tell you you can validate this if you do a search on what is the molecular weight of air.
Guess what it is? 28.6 to 29.
Well, now hang on a second, far cry from 18, isn't it?
Well, certainly it is, it's not quite double, but getting there and of course air, just quantitatively, let's think about this for a moment, there are two essential elements that are contained in water, but air actually contains both of those things.
Plus, I mean, that's a real simple way to look at it, right? I mean, if you're saying there are nine constituents to it, then that means there's more.
The primary ones are the nitrogen car, monitrogen and oxygen, and then they start becoming into the, then you start going into groups of inert gases and carbon dioxide and things like that, which again are molecules, other combinations.
But the general soup, the main ingredients are basically three or four, you can say go down to about nine, they'll typically list five as the main constituents for air, and we don't need to get into the air part, specifically too much.
But generally, when I do mention that the air is much heavier than the water, quite almost double on the molecule, the response I get from these water experts is, well, one is a liquid, one is a gas.
And I'm like, well, first of all, we're looking at one molecule, irrelevant to phase. Right? So it doesn't matter. The other thing is, water doesn't have a gas phase. It has only a liquid or solid phase.
And now they stop laughing. Now they start to sober up a little bit because they know I hit them on something that is so obvious. Now, when I say periodic table, we're discussing, I don't know, when do they start throwing in the periodic table in the public fool system?
About eighth grade, ninth grade from there? Yeah, somewhere in there, I would say what they would typically describe as the later part of middle school. And again, I say, well, hydrogen and oxygen being what water is supposed to be according to what they teach us.
I mean, that's one of the first things they show us on this periodic table is stuff like that and salts and other common sort of combinations that make up what is allegedly, you know, that allegedly make up, I should say, very common things.
Isn't it true that, you know, hydrogen and oxygen are part of the main constituents for air as well? So oxygen probably more than the hydrogen. But as we progress, let's just bear this thought in mind.
Let's say in a conference with these guys that are captains of industry and the heads of where anyone and everyone goes to get knowledge on water for. Now, just to continue on this thought, because this is important on what can be imparted from one's experience when you start learning about these things, is they no longer are laughing these professors in captains of industry, but they still stick to the idea
that one is a liquid and one is a gas or a density. Okay. Now, you can go and get what's called an A tank at a welding shop and tell them to fill it with compressed air, which is now in a liquid form.
Okay. And then you have a corresponding equal size tank filled with water. Okay. The one with the air in liquid form is still lighter than the one with water.
And it shouldn't be. So what is going on? This is the point where they start to get really upset because with the listener or just you and I, I've never introduced this to you by the way in before. This is the first time I think I brought it up and we've discussed it.
None of these concepts that we brought up so far are complex, ethereal or academic or aspoteric. It's very simple for anyone to look up.
Why does the bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air if water is age 2o and the period of table of elements is accurate? It shouldn't.
So now this is not such a ridiculous question. The important thing here is how can we have senior people in this field procuring knowledge on water and have missed such a fine but yet important detail that water being age 2o just simply doesn't add up according to their own experience.
So what is going on is how can we have a chance to get up according to their own memorialization of this science, meaning the periodic table.
So the importance of this chalk is that if this question which seemingly seems ridiculous on its face, the bucket of water, bucket of air question, if it is pressed, it has enough legs to tear down the entire scientific community.
So this is the water, that's why they hold on, this is real important here. This is the thread that unravels the cheap sweater if someone pulls on it and it hasn't been done yet and it will be done.
So I have in my mind an idea of how that could be answered by these academics that I am imagining sitting around this table. Of course I am not an academic and did not receive any training beyond what they call high school.
But be thankful you didn't. Yeah, I should be thankful but at the same time I actually have an idea of how that could be answered. So I don't know if you want to get to that but yes, do it.
Here is my answer. Wouldn't the shape of the molecules dictate how much space they could take up? So if you, for instance, were to come up with 20 cubic yards of something that is lighter by nature and it takes up more space.
For instance, a 3 by 3 by 3 block of Styrofoam is not as heavy as a 3 by 3 block of cement. Now why is that? Is it simply the nature of the material or is that the material at its most basic form is simply spread out over a greater amount of space?
In other words, even if the molecular weight differs, even if air should weigh more on the molecular level, if the molecules are in a greater amount of space, right, but Chuck, donuts, the donuts, apples, to apples, liquid air in water, both being liquid form, still the water is heavier and it shouldn't be.
Well, that's where the stumper is because, yeah, the compressed air would should be more important because it will take up way more.
Now here is the whole thing. Let's just repeat this. If water is H2O, remember not if that is, if it is, and the periodic and if the periodic table of elements is accurate, why does the bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air?
Now let me just preclude something here. I've been on several chats and late night call-in shows since roughly what they call 2010 on the Pope's work schedule.
And I would always introduce that question and there would always be anywhere between one and five people that would try to chase me around to answer that question for months or years after that.
For a while on the internet, seeing I was known as the guy who was always asking the question, why does the bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air? And one guy got tired of other people talking about it that he got drunk and called in.
And he says, hey, Greek, why does a bucket of shit weigh more than a bucket of air? I'm tired of that stuff.
Anyway, that's pretty funny. So the whole thing here is very interesting. We could look at it very closely. Well maybe why, let's just look at it this way. Why do they say water is H2O? Well, let's take it apart.
Because it's kind of difficult to wrap your head around the question, the bucket question until we start clearing up the H2O part. And the H2O is easy to clear up.
What happened was generally what was memorialized or canonized as the holy grail to water was a guy, one of the people was William Grove in the early 1800s, late 1700s.
He decided to put some metal plates in the water and electrify them. And he noticed hydrogen coming off of one side of the container on one plate.
And he noticed the oxygen coming off of the other. So the hydrogen coming off the negative and the oxygen coming off the positive.
And he kept doing this and the water volume started to decrease. And what he did, then he called a bunch of his friends and they did a peer review within a week and said, oh look, he's breaking up water into hydrogen and oxygen.
And they wrote a paper on it in that sense. So they basically did three days worth of research and it hasn't changed for over, I don't know, what's about 18, 11, 18, 13? Let's say 200 and what, three years.
Right. So there hasn't been any more research on that subject since then. So how difficult would it be for anyone to pick up research on this?
So we're talking about three to four days worth of research 200 years ago. It's been left at that. Wouldn't be that difficult to pick it up right now and further that, right?
Oh, it shouldn't be.
And nothing has been done since then on this. I assure you academically or scientifically that that that is told to the public, let's say. That's why in the beginning we're doing, I said, let's chuckle us, discuss water off of off the air and see how it goes.
Right. So here, this is the rest of the story as they kept applying electricity, the water volume would decrease and more hydrogen and more oxygen were being given off, right?
Now, but what they noticed is that when you got to a certain volume, that process ceased. In other words, there's something called electrolysis where you convert water into hydrogen and oxygen.
And it tricks you thinking because the water volume is decreasing, that water, you're breaking it up into its main constituents, right?
But no one in the history of mankind has ever electrolyzed an entire volume of water into hydrogen and oxygen. Once you get past a little bit more than halfway, that process stops.
And other things start to happen. Different gases start to come off where no gases, right?
And then they have to add electrolytes and the water starts to get hot and it boils off. But what happens there is when this electrolysis process stops, because in reality, let's give this water, what's happening is you're not breaking up water with electricity into its basic forms, you're actually creating that.
You're just integrating a component of the water into hydrogen and oxygen, but it's not what water is made of because as we continue this process, the gas stops coming off.
And that given the volume of water is still water, but it has an interesting quality to it and it's used in certain industries and when I give you the name, you'll reign a bell.
That water is called deuterium. And if you continue that under a vacuum, you might get some more gases and then it stops again. And then you continue and you get something called tritium, which goes for about 100,000 bucks for a 55 gallon drum of that crap.
So this is how these things are made very simply. Now you see why I don't want to discuss this on open air really.
So no one in the history of man is ever if water is H2O, no one has ever proved that they could take a given amount of water, meaning like you know, drink the whole glass, right, or the whole bucket into hydrogen and oxygen. No one was ever able to do that. It cannot be done.
So water stops and at that point that's when all the physicists and the scientists turn off the lights and leave and try to find an interesting party to go to because they can't look at the subject anymore.
Well, and that's really strange because that would indicate that there's actually more to it, wouldn't it, exactly. And in addition, you know, another strange thing that just sort of comes to my mind is, I don't know if you remember this from a few years ago.
And I'm not sure if there's companies in business anymore, but there was the company that claimed to add additional oxygen to the H2O, you know.
And that was sort of a weird health water thing that sort of came and went. I don't know if it's still a year old now.
We'll go down the line and you'll see what that if that makes sense later on as we keep discussing what's going on in water.
OK. Now, what's interesting about water just to, you know, because this can be of many, many hours just discussing the nature of water, but just to show how fantastic water is now.
What happened, what has happened there is we just showed how the over simplification of the label H2O is not true.
Right. Well, then what is true?
Well, what is true is, why don't we start discussing things that appear and disappear in reality right in front of us that no one discusses. Like, for example, if you ever see a thunder cloud come in and one that potentially will drop a lot of water on an area of a city or in the country or wherever you might be.
So, Roni, after the storm is over, you could see there is millions of tons of water if it covers many square miles because what I'm saying is roughly a gallon of water weighs about eight pounds or it's a cube that's about six and a half by six and a half by six and a half in weighs about eight pounds.
And if you've ever seen how much rain can fall down, if you measure all that over the square area, that is millions of tons of water.
Okay. Let me ask you, when you look at those clouds, do they look like they're being weighed down by millions of tons?
Well, no, not at all. And I've got to tell you something that's even more observable in case somebody might have missed what you just explained.
And if one just takes a glass or a bucket, some kind of container and puts it outside during rainfall, you collect, you know, a certain amount of inches, let's just say in your bucket, right?
And if you put out like what they call a five gallon paint bucket, you know, during a decent rainfall, you might very well pick yourself up a couple of pounds of water during a good, you know, substantial rainfall.
Right now, if you extrapolate from that, that over just the area of your town or the area of the nearest square mile, and you multiply it by the amount of water that's collected in that bucket, which could have only grabbed, you know, what are we talking about?
One soil left, you know, is circular, and you think about it, the amount of weight that that water would carry would be, well, greater than--
It's high-titanics, maybe a hundred titanics or rucotaneous over being held up by the clouds.
Yeah, and I'm just talking about, you know, a square mile or two that would be just the men, you know, you want to say titanics, we could talk about Mac trucks or--
Yeah, or building--
The way to buildings, you know, multiples like more than the way to the buildings that it's falling on, even.
If you think about it, so you look up at these clouds, and that doesn't make any sort of sense.
And there's no water in the clouds, and any pilot flies into the cloud to avoid the storm.
And it is not condensation.
Now, here's an interesting part. I was thinking maybe keeping it practical because anyone listening should be able to walk away from this conversation we're having and be able to improve their water quality.
But here's something to consider more on the extreme esoteric side is that typically the forecasters and the weather people tell you that the rain happens by moisture condensing around dust.
And that, of course, doesn't make any sense, but that's what people have bought and believed.
Now, there was a recent study a few years ago in Jerusalem, a few scientists decided to get the latest and the greatest toys, you know, scientific sensors and things like that.
And they measured the dust particles in the atmosphere and the amount of moisture.
And when the storm ensued, there was no correlation between the moisture in the air and the dust particles at all whatsoever.
There are many dust particles, or that much condensation, to make that much volume of measurable liquid water.
Now, just to finish off the esoteric side, a little bit, that's the practical side.
And the esoteric side was that they actually wrote in a paper and published it that it appears that a few nanoseconds, or microseconds, which is not milliseconds, microseconds, prior to the water forming,
it appeared that the water came out of nowhere, it just formed out of nowhere.
And this was on the internet for a little while, and they pulled it.
The entire thing has been pulled, the people have been redacted, you know, their names have been pulled and all that.
And they had spent over five years studying this.
So, this is very similar to the discussion you and I had about the container, the human body, as the body is under a slight vacuum condition.
And people, maybe, I don't know if I'm speaking too fast, or these are new ideas, they're seen in the chat once, someone saying on a replay on AFR,
the Greeks had the bodies under a vacuum, how come when I cut my cell files so bleed?
And the thing is, we say the bodies under a slight vacuum condition.
So, when you cut yourself, the vacuum is broken, and when the vacuum is broken, you wait for it to equalize, and then the blood starts to flow out.
So, that's, I just wanted to bring that up. But the reason I brought up the body is because when you sweat, so your skin is not porous, even though you have these things called pores, they're only skin deep, you know, no pun intended.
They're small, avoid shape depressions under the skin, and they stop right there.
And the moisture forms in them, and then it's ejected out of the pore in the form of sweat.
Where does the water come from if the skin is impervious? You see, and this is the entire crux of the matter is that when mankind, I used to always say, when mankind masters water, he will master the physical world.
And it's astonishing to see how people have fallen for the H2O idea, and all of the reasoning and folklore surrounding what water is.
Now, I want to get maybe further on down the road on the other things, because we've also covered the idea of what water may not be H2O, and maybe get into some of the meat and potatoes, or the actual wet stuff that people can grab and use.
Because at this point, I think we've done enough to kick the establishment and the shins about what nonsense they're procuring about, what water is perceived, or their science around it.
At this point, we could get into the fact that people do collect and store water for various purposes.
One might collect it for drinking, or it's collected in your water tanks in your house, or whatever, for various purposes.
There's been a lot of things that have gone into the way water is stored.
Pretty interesting that I'm still fascinated by the idea that a cloud contains no water, how does it actually produce, and of course they scrub that.
We could spend another quick second, there's something called field effects, not baseball or football field, but a field like how people are worried about Wi-Fi, micro waves, cell phone towers.
You don't see it, feel it, there are devices that can measure these fields that can be harmful, like electromagnetic radiation. Those are fields.
Water is a byproduct of a biological field effect. It's called the ancient's called the Eifer, that was also part of the science up until the 1920s, and it was squashed with relics of his and with Einstein, where everyone went really dumb, those were made in dummy load.
Imagine the world of Gene Roddenberry and Star Trek. It's not that difficult to imagine the concept of field effects in science fiction.
We're being attacked, trying to on the force field, or the food replicator, or being a board ship. These are fields that do these things.
Generally speaking, what it is is something that affects the environment, so that things don't behave in precisely the way they would in an unaffected environment.
Whether it's the force field, or something else, in other words, it interacts, it actually changes the environment, so that different constituents, once again, participating in that environment,
would then have different results to their motion, to their interactivity, things like that. For instance, the idea of shields, or the force fields, or whatever, you know, you haven't changed the weapon being fired, you haven't changed the ship, but you have erected a field as a buffer, because that's the purpose of it, but not every field is necessarily a buffer.
It may actually change, and the force field can actually stop physical matter. But you don't see it. Very similar to magnetism. You can have two magnets in your hand, and you could feel them either attracting or repulsing if you flip them around.
It's almost like when you have them in repulsion mode, and you push them together, especially if they're weak magnets, or stand most magnets, you feel like there's like a jelly substance in there.
It's like a jelly kind of feeling, like you're pushing on a soft rubber or some jello or something, and when you pull the magnets apart, that jelly doesn't fall to the floor. It's just gone, easy.
So these are all field effects that create the water, from basically nothing, but it's not nothing, just like when electricity will be understood in the future as it was 100 years ago, that it's all field effects.
I've cut wires many times, very carefully, while there was electrical voltage and current going through them. I cut them very carefully one at a time, not to short them. And I was always prepared with a dust pan for all the millions of electrons that were going to fall out of the wire.
I still haven't found them.
It's a field that runs between the wires. Once we, as a society, as a WE, because I'm still here, as a society, decide to accept the obvious, what is really going on in front of us, not what we're just being told about these things, we'll be able to group together and then have a true consensus on reality.
But right now everyone is just very glad to do about what they're doing, which is nothing wrong with that. Everyone has their own pursuit. And when they want to know about water or electricity or anything else, they have to go to these court of court experts because that's their field and they have to trust them because people are too busy doing what they want to do.
And right now all of these experts don't know what's going on and they're just in deliberately, in most cases, the population. And to actually get into the field science on how water is produced is quite as cauteric.
But with one understands the analogy of the gene rod and very stark-trick idea, how there were things behind that to do that when men understands the field science is then he can synthesize the field and execute the field.
And some of us can do it at this point, some of us meaning surface dwelling, earth and habitat, and it's not good for one's health to do even on a call like this to discuss too much of that side because you know what I mean, that's not good for your health, right?
So just moving on, one of the other items here I was thinking about getting to the nuts and bolts of things where people can actually hear this and walk away with something practical is what I always like to do.
It's kind of like if you see someone with a bleeding thumb, you know, you say, well wrap this around instead of saying, hey, your thumbs bleeding, yeah, I know jerk off, you know, what do you got? You know, help them, right?
You got to say something, you got to do something when there's a need, you know, and the reason I'm saying it that way is because you can go on the internet right now and you find all kinds of stuff about water, heavy water, light water, structured water, oxygen water, miracle water, healing water, living water, it's all garbage, it's all rubbish.
None of them get into the nuts and bolts, even got some old guy, you know, running around talking about, you know, whatever, whatever, and some young guy, you know, that looks real earthy crunchy.
And, anyway, these people are water experts, supposedly, and I listen to their stuff and try to communicate with them and say, why don't you just mention some of the basic points?
And they never answer. And just like the scientists who cannot explain why a bucket of water is way more than a bucket of air.
So one of the reasons I think we're doing this also is so people can walk away with some basic knowledge that works in a very simple approach. Now I think we over, over maybe beat that esoteric course in the beginning, but I think it's important for people to get anything, any information that kicks academia in the shins is worthwhile.
Right. And I have no problem with doing multiple angles of establishing shot for the short film here, because it is necessary to be sure that it has been covered from as many angles as possible so that no one is shocked by the information which is meant to follow.
So that's why I think it was worthwhile to beat that horse a bit. Oh yeah. And the thing is their criminality. See, whatever you have a high level of criminality and misdemeanor, the language is very strong.
And it's not that I'm angry at them. Actually, if it was going to be any anger, just content it should be to the masses. Why are they still supporting these academics?
All the colleges in the university should become homeless, shelters, museums, or storage rooms. There is no purpose for them or entertainment, whatever. Right. There is no purpose for them anymore in this society. They are nothing but a parasitic entity. And that's the Greek opinion. And it's been that way for 30 years.
But I hope it becomes more people's opinion we might actually end up with something which I discuss will be coming in the future a short age of reason.
But to go back to reason, we did want to make sure we discuss storage because this is a practical thing.
After all, water must be stored in order to be utilized, no matter what its components are, what its constituents are. I mean, as we said at the very beginning, it's one of the essentials to, well, efficient living.
One must have water in order to preserve life, I mean, essentially, not to mention the fact that it serves many other purposes.
But the fact is, it's one of the staples of life that is often overlooked, especially in what they call, you know, more civilized, modern society, et cetera, et cetera.
It's certainly one of those sort of given staples. And the storage of it is worth examining, I think.
The history is, it needs to be examined first, whenever I come across anything new, I always try to find its history.
Very young children that play video games now, if you ask them, they don't know, they think video games have been around always.
Until they learn the history of it and it's development. Now, when we look at the history of water storage, and what I mean by water storage,
it means that the water now is not flowing from point A to point B, as simple as that. If water is not going from point A to point B in its storage mode or in non-movement mode,
when mankind interacted with any liquid, as a matter of fact, not just water, but oils, milk, perfumes, any kind of liquid matter.
Throughout history, they kept it in vessels that were all-void shape. All-void is just a term describing something that might look pure like an egg.
Not a cube, not a pyramid, not a sphere, but egg-shaped. One can reference this by the ancient Amphoras.
You can go on the internet or any reference material you so choose, and look up what an Amphora is. A-M-P-H-O-R-A.
It's just a Latin or Greek term, actually, for a vessel. And these vessels, if you, anyone has ever had any memory of looking at any ancient shipwrecks from museums,
you would see these vases that didn't have flat bottoms, they had pointy bottoms, they couldn't stand up on their own. It looks almost like a urns, right?
And the common modern person would say, look how stupid the ancient were, they couldn't design a vase with a flat bottom, so it could stand up on its own. Why did they have to have a pointy side on the bottom?
Interesting. And also you'll notice that in nature, whenever water is not flowing from point A to point B, and water is in, I don't like to use the word "saggent," but it is proper to stay in a stagnant mode, it is contained in an ovoid shape.
For example, the eyeball is slightly ovoid, right? The eggs are ovoid, right? There's liquid in eggs.
The testicles, the ovaries, some of the organs in the body tend to take on an ovoid shape. In the plant kingdom, you will see seeds take on an ovoid shape.
What that means, essentially, it is roughly circular, but it is not symmetrical. One end is slightly blunter than the other that is slightly pointy, or so you have a pointy end and a blunt end. That's what makes the ovoid shape.
This is what was thought after to store liquids. Now the question is why did they use ovoid shapes?
Because when you have something that is a sphere, let's say, let's stick with the round stuff, not a cube or a box, or just like the square rectangular containers you get milk and juice is in the store now, or clear plastic or glass bottles with flat bottoms, let's get away from that concept.
Stick with the concept of the ovoid for a minute. Why not a sphere or a ball? You see, because when you have a sphere, by definition, the center point is equidistant from the outer, any point on the outer part of the sphere.
So any movement that takes place inside the sphere will always find a resting point in the center and then stagnation sets in.
You see, so then you have the water being stagnant, because even if you kept it moving, once the movement stopped, by the symmetry of the shape, everything would stop moving on its own.
Now, if you have a, let's say, let's make it elliptical, let's just pinch the two ends. Well, you still have an asymmetric point, the center moves slightly, and the material inside the elliptical container will move from point to point, back and forth, and then eventually find that adjusted center and settle in and become saglin again.
When you have an ovoid shape, where one end of the circular or curved container is slightly pointier than the opposite side, you still have a geometric center, but not a true mass center for energetic purposes.
So if you got liquid moving, what would happen is the liquid would move to the blunt end, come back to the center, move to the pointy end, and it would change its form, because it's in a 3D manner.
Try to move back to the center, but then pass the center and go back to the blunt end. So this would be this asymmetric reflection that would keep any liquid or gas moving and avoid stagnation.
This flight is, even a tenth of a degree temperature difference, anywhere on the container will set the liquid into motion if it's ovoid, very simply.
Because of the lack of symmetry, the energy, the liquid, the gas in an ovoid shape will always be in constant motion with the slightest impulse from the exterior environment.
That is why they always thought ovoid containers, because stagnation, absolute stagnation or stillness is where things start to breed.
So they were able to keep water fresh. And also by the way, when you have an ovoid shape, you'll always notice the liquids in the container are always slightly less than ambient, where if there are any other shapes, the liquids rushed very quickly to stabilize until the same temperature is the ambient temperature.
Which is very interesting as well. Now this is the concept of the Amphora, which is what the ancients used. And even up until I would say the 19th century, it was considered a standard way of storing liquids.
Well actually, I would say about 17th century started to go away. By the 19th century when the industrial revolution came in, that standard was still capped to some degree. But they started introducing flat bottoms so they can stack things.
Right, because they had big wagons and trucks and trains to move things. And they found that they needed the volume of space. Things now were being transported greater distances, so they wanted to be more efficient.
So they started eventually. That's why when you look at the older bottles from the 19th century, that cook bottle shape, you see they knew that the flat bottom in it was bad, but they put a double curve in it. Hopefully that would mitigate some of the flat bottom, you know, or the wine bottle, you know, as a curved top.
Like the bottom sort of puckers up a bit. And in that way you don't have an absolutely flat bottom, but you have something that can stabilize itself, at least the container can, you know, on a flat surface.
But you still have that sort of arch that's there. And I guess that's meant to partially mitigate the problem of stillness in the liquid.
In the beginning of the bottles were more curved and they introduced the flat bottoms. The pucker also depends on the amount of pressure that will build up. And also just having the bottom edge of the bottle making contacts so it doesn't slide around.
If you look champagne bottles have an extreme puckers so they can get to the 100 PS thigh in their pounds per square inch.
But the idea of compressing liquids into a small space, not compressing them in themselves, but as many stacking as many containers as possible, going for that efficient stacking has ruined the ability for liquid to maintain a certain quality level.
And it does ruin the quality because even if you keep the milk at a certain temperature, milk in an overweight container will taste better. And also once oil is quickly even if it was not refrigerated.
So one has to keep in their mind that these ancients were not primitive or savage for understanding the concept of the amphora, or the overweight or the egg shape.
So basically taught this from time immemorial until they forgot the importance of it and was overshadowed by the importance of modern industry, let's say.
So the water storage idea is something that would be difficult for anyone to incorporate in their lives by going out to the store and buying it is very difficult to go out and buy any liquid already in that shape or even finding containers in that shape.
But it is good to know that it is the optimum size because within your life you might make a decision to either pursue that and find overweight shaped containers and prop them up on stands or such.
And do your own experimentation because part of what we're discussing here is far into the modern convention and would require some experimentation for the user.
Well, right, like instantly I'm thinking to myself to have a container that is useful and in that shape, I imagine to myself that I would have to create a rack of sorts to put them in a place so that they were less cumbersome as far as taking up additional space and things like that.
And I could stack any shape container that way onto the flat surfaces, the shelves, etc. of whatever it was I was trying to stack them on but that requires a little extra work because I dare say they don't offer anything like that at your local Walmart.
Or even in the decorative let's say one goes out and says well I need let's say glass or porcelain or metal or whatever containers in that shape, you're going to be pretty hard pressed to find it on any search.
And just meaning referring to the marketplace now. Right. Yeah, you're going to be difficult to find. But this is very important to understand because it is one of the principle, principle geometric forms that is required to maintain high quality liquid storage.
And this is not only for something that reflects man's good stewardship of these liquids, not just water, oils or milks and things like that, but it also reflects what is going on in nature with the egg itself and parts of plants and parts of the human body even which have that old-wage shape of water is not moving from point A to point B.
And it does give me a sensible understanding of why an egg is shaped the way it is because I often wonder that actually it seems rather odd that an egg has that shape it must be for some practical purpose as I observe in nature of the things that do prevail and continue to exist or always the things that you know persistent based on the fact that they are the most effective and efficient.
So, you know, if a chicken was born and it was somehow dropping square eggs, I dare say it would not survive into the next generation or something. No. It would disappear as an aberration. So the things that do seem to have longevity in nature have a practical sort of a practical basis to them in their functionality.
So that is why the egg is shaped the way it is kind of deal. And these are creations. If you subscribe to Evolution or whatever, you know, have fun at a good luck as they say and see you later.
But if you see that there is a commonality, all biological things, all machines, even songs in music, literary writings, anything in everything that is created has a basic fundamental common denominator in it.
For example, let's go to music for example, it doesn't matter what music you are writing or genre. There are fundamental common denominators in terms of timing and chords and things like that.
All music share or musicians use or composers use or even the people performing the music must be familiar with. Even if you have never read sheet music, there are fundamentals in making music that all genres share.
You will find this in machines also all machines, whether it is a car and airplane or railroad, an old typewriter, any machine you can imagine they all share certain fundamental common denominators in how mechanisms work.
And you will also see these common denominators in nature. And wherever there is a liquid in nature that is not moving from point A to point B, you will always find it in an old void shape.
And the liquid, when I say liquid, it could be something that is like a seed as well, which is not liquid. Now, why would a seed also take on an old void shape to some extent if there is no liquid in it?
And that also explains what we consider to be hydrodynamic within the egg is that way because there is an incoming force that also affects things that are seeds.
Because these are still have some liquid matter in them. So it could even be a semi-liquid material. And an example here, just to send this idea home in another way, is I once saw an image of a north of Norway where they were doing a worldwide universal seed bank.
And in case there was a worldwide calamity, they were storing all these seeds in a mountain under the ice. Are you familiar with that story and maybe about five, six years ago?
Oh sure. They still talk about it from time to time. The heirloom seed vault.
Yeah, seed vault. Now, when I really laughed my ass off when I saw what they were doing, because they had these cubicle pallets of seeds that were stacking.
And I was discussing this with someone and I said, "If they ever pull those cubicle pallets out, only the seeds that would be within the pallet that would be an imaginary egg.
If you were to, let's say, use a computer graphic and do a dotted line of an egg inside of that pallet, only the seeds in that zone would be viable.
All of the other seeds, like in the quarters of the pallets of that cube, would not be viable. Why?" You see, because the, not only is the egg shaped container being imposed to hold the liquid important, but it also plays a part in these field effects that we were discussing earlier.
So this is another aspect of understanding the overwage shape.
Right. Now, how does, you know, I've heard you mention several times before a guy named Victor Schauberger.
Yes, right. Now, how does he come into this discussion?
Okay, Victor Schauberger is important to consider, because if we speak about electricity and we bring up someone like Thomas Edison or Nicola Tessaly,
it seems the conversation seems to flow well because those are people that are well known in that field. But when we bring up the concept of water,
still when you've mentioned Victor Schauberger out in public, most people have still not heard of him. Not that he deserves shame or infamy, but he has pretty much gained the ranks of a Nicola Tessaly or, let's say, Thomas Edison type person in the field of water.
Okay. And what's interesting about this, and ironic is, you know, you can live without electricity, right? And that sounds like a ridiculous question or a statement to some, but yeah, I sure you people live quite well without it.
Oh, yeah. But can you live without water?
Well, no, as we stated at the very beginning of this discussion, it's one of the essentials.
Yeah, so part of a part of the human society is certain people might gain certain knowledge and it's through duty and responsibility to themselves and their creator and to their fellow man to share that knowledge when they see it's not available, right?
And that's why we attribute fame to Tesla and Edison and people like that.
Right, because they were the individuals who sort of codified certain bits of knowledge, at least that's the way it's understood.
Not necessarily, they were the people who, you know, originated the idea or anything like that, but they are the ones who sort of put it together in a digestible format in one way or another.
And that we can use. Now Victor Schraubberger's work has all been set aside, but the work that he did, none the less was very important in critical.
If anyone can access his work and Victor would be spelled with a K and the Schraubberger would be with an S-T-H-A-U-B-E-R-G-E-R.
And he was an Austrian, came from a long family of foresters. He lived, he was born in the late 1800s and lived till the mid-20th century.
And being a forester, he had discovered that certain things that were not being discussed, that certain qualities of water that were not being discussed or acknowledged as being significant.
And being a forester, he was able to walk through the forests in the mountains and view undisturbed water courses and he discovered certain phenomenon.
Now some of the phenomena that he discovered regarding water, he was able to apply and transfer over into the physical realm in terms of technology and copy water movement.
And the geometric forms that formed in water moved and make machines that mimic that, those movements and found that those machines had a, was just, get technical for a moment, an incredible hysteresis cycle that allowed them to once they were cranked up and ran and begin to run, they seemed to have run almost autonomously.
And they would actually keep accelerating on their own without any extra input. It was based on something called a biological vacuum that he described.
Now that is not why, essentially, we should discuss Victor Schroberg, but that was pretty much his whole, all of his endeavors in a nutshell, was his observation and then his accomplishment, his technical accomplishments.
But before we get to his technical accomplishments, some of the things that he laid down that were quite important about water is that the quality, not just the quantity of water, but the quality of water must be addressed.
And what I mean by that and what he meant by that is that right now mankind, even today and even back then, was always addressing the quantity of water.
In other words, if you're a farmer, you needed X amount of millions of liters to water your crops and it was a quantity. If you were going on a camping trip or, you know, you needed X amount of water to go camping or if you were to build a house, you need a water heater with this many gallons of water.
But no one really discussed the quality, they always discussed water in quantity.
Right, even when they talk about, you know, droughts and rainy seasons and excessive saturation of certain land masses and things like that, it's always about the volume and the effects of the volume of the water.
Quite honestly, yeah, the quality of the water is there in the process.
There's only discussed in that, you know, purification is something that's necessary. That's about the extent of the discussion of quality is purification.
Now, that's kind of an odd sort of way to approach it, being that it is one of these, you know, very essential things in life.
One would consider that not only is the quantity important because you do need a certain amount, I imagine, in order to create certain effects in order to, you know, produce a certain living organisms, you know, to be able to live efficiently, etc.
But you would think that the quality of the water would also be important.
Yes, and the purification part of the water, again, they only address the absence of certain chemicals or the presence of other chemicals as being quality.
Right.
Which I don't see that as being qualitative again, it's quantitative again because they'll tell you, well, if you have this much uranium or arsenic in the water, you know, then it's bad.
And if you should have none of that and you should have this, again, it's quantity, quantity, quantity, whatever.
Yeah.
And directly it's quantity as in the contaminant versus the water.
It's how much contaminant, yeah.
Right. And the percentage of contaminant, how much you can remove and how much is acceptable and things like that.
So it is again a quantitative look at water as opposed to a qualitative look at water.
Yeah, absolutely. Now I'm going through the computer file, because I want to bring up some ideas and I have got to, or something, people can look up and maybe through this conversation, I will.
And one, one of the ideas I want to bring up and this is a fact, and I'm just going to throw this in before we get into the quality that when water reaches a certain quality, it becomes a levitative.
Okay. Yes, not necessarily like, you know, you would levitate that like from the seat you're sitting in.
But what I mean by that is there's, in, I think it's the Czech Republic, there's a certain region in the Czech Republic where they have their own secret top secret facility, their own area 51, if you will.
Okay. Now it has nothing to do with aliens or flying saucers or anything like that. You'll find it's a fence-dough area heavily guarded and it's a linear area.
And what you will discover is they have fenced off a river and no one can approach it. Now why would they have to fence off this river?
Because over its water course of several kilometers, it actually flows uphill. Yes, you heard me right.
Uphill. Uphill, slightly. Over several kilometers, I would say it's over a dozen or two dozen meters uphill over that distance.
The very slight slope, it would look pretty flat by the eye, but if you were to come out there with a surveyor, you know, a theodiliter laser and do it to topographical map, you will see that the elevation rises in the direction as the river,
in the direction that the river is flowing, which is completely contradictory to one of the most basic phrases I've always heard, which is war flows downhill. That's right.
That's why it's fenced off and it's their area 51. And I was going to give the exact location I'm looking at. It's on another computer and maybe we'll just put, we'll write it in.
I'll also apply that later underneath the audio file. I don't seem to be pulling it up here and I don't think it's on the internet. I just tried a few searches for it.
So how can water do that? How can water be so in-live and so levitative that it would do that? That's an interesting question. Victor Scharberger had observed these things.
Now, the main thing that he observed is that water was most active when it was cool and in the shade, not exposed to sunlight, and even further active at certain times of the month during a full moon.
In the cooler times of the year, when it meant the water being more active, there's the streams and the books and the rivers ran quicker without eroding their banks.
And the wildlife was more lively and the water quality was better. And what he's surmised also by watching water is that water tends to be self-organizing into a vortex that funnel shape that we call a tornado, let's say.
Very common geometric form that we are used to recognising that is the self-organizing condition that water takes when it's moving from point A to point B. As it water is flowing, it will form vertical vortices or horizontal depending on the terrain and also the quality of the water.
So his main attribute that can be shared with anyone is initially to recognise the quality of the water is depending on its surrounding features.
If it's being stored, it would be in an old-void container in the dark and kept cool.
And if it's moving from point A to point B, the water body is being accommodated. What I mean by the water body is he pretty much discussed something called the water body.
For example, if you walk to a clothing store, you recognise the clothing based on the human anatomy, a glove, a hat, a shoe, those items of clothing are designed with certain geometric shapes to accommodate the human body, the anthropomorphic form.
So if you were to study all fluids in nature, if you were to look in a mirror and look at the blood vessels in your eye, or if you were to uproot a tree and study the geometric patterns of a tree root, or if you were to look at a map of an undisturbed river, you will notice that the geometric forms of those three things I mentioned, the blood vessels, the roots of a tree are a plant and natural river course, is they all share almost identically the same geometric forms.
Now that is not what people say at Sequence Instance, but it coincides with what that is the shape that the water body has.
Fluids tend to assume that body shape when they're moving. So when they move from point A to point B, they do it in a meandering course.
Very much as they snake would move or an inchworm or a worm, you notice how they contract their bodies and then they stretch them out for forward movement.
And there's a breaking action in the back and a sliding action in the front to move the body forward, if they want to move in reverse, they put the breaking action in the front and the sliding action in the back for a snake or a worm or an inchworm, you see?
Now water moves that way as well. So now if you were to push something uphill, Chuck, and you want it, this day you start moving the third of the way uphill and you want to take a break, you need to, no pun intended here,
have something that would act as a break on what you're pushing the uphill so you can stop and then continue forward, right?
Well let's say you had a, you were rolling a cart that can only move forward and if you try to move back it would stop. Like it had a gear that would stop it from moving back, like being in drive in a car versus reversed.
So when water has this meandering feature, it creates a force behind it that is a breaking action that prevents its reversal and the front part of the water tends to move it forward when it's in a very high state of quality.
Now what we just did there is explain how the river can flow up an incline. It's almost like it's a living, it takes on the most primordial and most basic of living, what would you say, mechanics of mobility is exhibited in natural water courses.
Now and also just to go back to the ovoid shape real quick, a raindrop is the only liquid that takes on that classic raindrop shape which is ovoid, it's pointy on the trailing end and on the leading end, it's more round, okay?
Yeah and well even though the water itself is moving from point A to point B within the drop it is not moving but kept in live and by that raindrop shape. Now why did they bring up the raindrop shape just to go back to the ovoid is what's interesting about that is that you could spill at high altitude, any other liquid, whether it's oil, paint, ink, anything that's not water, it will not take that, take on that raindrop shape.
Any other liquid dropped from altitude will fall to the ground as amissed, very interesting, okay? So there's a specific quality what we're discussing here is the water body and this is what Victor Schalberger's work was based on and just like Edison with the light bulb, let's say he did many other things but let's say when you say light bulb you say you think Edison, right?
Or Tesla wireless transmission of power, Victor Schalberger's claim to fame would be that water actually has a body and this is what it looks like. Now one of the commentaries that he made for example is if you look at how mankind is handling water right now, if you look at the canals or the channels or the plumbing that he builds, you notice that all the pipes in the canals and channels and things that are not.
That are made through engineering are straight. Yes, all the plumbing in your house, but that's like putting water in a straight jacket.
And you end up the water can no longer have this meandering effect and what it ends up doing is it ends up eating away at the walls of the pipes or whatever is holding it.
Whether it's a canal, they'll have erosions. If you have plumbing, it'll start to eat away at the pipe. You see, just like if you put someone in a straight jacket they might want to start gnawing away at it.
Well, and also if you try and say you put your foot into a shoe which is not properly shaped for your foot, what will happen is eventually the force of just your physical body being in that shoe will begin to create pressure on the garment that will the garment will either take the shape of the shoe or it will burst eventually.
And this is why we have erosions in the breakdown of plumbing, I think, based on what you've said so far. It should not run in a straight line because it's not in accord with the water body.
And it sounds very simple and it sounds very contradictory to basic engineering because we just want to move things from point A to point B.
As long as it doesn't leak, it doesn't matter. This is the attitude that's being taken. And another thing, Schroberger, discussed is when water is moving in this straight jacket form, it starts to create negative or let's say, feel negative fields, negative being not in charge but that are not conducive to a healthful condition in the environment.
And he had done an interesting chart back in the 40s that he noticed that some of the government officials were quite upset that 3% or 2% of the population was coming down with cancers.
It was just over 1%, it was between 1 and 3% and he said the more of this type of straight canal, straight plumbing that you're doing the more your cancer rates will go up.
And he actually did a chart where he showed by the 1950s it will be 5% by the 60s, it will be so much and by the 80s and 90s it will be 30% and by the year 2020 or so he said it will be about 50% of the population will be coming down with cancer.
And by 2050, 90% of the population will have cancer because the way water is being handled.
And if you actually look at a lot of the academic works on how many people are getting cancer today in the early 2000s and look at their records, what they have in their records, the crack academics, it's almost identical to what he predicted in the 1940s.
Well, you have observed this several times and wondered why actually there has been such an exponential increase in what they call cancer.
And it is apparent, there is no way to argue that it has been increasing exponentially.
This would be a really almost laughable simple answer as to why it is increasing so rapidly.
If we were to find one constituent that needed in society in the physical world that needed to be addressed immediately would be how water is handled first.
Forget about the fluoride, the chlorine and all that other stuff that they are telling you are the bad stuff in the water.
You must change the way the water is being handled.
I was once doing some correspondence with a pretty high, muckety muck person in Australia, minister level type person and he said, what can we do in Australia to improve the water quality here?
And I said, you have to pull out every piece of plumbing and read you every canal so it meanders like it does in nature.
And he says, that's never going to happen. And I said, well, you just answered your own question. You're never going to improve your water quality then.
And that's why very often when I speak, I don't like disgusting things that are hopeful because if I do discuss things that are hopeful they sound so far and so bizarre.
So the chances of all the plumbing in the world being replaced with pipes that look like blood vessels, let's say, or roots of a tree is pretty much null to zero.
There is no hope in expecting the water quality to get better. So let's move on to the next subject. But within the same subject, what can one do within their own environment to understand how to mitigate this?
And just to touch back on the cancer idea, when these fields are being emitted by water moving as it does and being conveying the quality because it's not been handled properly first.
That affects the field and the body. Now, there's something called cancer and what's not being discussed in mass but has been known by some and discussed by some is what are called cancerous tumors and cancer conditions or things that can appear in a body in minutes or hours.
It's not something typically that yes takes years of, let's say, poor health management to lead to or bad food. Yes, it's that as well. But the actual physical condition of a tumor and things, those things can appear overnight or in minutes where they were, you know, we're talking about, you know, someone getting a scan of their brain and then five minutes later getting another scan and there's a walnut-sized tumor there.
It's like, where did that thing come from? You see, this is the idea of field science, the concept of things appearing very quickly and disappearing very quickly.
That's why there is someone called Lakowski. Back in the early 20th century, he had these thing called Lakowski coils. He built these two antennas that you sat between.
He basically pumps very high pulse voltage through these antenna rings and people that had very terminal diseases either got better or rid of them within hours or days. They just disappeared.
Now, what do you think is, what are you impressing on the individual? If you're sitting, imagine sitting in a chair and there's been antenna something like a circular antenna, four feet to your right and another antenna four feet to your left.
And nothing is touching you and this type of therapy is applied for, let's say, a few minutes, a couple of times a week and your condition just reverses.
That is a field of fact, is a field therapy. There is nothing known as poking or prodding your administering. There's nothing in your rubber in your body or drink or take, you see?
We're looking at Ghiblikowski as an idea here because if he had so much success with field effect therapy as such, could you imagine the negative consequences of the fields that are coming out off of water running through straight pipes along?
It's massive and if one were to really contemplate it and be able to discern it, it would be almost like the industrial world is a nightmare reality.
And meanwhile, like I said earlier, when you started to say, what can one do about these things? Obviously you provided the concept of what might be imagined as far as affecting fields and what could be changed about water and it was changed the way it was handled through the plumbing etc.
Well, that would be great but it seems rather impractical and one of those things that can't be realized at this point. But I did bring up earlier this concept of adding oxygen to the water.
And people have talked about the different qualities of water because there's minerals in it and all these other things. But those are really additives.
The gas and the minerals, yes. Well, let's just get into the proper handling and enrichment and health. Let's say those other items wanted to discuss.
You ever notice when you put a glass of water on a table, you come back half hour or so later and your bubbles stuck to the glass?
Sure. That's because of dissolved gases in the water. So when you're holding up a glass or a container of water, there are dissolved gases in there. And when the water stops moving, a lot of the gas is kind of shuttled out.
There's either, it's not a photosynthesis but a photo, there's a term for, technical term for it, when light affects water or any objects, it changes it slightly, right?
We're talking about, we're not talking about plants now, we're talking about just water and liquids and things like that. Some people can get a dental treatment where they use light to set the epoxy and things like that.
Light has an effect on water that will either change its quality, bring up dissolved gases and such.
Now when we're looking at the water body in its purest form for human consumption, we all stay spring water, right? Like the best water to drink is spring water from the mountains to the spring.
Well water, okay, tap water, whatever, you know, bottled water, you know, however, but this source is always touted as being the highest quality from the spring.
Now what's interesting about the spring water quality, you know, it's not the location, but it is the location. In other words, the spring water itself has a quality that can be synthesized.
In other words, it can be recreated. But right now because of the way commerce, industry, understanding, education about water, people are still pursuing the spring water because it was known throughout humanity.
That was the highest quality water to drink. Now the many springs that existed and still do the highest quality for drinking water would be typically two thirds up a mountain, not at low elevation.
Lower elevation springs tend to be warmer and carbonated. Now what is drawing the water out of the high altitude and makes it such a high quality?
When the water passes through the earth, and by the way, if you ever see some spring water companies that say, well this is like 5,000 year old or 10,000 year old or teesion water, that's all crap.
Water tends to move healthy water, or water in good condition tends to move at about 10 feet per second or 3 meters per second underground.
If water is moving faster, it's doing something else and probably causing earthquakes somewhere. And if it's moving slower, it's becoming heavily acidified and it starts to warm up.
So there is no such thing as a 5,000 or 7,000 year old water or anything like that because there is a tremendous lattice and plumbing underneath the earth.
The water is constantly moving at a pretty good rate. And what I mean by 10 feet per second if you're standing by it, you threw your baseball cap in the water, count one second, the baseball cap is 10 feet away from you. It's pretty quick.
So this is the condition of what we consider good spring water underground. And by that point it is degast.
What I mean by degast that is abstent of gas is, so this is maybe indirectly addressing, what if we pump oxygen in the water? What are we doing? Are we increasing the quality of the water or decreasing the quality of the water?
You're decreasing the quality of the water, right? Now in one slide they're telling you oxygen is good and that's why you need more of it.
But in the future mankind will discover that there is oxygen, yes, it's necessary in the air as a catalyst, but you're really breathing nitrogen and the lungs convert nitrogen into oxygen and sit too, which is kind of strange to discuss.
Maybe we can get into that some other time about the hell. But you're really, the only oxygen that you need in the air is a catalyst to stimulate the pulsing gas known as nitrogen and the oxygen is created in the lung.
So similarly to water, water shreds itself, or vaults, is all gases. And once it gets to that point it becomes more resistant. And also when it's at four degrees Celsius or 39 degrees Fahrenheit, which is its optimum temperature, and we can get into that as well, it becomes resistant to a magnetic field.
And so it becomes what's called diamagnetic. Diamagnetism might be something that people see in superconductive experiments where they freeze a piece of, when they put an iron or magnet over helium and it tends to float over the liquid helium.
Okay, that is diamagnetism where it kind of does not want magnetic lines to pass through it. And now we have this diamagnetic water that is flowing underground, there is no gases dissolved in it. And as it sees the mountain crevice, the gases are actually in the atmosphere, actually sucking the water up out of the mountain very much like one would use a straw to suck liquid out of a container like a soft drink or something.
And this is the apparatus of how springs work. Now what they'll tell you is in academia is that springs are geothermal, but how can they be geothermal when they come out almost ice cold at four degrees Celsius?
Zero degrees Celsius would be freezing, or 39 degrees Fahrenheit is four degrees Celsius, which is only seven degrees away from freezing again. We're begins to freeze.
So water to judge it if it's in good quality would be absent of light and at 39 degrees Fahrenheit. Now fortunately most refrigerators in the western world, if you were to hang up a thermometer in most refrigerators, guess what they read?
39 degrees and when you shut the floor, it's dark.
Now this is the idea of spring water. Now personally, myself and a few other people, we were studying Shawberger about, well I've been studying them for over 12 years, but we studied, I brought it to the table that they wanted to start a small business.
And I said, what do we get into synthesizing spring water? We can take any water and turn it into the highest quality water on the planet, bar none. And we did that successfully.
And we built the apparatus. This is actually mimicked the way the earth creates spring water, you know, degassing the water in an avoid shape and creating a biological vacuum. Go figure.
So we succeeded at this point. So from this point on, we're speaking from experience, how can we practically import information that the listener can use with just regular household daily things that they come in contact with without having to build special apparatus as we did that we actually mimicked Victor Shawberger's equipment, which some of the equipment took 15 years to build back in the 1930s that he did.
We were able to achieve that in a matter of a few months. And we actually achieved the water quality that he was speaking of. Now how can we take the principle that is not almost seemingly not discussed by anyone?
They want to do all these funky things to water. They want to structure it or they tell you about pie water or I don't know if that's a brand name, I should have said it. Or just this ridiculous bunk about water.
And what we're looking at is the water. And what we're looking at is the water quality. And what we're looking at is the water quality. And what we're looking at is the water quality.
Now also wanted to ask, can we take a five minute break and come back to pause the audio or would that be all right? Well, yeah, I could probably just cut it out.
I don't want to interrupt the recorder, but I could just cut it out. So be back in five minutes. Sure.
Okay. And you're me? Yes. All right. So where were we? Water quality. And let's tie all of these things together.
So we're going to talk about quality, quality, and what we're looking at. And maybe even not discussing that. I think if you say twice, you get a honey, right?
So the idea here is to not necessarily sum it up, because this could be a very long discussion, but let's just at this point. Maybe someone who could be listening on what they can do.
And then somebody at very little or no cost, depending on your resources right now, how can they improve the water quality that they have? Right? And this is mainly for consumption.
Well, what we talk about to work it was, which is the old name for consumption, but the actual taking in of water. Yeah. And by the way, you know, when they call you a consumer, what do you call someone who has consumption?
They're consumer or consumer. Yeah. So at this point, regarding the, how does one tie tie this concept? Okay, we're talking about water. What, what can anyone do? What, what can anyone do practically?
Now one has to consider there's a lot of talk and it's more than talk about what the municipal municipalities are doing with water adding chlorine and fluoride. And there's a new nasty thing they're doing now where they're adding also ammonia, which creates with the chlorine, which creates a chloramine compound, which is pretty nasty as well.
And also to address various well waters or rain collection waters, I've been discussing with some people they say they collect rainwater, only because they have no choice or off the grid, let's say, or any wall, what can one do?
Well, the first thing is to consider that waters of normally point is four degrees Celsius or 30 degrees Fahrenheit. And what I mean by that is the human anomaly point is 98.6.
Okay. Well, what do I mean by that? Well, let's say, I say Chuck, you know, my body temperature is 102 degrees. How do you think I feel?
Well, probably a bit too warm or 104 or 106 as an adult, you'd probably say you're not doing well and you're probably hurting yourself at this point.
Yeah, at this point, you're going to start to feel as if you're freezing my contrast with your environment because you're definitely running a fever, let's just say.
Yeah, well, you know what's interesting about that is just a little short thing. In colder climates, fevers are hot, in warmer climates, fevers are cold to the touch.
So this is another thing about the way biology works. But okay, so if I said Chuck, my body temperature is about a internally is about 90, you know, we've got hypothermia or the opposite of hypothermia.
I'm not doing well again. So I want it to be around the 98.6, right? To be in a healthful condition where I feel good and I can do things because if my temperature internal temperature is 90 or 105, I'm not going to get up.
I'm going to probably be horizontal, right? Or you may be a cooling corpse. Yeah.
Now, water's anomaly point is 39 degrees or 4 degrees Celsius. Okay, so if water is at let's say 50 or 55 degrees Fahrenheit or 10 or 15, let's say 10 degrees Celsius, it's no longer at that point where it's most healthful or it will do work or comply to doing anything.
That's why, for example, when you look at a lot of basic carbon filtration, carbon filters are the most common, whether they're picture or inline filters or whatever, and they tell you they have a do not use above 80 degrees, right, because the water, the efficiency of the filter drops to nothing.
Now, if you have the most basic available carbon filter, whether it's inline, they have these canisters or they have these things called picture filters now, right? So it'll cartridge suck in the middle.
Right? You want to start off with water that is as cool as possible. Now, when I see as cool as possible, not with frost in it because what's interesting again is we want to stay near the 4 degrees Celsius, 39 Fahrenheit.
Now, here's interesting thing about that and it's efficiency. At 39 degrees Fahrenheit or 4 degrees Celsius, water is its densest condition.
If the temperature is higher than that, water begins to expand and take in gases. Now, if the temperature drops from 4 degrees Celsius or 39 degrees Fahrenheit, it starts to expand again.
And if you don't believe me, to draw a water, put a lid on it, stick it in the freezer. Wait, and what happens? Right? Okay. So, yeah, so at 39 degrees water is its densest point.
And one of the things I like about a very old encyclopedia Britannica that I have is back in the day when encyclopedias were written, there were encyclopedia writing companies.
There were people that did that for the academics. And they didn't like the academics because they didn't get to have fancy parties in the towers or these were the encyclopedia writers.
Like nobody wanted to hang out with them, you know. So, they always wanted to put in little digs towards the academic. And you could see that they were writing the old encyclopedias.
And when you look up pre-1913 encyclopedia definition of water, these encyclopedia writers like to make fun of these scientists and they said, well, they said, you know, one gram is a cubic centimeter of water in the metric system.
But that's not really correct because they measured it at room temperature. So really, it's a centimeter of water at room temperature is really 0.999 grams. And we'll leave it at that, you know. So, the guys in some other words, the guys that wrote the encyclopedias are making fun at the scientists overlooking the fundamental quality of water.
So, yeah. Yeah, yeah. If we had more time, I'd pull it out and read it. But anyone could look up in an old encyclopedia. So, the idea here is, let's say you're passing water through what's called a filter. And in the industry, they call it scrubbing, believe it or not.
You know, when you scrub something, you know, it's like, you know, not someone on their hands and he's, let's say, on the floor or something. But it means cleaning in general terms.
Now, when you have water that's above 39 degrees or 4 degrees Celsius or below that, it's in an expansive mode and it likes to take in gas.
And when you're passing it through a filter medium that is scrubbing the water, cleaning the water, you have all these other things in there like gases that prevent the full contact with what you're trying to clean it with, you see.
Right? It's like little micro bubbles in the water. We can do that.
So, if you're going to increase the efficiency of any filtration system, you have to have the water as close to 39 degrees as possible.
Now, that will not be achieved in 99% of cases unless you have an in-line water chiller or you live in an area where the climate or the weather permits, I say more climate than whether permits that water to be so.
If you've seen some artesian wells or springs that have been tapped into, where the water comes out at 39 degrees or anywhere between 39 and 41 degrees Fahrenheit or 4 to 5 degrees Celsius all year round.
Those are the most fortunate people.
Okay? So, if anyone starts to get interested and wants to do more experimentation, just get a waterproof thermometer of some kind and go to your tap and whatever and start becoming more conscious of water temperature.
Just like, for example, when someone goes to be examined by a doctor, what are one of the first things the doctor does to examine the quality of your health takes your temperature?
That's one of the primary things he does, right?
So, the temperature of the water must be considered. The other thing is absence of light.
If you ever notice that water being stored in containers were light effects that you get things like algae and other things growing in it, right?
So, you have to keep it absent of light. These are the first two things to consider, your water temperature and absence of light.
Now, without really focusing on the municipal aspect where they're actually pumping in chlorine, ammonia, fluoride, and all these other things, we need to discuss if we're going to discuss what anyone can do to increase the quality of the water.
Let's consider all the waters, whether it's well water or rate of water or municipal water.
What is in common? What can people do to increase their water quality for drinking?
The first thing I would suggest is get your the mass or the amount of volume of water that you would like to process into a higher form of water into a refrigerator.
And when I say that, fortunately I can say that in common terms, most refrigerators across the world are either at 4 degrees or at 49 degrees Celsius for 39 Fahrenheit.
So, get your water either for a few hours into a refrigerator in the container that you're going to use. This is in an unfiltered state now, for a minimum of 2 to 4 hours.
Overnight is best. Once you remove that water, and this is now discussing people that are going to topically process the water, not an inline filter that you might see in a restaurant or many houses or things like that, because there you're going to need a pre-chiller to do that.
But if you were to process water, it would be topically meaning that you would get the given amount of water again in a refrigerator overnight would be best.
What you do then, the simplest thing to do is obtain what's called these picture filters. I've seen them at these big walley world, big department type stores for as little as 10 bucks these days.
And what you do there is you would pour that water through one of these picture filters at the 39 degrees Celsius. And the reason why you do it at that point is that water is at its anomaly point, it's willing to do work.
The filter will be efficiency will work up in the 99% efficiency versus the 80% or 60% or 40% if it's regular warm water or water it's been exposed to light.
So now you're going to get the most out of whatever you are doing to process the water. Now a lot of these picture filters are made of plastics.
What I suggest then is if you have some old beer bottles or wine bottles or that type of bottle, glass bottle that is amber or dark blue or dark green regardless.
After passes through the picture filter, funnel it in or decanted immediately into these glass bottles that are dark that obscure light either amber color, green, blue, purple, anything that is not clear.
And then immediately place that water again into the refrigerator overnight and let it sit. And now you will have a higher quality water than you've ever had. It would actually rival most bottled waters at that point.
Simply by processing the water at 39 degrees and then letting it rest after that.
The in-live amount of water is also very important which is called like a hydrodynamic action which is the meandering through the river or the blood vessels or the roots of a tree that's that geometric form or a vortex or a tornado.
Fortunately when you do a picture filter the very act of the water running through that and dripping out into the picture allows the water to self-organize and bottle it but some things and will charge the water from the environment.
And that's why again I am suggesting that this type of water processing where the water is processed in your 39, at least for a night or 4 degrees Celsius and then allow it to rest overnight or for a few hours before taking.
You will notice the quality of water is very high. Now sometimes if you're very afflite person they say don't drink very cold water could cause cramps in hot weather. That is true. It could.
But I would still drink it cool. Wouldn't let it go more than let's say 50 degrees or 45 if you're looking for a high quality drink of water.
You know Fahrenheit or 5 to 8 degrees Celsius. Now for someone who wants to go a little bit further.
Now what I mean by further is a basic picture filter like that.
Typically most of them are made up of carbon.
But go ahead and take them because this is interesting to me the fact that the picture shape itself would sort of imply that it gives that opportunity to go into the vortex sort of shape.
And you know what I keep thinking of is water going down a drain. It's allowed to collect and go into that drain but it doesn't get to stay in that shape.
And yet creates sort of a natural vortex. You see it spinning. Of course I've heard discussions about it spinning in different directions in different parts of the planet and things like that.
But yes at this point for the quality wouldn't yeah even just the fact that a drop of water would fall into another body of water that toroidal action which is it moves the water aside it folds on to itself as it again of vortex because a toroid would be a smoke ring for example.
That is another form of a vortex also. Let's like it just stuck on the standard tornado vortex which is that axial radial to axial you know it's wide funnel at the top and it comes down into an axial you know vertical any portion at the bottom that's the radial to axial form of vorticity or hydrodynamic action.
Another hydrodynamic action is the toroid which would be someone blowing a smoke ring looks like a donut or a truck or truck inner tube let's say and that is also very effective another hydrodynamic action.
And the very fact that water dripping out of it would form some kind of action as such is beneficial.
Now the if someone wants to take this a little bit further and has in the reason I brought up the picture filters most people have ready access to that right now if you want to if you have a little bit more resources and want to go a little bit further.
There on the quantity side of water there is a lot of discussion of heavy metal in the water there is a lot of discretion of arsenics and things like that in the water floor eyes mercury things like that that could that need to be addressed your carbon filter that you will find that is the most common when you say water filtration if you were to buy it and as standard departments or hardware store they're only going to supply you with carbon and particular filtration.
And that is only good for most of what's called organic materials.
Okay certain you know what we find in petroleum products let's say and chlorine and things like that.
Now if you want to go a little bit further with heavy metals and ammonia compounds let's say and other things is such and you want to invest a little bit more what you do then is there's this thing called zeolite.
zeolites are basically an alumina calcium sort of compound that is basically ancient river beds or ancient lake beds that have been dug up and it's a very soft porous white material it's called zeolite zeolite.
O-L-I-T-E and it's a very inexpensive thing to get why do I say that and why am I even bringing up if this is going to be something practical why do I bring up zeolites well if anyone who walks into what they call a pet shop or a pet supply place which is very common aquariums are very common for people to have you find a product on the shelf and it's usually zeolite they're white minerals they call them ammonia pellets.
Amonia pellets sometimes because they take ammonia out of ammonia compounds and nitrate compounds because ammonia is basically a nitrate.
Out of aquariums and this can be gotten very inexpensively your supply in this use in this fashion would be less than ten bucks as a matter of fact more maybe a five years supply would be less than ten bucks right so you can we're talking about not much of an investment here.
And you buy some of these zeolite material and do what they say on the package for cleaning it you really want to clean it very thoroughly because even after five rinses you still see it releases a cloudy water right so just take your time and how to clean zeolites is usually on the package because you have to take care of it if you have an aquarium you would want to cloud up all the fish water so.
Usually the instructions on the sold as ammo chips or ammo pellets meaning a money pellets or just zeolites any pet store or pet supply will have it on the shelf or discount department store has it I've even seen it on regular super market shelves and where you might go to buy some fish food.
So what you would do is purchase some of these zeolites and zeolites are very effective in removing any ammonia compounds which would be these chloramine compounds that are putting municipal water now very effective at removing heavy metal any heavy metals matter of fact all of the.
Nest teams nest stands for nuclear emergency safety or nest teams in the u.s. these are nuclear safety cleanup people when they show up to a site and they usually close it off and tell tell you that you asked them why is the road your clothes and they say well because there's a meth lab here we have to close the road and you're like well there's no houses there you know what you're talking about you know it's always secret when these guys show up to do a nuclear cleanup guess what they show up and guess what follows them a big.
Truck of what?
Duck truck full of what zeolites.
To absorb all the material that's interesting so you know not to get nothing to far off you know because we were talking about you know the filtration and yeah that's one of those things that would be you know accessible.
But it almost sounds strange really to think that you might be able to get a hold of something like that in order to improve water quality you know but this but this wood contribute to the the better health of someone who pardon the phrase again is the consumer wouldn't it right right now the reason I bring it up is because simply because let's say through industry the very fact that industry sends to you.
That industry sends stuff up a smoke stack and cars have exhaust pipes is really nasty stuff in colloid form in the environment that settles in water courses that are eventually processed and given to the people of drink.
So a lot of these things will not be handled by your typical carbon filter with little ion I they usually have small ionic resin beets in them as well that doesn't really handle this stuff so the heavy metal and ammonia constituents when they say heavy metals I mean the entire spectrum.
Will be handled by the deal light and the deal lights you know even on a cursory search look up.
We're not talking you know look up to deal I said I'm not talking about a lot of people promoting it for internal health reasons I'm not promoting it for such.
I'm strictly promoting it for a quantitative reduction of nasties in the water.
Yeah and we remove some of these heavy metal constituents and other things radio nucleotides and things like that you will you will notice that the water is more refreshing more.
Vinylizing and eventually as you've heard you know these heavy metals without getting into what you know the entire broad spectrum of them can be damaging to the organism you know the body you know and animals as well humans and animals and fish.
And they tend to not hurt you immediately they tend to be damaging through the cumulative you know they tend to stay within the body right and.
Okay so this is one way the deal light would be a thing that I would add to the picture filter now how would you add it to the picture filter simply by putting a few tables in the picture filter itself because remember it has a small filter module in it it will not allow the deal light to pass through.
So the stock filter module that comes in the picture will actually contain the deal light or you can put it in a a painter's strain bag or cheese cloth if you wish because it comes in pea size granules typically.
Okay now if you if for those that so now we're talking about an investment of roughly ten bucks for a picture filter at a discount department store and even not at a discount department store they're roughly between ten or twenty bucks.
And we're talking about an investment of anywhere between three or ten bucks for a deal light which the amount of zero light that would that would get you would be about the size of a half gallon container of milk and that would last you pretty long time I have some that I've been using a container that size for five years now and it's still about half full just to give you an idea.
So five people can go in on a ten dollar investment and that would be enough for five years two bucks for three bucks with a zero light.
Okay so this gets rid of your heavy metals now in some places there's something there's an arsenic consideration arsenic cyanide and things like that traces in the water at Southwest.
A lot of municipalities were heavily fined by the federal regulatory authorities because of the high arsenic content in the water and the only way that they know how to remove arsenic from the water is by very expensive what's called ionic cationic resin beads and these beads cost about five hundred bucks the pound and they're very difficult to get and they also remove the arsenic but they also introduce other polymers into the water which have to be removed.
So let's just say how do we remove arsenic from the water well you do it through something called adsorption you've heard of adsorption with a bee where you know a towel absorbs water.
Well there's another concept called adsorption with a D so be A D instead of A B as an adsorption what adsorption does is when you have one material that has so much affinity for something that as the liquid passes or the water passes over this material
that material that what you're trying to remove out of the water sticks to the surface of this other material that's called an adsorber that adsorber would be something called magnetite M A G N E T I T E.
Now what that is is basically another term for is black sand.
What is black sand you ever go to the beach and notice that the sand is white but when you look at it really close to the little black specks in there.
That is usually iron crystal. Magnetite is Fe 304 is what they call the chemical combination which is three parts iron four parts oxygen.
Fe 2 or 3 would be hematite you've heard of like hematite they use it in jewelry it's like a grayish material.
Yeah actually I wore a vial of magnetite and actually had a crystal shape hematite before around you know I used to wear both of them as jewelry at one point in time.
Okay great. So people can look these things up and how do you get magnetite?
Well if you're near a water course beach or river or whatever you could just drag magnets take a 15 minute walk with a magnetic strip behind you and you'll notice all these little black sand particles you know pick off all the staples and rust emails and things.
And you'll notice that this is a type of iron that does not rust does not combine with oxygen it's in crystal form.
And as a matter of fact if you were to look at it under a microscope it would look like a double sided pyramid would have eight sides four sides on each side and the angle of that pyramid is 51.4 degrees which is basically 360 divided by seven.
And also what do you think the angle of the great pyramid of Giza is 51.4 degrees? Right.
Interestingly enough when they made this type of jewelry that I'm talking about they would they would terminate on either side of the crystals try to approximate that symmetry as well when they terminated the crystal or the container that the smaller pieces were in both of them were designed with that same principle in mind.
Yes, yes very interesting that's part of the common denominator of geometric you know fundamentals that underline anything whether it's in that man made or in nature.
Sure you know things tend to follow certain geometric forms.
So what you do with the magnetite is very simple very much like the zeolite of the top of the picture filter you would just put a table to the magnetite there under water would pass over and be an adsorber to the arsenic or arsenide compounds.
Now the way you would treat that is maybe every three or four six months or once a year you it's easy to separate the zeolites in the magnetite.
You would just soak the magnetite in hydrogen peroxide and the zeolite and when I was doing this in Los Angeles by the way we cleaned out some canisters we were cleaning out we were processing L.A. tap water.
We stripped the materials and we got this really bright you ever see the energy drink I think it's called Gatorade they have one called lemon lime it's like a yellowish greenish kind of color to it when you strip the magnetite and zeolite of arsenic using hydrogen peroxide the water turns that color that is the sign that you have arsenic in the water by the way.
That's why I could never drink that flavor it's called lemon lime there's several companies that put out sports drinks that they call it.
Virtually the same flavor it's like a common common thing now much like raspberry is often colored blue anymore yeah.
If you ever see that lemon lime color in the convenience store that's the color of arsenic when it comes off from an adsorber and yeah so right there the combination of a basic picture filter where the water is processed through it at 39 degrees or as close as possible.
With zeolite magnetite we're going to say you thought a lot meaning a good way that is better than anything you could buy for but bought it doesn't matter from what our tea's in well they're getting in from this is a very simple way to process they very high quality water and essentially if one a lot of people don't drink water these days as much as they should let's say they tend to get their water from other drinks and their food.
This information hopefully will be more helpful to people that are considering drinking more water or will be you know eventually maybe we can start discussing this more and maybe create some water connoisseurs which I think are lacking in the world but if anyone wants to understand more about the concept of hydration there is someone out there called Dr. Batmengala they call them Dr. Batman.
The water doctor and he wrote a book you're not sick you're thirsty but Mangala and he was an Iranian Persian doctor he was also a prison in Persia for his writings and other things he was healing people with water and when his sentence was over and they told him to leave the prison he said no I want to say a few more months and check on some of my patients here he was that kind of guy.
He died recently but if I want to look up you're not sick your thirsty doctor Batman or Batmengala I don't have his spelling in front of me but you're not sick your thirsty is one of his publications if you're interested in what water consumption can do right I'm sure that'll be enough for you to rely on it so yeah yeah so we can then discuss if anyone wants to go to a higher level than that.
Any other water treatment if you believe your water is good enough let's say if you're going to go on a higher level see what I mean by that is if you think your water needs filtering you're you're ready dealing with water that you know needs filtering it's suspect it's not a high quality water right but on a higher level would be is if you are near in proximity of a good water source and that doesn't mean a store bought water now.
It was just digress for a second how many times have you gone to the shops any shop and there's and they're procuring water how many times have you seen the water being stored absence of light absence of light in a 39 degrees or do you see the water on the shelf in clear plastic bottles at room temperature most of the time yeah it doesn't require refrigerations so therefore it's put on a shelf you know.
But I think we just brought up the point that it does know I know I'm just stating to you what that I know exactly you know so you see how contrary this concept is it's very difficult for anyone to listen to what we're discussing and then go out into the world they'll see that the two don't match they don't agree with each other at all you see.
Now and you know there's more than one reason why chilled water that's been refrigerated is pleasant you know it makes more sense to the body it's not that it tastes any different really it's just that it's in it's more correct effective efficient it'll be more refreshing initially and then after a few minutes it'll be invigorating.
So there's two ways to test the water quality by a lot of biological sensor which is your body would be how refreshing it is initially and then how invigorating it is following that let's say within a few minutes even up to 20 minutes if you feel invigorated or so.
Now for again for the people that have a higher calling or a higher source the primary thing there would be to avoid contact with metal metal containers or metal fixtures and to keep it in the dark and keep it cool so if you're let's say fetching water at a spring.
Organic material is a plastic is considered organic material it would have to be a high density polyethylene or glass or terracotta but of white metal if you can now a lot of can teens for camping and things is such our metal a lot of these there's been a water bottle phase in the past decade or so where you see people carrying carrying water bottles around like it's a baby.
Wherever they go in that case there's selling stainless steel now for that I would avoid the any any metallic container at this point because simply because of the from an ethereal point of view when I see ether I mean the how the initial people that discussed electricity considered electricity to be a form of the ether there is interaction between water and the environment and water and when it makes contact with.
Excuse me most metals especially ferrous compounds iron compounds it discharges the quality of the water now if you have a silver container or gold plate it actually silver plated would be best or perhaps a stabilized copper that would not affect it as much as a stainless steel or iron so you want to avoid metal in general because even though silver would be favorable how many.
People have access to silver and it wouldn't be very affordable so look in the past two hours here we've we've covered a whole lot about water that I dare say has not been spoken about in public in one place certainly all these aspects wouldn't use that.
I would say so yes absolutely so I think yeah it's quite a big journey as long as we feel like the end of this two hours or two hours passing if you feel like there's anything else that we could say along these lines that people can walk away with and feel that they can implement in their lives immediately.
So this is yes certainly and you've given people a much more refined way to look at how they could increase the well the efficiency of the water they consume we've given them the idea that you know consumption excuse me for using the term again of water is one of these things that they need to be concerned with the why the how and.
So I think we've done a great deal that is never discussed anywhere has been discussed here so I don't know if you want to close it out of this point or I think we've done we've done something pretty good here and tell you the truth I've heard some things here that I have never heard before and had some other things that presented themselves to me in the past.
For instance you know just a parking back to one point the concept that an egg has a certain shape and there is a logical sensible purpose for that you know now makes a whole lot more sense to me now that we've discussed it so you know.
Oh good yeah that's one is absolutely it's all that one is a great thing I take from it is that you know an egg makes sense the way it is shaped.
Sure yeah these the people who people those who put it all together yeah they don't act in futility as they've said before so exactly so I guess we'll believe this be here and I hope that you guys have gained something from it and obviously if you have access to this then you have access to replay it as I suggest you do because quite honestly I'm going to have to listen to it a few times myself in order to really sort of internalize the water.
Sort of internalize all of the information that has been given here and remember there is a great deal more to be learned this is the merely like the the primer or the primer depending on how you want to pronounce it for some information that should be obvious should be sort of self evident if we were not under the cosmic censorship that we have been for so very long when you agree.
Oh yeah certainly and again the point is you know two hours invested can people can anyone listening to this walk away and do something immediately perhaps I say yes and I think we've done done some good.
Well absolutely and I want to thank you for taking this time with us and and thank you to you guys who have decided to subscribe and listen there will be more in the future not sure where it's all going but I guarantee you that.
If you continue to remain here with us at this website you will learn more than you have elsewhere and hey I've done that alone with just the shows that I've done with which Kelly and the Greek which is also available on this site as well as the American Freedom Radio so there you go guys and hey until next time.
Thanks, folks.
(Bell)