[Music]
Hello and welcome to the Free Zone.
Well, it has been one wild ride as we have all been expecting.
But we need to know, are we communicating?
I mean, who wrote your operating system?
Is your head in a vacuum?
We're going to find out as we speak with a natural philosopher today.
I call them that because if I ever felt like I was talking to someone from the future,
it's while talking with the Greek.
And so, after all of the shenanigans that we've been witnessing,
I could think of no one better to come and really give us a heads up view
of our world as it is, as it has been, and what it will be.
So, please welcome to the show The Greek.
It's great to have you here with us.
Oh, thank you, Freeman. It's, I guess, good to be back.
Any kind of venue that we could come out and display or do a good public report
is always advantageous for the audience.
So, again, thanks for thinking of me.
Yeah, we are hungry for the knowledge we are.
And we're looking at a world in chaos.
We're seeing everybody function on the programming inside of their operating system.
They don't even know that it's happening.
They don't know where this operating system came from.
Now, in February, nine months ago, we were speaking.
And you said, your vote is your vow to accept the electors' choice.
And I think we should open the show with that in that,
you know, nine months ago, you said this.
And now here we are with liberals in the streets and bloody, violent riots trying to flip the vote.
And it's blowing my mind, honestly.
I didn't think that the Hillary supporters would be out beating up people in the streets.
But what I do know is that what they, the they want is chaos.
And so let's look at the operating system that would develop into this idea that
you would write in the streets over this.
And the legal and lawful ways that this is also wrong.
Take it from whoever you want.
Sure. Let's look at it real simply.
What is possible, pretty much anything is possible.
And who can ponder all the possibilities?
So you have to be a good observer to see what's happening.
And what is happening is possible because it's happening.
So when you talk about the operating system, let's use the computer as a metaphor.
You have an operating system, then you have programs, then you have files.
Most people are actually trying to process files and programs, and they have no operating system.
And what I mean about that is your operating system, this might sound dogmatic now, comes from your God,
comes from your deity, someone you look up to.
Like if you're three years old and you're formative years, your parents are your God.
So what I mean by God is a higher authority, not only in concept but in actual power,
like the unseen world, rules, the scene world, you know, shadow government, anyone, anyway.
So what we're talking about here is things to come might seem fascinating to people
or how things work because they really just haven't thought it out or they don't have the
convention to access this way of thinking or seeing things because the operating system comes from
your deity and they don't acknowledge that. For example, every country has a patron or patron deity
in the Western world. Most of the countries have adopted the revived goddess religion.
And when I say operating system, it's where you get your law, not traffic law or tax law, but
what you eat, what you wear, how you operate in business, how you raise a family, how you keep time,
that comes from your God. And they have the Western world has incorporated the revived goddess
religion, aka known as justicia or justice, Statue of a Woman Holding Scales Blindfolded and such.
Right, you'll see statues. She's also known as Columbia, Britannia, you know, a lot of other
aspects of, you know, let's say smaller societies have their different gods, right? They've
revived various different gods and that's where they get their law form from.
Now, the interesting thing about that is if you are atheistic in any capacity,
you still cannot escape this. Like, for example, discussing, you know, having this discussion with an
atheist, they'll say, well, Greek or Freemony, I don't believe in any God. Well, that's really simple.
You just ask them, do you then follow or believe in the laws of the state? And they almost always say,
yes, well, then there's your God in April 1st is your holiday. So you see, this is the operating system
and it's in place and no one is paying attention to it, but it doesn't mean that they're not subject to it,
right? Let's go back to the justice aspect. How many times have you heard in terms of law
form? Let's, in this case, it would be legal form. You'll have to be brought to justice. You serve
justice is a miscarriage of justice, right? And all of these things. So they're using this in front
of you. They have the iconography and statuary to prove it. Now, their agents and the priesthood
and the entitled classes that rule the rest of the people, guess what? They don't even know it
in most cases. They are just following along. So tie that into what's going on. I think you mentioned
what the month is called February discussed about what voting actually means. It means to vow that
you are supporting the system and whatever electorate body decides to elect, you are all for it.
Like I'm with you guys. And this is what's going on. Let's say regarding the condition of what is
possible. I guess there's a protest against the electorate. But so these are the possibilities
that cannot be thought of but observed and maybe described. So that could tie into the rest of
the discussion because it's not very narrow and linear. So what do you think? Do you want to maybe
perhaps go down the path of the political path or just still maybe the general aspect of
the operating system is? I'm really happy to hear your general views of things because I swear that
you are from the future Greek. So I think that you're you are the master of the obvious that no one
ever sees. And thank you. I want to share that with with my audience because you point out things that
just right in front of our faces and we never stop to think about them. So I really want to follow
your lead. Okay well you know I have like a stock way of speaking and typically it's
metaphorically you know the last thing for mankind to discover is what's obvious.
And the obvious is just what's right in front of you. Let's not be hypocritical. I mean people
want to go out and to far away places and far away thinking to discover things but typically
they're shallow thinking gets them diving off into the deep end. So if you're going to be shallow
about things take care of business and what's just five feet around you first.
And the stock way of starting off on anything like this is people don't even know what day it is.
Now what I mean by that it sounds kind of bizarre whether you care or not it's the concept of time.
You know you've heard in the new age movement a lot of loosely thinking people say well there's
no such thing as time. Well that's correct in a sense because time is nothing other than the
recordation and memorialization of events. So when you hear about time travel you're not really
traveling in time you're either going to past or future events and time is the recordation of such.
So currently if you ask anyone what day it is they're actually not giving you the day they're
giving you the date they're giving you something off of what I loosely call the Pope's work schedule
which is anything between January through December Monday through Friday and they usually have
this thing called hours and minutes which is what I call the wind up toy known as the clock.
So typically you know just to refresh people if you don't even know what day it is how are you going
to navigate because time is important for navigation you know if you're moving 20 miles per hour
for one hour that you've covered 20 miles right anyone that navigates or plots things
understands time is important. How are you going to navigate the waters of the universe
social aspects and even any cosmological aspect if you don't know how to reckon time.
For example if you observe a what's called a birthday or anniversary any year you'll notice that
it's a different day of the year every year right. If you look at what day it is today folks you look
last year and look at next year it's a few days off so what day is it it's none of it it's the Pope's
work schedule meaning it is nothing more than is if you worked at a corporate headquarters and they
gave you a chart with different color days and this is when you work. So no one really knows what
day it is and in that day aspect is not about being usurped by a schedule but actually accessing
information that anyone can access without buying anything or having an allegiance or subscribing.
So this convention of what's called the Gregorian calendar that's been accepted by all society is
very much considered you know the state of society on the planet as being pretty piss poor if you
can't navigate using any good timekeeping and let me just throw in a quick thing this is kind of
long-winded. See years ago people settled their debts with the full moon which is really the new moon
rises in the east that's why today you still get a moonfully bill don't you don't think give you a
moonfully bill it's called moonfully but you see the moon rules the month and the day starts at high
noon right not at midnight if you remember banking before the electronic convention if you'd made
a deposit afternoon it was considered the next day in the Wild West type of society in the US they
had court in the morning and they executed sentence the next day they hung you when high noon so we're
having the day beginning at noon and actually the timekeeping conventions of the world which would
be Greenwich and the other one I believe is in Colorado Springs and Naval Observatory if you look
up this was I'm not sure if it's still there but on their website Julian calendar day they clearly
tell you that the day starts at solar noon but for scientific purposes I mean it starts at high
noon for scientific and astronomical purposes but for the people at civil midnight that's like how
it's kind of a put down sort of how like the dictionaries were assembled 200 years ago they weren't
sure how to define words when you looked up the word oats it said what they feed horses in England but
the staple of people in Scotland so this is being put in front of you and no one is really noticing
that there's a shifting of time meaning the way you record time time doesn't shift because the
events are the events it's just that you cannot record it so now if you don't have a way of memorializing
time how are you going to memorialize or record events very loosely so that's why you have a lot of
this false hope in things let's go you know keeping it back to the conversation tying it back to the
recent election in the U.S. you have a character now under the covenant that I live by by the way
any I don't speak poorly of the leader of any people because they're put there by divine right
believe it or not this is where the Asians are correct but you have a character here who is let's say
allegedly the leader of the American society now North American known as the United States of America
what made him so popular is a very very loose statement let's make America great again and that's
all that it took there's no understanding of that what do you mean by that just getting people
rouled up about it you see and if you want to understand that concept a little more even though this
is a perhaps a one hour or a one hour or two hour recording anyone is interested a little bit more
on what's called this crowd mentality I recommend them to consider Gustav LeBond the crowd it's
it's on a book form ebook form audio book form and start delving into how the crowd mentality works
and you will see it from a social perspective how this man really compiled something really well
in the 1895 I believe and that will give you an understanding on that but again just to go back to
maybe leading this conversation you people still have not realized that they're not able to memorialize
timekeeping and will awful timekeeping other things are within their physical reality you know
you ever notice how heat rises and cold descends but in all biological systems the cold rises and
the heat descends like a cool feet and more cool head and warm feet or when you go up into the sky
it's cold and down in the valley it's hot all biological systems have opposite movement
why aren't people demanding from their technicians and engineers to design artificial heating
equipment to do that so right now they're just passively ignorant of this fact and they have
air conditioning and heating in their cars homes and boats and places that give them a hot head
and cold feet and no one is paying any attention you see you know the other stock thing is going
back to their deity now most people when you bring that up you know they're God they think of religion
and you have the major religions Islam Christianity Buddhism Hinduism and such and all the spin-offs
do you know that none of those religions know or do anything that's in the text that they alleged to
subscribe to yes at all and and I'm not talking about taking it out of context and it's really easy
to start a religion like for example if you look at the a lot of the Catholic Christian memes
you know if you want to start a subgroup in there it's very simple get a chocolate chip recipe
bake a cookie bake a set of cookies and if one of them looks like what's called the queen of heaven
you tell everyone and in about a month you'll have a thousand people following you asking
you about how that cookie crumbled right so this is very very simple I mean people again the
crowd mentality but going back to no one knows or does anything that's in the text that they alleged to
subscribe to meaning in context and here's the thing if these texts are divinely inspired
and you are told that no one can understand them or that's your interpretation indirectly what
people are saying is the gods are acting in futility and I'll tell you for sure the gods do not act
in futility they might have an IQ of two million and they're giving you baby talk and you still can
understand it but that message is not futile now here just to lay something out a lot of times I
refer to the what's called the biblical text and that's very difficult to discuss because guess what
all of the versions that you have in all the languages has been translated in based on king James
or other things is not a translation it is a version there's over 27,000 critical mistakes in
that document it's irrelevant in terms of getting the proper message now what you're getting is a
general outline of the story but you will be it is wrought with error so you're going to have to go
back to the languages of preservation sorry you know but from that point of view the same goes with
any of the texts in any other language these texts are preserved in their original languages and
you're it's not going to be given to you on a silver platter you're going to have to do the work
now when you look at these religions as being the let's say or as I stated earlier your god is your law
form and such and you have now debased it and are going by tradition right like you know for example
Christmas and Easter bunny and all these other things are not in the biblical text but the majority
that is what how Christianity is defined public prayer and Islam mosques and other things about
women covering their bodies and all that is not in the Quran right but they still do it so these
traditions or let's go back to Buddhism you know they have a little statue or Hinduism you have
certain practices you will not find that in the Rig Vita's or any of the writings either so these
cultural traditions behaviors that the people engage in also have a deity or an entity behind them
but it is not the one that they think so they've been kind of winked right so again we have many many
layers let's go back to the political aspect with this election how many times have you heard of
what's called the shadow government I believe there was even a public speech warning by Kennedy
regarding that right and even right yeah and the WikiLeaks and actually would your willson had
alluded to that about there's a conspiracy so great no man can go against it or something like that
and paraphrasing right there is another entity behind that so we're talking about a world of the unseen
now what I mean by that it just hasn't been properly identified just like years ago if people
used hot coal to cool to heat their house and they close the doors and windows they woke up dead and
they didn't know what killed them it was the ether they called it but later on they discovered
there's something called carbon monoxide and they had a carbon monoxide detector and now you know
not to do that because you can specifically identify the agent that brought that a situation on
currently humanity is in a state where they cannot specifically identify the agents that bring
about their condition aka known as the gods or unseen beings yes and where I'm not really crazy
thinking that I have friends that you can't see this is just based on what has been memorialized now
if you memorialized in texts and information we can access meaning if you think like most people
that everything came into creation less than a hundred years ago and everyone that wrote anything prior
to you regarding the gods is an idiot or you don't have to believe in it you are not examining
information that is that is available to you to explain many of the things that are going on
without a doubt you know exactly what you're saying it's all social norms and none of it is the
documented evidence which again they're only allowed versions and then with this traditional standpoint
and the versions that they're dealing with and I've seen you know Christians that disagree with
interpretations and get thrown out of their church or whatever you know back and forth because of
interpretation and we're looking at a situation where they want to rile up the mob and
all the fanatics are out there screaming kill all the fanatics so right well here's the thing you brought
up church and all of these institutions these temples they are just revived a post flood let's say
paganism like the word church comes from circuit it actually Latin word for circus the three ring
circus or what's called the trinity they won't find that in the text but they memorialize that now
let's just get down and dirty about it which is actually true and clean is the Christianity was started
pretty much very much how 9/11 conspiracy movement was started no one really knew how those buildings
came down in public and mass groups so they they have all of these people saying oh it was thermite
oh it was some space weapon or whatever but actually what brought them down is quite simple
device and it's not what people think because they don't understand the structure of the building now
what was going on around the first century there was a lot of incredible events happening and there
was a lot of was a rumor mill that was going and the events where you served by the typically a fellow
named Simon Magus Simon Simon the magician and he was quite popular and quite wealthy like a
Houdini or a David Copperfield with the budget of let's say Bill Gates or George Soros right and he
was at that time period and he didn't know what was going on either but he was able to promote
for his advantage the frenzy that was going on about the events in the first century then
to focus on what he was saying about it right and he was also a Samaritan descent which the Samaritans
are very interesting if you look them up back in the day they had their pagan gods but they also
invited let's say scriptural law so there were a good mishmash of everything and also when you look
at the history of Simon Magus you have the offshoots of what's called nosticism right and all these
other aspects of Christianity but if anyone studies the biblical text you'll see that everything that
they're doing not some of what Christianity is doing but everything Christianity is doing is either
on the abominations list or the don't do list of the biblical text now the problem with discussing
this like this and not making this a quote-unquote religious discussion is I want to just make a
comment there's quite a few people unstudied and unfamiliar with the text that come out and say
it was a different god of the New Testament than the Old Testament right many times have you heard
that well the thing that they miss out on that the so-called god of the New and Old Testament is
the same one and it's not what people think it is the Christ himself in the text now this is not
nothing to do with what you believe in because the Christ was god himself manifest in according to
the text so one of the main things that they bring up is how in the Old Testament the Israelites were
told to go and kill every man, woman and child in certain cities before they occupied the land
and in the New Testament it's all about love and peace and all this and there couldn't be anything
further from the truth they have not studied the text now I tell people in passing and they find
it very shocking but who is the most hateful character in the biblical text pause they can't answer
it's the Christ how do you know well you just read the text he'll say things like think not I brought
here to bring peace I came to divide with the sword I will bring terror amongst you oh another thing
that's stated in the in the in the in what's called the New Testament is that you've been better off
been at Sodom and Gomorrah than what's going to come upon your village or city or how about this
one why do you speak to the people in parable and riddle it's is the truth is not given to them it's
given to you right so you have many of these aspects now what I mean by hateful meaning that hateful
of the way that man operates at this point right and even at that point now let's just jump back to
the Old Testament remember I just mentioned that they were told to go kill every man, woman,
and child and animals as well so it can't be the same god right because they have this concept and
I just showed that he's not about love and peace well why why did they tell the Israelites to go in
and kill everything and everyone that moved you ever wonder why well it's very clear in the text that
they were engaged in pretty abominable acts that are actually represented in parity today hey
Freeman let's go back in time we're gonna walk down an ancient canaanite village you ready I'm gonna
let's hold hands and go on a windy walk through let's say ancient canaan right this is we're talking
about the time that the Israelites were told in and go ahead and slaughter everything and everyone so
what we're walking down a public square right now and we're looking in one shop and what do we see
well we see a whole bunch of animals tied down donkeys horses sheep chickens and like you're like well
what's that for I said well this is a sex shop you know people like to get off before they go to
you know into the marketplace down the road this is what they do right so you get all these
animals possibly knocked up with human sperm oh let's go to the next shop what do you see there oh I
see all these little children in cages with it what's that for oh well you'll see down at the end
of the square there you'll see a seated statue it's made of bronze and it's a glowing red hot
and people are told to make a wish a prosperity by placing a child in its lap and searing it alive
but it's kind of hard to do business when you hear children being burned alive so they ring bells
you know if you've ever heard of a fat red character where a child is placed on his lap and you have
bells involved like jingle bells right that's mullick revived mullick now this is the type of society
that was operating out and open out in public back then so that these people were unreabilitable
that was so incorporated into their society that they would rather die then let it go and they
were accommodated by that now what you have in this modern society how many times have you said have
you heard let's say people saying oh we have to preserve Christmas you know the actual thing right
you see you see what's going on it is exactly the same society but it's in parity another thing I
bring up is what do cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common right I think I don't know if
we brought this up previously but you see these things all tie in together and we can go into what
cannibals birthdays and dolls maybe have in common in the second hour perhaps because that's a little
bit of a litany on its own so perhaps all of these things and these misunderstandings something is
minor of what religion is and discounting the facts behind it and then having pseudo academics or
academics promoting a dichotomy that doesn't exist for example the Old Testament God is different
than the New Testament God is foolishness right and by the way at this point I'll say this publicly
I am embarrassed to be in a room with anyone who has more than an eighth grade conventional education
you know for example have you ever seen people drive around in the cars of a bumper sticker
my child is an honor student at this school or my child goes to that school and they're so proud of
it sure well I want to make a bumper sticker that says that the only reason I'd said my child to
a public school or university is if I knew there were a complete moron so anyway that is a
personal comment on the current system and everyone's the idea that everything is propaganda that
this is just a tool of indoctrination and is that what you mean by this?
well yeah it's indoctrination but either accommodating the people like for example there's
there's a reason why fast food is so crappy because people want to be accommodated by fast food
but and they don't really care about what the ingredients are so how are you going to make a profit
if you use higher quality ingredients so you keep it at a minimal high profit because the people
don't care it's what you get away with it's with the market will bear you know here there's
something that I've always discussed in the past it's called pranking humankind right now is
subject to a cosmic prank and in other words all of your entitled classes your doctors your attorneys
uh your professors your scientists are pranking you now what's a prank look it up it means ludicrous
trick but the primary prankers are your parents in most cases meaning like when you're a child you're
told about Santa Claus in the tooth fairy or you told about this or that and um and one of them is
like you can't see ghosts either right there's a boogie man in the closet no you didn't see anything
yes you did okay so you're being pranked by your own parents who take the seat of God at that time
because you're not aware of any higher authority even the state as a child and at some point the
parents told you oh you're you're too old for that right now you can't talk about Santa Claus or
the Easter bunny what's wrong with you right they never apologize see that's why you have a lot of
psychological problems with teenagers in the western world is because the parents never
apologized for all the pranking they did here's another former pranking the parents
yeah they have the steep psychological embedded thing that you'll need to do is apologize for
lying to the child now here's the other yeah i was just gonna say that's how Catholics become
Satanus well yeah you can't you can't be a Satanus without being a Christian and uh i see so
often that what happens is is that disillusionment when the you know the prank is revealed and they're
like they become the complete opposite of what they were you know their operating system but it's
but again it's not let's let's hold the pranking thought for a moment Satan is a character that anyone
can research he is only dealing with major institutions he doesn't deal with each individual at a time
he will in the future with one individual aka known as the anti christ he's the only man in history
that Satan will actually possess all of the other ones are demonic possessions there are trillions of
demons you can even have five thousand demons on in in one person in one man or woman right so they're
forget about the seven billion people there's trillions upon trillions of these of these entities
in the spiritual realm so you absolutely believe in deities and demons well it's not a matter of
believing in them as a look that what's been memorialized about them and i found it to be validatable
and sound information and if you want to go that's what belief should be based on if i write you a
check for fifty grand and you call the bank and and there's fifty grand in the account to be transferred
to you for example you can go around telling people you just got fifty grand even though you
haven't yet because everything's in place for it to happen believe should be based on things that
are in place that will happen not some obscure abstract insanity that most people are operating on
but let's go back to the satanism well you hear a lot of people in these small occulted movements
known as satanists they're really not and they will tell you when they set up like a satanic temple
that who their entity is like for example the temple of set that is not satan that is an ancient god
revived from a jeb for example and there are others various bals or bals or lords satan is in control
this this whole entire social construct is his meaning satan doesn't deal with a little satanic
temple that is a revived a demon as a minor very very minor impure demon satan is in control of all
the governments of the world all the religions of the world all of your sciences all of your entertainment
very very subtly you see so to say that catholics leave that to become satanic well is Catholicism one
of the major religions of the world yes right so it is also under the control of that right it's very
easy now satan just means adversary now i want to just we're going to go back to the pranking
hopefully because that's very important i believe in some of the disclosure that i like to give
i didn't mean to derail you because we did cover satan pretty good last time yeah but actually
let's cover one one more thing in there when you read in the book of genesis what would they give you
regarding satan and all that is known as a serpent right people they it's been in iconography
statuary and in legend even in film shown as as an actual animal a snake right now if you actually
go read the text in in context you will see that is the name of an individual that is very
and very anthropomorphic have you ever heard of a man or a woman's name called robin or someone
called hawk does that mean that they're a bird no you just have to be their name so when you go and
look at what's in the original language of preservation what is being translated as the serpent is
actually someone's name and this is someone that has taken the form anthropomorphically spirit being
that is engaging primary man and primary woman let's say right you know so there's a there's an
aspect to that that needs to be looked at and i mean we can do 500 hours and not repeat one thing
and and give an encyclopedia on this that anyone can access the problem is people just don't
care at this point right but we're going to say it anyway now i want to go back to the pranking
and um you are all subject to a prank which is eluticrous trick and uh what i mean by that
is that if you try to rationalize a prank you cannot it's purely emotional and if you ask the
prankster why are you pranking me they never give a rational answer but the ultimate answer is
because i can and i feel like it that's why i tell people do you know i'd have a false sense of
optimism on this planet if you woke up this morning alive be thankful that you are because the reality
of the violence level of violence spiritual and physical on this earth is not really
comprehended by most people i tell people basically be thankful that while you were sleeping last night
wherever you were that no one came through the door of where you were sleeping and ripped the
liver out of your body be thankful that didn't happen this is the potential level of violence
that everyone is living under right now and if you by the way someone did do that or attempted to do
that to you while you were ripping the liver out of you bought your body if you ask them why are you
doing that they say because i feel like it and that is good enough and that's what i mean about the
level of pranking on this planet if you talk to any of the entitled classes the doctors the attorneys
the leaders of the people the academics and all that they're all working on a particular field of
their specialty but none of them know anything about what's been memorialized about that field in
other words there are set memorialized documented rules and how are they or to operate and none of them
know any of these rules are very few and operate along them at all the given example
like what's called law enforcement you know there is no law enforcement that knows any law they're
being directed by the attorney general's office to do things right now for example if you get pulled
over what's called pulled over with the flashing lights and they issue you a ticket or whatever
it doesn't matter if they're a sheriff a local police or highway patrol or whatever do you know that
in order for them to properly be able to do that they have to have what's called DOT certification
and they the actual ticket itself has to be signed by the director of the department transportation in
federal office and how many of them do you think have department transportation certification not
one and it doesn't matter because the the rest of society will say if you tell an acquaintance a friend
of family member what happens it well you shouldn't have been speeding well you shouldn't have done
that that's what happens here i'm like but it's not according to the rules but does it well let's
that's the society we live in this is how people react right so they're subject to the prank and
also there's a sense of voluntary like is him in it who has to be voluntary but most people don't
know what they're volunteering and like a prankster will say here would you like to sit and you say
yes and now he's placed a thumbtack on the seat you sit on it and you get you know damaged or injured
from it and you jump up and say why did you do that it says well you know you're the one who said yes
like you wanted to sit you know the pranking part well that was you know that's how i have fun
you see that's just how i roll that's how i roll and this is how your professors are this is how
your law enforcement is this is how your legal this is how your religious people are confront any
imam priest bishop guru regarding what they're doing and they're saying it doesn't matter as just
need to believe or leave me alone right they don't want to know anything so we're not saying this
because anything is going to change but we're saying it because this is the rationale behind the
irrational that's going on on this planet right now and what is going on on this planet ultimately
in a big sense is that folks time ended almost 18 years ago and you're in the credits part of the movie
right now what i mean by that is if you're going to shoot a two hour movie do you get just exactly two
hours of film or do you have to get two hours and ten minutes because you have to roll the credits
the credits started rolling around the fall of 1998 and what's in the reason i use that metaphor
is simply this the purpose of the credits is to give credits to the efforts and the people behind it
and also it's to show what you didn't see in the in the main feature and also the order of importance
sometimes is changed but you get to see all the things behind the scenes and the other interesting
thing about using this as a metaphor is you ever notice while the film is running if someone speaks
or stands up you're promptly told to be quiet or sit down but when the credits are rolling the film
is still technically rolling but people are talking people are moving around and there's disturbance
in the theater but it doesn't matter because it's the credits that's why since 1998 when you see all
these things happening it just doesn't matter people don't see it you see so we're talking about all
the corruption the child trafficking even spirit cooking all coming to the surface coming to the light
and who cares right it's the movie is over you know it's they're not going to tell you shut up
and sit down and and this is how it's just pretty much you know metaphors are simple and this is not
an oversimplified metaphor it's just another perspective on what is going on here's another
perspective on what's going on I like to use architecture as a metaphor meaning a thousand years ago
structures especially public structures were built to last a thousand years I remember growing up
at the bicentennial in the us around 1976 speaking to some people in Europe and saying 200
year bicentennial you kidding I'm living in a house that's a thousand years old right so a thousand
years ago public structures were built to last a thousand years a hundred years ago public structures
or most structures were last were built to last a hundred years look at the skyscrapers in New York
that were built around the turn of the century or a little after they're still very robust and structurally
sound now structures since 1998 structures are being built to last only 20 years go look at those
big towers that are built in Asia or in Dubai actually go research it a little bit what is the
life expectancy of these large towers 20 years and to put it a little more perspective on the subject
I was conveying down what's called a road one day and I saw what's called a housing subdivision
going up and I took a glance at it and I pointed to someone look the people are so far gone they're
putting they're building their houses out of compressed sawdust think about that for a moment you
know what I mean by compressed sawdust you ever see that particle board yeah it's all a facade folks
that's very sad it doesn't matter the reason why is why do you why should it be made it doesn't need
to be robust because this information is ingrained in everyone just like a plant knows when to come to
seed society is now coming to its point now it doesn't mean doom and gloom because anytime you
preach doom and gloom in human history you will always sound correct but the problem is whenever doom
and gloom is preached they cannot give you specifics what we're trying to do eventually
well least we meaning what the Greek is saying is give specifics and one of the specifics here
is that what everyone is experiencing right now is the precursor to the precursor of a middle
east union that is going to be forming it's a group of ten nations which only nine exist right now
in what's called the middle east area and when this union comes together it's going to be a very
loose union not like the European Union all of your government economics judicial recreational
entertainment education religion is going to be based out of there and then coming out of there
you see it's going to be the hub and it's going to be projected from there through the entire world
and if you want to keep it really simple before getting into more specifics or maybe not
you ever hear grandma say what goes around comes around you ever look at a racetrack where's the
starting line okay look at the starting line now where's the finishing line the same thing even in
the rubbish secular education system in academia they tell you that man society started where
messopotamian region well guess where man society is going to end based out of there as well
so it's very very very very simple and by the way this has also been prophesied in many of your ancient
texts but who wants to read the ancient text because those people are just ignorant you know it
doesn't matter why i don't believe in that you see so you know we're modern now and by the way if you
study any of the ancient writings do you know like ancient Babylon or ancient Greece or even parts
of Rome before they fell from their prominence in their writings they describe themselves as being
modern yes so so you know let's let's tie this back we kind of like got more of a narrow aspect here
but i believe in going deep in certain aspects but just covering broad things because you know
shallow thinking usually gets people diving off something deep so you've got to pin yourself
down into a thought that's what meditation is by the way meditation is like re chewing the
cut you have a thought and you you keep processing it just like you ever have a diamond
inspected or they just glance at it and put it back in the but in the sack or do they keep turning
it and look at every facet right and how the light goes through it from every direction
and when you hear about meditation by the way they really screwed up the western world on that
because when the body is active the mind is quiet and when the body is quiet the mind is active so
back i think many people that consider themselves contemplate over meditational are trying to keep
their body still and make their mind still that's how you go insane folks meditation happens when
the body is still the mind is fast you know if someone is running a marathon and you want to ask
them technical questions or shoot you to the side they'll say listen let me finish this run and
then we'll talk right because when the body is active the mind is quiet and when the body is quiet
the mind is active so if you're laying down in bed and you find your mind racing that's good you're
probably not used to it and you don't know how to take control of it but once you understand the
simple premise that i just shared with you folks you know you'll have fortune in understanding
what meditation is so that does help because yeah who can stop that you know he's supposed to stop
all the thinking or you know again that is a tradition instead of an actual practice the way that
we see things in the way that this is all going what crazy times okay so we're looking at
we're in the uncredits we've been the revealing everything going on behind the surface we find that
our elite are all bloodline tracking back to ancient lines we find that they are all trafficking
in children every single person that has come up in this last election has been accused of rape
and then we get a Middle East union where the laws and the you know the the traditions are quite
different America has been set up as this role of Satan as the evil overlords of the planet
thanks to things like the use of nine eleven truth and all this revelation of how we know try
try and pizza parties and hot dogs and things of that nature that are coming to the surface
what happens when as we start to boil into the second hour here we're going to lead into the the
process of enacting these stoning laws in in the west and and how this Middle East union will
affect us sure sure and now when you when we say stoning laws and you brought up nine eleven you know
I've got to say this and and many aspects perhaps people have no comprehension or don't want to
have comprehension about the one of the major traditions that goes on is from the secular point of
view is the preeminence or predominance of the Christian era all right if from a secular point of
view this is known as the Christian era right that's why your your years are numbered as such right
and it's all erroneous the the figure of the Christ for example in all that you will not what
shown by Christianity the crucifix and all that and the continents of the man with long hair wearing
a loincloth and such is not in the biblical text at all and when you say nine eleven
that is also a loose reference to when let's say the the birth of this biblical character took place
so in essence just to tie it back to what sparked this me to say this is when you said nine eleven
two things that are very important folks to consider about nine eleven one is all of the discussion
that is out there regarding it no one goes back and discusses the type of construction that was used
for those buildings and people don't know that that type of construction was around for decades before
or a decade before it was actually implemented in the reason these buildings were not implemented
because no one knew how to take them down and until the method was developed or procured then they
were built and it wasn't just the world trade center it's the UN building dighamershide plaza the
sears tower this is a specific type of construction now the reason i'm mentioning this is no one is
speaking about it the other thing that almost no one is speaking about is in the in the Christian era
you have something called christmas the birth of what's called the christ and no one discusses
the accuracy of the information that is available for that they all take for granted we don't know
when it was this is what how we celebrate it but what's interesting in the biblical text it gives you
an astronomical alignment when that happened very specifically and if you're going to do a cross
cultural cross-era communication of time you have to use astronomical alignments you can't use
ridiculous calendars right because they change you know so in the biblical text it's very clear a
virgin was giving birth with twelve stars at her head cloaked with the sun in the moon at her feet
that is very specific alignment and we know from secular records that during the time of let's say
the biblical record when the christ was born there was a census or head counting of the empire
by a gustus and also we know that herod had died about two and a half years after that time according
to secular records that puts you between two a.d. or eight b.c. so if you go look for this alignment
that i just mentioned the constellation vergo with the tail of draco at her head with the sun in the
middle and the moon at her feet that is in the late afternoon and if you go to an astronomical
observatory or computer that will show you that happened between two and eight b.c. and that
happened on three b.c. on the day of eleven on the month of september around six forty p.m.
so what when you say nine eleven that was what's called a birthday party right if you get the
meaning of that we'll talk about what cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common as a metaphor
to understand this society so i just wanted to throw that in there as well to give a little more
comprehension on what's going on yeah absolutely we are seeing the birth of a new world and folks it
is the year five thousand seven hundred and seventy seven in the hebrough calendar or yes the year
six thousand sixteen anolusius calendar or you know year two thousand sixteen and yeah well we
from memorialization it seems to be there's a new kid on the block known as atom and that was around
six thousand eighteen years ago so when you're referencing the biblical text you would probably
around be around there now what's interesting about the hebrough calendar by the way the reason it's
losing losing out a few hundred years is because they decided to eliminate the years when they didn't
have an unrighteous king so for example if you didn't like george bush junior you you reset eight
years like never happened right never happened and that's what the and i don't know is that lawful to do
that you see the answer would be no it's not lawful it's not a lawful timekeeping well for the pranksters
in the historical system it absolutely as they've kept us veiled this whole time hood winked as you
had said and now they've got us running in the streets screaming kill all the fanatics
yeah and the fanaticism is what you are being shown like for example back to nine eleven for a moment
when nine eleven happened and when in thirty seconds they said it was Muslim terrorists it was
loosely accepted because since the seventies eighties and nineties hollywood had done a very good job
in procuring Muslim terrorists in film right and also news and uh... and also the xenophobia of how
look how different they are kind of thing it's always you know just like with asia in world war two
it's very easy to pin out an adversary because they look very different because you have the sports
mentality you know people are into sports you know it's about bunch of people in uniform chasing a ball
and the reason why they're so easy to follow sports is because they look the teams look
very different you don't need to be a genius to figure out what's going on right
so without a doubt and we saw that whole sports mentality come out that's exactly what runs these
politics and everybody's like my team has to win and and now we see the results of what happens
with poor losers uh and and in these in this very thought that you're having here i i made me consider
this idea of how many bloody murders would you personally witness without television or hollywood
sure uh very few uh but it's kind of difficult to say because without television or hollywood there
might be fewer distractions and people might be out actually committing more of them right all right
to Shay but so we can see how this has been melded into the system just lowly and subtly that this
has been going on forever and ever and and that's the thing is that they have they've spawned these
reactions when kathy ol brian who we will be having on the show folks very soon uh you know as
been talking about this for 25 years and it's only now because it's a mob rule situation that
they're going to react to this knowledge and what we hope the greek and i folks is that we give you
data so that the reactions will will you know be tempered by understanding and knowledge that this
is not new it's not time to react they're forcing you to react at this moment
sure and you know the reactionaryness of everything you know uh if you were growing up let's say in the
50 60 70s or even 80s when world leaders or captains of industry were speaking we're speaking you
notice how they spoke about multi-generational terms they wanted to do these big public works projects
and social changes you ever notice now how captains of industry and leaders of people only speak
from a reactionary point of view when event happens they're taken out of wherever just to make a
comment there there is no more discussion about uh you know multi-generation no or long term thinking
at all and that is another clue you need to look at folks to see uh how things are falling in place
but you have to remember if anyone is familiar with homeopathy uh right which is how little of a
substance you can give or the subtle energies it's the subtle energies that actually dictate the
things that come later it's the shape of the river uh not the water that dictates the flow you see
so what's happening now and it's been happening for a while is a lot of subtleties are being put in place
that are allowing people to accept what's happening and we'll probably get into a little bit more
on uh the current situation like you brought up you know the pitophilia the human sacrifice let's say
you brought up the murders and uh the stoning and all this how that people are being let's say
indoctrinated or being it's being they're being warmed up to these concepts because these things
are going to be very significant in the near future actually in the next decade let's say the secular
decade don't be pranked by the systems folks uh mob does not rule the subtleties of your very
character will make all the difference necessary don't run around screaming kill all the fanatics
because well that makes you a fanatic so what a wonderful understanding to to start to bring about
the knowledge necessary to to stand on a firm plane as the world just erupts into chaos around you
and know that you're not being pranked by this very same system if you guys prank yeah
I'm gonna ludicrous trick yes yeah it is ludicrous it is all ludicrous this whole thing that I'm
watching right now is ludicrous folks it's insane I mean uh I mean I wouldn't pick either one of
these people to you know take care of my dog uh much less be the ruler of my nation I the the things
that have come out that people just don't care is blowing my mind but I don't want them to really
get it all in one punch like they are this idea of child trafficking and MK ultra and all the true
things that are going on behind the scenes in the dark dark occulted world of politics and global
governance so I don't want you to be reacting to that I want you to be knowing that this information
has been here it's it's we've been talking about it and we can change things but homeopathically
with subtlety as we interact with one another I want to conclude this by saying you can find the Greek
very soon at uncommon radio dot com that is uncommon radio dot com and he he gives you his work in in
bits and bites and lets you take that in and I want to announce that next week we will be talking
with Fritz spring Meyer on the beast system because we got such a uh wave rave review from last week
show we had to we got to get deeper into this so Fritz spring Meyer next week on the beast system
and tonight I will be live 8 p.m. pacific that's 11 p.m. Eastern I hope on kb k a b c in loss angeles
so if you're in the LA area 8 p.m. I will be live on the radio and that should be an amazing show I
certainly hope so I'll do my best I promise you that so we're going to take the Greek over into
the members section we're going to look at birthday cards cannibals and dolls we're going to bring
up a little bit more doom and gloom and then we're going to discover something special about people's
tattoos as a matter of fact have you seen this latest one I'll put it in the artwork for you folks
this one blew my mind it's gonna be right there on freemontv.com for you uh it is a woman who had
Donald Trump is not my f.ing president down her entire back in a tattoo this is blowing my mind
because hell Hillary might still be president in a not too distant future it should be stuck with this
for the rest of her life we're going to talk to the Greek about tattoos the Middle East union doom
and gloom and really look more into our homeopathic stasis these deities and demons that we're dealing with
so I hope you all will subscribe get over to freemontv.com and click subscribe there are numerous ways to
do it and it all helps in getting this media out to a bigger and bigger audience so that we can really
start to affect change in ourselves and then watch that radiate as it comes up through the plant life
around us though those around us all you can do folks is plant a seed and watch it grow you're never
going to beat this stuff in anybody's head and the more you listen to the Greek the more you realize
that they don't care they really don't you can bring out their own books you can bring out their own data
and say here you are completely wrong and they'll say well that's not my book any final thoughts on
that gree oh well you know I think we're gonna really finalize it in the next hour so I encourage
anyone to uh just come on over to the membership area it's a fantastic time folks it's really been
going great and thank you all so much there's been such a great rave review recently and over the last
few months and you know all of this last year obviously he's been just epic so uh get tuned in
and we're all here for you I promise and there's gonna come a time where that river is gonna guide us
all together so I really look forward to seeing you all out there until next week we will see you later
[Music]
[MUSIC]