You Chilly Effect is sponsored by Wall Street Window.com and listen to this like you.
May 30, 2022, allegedly according to that thing we call a calendar, and this indeed is
the show you were looking for.
How do I know that?
Because you're hearing me say this.
So it is a Monday or Monday according to the Pope's work schedule.
There's a phrase that I don't often utter along with the rest of the beginning of the
show, you know why?
Because I got it off of somebody who explained it to me quite a while ago and was absolutely
correct when he did.
Of course, the first day of the week would be Sunday according to your calendar, right?
Sunday.
Why anyway?
Sunday, Monday, Tears Day, Wotens Day, Thursday, Friars Day, Saturn Day, and that completes
the cycle, doesn't it?
Where does it?
Where did we start talking about telling time and the fact that nobody on the planet actually
does it?
We did that on, well first, it was introduced to me on a show where I interviewed a guy
that I just knew as the Greek.
Now, I'd heard about him but didn't really talk to him before, did this some years ago,
and I think it was on American Freedom Radio.
Well, anyway, thanks to Danny Romero, we ended up doing a little show called O'Chelly
in the Greek.
What the hell?
You gotta say the things that people aren't saying sometimes because if you have knowledge
and you don't speak it, there is something about that.
But we might wind up discussing all that as we attempt to recap or add commentary to the
O'Chelly in the Greek shows, which were in two sections, two major sections anyway, and
we have revisited those topics over the years and done separate interviews or discussions
and whatnot and the Greek has been invited into many places, at least many by my count anyway.
Many places where they thought, "Oh, the O'Chelly in the Greek show is great."
They invite the Greek on, they never invite me because I'm just the guy framing it.
But anyway, thanks Freeman, who I invited on to my show and never invited me onto his,
and stuff like that, but all petty, petty concerns, the world is strange and it's even stranger
when you actually pay attention to what's happening and what's about to happen.
The Greek is with me, how you doing, man?
Hey, I'm doing, doing what the Greek does.
So we're here for another one because every time we do something, it's another one, right?
It absolutely is.
It's certainly another one.
I forgot to ask you before we went to air, we could take phone calls, but I didn't really
promote this or anything, so probably nobody's prepared to take the calls and they'll get
the podcast later.
I guess they possibly say anyway.
Any question they have has already been answered?
Think about it.
That's true when we're talking about recapping the stuff we already covered.
Of course, you and I discussed some things in private and semi-private before, the public,
the private conversation and public concept, the water episode, which is still somewhere
on O'Cellys.com.
It's not there right out in public because it wasn't meant to be shared far and wide, but
we should be.
We've got more stuff in the bag as they speak.
We got something, let's say we meaning because you never really come up with anything on your
own, right?
Completely.
Cosmic forces, right?
Oh, look at this.
I have a listener in the chat room who's very familiar with you who is actually asking what
day it is.
That's what I was about to do.
I think, I don't know if you stepped on me or I stepped on you, we cross hairs there a little
bit and I was going to say it's very simply the 16th day of the third month.
You got to really think about it this way though.
The day starts at noon.
You know how they, you look up moon phases on Wikipedia and it's 29.3 or 28.6 days.
That's because they're trying to wiggle it into a midnight schedule, but if you do it at
noon, if it starts at noon, meaning high noon, right?
The zenith.
Because you know there's actually a noon in the middle of the night also, but that's
another story.
That's more advanced.
We've only talked about stuff on second grade level.
That would be third, fourth grade.
But it's the, as of noon time today, it kicked over to the 16th day.
And your day of rest, you know how every culture has a seventh day of rest, you know, culture
had it except for the Mayans because they were working on another solar system.
They only had a 20 day month, right?
But every culture, you know, even the, you know, I mean when I say pagan, you know there's
about 3,500 different tribes or groups of it.
They know about the seventh day.
So that just happened.
So your seventh day of rest is on the eighth day of the month, the 15th, 22nd and 29th,
and then your last day is the 30th.
And when you figure out that the day starts at high noon, just like anybody grew up in the
50s, 60s and 70s, remember the old banking convention before it was electronic?
What happens?
Well, how did they date the checks when they brought in after 12 o'clock?
They dated them the next day, remember that?
That's right.
And no, they did that.
And actually they did that all the way up into the 90s even with the different communications
now starting to really be prolific as far as computers go.
It still was that way.
Yeah, you bring it in.
Why is this, I actually ask that question, I think, when I was 16 or so.
And I cast a check and they stated that it was cast on the next day.
I said is that a state?
Is it the old system?
It's the, well, it's the slave, you know, instead of calling it the United Nations, it's
really, it was initially, there's two United Nations, the one that started in the Presidio
to fight Japan and then it was reorganized in '47 and it was the Vatican consolidated slave
holdings.
But that didn't go good, so they bought the United Nations anyway.
Anyway, yeah.
So where are we at?
Where are we at?
By the way, one of my regular listeners actually said he's very happy that he is still tracking
with the correct date as he knows it.
So you just declared it.
Yeah, I know who it is.
Yeah.
He's made me aware of that as well.
Oh, okay.
Well, it's not, it's not Joe just in case you think it's.
Oh, it's not.
Well, I hope there's, well, you know, here's the thing.
If half the world helped one person, everybody's taken care of.
True enough.
So if one third of the world took care of two people, everybody's taken, if one person took
care of 100 people, everybody's taken care of.
So you know, in meaning one percent, see, so if you do something in life that makes someone
else's life better, right?
That's quite an accomplishment.
You know, there's a lot of sayings about that, right?
Oh, yeah.
So I've gotten about 1200 emails in the past seven years that are specific, not 1200 emails,
total, but 1200.
A thousand or 1200, including some that are 24 pages long, not paragraphs or pages, they
have to be PDF.
Anyway, that they tell me generally because of what you've said, not because of me, you've
got to be very careful because you told me your life is better because of me.
I'm going to slap you down or drop you like a hot potato.
It's not me.
It's what I'm saying.
It's a big difference.
You know, when you get a $50,000, let's say check in the mail, do you go and hug and kiss
the postman?
You know what?
You know, there's nothing to do with it.
He just brought it to you.
Yeah.
You don't even know.
You don't even want to look at his ugly face.
So anytime, so I'm just saying.
So for her.
Yeah, I'm just going to say I have a lady who I know.
I know what to keep time.
I know who the gods are, which is a bad word.
I think we've gone over, you know, as we go down, we're going to pick these titles down.
You know, there are no gods.
I hope you guys know that.
It's a very poor use.
We'll get into that briefly.
Chalk the hashtag up, but they eat better.
They think better.
They sleep better.
They're finances are better.
Right.
We're actually finances are better.
There may be less in fewer zeros, but the quality is better, right?
Fair enough.
So on and on and on.
So if everybody else, I can get a couple more people to do that on what they do well.
Nope, not, not say what I'm saying, but say what they say in their expertise field and
share it.
Right.
So.
Okay.
Well, let's go.
You know, let's, let's, let's begin.
Well, let, let, let's, let's take the old episodes as a framework, right?
And I know exactly the first organized episode because we had a couple of discussions before
that and we went around different things and made some jokes and had a good time and,
and, and, and by the way, I never object to that.
We consider you until jokes, Greek.
I mean, this is a positive thing to do too, but since we're on, on, on track here to do something,
I, I have the idea that we should begin with, everything is external input.
Now, right.
And I said, I found the playlist.
It won't show up on a search, but it'll show up on a regular search on a browser, right?
On, so it's, and this is the first episode is on the bottom of the playlist.
Okay.
I don't know if anybody could follow because I, I, there are a couple of people that I've
told that do have you two, right?
And I was to go listen to this series, right?
And it's old because it's, it, it doesn't matter if you listen to this, we had a hundred years,
a hundred years, and I would still be relevant.
And it would be relevant a hundred years ago.
External input.
Yeah, we got into how we're, um, listen to the episode, you know, you know, when, you,
when you have a squirrel raised, I mean, a dog raised by gorillas, it still acts like
a dog, but a human raised by gorillas will act like a gorilla.
Why?
Because most of the animals and creatures on this planet come preloaded, preloaded software,
don't they?
Right?
We don't.
We actually mimic, we need a school.
I mean, like, you know, a training from the beginning.
I mean, think about potty training, right?
Oh my goodness.
Could you imagine when, when, when would you figure out, you know, how to use that apparatus
or that the proper squatting position, right?
What, you'd have to be able to walk first, right?
Right.
And we talked about how that's not just psychological, but it's physical.
I mean, for instance, a horse drops out of mama horse.
That thing will stand up pretty quick and be able to walk around.
I mean, it may not run like a race horse right away, but, you know, that's, that's an added
feature, right?
Typically, those herd animals within a week, they're capable of the herd, they're capable
in the herd within a week.
Right.
There, there's a level of being adept, maybe a bit limited at first, but it's, it's not
long after that they are equal and growing into their place, quickly.
People are not so much.
Never so much.
Right.
The thing I would add to that is, this work always continues.
It'll be, until my last breath, inquiring about the truth.
This kind of stems over into the container, but there's a lot of talk.
But, you know, there's this echo chamber in Italian they call them papagallo, right?
It's like a parrot, you just want to, Polly want to crack her, right?
Everybody's repeating everybody else.
I understand the political stuff because if you got, you know, and I understand the current
event stuff, but if you spend more than five minutes on a year of papagallo, you know,
I know you do that too.
I'm not saying this against you, because we have a relationship, but it's a, it's an honest
and objective criticism.
There's so much stuff that can be discussed and if you start from the beginning, you won't
you'll be discussing current events from 3,500 years ago and you'll never catch up.
So I could see why people do want to discuss it.
The thing that I don't like about it is they're just piggybacking, they're riding the wake
of the mainstream, you know, because most of these people on this planet, which we'll
get into later when we talk about the constitution, it's important too, our, it's a herd mentality.
And it's beyond that.
That's how they were raised in external input, right?
But the thing that I want to talk about really that bridges over to the physiology of it.
I've been looking at this DNA and that's what I said, why, before I said DNA and genetics,
it's really genetics.
You hear a lot of talk about that, you know, how they want to mess with it and the alternative
talks about this and that and star seeds and this and that, but no one really takes the
time to research all the grunt work that's been done on it, you know, in other words, lab
reports, scientific reports that are real, not, not as, you know, something that someone
is reading about what someone else wrote about something else, but actually the actual, you
know, the grunt work, you know, that was done, the good research, right?
Although you could say that that grunt work is often built on earlier grunt work, I mean,
the course of life.
Yeah, be careful.
Well, I'm talking about isolated experiments where the, all the controls are within the
document.
Oh, certainly, but they're informed by previous work, okay?
There is a continuum here where in the, you know, say someone is alive 80 years, in those
80 years, they only go so far.
So quite frankly, they have to have a beginning.
No, I'm strictly talking about like when they teach science, the way they used to teach
it 50 years ago, you had the theory hypothesis experiment conclusion, right?
Like you approach it, you approach the problem, you chew gum and then you figure out the
answer just by chewing gum, right?
No, you just joke it.
That's what they're doing now.
Yeah, really.
So, no, no, what I mean to say is that what happens though is that they must be informed as
to there is a problem to begin with for them to begin the exploration, right?
You don't have a hypothesis without a bit of speculation, one, yes, and also some level
of information.
I mean, even any theory must be based on something.
So you have a basis that is not often picked off by the person who is now going to take
it further.
I'm saying there is a continuum of information which is built or can be, I should say, and
has been disrupted, manipulated and hidden.
But the idea is that, you know, at first maybe there was a concept that things that were
invisible could be, you know, they're not observable by the human eye necessarily.
Maybe they don't exist at all.
And that had to graduate into no.
There are things that cannot be seen by the human eye which are present.
Well, right?
Yeah, 99.9999999999.
You want to add 1,0009999 so that is invisible to us based on the instrument of the eye, the
senses.
We have to use tools.
You know, and they've always been around.
You know, when they dig up, you know, when they find high tech devices in the US, the Smithsonian
comes in, they put it in a shipping container, fill it with concrete and take it out to the
Marianne's trench and drop it, right?
Because it doesn't match history.
So everything you see around and more dances around long time ago.
But what I want to say about the genetics and the hereditary is very interesting.
This was very difficult to find.
But within the DNA itself, there's a whole other world of it.
Like an easy way to start off, and it does have memory.
You do carry memory, but it's not tangible.
It's what I don't like to use Freudian terms, but it's more in the subconscious, right?
You're not conscious of it, but it could be ferret, ferret it out if you push yourself.
And there's a very deep layer.
Let me just cut to the thing and we'll bring it up again with the container.
You know how when you cut a tree, it has tree rings, right?
And it shows the summer grain and the winter grain, right?
Your mitochondria has that too.
And it emerges differently in everyone when you're born and they don't know where the
whole this comes from because the actual might interior of the mitochondria is very, very
old.
The actual composition, the chemistry and the organic chemistry is aged.
So a new baby comes into the world, but their mitochondria could be three, four, five,
twenty thousand years old within the cell itself.
And they're like, how the hell does this carry over?
Well, it does.
Okay?
So, but they can't, well, you can't talk about this publicly.
We'll get into some other stuff.
How simple this is.
There's a bit of an influence that you carry over.
So as you, everything, yes, learning how to poop properly because everybody poops, right?
All that all the way to how you speak and how you act as external.
But there is a very, very base, you might call it psychological spiritual, recordation
of everyone that came before you within that genetic line and what might be in there
is previous traumas, previous successes, right?
These tendencies, meaning what your spirit, you know, mind is, is, is, is what you have
proclivities for.
Not necessarily the way, what language you speak or whatever, right?
So there is an influence, a very subtle influence, which I don't think it's as subtle as people
or am I put it just because it's small doesn't mean it's, in, in significant, you know?
Well, it's the most ladies will think so.
But anyway, so, so that's the external input.
I'd like to leave that one on.
There's only one thing, one comment.
I never leave comments of you, animals are not homosexual.
They might have those kinds of behaviors and things like that, but there is no homosexual,
the animals and we've explained what homosexuality is.
It's a mind control thing, right?
It's actually a ritual.
We'll talk about, we'll talk about that as we go on, you know, like, like in a perfect
society, there is no military, meaning that everyone is in the military.
If the country needs to be defended, everyone is boots on the ground and everyone has
at least five hours of training on some kind of weapon they could use to defend themselves.
So you don't need a military if everybody is in the military, right?
So you see, so, so the, so when you get to the point that the humans are now, which will
discuss external input here, I'll throw this in also is, when you read the ancient texts
and you will talk about this when we bring up the gods, you know how I talk about how simplistic
life should be, food clothing shelter, which we did want on that and all that.
And maybe I'll save it for that because this is very, very important and it's, it's things,
you know, how I've kind of hold back because, you know, new information should be given
as such and then if it's appreciated, you continue and then if it's not, you just let
it be, you know, and we'll get more into the, the, what shouldn't let be on this one.
So we run out of time quick.
What was the next one?
What was the next one we did?
It was the container.
Oh my goodness.
Right.
Well, the container, these two things are logically, it makes sense to go from one to the
other.
Again, about the container, you have to know what the container is even to begin to tackle
something like DNA because, well, as you said, trauma, well, that's definitely external
input, right?
But also external input has to do with the other things that are taken into the
body and utilized to keep building the body, right?
So what could be getting a, a, a big dose of arsenic, it feels like, you know, your stomach
is like a cement block appeared in your stomach suddenly, right?
Sure.
That could be part of it too.
But naturally, before we continue, yeah.
Well, but naturally, there's another part of it.
We're talking about the human body and biology.
Yeah, of course, but naturally one must assume even external input, okay.
What do you might say about the psychological end of it?
Well, the psychological end of it creates a physiological response, spiritual, true.
But you know, that is a psychology means spirit, yeah.
Yeah.
And what you breathe and what you are breathing in, that's why I often mix those terms because
spirit is breath, okay?
No, that's salt.
Well, either way, that's the, the whole thing too.
That's the thing if you, if you missed, you ever see the movies where, which wire do I
cut, so disarm the bomb?
Why would you tell them to cut the red wire when you should cut the black wire when you
want the bomb to go off, right?
So they reverse definition like the word nice.
That's a terrible word to wish upon someone, especially in the beginning of the day.
Well, this is why we're constantly looking at the etymology of these things.
Yeah, so the etymology, like psyche, in Greek, psyche is the spirit.
And in English, it has to do with psychosis, psychology, right?
Anything that has to do with the mind, so the mind is the spirit.
The soul is the numa.
In English, it's spelled with a P and U prefix.
So when you have a pneumatic tire, pneumonia, right, it has to do with air movement.
So the living, you know, everything is part of biology, even rocks, right?
Because otherwise, you wouldn't have a fossil, that's a rock, right?
So if you have something alive, becomes a rock, a rock, you know.
And who's to say a rock doesn't have a thought every thousand years, which is more than most
people I met, by the way?
But the thing is, we don't consider these things that don't breathe air and have a metabolism
to be alive.
They do.
I actually suggest that everything has an inhalation, exhalation.
You could suffocate a rock as an experiment.
You can do it.
Meaning when it suffocates, it loses its properties, its color changes, its strength
changes, right?
So the, that, again, think of the, without even getting it, see, it's very, how would you
say, if you say there's no such thing as a virus, right?
Because a virus as such is part of toxicology, which is part of liver function.
If you want to create a poison to toxify someone, you have to know how the liver works.
Like for example, if you want to suffocate someone, you got to know how the big toe works.
No, I'm just joking.
If you want to suffocate someone, you got to know how the lungs work, right?
Okay.
Look, this is why I'm trying to get you to settle down a little bit.
Because you're kind of, you're kind of dancing along a little bit quickly here.
And I want to, I want to go step by step so that it can be easily understood.
You and I have talked about being easily understood as well.
Here's the thing.
The external input, right?
This is relatable to all the things that come next because, as I was saying, when you're
talking about even DNA and what goes into it and trauma, what I was trying to get at is
that the body will create a chemical which will affect things.
This nowadays they refer to as epigenetic.
It is above the genetic response.
But what it does is it creates a response best I can understand that literally does alter
the structure of the thing.
It is.
Hold on.
The body doesn't, you stop to a little too quick there.
You said the body creates a chemical that.
No.
The reason the body creates the chemical is to be a carrier.
Diamonds are carbon, right?
I got a barbecue pit outside.
Lots of carbon in it.
Can I call it a diamond?
It takes the chemical, the basic organic material and develops it into how a lumpic
cold develops into a diamond.
At that point, it's imprinted.
So in other words, when you say carbon, for example, you think of a hard material like a lumpic
cold or a diamond, or CO2 gas that sublimates, it doesn't have a liquid state.
It goes from a solid to gas, right?
Like carbon dioxide, right?
But what people aren't talking about in biological entities, there is a gel state of carbon.
Pure carbon, it's a gel state.
When I mean a gel state, I mean like hair gel.
It's like jelly.
And if you pour it on a table in any lab in the world and say, test that with your inforomature
spectrometer, tell me what it is.
You want to ask say, the best equipment in the world, it'll show it's 100% carbon.
How is that possible?
Oh, we don't want to discuss that.
Right now, it will be in the future.
So when they say that we're carbon based creatures, you've heard of that.
Of course.
Well, it's not the carbon that we are familiar with externally.
It's the carbon that we're familiar with, not familiar with that happens in all biological
beings.
What can you do with a gel?
Could you imagine metallic hydrogen?
I drop a bar of metal on your table, heavy enough, that'll break your foot if you drop it on
your...and if you have it measured, it's pure oxygen.
It'll be scratching your head all day, right?
Think about how incredible that is.
Now, all these materials in different states can carry different things.
Hey, here's an idea.
Let's take a plastic tape, put magnetic particles on it, and when the music is playing
through the input board, we'll stimulate those magnetic particles.
So when we replay the magnetic tape over the inverse head, a magnetic head, it'll create
an electrical impulse that will record music, because before cassette tapes or regular tapes
they used wire for that, right?
And then we got to the point where we're using light.
And now we're using light within little chips.
Do you know that here's a statistic and I'm going to be conservative, I'm not going to exaggerate.
Do you know that your typical stupid rectangle, what they call a smartphone, is got 16
billion transistors in it?
Think about it.
Why do you know that many?
Yeah, look it up.
It's actually conservative.
The iPhone 13 or whatever's got 23.
Okay.
The new ones...yeah, or 10 years ago they had 7 billion.
You know what a transistor is, it's a switching, in other words, the old vacuum tubes, the
good guitar amps and all that.
Each tube represents one transistor.
So they went away from the vacuum tubes, they put it on a solid state silicon chip and
they made it so small that they could put 16 billion.
You know if you stood here counting 16 billion seconds, you know you might run out of time,
right?
In your life.
That's how many transistors you'd be.
So all of these...we're doing this.
I mean I'm saying, human hands, human artisers, we're talking about, you want to get real
13 year old slave girls in the Far East are building these, right?
Think about it.
You're not going to argue with me on that, right?
No, no.
Okay.
They're putting...so 13 year old slave girls in the Far East are assembling devices that are
fairly cheap with 16 billion transistors and that we can't count to 16 billion if we
lived another hundred years.
Are you carrying this around?
And this is commonplace, this is nothing special I'm talking about.
Well, right.
No, they're...they're much more sophisticated things that are...
Yeah, not that sophisticated things are so sophisticated that I cannot even talk about
it.
Right.
I will.
We'll broach it a little bit and I'll show you how simple some of these things are.
This is...we're talking about the...what it means to be in this universe.
When you listen to Greek speak, it is extremely rarefied.
It talks about what this universe is about.
Which, by the way, is a great B universe.
We're not in a great...okay.
It's a B movie universe, okay?
How else would you say it?
It's where...this universe is set up to be like a bad Saturday morning cartoon.
How else can I say?
Actually, you know, I'm using references that you have to be born in the 70s or 60s to
know.
But so tell me if I get too retro.
It's all right.
This is the universe we're in.
So...and it's a fine place for what it is.
Let's go back to the container because we're going to run out of time.
I always...we always do.
And you're always going to run out of time on this stuff.
But the reason I use the container is to get people away from their body because you're
not your body, right?
You know, we'll talk about consciousness transfer.
That's one of the technologies that's been around for over 90 years and it's completely hidden
from people, right?
Well, people are still conscious about that.
People are still conscious about that coming, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, it's already been around for 80 years and it's constantly being developed for 80 or
90 years.
The container...here's an interesting thing.
You know when people are illiterate, you show pictures.
You don't write, remember the old towns?
You had a shoe on the store.
You didn't write any...but you wrote shoes because most people weren't interested in learning
how to read, right?
Yeah.
So when you go into biology, any human anatomy medicine, any study, let's say gastrointestinology,
right?
You'll find anatomy drawing of an intestine and you're illiterate and you look at it and
they tell you that some holistic idiot doctor says, "I make a natural product that
your body absorbs better."
Look at the intestine.
Show me how anything gets absorbed through three or four hydrophobic layers.
As a matter of fact, you could download a cross-section of firestone steel-belted radial
tire and hold it next to the intestine drawing and they're the same in principle, right?
Yeah, nothing goes through these membranes.
Your lungs, look at lung tissue.
It's not as robust as the intestine and the billi and all that are different because
you need a higher surface area to a certain degree because things happen faster in the
lungs.
Hopefully your body thinks happen faster in the lungs.
But anyway, nothing goes through the body.
It's in a vacuum.
In other words, it's a two-separate atmosphere here, anterior exterior.
You have a tunnel that goes from the mouth to the end.
This is discussed.
That throws contagions completely.
The only thing that could be contagious is something actually lodging on the surface,
interior or exterior.
We have a serious problem because let's just think about it simply.
We're just visiting here.
We notice that they offer you the common courtesy that if you don't know how to read their
stuff, they offer a picture once in a while, right?
Only, not only are all the medical textbooks and anatomy books full, chock full of text,
but they have diagrams for the completely illiterate.
In this case, they're highly educated, nor the illiterate are picking up on what I'm talking
about here, which is self-evident, by the way.
As a matter of fact, you ever go to a place where they, of course, sausage is, right?
What is a sausage?
It's ground meat, stuffed in an intestine, right?
Yeah.
What it should be anyway, yeah?
It's, well, yeah, so nothing goes out through there.
In many, the concept of a soccer ball, they used to take animal bladders and put air or
carry water.
How are you going to carry water?
Do you think they had wine flasks and water flasks made from animal skins because the skin
is the same and animal organs because they leaked?
No.
They made liquid containers out of animal skins and animal organs because they didn't leak.
There's nothing that goes through that.
So again, if you set 100% of the human population is moronic, that's pretty true, but if you pick
out, statistically, you can say 99.9999 because the medical textbooks and the biological textbooks
are accommodating the literate and the illiterate and no one is noticing.
So what do you do with a population like that?
Well, you do a cell in the Greek once in a while.
It's always the same thing with the cause.
The only amendment I would make there with the container is that there are states of
elements, a metallic hydrogen, gel state carbon, on and on and on, that human bodies can
make.
I mean, any bylaw, a plant can do it, right?
Anything alive that has a metabolism, a soul is a metabolism, right?
So metabolic rate is breathing, circulation, various systems, nervous systems, circulatory,
respiratory, right?
Right.
When all those systems shut down, the body, the physical part goes into chemical decomposition.
It starts to, that's what death is, right?
And then the mind and the spirit no longer is carried.
Just like if you're, right now you have a soundboard and all this in front of you recording
and you're broadcasting.
If I went in and pulled all the wires, I just took the soul out of everything and it's
just going to shut down even if they pulled the batteries out, right?
Nothing works.
Right.
So that's the soul.
The spirit is the information that's being carried.
So on the container, I would leave that alone for now and going into how deep it can get,
it gets very, very deep.
And it's already been exposed.
Like I said, they have it in text and they have it in pictures if you can't read and
nobody still notices.
What are they supposed to do?
Walk on your door in the middle of the night and tell you, hey, you better learn this, no
one's going to do that, right?
So.
Well, you know, I take note that in the third episode, we went to the Constitution.
Let's do that.
And you know what's interesting there is that I was just thinking to myself, where are
their pictures for the illiterate of the Constitution?
Well, why is it a con?
Why isn't it a pro?
Wouldn't you rather have the prostitution?
Why do you got to be so con all the time?
I got you.
Anyway, okay.
So the Constitution here, let's, that's pretty good there.
I don't know if I nailed the, sent home the point that it's a free, Masonic document, right?
And there's something called, I'm going to be loosely going around the airy fairy woo-woo
circles, right?
That the new age, okay, we give you an example.
Back in the late 80s, I was living in Manhattan and I had roommates and neighbors in kind of
new age.
And about flat earth, concave earth, indigo babies coming in and nurse says, yeah, babies that
are being born out, they have a red spot behind their knee and they're like special babies.
All the stuff you start hearing now, you know, the new age stuff that started in the 1800s,
but I was around the flat earth.
Look, in the 1990s, I was telling people, you know, the earth, they're lying to us, right?
I really knew the moon missions.
Look, when they broadcast the moon mission, I was four years old and the parents had a friend
come over.
And at four years old, you might remember a good amount, but I remember looking at him and
he says, everything that's showing on TV is a lie.
This is being done in a film studio while it was happening, not later.
And I remembered that.
So I started talking about that later.
I was like, hey, there's somebody standing right there, right?
In real time.
So when I say about woo-woo airy fairy, I've seen that my whole life, you know what I mean,
right?
That's like way off with the mainstream beliefs.
Of course.
And I'm not one, you know, it's something that, you know, it has its place, right?
Because it's a communication.
That's all.
I don't take it to heart, but it's just, you know, you know what's there?
And if you got access to the access to the airy fairy stuff.
So anyway, they talk about like the Luciferian rebellion, you know, there's like this cosmic
war, right?
Negative versus positive, the dark versus the light.
The light is always portrayed as having a monarchy, an imperial reign with Princess Prince's
King Queen.
The dark force may have that, but in a more evolved state, what they want to do is get
out of people's minds that they should ever accept a king or queen.
So they invented this constitution thing where they have these various sections of government.
So when you don't like what they're doing, you go to one group and they say, well, this
other branch made us do it.
And then you go to the other branch and they said the other branch made us do it, right?
It's a typical scam.
So the whole thing about this constitution thing, and by the way, I have not met, I met, I
had a long discussion on supposedly a constitutional lawyer and a constitutional scholar.
And when I brought up things, they didn't even know was in the constitution.
So if your job is to study this document and I say article such in section 10 says there
will be no US court will have any power in law or equity.
They didn't even know it was in there.
Right.
And that's a major thing.
If the constitution says that US courts have no power in law, then what the hell are they
doing?
It's in the constitution.
Yeah.
I got you.
Look, there's a few things in there that are rather contradictory to the things that you
will ever have been made.
Yeah.
And there's no rights in the constitution, right?
Talk about that.
Well, that's another thing.
That's the bill of rights that came 14 years later.
That was the second revolution was the bill of rights.
You know, the constitution is a really good guy that studied this in Arkansas, Jerry Kirk.
His dad was studying it.
His grandfather was studying it.
Okay.
They found documentation.
The constitution, it was 1789, way down.
They sent it to the Vatican and five years later it came back approved.
You know, the copy from the Vatican was the one they used, right?
Because the whole thing is to get in your mind here.
Here, here, give another thing.
Let's want to say the constitution is government.
You have no government.
You have the state is it's not the same.
That's why if you go to any form, birth certificate form, driver's license form, the last, you
know, you fill out all the stuff they want in the form and you sign it.
What's the last thing on every form?
Oh, they all say the same thing.
It doesn't matter what form you use.
It says all in front here in information is to be used for the good of the state.
It doesn't say government is a big difference.
So that's another mix up.
Like, soul and spirit.
I don't know the difference between the state and the government.
So just like federal reserve, it's not federal and it has no reserves, right?
That's why one day I think I'd like to talk to you about the Magna Carta, but not today.
Magna Carta was a step in to create a lack of confidence.
Okay, you can give me an example.
I live in a free democratic society where the government has secret police agencies, secret
spying. They put toxins in the food.
They prevent healing methodologies.
They arrest those that put healing methodologies out there go against their alopathic system.
They have, they don't have any money.
They have credit.
They create money off your signature and they lie to you every day.
Okay?
And there's no private ownership a lot, even though people think.
Okay, let's, that's the situation.
And they basically deceive you.
But it's a free democratic society constitutional republic.
Now here's this other society.
It's a fascist dictatorship and they're communist also, but they have a benevolent royal
running it.
And he makes sure that there is no secret police.
The money is based on substance.
All of the food is grown with strict measures that there is no toxins put in.
The education system is free and open and there is no revisionism in it.
There is property ownership and which one would you rather live in?
Do you see?
Well, obviously the communist fascist where everything is good.
Well, see, but how is it communist and fascist if it's like that?
You see, that's, that's, that's, that's, yeah.
Exactly.
So when you, they've got names against you, those, oh, communist, that's bad.
Well, it, it doesn't matter what form of government they have.
Is it my level in?
Or is it benevolent?
Is it parasitic and predatory?
Or is it nurturing it and benevolent?
Yeah.
Okay.
That's always, that's always the larger question.
You know, when you, I, I, I find this going round and round with people about these isms
all the time that, that, that, that is the ultimate question to me is, well, is this a better
circumstance to be in than that?
Because I don't care what label you slap on it.
Here's what's actually happening.
Right.
That's the point with this whole thing and that's why you don't have a government anymore.
And then you, and you can actually, there was a congressman, and they killed him twice, believe
it or not, if that's possible.
He, he did the last in 1992 congressional report says, hey, we're completely bankrupt.
This is the largest trust in you in world history.
1933 bankruptcy, right?
So you're living in a bankrupt entity.
So the bottom line is they drove everyone to places that they evaded the royalty because
it's, if you have a malevolent government and it's got all these branches and sections,
the chances of flipping them over to being benevolent.
And by the way, when they're malevolent, they don't tell you they're malevolent, they
tell you the opposite, right?
Always, right?
Because when someone's going into the hardware store to steal, they, if you ask them what
you're doing here, they say, I'm here to steal or they say, hey, I'm just a customer.
Right?
So, so it's, if you can't change it when, when it's, when it's a multiplex system, but
if you have one guy in charge and his wife and his son or whatever, it's a lot easier to
convince them, right?
Two or three people.
Then in what?
You got 623 congressmen and whatever.
And senators, you got the executive groups, you got all the intelligence agencies, the
court system, you're going to convince all of them to work together, make it better,
let's never, never, never.
So, the purpose of, of this whole discussion is to show people that careful in what words
you use because the word in itself doesn't hold the function.
So, a malevolent democracy versus a benevolent fashion, you know, dictatorship, which one would
you rather have?
Most people, most Americans that rather have a malevolent democracy because they're so,
you know, over the edge right now, right?
Well, because they're attached to the term as opposed to the, the, the, the, the, the
circumstance to reality, the function of it, you know, and, and that is, again, a, a,
reason why I'll move us ahead just a little bit, because I titled it strangely the next
time and I think it was God is dead question mark.
Mm-hmm.
And, and the reason for that, because now I've went and gotten a list as you suggested, which
people can do if they search for it.
And, anyways, you just keep it in order.
It is very important because here is the greater question, right?
What, what actually is all this organized upon?
Because all along the way, whether it is the design of the external input or the intention
of the container, right?
What always enters that, that discussion?
I mean, even atheists, which I find funny.
Uh, well, the atheists I like because they know the gig is up.
They know that they're being served bullshit with religion.
Yeah, but they don't.
So it's easier to say it.
Wait a minute, but they don't because I really honestly, most of them, they, they, they
don't actually adhere to that just like everything else.
Nothing is.
Oh, they use, they use divine language.
They said, well, the, this created that while you need a creator, right?
If you read the atheist books, they, they use the language that would mean there is
some, an external input, right?
But they have, but here's what the problem is though is they always seem to find their way
to another deity and they don't, yeah, it, it, it, it, exactly.
It's the state.
You just ask them, you don't believe in God, but do you believe in the laws of the state?
And they say, well, then the, the state is your God because your law comes from your
God.
And guess what?
April 1st is your holiday, right?
Exactly.
But, but that's my point.
Is it?
And they do Christmas.
They do Christmas, by the way.
There are the exceptions who actually seem to internalize the concept and yeah, they know
the gigs up.
But my friend, most of these atheists are just basically adopted sadism.
No, they're just as ignorant as your typical human, but the God's okay.
First of all, just delve right into it.
There is no such thing that God is a word like democracy or fascism, whatever, eludes
a certain thing.
That's a tutonic term.
It means the sun, tutonic meaning old German English.
Yes.
And it means the sun or the sky or the heavens.
Like even today, if you go to, is this, this was worldwide.
If you, like in Asian cultures, they don't use the term God.
It's the power of the heavens, meaning if they're flying in the sky and they could drop
shit on you, you better pay, you know, you better give them respect.
That's basically what it is, right?
If they're, you know, in military, it's called the higher ground, you know?
What kind of sensible?
And, you know, just a quick illusion to a formally tied way.
So there is no, there is no sense.
No, no, no, no, I'm just saying this is sensible though to, to reckon with, to respect the
power of something that can drop something on you out of the sky.
Okay.
And just essentially what it is.
Right.
And a quick allusion to somebody who passed on recently is that, you know, Jordan Maxwell's
big point at all times was, you know, makes sense to worship the sun at least because
well, it is a life giver, but it is a life giver without it.
You know, it does.
I don't, let's leave a hope he's resting well, but let's go on.
But my point is this is yet another thing which is up in the heavens as far as your concern
from your point of view, which you must reckon with.
I mean, you can't say you can ignore the sun.
It doesn't have to be over in the sky.
I'm using that as a convention that even the Easterners use, they could be under your
feet.
Also, the, so for, for example, the easiest thing to say is when you look at the biblical,
it's the alohem, the word, GOD is not in there.
I don't know where they get, I know they get the GOD from the English versions and all
that's incorrect.
Yeah, of course.
It's a derogatory term, actually.
They're, they're a race known as the alohem.
And if it wasn't for the alohem, we wouldn't be here because they're basically preserving
us.
In essence, as we go on further on, you're not put here on this planet.
This is the addendum to that, to do anything.
What people would call Genesis one, I mean, alohem is right there.
That's it.
There is, yeah, that's all there is.
It's alohem and there are other alohem within their scope.
And also the biblical, we could get into it, that is all local.
It has to do with a certain group of people.
If you think it has something to do with you and you're not one of those people, well, you're
deceived.
Right.
So, and you, you can be one of those people by allegiance, just like, you know, well,
you could have someone born in other country and they get, it isn't shipped in another country
by creating an allegiance.
You do that.
That's another way to do it.
That conversion, the only thing that you could convert is rice and currency.
But so, you notice they never talk about allegiance, they want to convert you to another religion.
But then they take God out of the, and these beings out of the picture completely.
But give you an idea, you're not here, they didn't put you here to do anything.
That's why you're always running around with horse and carriage.
You're going to say, "Greek, we're not running around with horse and carriage."
Oh, hell you were.
You, the only time you haven't been running around with a horse and carriage is the past
hundred years.
Yeah, right.
There's that.
99% of the time the year has has been on this planet.
It's horse and carriage, dude, and you're walking with sandals.
I know, 99.9% of the time you've been on this planet.
So, the reason they set it up that way is the same reason you ever see that Norway seat
bank where they got these four cliffs with these big pallets of seeds and they're putting
it in the side of an icy mountain to storm.
In case all the seeds go away, they got seeds in the mountain, right?
Yeah, this is where they're supposed to be keeping all the heirloom seeds with the
original, you know, nontampered with, non-g.
Supposedly.
Yeah.
That's what we are here.
We are put here.
We're seeded here, literally, to a very, to preserve the human, a certain type of human
away from all the mess.
It's kind of like a really bad neighborhood.
Like, I had a shop in Brooklyn and it was a really bad neighborhood.
I mean, like, really bad, you know, talking about the cliche crack houses and shootings every
night.
Right.
And there's, there's industrial building.
It was a welding closed down welding supply.
And you went through the building into the back and Brooklyn is a very old suburb.
And then the back, it opened up to this alleyway and there was another building in there that
used to be an old carriage house.
And it was just basically brought up to 1930 standards where it had one outlet in the whole
building, right?
And I used that as my shop, but it was beautiful in there.
Because you couldn't see it from the street.
You imagine you can imagine what I'm saying here, right?
And it was, I felt like I was in paradise.
You know, this building is 150, 200 years old and all, well, they used to shoe horses and
things like that.
And I used it as a shop.
And when I was in there, I didn't know what, I mean, you could hear the gunshots and all
that, right?
You see?
And they didn't know that that, no one in the neighborhood knew that that was there.
They saw me going in and out.
But you see what I mean?
So that's how the earth is.
You're in a really bad neighborhood, but you got this corridor that you're in right now.
So let me ask you, let's go back to the seed bank in the pallet that's stuck into the
frozen mountain in Norway.
What, what, what, what two seeds inside that pallet and they, hey, Chuck, what are we
supposed to do?
What do you mean we're supposed to do?
We're wrapped up in this pallet inside of the mountain.
You can't do anything.
Think about it.
You're not supposed to do anything.
You're in a seed bank, right?
But it doesn't mean it's terminal.
Well, it seems terminal, right?
No, it's preservation.
It's preservation.
You're going to be taken out and you'll be able to grow.
So, that's why 99% of the time, if not 100% of the time, you talk about making the world
a better place, you get, you find yourself eating out of a garbage can or dead.
Which is great, but it's, yeah, already be dead, by the way, being out of garbage can't,
even though there is a true science to eating out of a garbage can.
So, no, guerrilla survival is a, yeah, urban guerrilla survival is a real thing, but go
ahead.
Sure, sure.
You want it, yeah, because you don't want to get food poisoning, but here's the thing.
These Elohim are a very, very specific group, right?
You have other groupings and then you have other beings, right?
For example, here, you want to go for the hairy, this is a stretch.
There's something called the dragon of old, that keeps coming up.
When you hear that, of old term brought up in any text, that means that's as far back as
we can go.
It doesn't mean, in other words, that word of old in any ancient writ has incredible import.
It's almost like saying original.
The dragons were the first ones in this universe, not the Elohim, not the humans.
Think about it.
The humans, the Elohim, what people call Yahweh and God and all these other human beings,
came later.
This is a very, very, very, very, very complex situation.
Yeah, I don't think you've ever actually talked about this specifically before.
No, I'm not going to get into details because there's no, you don't talk about the eighth grade
when you're in the second grade, right?
You can talk about it, but it ain't going to happen.
You've got to progress through the study.
Yeah, you do.
A little glimpses of it.
Maybe, you know, look, eventually you're going to be doing this.
Yeah.
Yeah, so there's an alliance.
There are alliances between different beings.
Well, look, what do you think?
One of the things we talked about with the gods is that they're going to be making themselves
known, but they're going to be making themselves known the way they really are, not the way in
your King James or the way church or whatever tells you that none of this stuff, they are
from the sky, they're from above, and they have interests with us, both positive and negative.
Okay?
We're in a time right now starting.
And this is advice.
I do give advice, all kinds of advice to people.
You ready for this?
Your prayers and meditations mean nothing.
You're in that time period starting now, actually started a little while ago.
As time goes on, no one's going to be listening to you anymore.
So you can get on your knees and pray for help.
You ain't getting nothing.
You're on your own.
There are beings, lesser beings, that are predetermined to help you before you pray.
So when you think you're praying and you're getting help, well they knew about that before
you even, you see what I mean?
This is the point that you're at right now because the level of danger, cosmic danger, spiritual
danger that exists is radio silence, right?
Right before a war, right for the first battle, they do radio silence.
You ever notice that when the bombers, even in the movies, they show that bombers are
ready to fly over the city, do they start yipping in the appen over the radio or is it radio
silence when they take off, actually?
You know about this, right?
Of course.
But the police, the police are going to go raid someone, they're radio silence, right?
Right.
Now this is what causes me to actually skip over, learn to tell time, which is episode
five and then go to the dummy load because I fear that that's where we're going to start
and that was one of the most evocative phrases you used, which got people upset a little
bit.
We're listening a bit.
The keeping time or the dummy load?
The dummy load, of course.
Keeping time was sort of like, well, okay, I can understand that and that sort of makes
that made sense.
You see, to a lot of people who said, you know what, that makes a lot of sense because how
do you do this?
You have to observe.
Why is it, you know, we talked about how the clock is really kind of a meaningless thing.
It's meant to represent something, but you know, hold on, the clock is good for navigation.
Navigation?
Sure.
I mean, it helped us get together.
You know your speed and you know your time, you can measure your distance, literally.
Of course.
But no, no, no, look, it's perfectly good in trigonometry.
You know what I mean?
Where you do require three factors, okay?
It's fine.
But when you got to the dummy load, it just, people took it personally, which by the way,
the question in the chat comes up, which, let's see, let me just read it verbatim, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
What is the Greek value most freedom or truth, which would he prefer?
Truth, because you can't have freedom without truth.
There you go.
And I think that's it.
It's like which one do you value, you know, food or water, water, because if you have water,
you can make food.
You're true enough.
There you go.
So, but back to this, I think this leads right into the dummy load because again, it was
a misunderstood term.
Some people took it regardless of what you said as, oh, okay, so we're all dummies, which
you had said a hundred times already, but they didn't hear it until you used the word dummy.
Well, if you took it personally, it means they were, well, hold on.
If someone takes something personally, aka, insulted to a certain degree, you can only insult
the ignorant.
Someone who is well versed in whatever they think they want to know about and they're looking
for the truth cannot be insulted.
Hey, if we were in the same room right now, and you said, hey, Greek, you got tomato sauce
going down your shirt.
No, I can be insulted or I could say, hey, I didn't see that.
Thank you.
Right?
No, you try to insult me.
You say I'm a slob.
You see?
The character, so people that take things personally and get insulted, it tells you a lot about
their characters.
There's a lot of character tests.
Here give you an example in terms of the dummy load.
I have a greeting on the phone, right?
So when you call it, and this weeds out, you know, when you get a number that you don't recognize,
you might want to answer, you might not, but you know, it's a new incoming, right?
Well, you still have that greeting on your phone because that was pretty funny.
Yeah.
It says, you have reached the number that you have just dialed.
If you believe you've reached an error, hang up and dial it again.
And very often I'll see a number, the four rings that get the greeting, it hangs up, and
then 30 seconds later, the same number calls back.
So right now, I know who I'm dealing with, someone who is not listening, someone who's
not paying attention.
I just weeded out about 75 to 80% of all the possible headaches I could have with this
person if I'd end up doing business with them, whether it's for a month or a year or 10
years, I just weeded them out.
I just boxed them, I pigeon-hold them in a category that is actually objectifiable and
usable in my advantage.
Say, hey, this guy can't pay attention.
Why would I invite him over to something, you see what I mean?
So when I say these things and people get insulted, hey, fine, go sit in the corner and
be insulted because you deserve it until you change it.
That's the thing about external input.
You can change it.
It's malleable.
Well, that's the thing.
And new information or different input from what you've already received then changes what
it is you have to work with as far as making evaluations.
I mean, so, yeah, we've been through, you look, we've been through, you got the Buddhist,
you got the witch, you got the born again, Christian, all of us on air with all this stuff.
And I can't engage, I don't mind listening to a witch or a Buddhist or a born again or
whatever, but you got to bring something that has some value, not something, you know, like
giving an example, I've found out a lot of people in America especially, they get, when
you talk to them, like, old commercial jingles, right, they get, that's what they were raised
on, like you want to explain something to them, if you say, oh, Caligon, take me away, they're
like, oh, yeah, you know, or if you use things that they saw on TV, come on, you know,
commercials, this is their, this is their character, this is how their characters, they were raised
on junk, right?
You see?
No, I totally understand, that's one of those things that, you know, whenever people are
caused to, what is the term used actually, where you, you reminisce, it's, you know,
and what though, it's the quality, oh, I understand, but before you get to quality, you can strike
that tone because of repetition because they were steeped in it and that's what it is, it's
got nothing to do with the quality actually, which is because they were steeped in it, they
immediately recall it and it creates a comfort zone, you can, you can bridge gaps with
people that you disagree with by getting them to relate to something where you're, you're
now wearing these things.
She's not a dummy load, a dummy load is, see, I know all those jingles, I was raised in the
'60s and '70s, right?
With that, but I don't, I don't incorporate it in my character at all, but I noticed that,
other people do and that's, that's fine, you have a choice, right?
We do live in a certain amount of free will with that.
No, I'll throw some, yeah, I'll throw some, yeah, I'll throw some, yeah, you're right now,
Greg, we'll walk downstairs, the loner and pairs and I bet you, you know what it is, you,
you've already got it in your mind, it's actually not a bad thing.
It's just a linky, all right, anyway, how many people know that, you know, when you want
to see, but see, now listen, even in your voice, we use medical, can we use medical terms
on this or is this going anywhere?
Anyway, you know, it, it'll go places, but you know what, YouTube has suspended right now,
so screw it, God.
Okay, so anyway, anyway, anyway, you want to see something funny, hand somebody who was
born after 1990, a regular dial telephone, not a touchpad, but a dial phone and ask them
to dial a place of local, they can't, they don't even, it's like watching a monkey trying
to fuck a football, right?
So anyway, what do you do with that?
Well, you know, you, they're enlighten them, like I've met some wonderful, wonderful young
children and the nanny would put them in front of the TV and I told the parents, they'll
let the TV, the nanny, and the nanny just puts these wonderful children, twins, boy and
girl for turnl twins, and the parents got insulted, I said, you know, your nanny has the
children from the TV all day, the TV is raising your children, they didn't want to talk to
me after that because it told them the truth, right?
But I have to be said, but I talked to the children and they, they thought the TV has been
around since Noah's Ark, they, they, they, they didn't know when it was invented, I said,
you know, TV is pretty recent, 1920s, 1930s, people didn't have them in their homes till
really the 50s and 60s, they were like, wow, no one ever told us that, you see?
Right, you just give it, so yeah, they never looked into it and I just give them a
little, it's not really, you know, we're not made for that, you know, at this point, you
could be made for with a chip in your head later, you might have to have it, but, but anyway,
well, you know, you've been around young children recently, right?
Because if you're around younger children recently, you'll find they have no concept of
a, of a time when there wasn't these little computers and, and like you said, the, the
stupid rectangles.
I mean, it's almost like that's a given, that's been here like air, you know what I mean?
And the thing, the thing, the thing is, you know, it's just like, you know, there's a lot of,
you know, a lot of things, you know, that's, you know, a lot of things, you know, it's like,
you know, you have to, you know, you have to have to have a, you know, a lot of things, you
have to have to have to have a lot of things, you know, a lot of things, you know, you have to,
have to have to, you know, have to have a lot of things, you know, you have to have a lot of,
you know, you have to have that thing, you have to have a lot of things, you have to have the,
you know, in a real world situation.
An example of that is if I had a treadmill in here and I ran a mile on it, I can tell you
I ran a mile today on a treadmill, right?
It's fairly accurate in terms of effort, but did I go anywhere?
Right here in my living room.
Did I go anywhere?
No.
That's a dummy load, like a treadmill is a dummy load.
I hamster a wheel is a dummy load, right?
So when you turn on all this media, it doesn't matter what it is, you know, I have a bullshit
filter I designed for the computer and a lot of times what it does is it filters out the bullshit
sound.
I'm like, wife said sound in the computer, so you got no sound on the computer.
I go to these different websites.
I see it because the bullshit filter is on trying to bullshit filter off and you'll get
some sound, right?
So this is part of the, oh, Calgon, take me away, right?
So the dummy load is a waste of time.
So people, all these issues, again, I see, I've actually been very good about avoiding.
I use the computer like a reference pocket.
Remember, okay, go to a hardware store, they might still have them pocket reference books.
I don't know if they still have them, but I know what you're talking about, yeah.
It has everything conversions.
In fact, you know, it's usually machine issues.
I mean, people in the technical are, you know, if you like building stuff, it's good to
have one of those.
Melting points, boiling points, you know, chemistry, it's got a little bit of everything,
you know?
Right.
You've got your computer out of table in there, right?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
So anyway, the whole thing about, I lost track now, we were still on the dummy load.
I got to go to the computer.
You know, we'll take a little break, all right?
Because we've been at this for about an hour and you've got a faster pace today than
I'm used to it.
I got to be honest with you.
That's right.
But it's okay.
We will adjust and return after just a little pause.
Be right back with the Greek.
[MUSIC]
happening today. Larry Hancock's book, Indonile, rembs the cover of many of them. Using new files
that exposes things about the Bay of Pigs that no one has ever written about before. It shows why
it really failed and why the United States did not learn from it. Secret Wars became a stable
US-covert operations that are still happening today. It also shows why other countries today are
doing a secret operations with more success. This is the book that puts what some want to deny
into the light. Indonile, secret wars with hair strikes and tanks. Larry Hancock,
for more information, go to LarryHiphanHandcock.com, pick up your copy of Indonile at Amazon.com,
in digital or physical- This is James Corbin of CorbinReport.com and you're tuned into the
Oceleaf- Ocele.com. Revelation through conversation. Second hour of the Oceleaf
begins now at Ocele.com but of course you're probably catching this further on down the stream by
your final slab of choice, your applicable application, your pod catcher, it is yours. So you're probably not
on the same timeline as me at the moment. Anyway, it's Monday and according to that thing we call
a calendar, it is just after, well, Jesus is actually more the quarter after 9pm in the eastern time zone,
but I'm sure you're hearing this some other time, some other place, so no matter who you are,
where you are, when you are. Well, okay, so I'm talking to the Greek and you know, something comes up
here, we're going through this list, which is publicly accessible and you can find it out there of the
many Oceleaf and the Greek shows, which were done in two sections. One of them were episodes and then
the other were chapters. Okay, the second one was chapters. Anyway, you put them in order, they're
pretty interesting, but they're not totally available out there on the internet unless you're a member
at Oceleaf.com. Now you do that, you have access to the Oceleaf and the Greek list where I saved all of
them and there's also an episode which was not publicly ever aired anywhere and so that's that. If you
choose to support me over here, you do get all of the episodes just so you know, but there's a lot
of other stuff over there and I constantly put up content, which is only available to members at
Oceleaf.com. So I say this because you know, it's been waning support lately, Greek, I just want you to
know again, seem to go up a little bit and then back down. That's that's very easy to do if you're
looking for support. I don't mean like just a plain old jock strap, but if you're looking for
input, there's seven billion people out there, right? Right. You ever go fishing? Sure. You have to
use the appropriate lure, you have to use the appropriate bait, you have to use the appropriate, right?
Location. Very easy. Well, I'm sorry. I totally simple. I totally want to see how simple it is.
You start with the simplicity of getting quote unquote. What are they, what are they called? Well,
yeah, internet people, they don't put up subject matter. They put up, they call it content. That's
what they call it, right? And then they get followers. Okay. Yeah. Well, yeah, here's the thing.
Here's a go. There's a, was around an old school salesman and you take out a contract, you know,
and the the the perspective buyer, you know, when he signs the contract that's done. If he saw you sit
in there with the buyer for more than 20 minutes, he walks up to your desk with the perspective buyer
sitting across from you. He doesn't look at anybody. He puts his big hand on the contract and crumbles
it up and throws it in the garbage and tells the perspective salesman the leave. I mean, perspective
client to leave and I'm like, what the hell? Annie, what's going on? He says, I told you, if you can't
get them to open their wall in the 15, you know, first 15 minutes, some kind of commitment, you could,
you could like, what do you, what is it? You court them for the next three months or wasting your time.
Better, I'd rather have you doing nothing than doing, you know, courting these idiots, you know.
Right. Well, you know, throw your effort here. This is, we should probably,
do something that is in less than 15 minutes, you want people to join.
No, I understand. Look, that's an illuminati number, by the way, 15, 5, 1,
any, you got to play the numbers, 3, 2, 2, 6, 6, 6, you remember play the number, they tell you play the
numbers, right? Which by the way, that comes into the next part of the discussion because we did
talk about numerology and all that and exactly how this really stands, what, what the circumstances is
with the three, sixes and all that. And, well, what does everybody think of when you usually bring
this up? Well, Satan, Satanism. We had a discussion about that after the dummy load.
Let's just, let's just interject what that is. Okay, real quick, you have a race of beings, let's say,
known as the Elohim. There are many races. And they had a re, an internal reorganization where a group
of them fell out of following, a following, favor. And the ones that fell out of favor became
messengers or angels. And the angels that had a bad reputation and fell out of favor even more were
known as demons. That's all it is. Imagine a corporate structure were, or in the military or whatever,
where someone gets demoted, where in the military an honorable discharge would be an angel, a dishonorable
would be a demon. And by the way, I talked about the quote unquote dragon types. You have both on both
sides. No, you have more dragons coming over to the human side, like a hybrid type. This is
sounds very, very woo-woo to people, but that Satan character was one of those. And, in persona,
in meaning, because they're not physical beings, right? So the persona generally, just like in Star Trek,
they were fighting the klingons and then the later on they rebooted the series and now they have
a klingon, you know, they made a man's and the klingons are on the bridge, you know, he's an officer,
right? Right. Yeah, that's the Satan character. And there's many, he's part of a program.
There's many of them. But yeah, you got to, you know, if you spend your whole life finger painting
on the wall with chocolate pudding and you think that's psychodynamic or religious or whatever,
you got to boil these terms down to very simple black and white, you know, immature, spiritual
and maturity. You can call it. Right, right. And you know, we closed out that first portion, excuse me,
of the series with random thoughts where we kind of attempted to do what we're doing right now,
which is to address each of the issues already addressed and discuss that. And that's what it looks
like it closed out at, but it didn't. It actually went on a bit. But I know that that was an effort to
sort of clarify everything that had come before. But which, by the way, everything I've ever said
publicly is an introduction, right? Even if it's a two hour topical episodic sonic event, it's still
an introduction. Of course. The point is that no one seems to get very if you get is there's a formula
to doing this stuff. It's basically comprehension and you don't have to make stuff up like people do.
You just look at what's been memorialized that came before you. It doesn't matter if it's written or
audible, something that came but don't piss on and shit on everyone that came before you. In other
words, if they wrote something down, guess what? It might be worth reading. Well, see, that's what I
was trying to get at before when I was talking about building on the knowledge previous because everybody
does regardless of how there's, you know, there's an innovator, they've come up with something that
nobody comes up with something out of nowhere. It's all based on something. If it's an
evaluation, you got the super high. We have the informational super highway. Most of the universe,
most of existence is say universe is not physical as we know it. The physicality that we live in,
what they call the three-do-you-world is no different than as if you went inside of a mountain.
And I'm not talking going inside of a mountain after you dig a tunnel. As if I just snapped,
you snapped your fingers and you appeared inside of solid rock. How much mobility and freedom do
you have? You're like, holy crap, I'm inside of a rock. I can't do anything. And pretty soon you won't
be able to breathe. So the density that the humans live in, this 3D is, is, Miniscence, one
millionth of 1% of physical, of the reality of what's out there. And this is the next level for
humanity to realize that. Well, this is why the cosmic censorship issue is mentioned throughout
all of the episodes, too. Of course. And, you know, for someone who's saying cosmic censorship.
Well, and also remember, we pre-cognate a lot of the stuff. We said the word "sensorship"
more than anybody else did five, six, seven years ago. And then what do they have now?
Oh, well, now everybody's screaming about the censorship everywhere.
We use that word at least 10 times each episode. Oh, I know.
Seven years ago. And we're trying to tell people, hey, you're always censored. But now it's in your face.
And you still don't care. Well, no, that's the thing is they care about what they think their freedom is.
And it's always so funny to me. It's always based on a bad premise. You know, I have the
freedom to be on Twitter, do you? Okay, well, I didn't know. First of all,
When I hear the word people want freedom, it's like in the police report, we shot them 14 times
for his own safety. Yeah, right. But that's in that police report. They killed the guy for his
own safety. Well, that's the thing. You know, you're fighting for peace. You know, you're making a mistake
here. You're engaging in the wrong thing is not by making war on war. Yeah, I know. But that's
what I'm saying is that there's always this false premise built into either what they're saying or
what they're aiming at. You know, it's like the people that say they want to get to a certain thing.
I always look at and go, well, that's not what your actions say. I understand what the words are
being loaded. Anybody? Got me load anyone? Right. There you go. So, okay. Now, I again, I want to run
through some of these other things. And I know we're not going to get all the way through the list,
even if we had the complete list. And I had all kinds of notes. But let's see what we can get done
here in the time we have. And I think that's always a worthy thing to engage in. All right. Stop
looking for land as you're standing on it. Okay. Well, that's right. Now, that was fun because a lot of
people started asking about the, you know, the different place. By the way, somebody in the chatroom
says they had not heard the, you know, like, like watching a monkey, fuck a football since their
grandfather and they appreciate hearing that because they haven't heard it since. I use that term
on occasion. I just usually don't say it on air because I usually don't use that language on air.
But yeah, right. Well, the other one I really like is they couldn't pour. The other one I really
like is they couldn't pour piss out of a boot even with instructions on the heel. You're putting it
on the bottom. Yeah, we're putting it on the heel. Yeah, even with instructions on the heel. So
see, that's the whole thing about you just, you know, look, if it's, if someone took the time to
write something down or it doesn't mean all of it and everything, that means that, you know,
a technical manual here, this is going to tie into what you're saying about a grandisanal.
Really, really, really, really fast before we go to Atlantis is that another question comes up,
which is what, what happened to the old question, everything in quotes archive?
Archive? That's your business. I never, I never put anything on the internet other than a single
page and an email. Right. I think it may be that that was a site that someone else had put onto
a server. And I think maybe it does not look very easy. Look, here's the other thing. I give my time
freely because I know that if you live your life here and you help one person with something,
even trivial, your job is done here, right? So the easiest way to get in touch with me is uncommonradio.com.
And if you hold your mouse over where it says email or whatever, it'll, that's the email. It's
uncommon sense radio one, number one, at email.com. And that's an email. Or it's, they use the same email
for Skype content. I'm very easy to contact and I'm free with my time. Right. So if you, you know,
you want, you know, if you want a frozen dinner, that's the archive. If you want a fresh cook meal,
hit me up. Well, that's the other thing. He gave me a very good way to freeze fish actually one time.
Water, you don't never get the freezer, you know, water evaporates more than room temperature in that
freezer. You know, but once you go, that's the freezer. But if you go below, you know, the, like, what
they call a medical freezer, they, you know, below 70 minus 70 or so, which is very dangerous, by the
way. You know, the double door freezer is and all that. You don't get freezer burn. But if you throw
it in water, it's not just fish, but anything else that's like that. Well, no, but it was a great way
to actually get the fish to not be damaged by being frozen for it extends the life in the freezer.
You believe it or not? If you don't open and close that freezer door alive, it's good for 10 years
in the water. Hey, believe it. They put it down. They pull stuff out of glaciers all the time, right?
Thousands of years old right and is still edible, right? No, no, I understand. I'm just saying that
that was just one of those things I never considered, even though it should have made sense to me.
One of those, I'm just pointing out that you actually have what makes sense to you.
Careful. Culinary thing. Well, you know, I got a friend named Joe who told me you had a great way of
cooking potatoes too. So, you know, I'm just saying. Stove top. Yeah, but I know that you got that
for the stove top cooking, by the way, got from Gil Cherokee Indian, you say, white man uses a lot of
wood, makes a lot of smoke, very little heat. The Indian uses very little wood, no smoke, a lot of heat.
Right? So, no, no, fair. No, I'm just saying that it's just, you know, you never know what it is you
could gain. Since you mentioned, you know, I could show you how to cook a good meal. I was just explaining
all along the process. You've actually got some good knowledge there. If that's all you want to hear,
I'm sure you'd be more than happy to provide somebody with instructions on stuff like that. So,
anyways, um, okay, so stop looking for Atlantis. Yes. And then recaps and ginger snaps. So,
again, we had to go back over stuff is what happened there. That kept happening a lot. Let's see.
Uh, reference to history. And I guess that was, you know, talking about what we, really we covered that
at the very beginning of the show when you and I were talking about that. And then of course, quality,
food, water, uh, and law, which, okay, that, that's an interesting mix. Law, you don't have any law that's
gone, been gone for over 90 years worldwide more than 60 years. Some very religious societies try to
have some law form, uh, and money. Law and money go together, by the way. Uh, if you lose your law,
people say, so what, Greek, what's the difference? If I use a piece of paper or get food or substance back,
money, well, the problem is you lose your law. You know, they, you know, they, you could be arrested and
charged for stealing rocks from the moon, right? No, what are you going to do? So it's, it's set up that way.
But that's again, okay, there's, there's a, there's a problem that you have. The solar system is in
a neighborhood. This is something I never brought up and this goes with it, land this and all the other stuff.
Good. You build a new house, right? Life savings is a big house, like MacMatchan, whatever, big house,
big beautiful house, everything, all the amenities. So what you do is you live on the roof, right?
Rainers know you live on the roof. No, you don't live on the roof. You live inside. Right.
When you have an advanced society anywhere, you don't live on the surface. You live on the, you build,
you live on the surface, you subject to solar events, meteorites, weather, attacks, yes, attacks from other beings.
Right? So you live inside the planet, inside. So when they tell you all these planets are bare and
look at the surface, they're very advanced beings living inside. Nothing is wasted. They're all inhabited.
There are some dead planets like the moon is a dead planet, meaning it's dead. So it's been hollowed
out and used and repurposed as a satellite as it is because there was a time when we didn't have a moon
not too long ago, like half a million years, let's say. So you know, reading HD Wells very carefully when
he said Martians were coming, it's kind of interesting because people would say, oh, well, we didn't have
the telescopes to see that there was nothing on the surface of Mars. What we did actually. Yeah.
Was right. You could look up right now. Lowell, the astronomer has lots of notes of what he saw in the
telescopes. There's a war on Mars. Explosions, smoke every night. Well, what are they going to do?
Just credit him. They just put it in a hide it away. Up until the 70s NASA used to put out transient
lunar phenomena. Transient mean like, you know, weird stuff going on in the moon. They cut that off.
But it's very, very, very active. The thing is though, we're intelligent beings from other places know
our purpose, which is no purpose just to exist until a certain time. We're in a seat vault in a seat
bank. What are you supposed to do when you're in the waiting room? Remember the waiting room?
See, that was another, it was another long concept where we explained that along with the end
of credits, which started to get a little bit work up. We're in the credits. Well, no, but we were in the waiting room.
Until 2025, we're in the 2021 and a half when you pass that point, I said this even before.
When you pass 2021 and a half, that will determine those three and a half years after 2018,
what the next three and a half years will be like till 2025. It's been on point.
No, so far that's the thing. It's all A plus plus plus material. But as I was saying, we were in the waiting room.
But we are in the time when it is the end credits. So here we are. And now actually it's kind of
interesting because 2022, that would be definitely the end of the first phase of what you talked about.
And we were doing that in, I don't know, 2014, 2015.
No, it's not really a phase. It's okay. I gave the play school room a version of it.
You have four seven year periods and seven four year periods and they overlap.
But the more predominant one is the seven year periods in the middle of seven is three and a half.
So when you get to that three and a half year into the seven year period, and this one would be
28 that started in 2018. So three and a half put your 2020, 2021 and a half.
When you get to the three and a half year period, what that does is it shows you basically this is
what the next three and a half is going to be like. So it's kind of like a stalled.
You know how, one of you ever heard about this using a slightly like the 20th century was a stalled
century. They stalled it with World War One, World War Two, all the other wars, the bankruptcies,
the UN, all this stuff, they stalled it. In other words, you know, when it was stalled, I mean,
literally stopped it. There was the creativity that you had in the 20th century,
Harkins back to whatever was developed in the 19th century, right? 19th century they attempted to
stalled it in the beginning, but it was super creative all the way through. 21st century definitely
got stalled because it started with 2001, right? You know people think, you know, when did the 20th
century start? Not 1900, 1901, right? So like when you're born, you're in your first year or when
you're born, you're in your first decade. When you're born, you're in your first century. When
you're born, you're in your first millennia, depends on how you want to, you know, break down the
time period. But the 21st century was definitely stalled seven months, I think it's nine months
into it. You know, they, they, they, uh, nuke, lower Manhattan and, uh, brought in, you know,
airplane restrictions and all this other stuff. You know, made a lot of people rich, you know,
when there were no airplanes involved. So they, they, they, they keep stalling it. So there's no
creativity. It doesn't mean that you don't have little tech advancements here and there, but
there's no great, when I mean stalled means the creativity goes away. And then when the creativity,
see, when a century is stalled, it could go two ways. One is you, you, you stop creativity in advancement
or you, you create a period of destruction like they did in the 20th century. You know, before
World War one and World War two, Europe was completely different, right? You know, right, right.
It was totally all none of the old buildings, very few of the old buildings survived. None of
the maps read the same and the cultures were completely, uh, there, there was over like 140 different
groups of Germans or, or, or Prussia, you know, anyway, all that was boiled down. Anyway,
it was a period of destruction, but if you, if you do the destruction too much and there's too much
power in the people, the hands just like now they, you know, they're doing the school shooting
programs again, right? Right. Well, why would they want to take your guns away if they didn't intend
to do something that you'd want to shoot them for? So you see, yeah, now I keep saying that,
you know, these people that talk about the guns, they're, they're, they're absolutely wrong. But they,
they're not really, you see, that's not the pistols. It's the heavy, it's the heavy armament, you know,
I was at a shooting range once here and shooting all kinds three or eights, you know, all the standard
stuff. Yeah. And a guy pulls up, uh, pulls a canvas off the Jeep and he's got a 50 caliber anti-aircraft
loop that pick up truck target in the shed to, to smith the reins with tracers. I was like,
holy shit, I didn't know that they were people, you know, quote unquote civilians with such
ordinance, you know, and there are. No, there are, but it's, it's weird. Just pick what see weapons now,
they could get you from space, they can get you through your telephone. You know, your telephone
has a smartphone of sensors that has your body temperature, heart rate, breathing rate,
and all that in there, right? Well, I've tried to explain that, you know, people that are worried
about the chips, I don't buy the whole chip thing because it's not necessary. There are biometric
measurements where, remote, ID is, all you got to do is scan, you got the ID and you don't need to
physically implant anything because you have a connectivity through waves. So, also they have
time tech. There's no time travel. You just go from event to event. Hey, are you ready for a little
twister? Sure. Okay, so when you do a history lesson to children, you bring out what they call
helps, like books, films, whatever, right? To do the history, all right? So imagine 10 million years
from now they're doing a history lesson for children and they create this hologram, it's a physical
hologram and we're in it. We are merely being demonstrating a history lesson, right? So imagine
instead of a pop-up book or a film, they actually have a 3D reality. Okay, it's one thing. The other thing
is if everything's predetermined in the future, just like a blueprint, it has all the renderings of
the building, you know, you look at the ground, there's nothing there. Guy shows up with his pick-up
truck, he unrolls the paper or his iPad and he shows you what they're going to build there.
Well, that's the future, right? It's nothing there now and it's got every detail in it, right? You
know, a comprehensive architectural drawing even goes down to every nut and bolt, especially on a
ship or an airplane, right? Okay, so, so if everything is predetermined, when they finish the
design, 10 million, 50 million, 100 million years in the future and they start replaying it now,
when we go into our past, we're closer to the future because that's when they started it and as
we go into our future, we're going more into the past. This is how time travel, time, there is no
time travel because time travel is like you said with the clock, right? It's events, how events are
structured in the ether because everything, the most solid object, the atom, even anyone will tell
you that analyzes this without the BS or you know, stuff they put out in colleges. The researchers,
let's tell you that the densest material, when they look at the atomic structure, it's 99% space,
you know, if you say proton-neutral electrons, all space, even a diamond is nothing there. So,
it's how the ether is structured and vibrating. Right. So, the way you set up, let's say,
the mathematics for something, see, math, nature doesn't do math, right? This is guy,
Thuria Paphoses, Ken Wheeler. He says, "Mother Nature is not a crack core with a calculator." She's
just barefoot, honey, with hairy armpits running around. That's Mother Nature, right? Okay. So,
all right, so time travel, the way you do the math, I've gotten this recently and it's not anywhere,
it's... (inaudible)
You're going robotic on the Greek, moving around or something?
Not times for... Wow, totally robotic, they're... break.
Not... Yeah, you're not... Your sound does not go here, hang on a second, because it's just
going all over the place. Maybe you're moving around, I don't know. Can you hear me?
I can hear it. All right, you're still breaking up and going weird. All right, you know what I'm
going to do, guys? I'm going to quickly take a little break. And, yeah, I'm going to just do that,
because I want to see if we can get him back and see if we can finish this thought at least,
before we're done here tonight. So, hold on, Greg, we'll get back to you and attack the O'Chelsea
Effect of Return. (inaudible)
Get ready for it. We are telling it back now.
So, after a slight electronic disturbance, we returned with the Greek. And it was so funny,
because he says, "I know what time travel works," and then all of a sudden...
Yeah, you got that. So, anyway, let's try again. Greek, you were saying.
All right, so let's just leave that one alone, but it's not how time travel works, because there
is no. You're actually moving from a different events in the ether, let's say, in the substrate.
And it's not... I got the math for it, meaning, you know, it's the kind of math that people use,
not like I've measured this board... I've cut this board twice and it's still too short, right?
Or you see someone on a construction site and they don't know how to read a tape measure.
It's 16 and two lines. I'm like, "Whoa, come on, you got to learn how to read these things."
That's just the math, right? So, the math behind it, nature does it use math, it's just the form of
communication, right? Like, I got some eggs, I got some beers, all right? How many? You know,
that helps me, you know? Because some could be two or more, right? So, the math is just that. It just
helps one organize... get organized, let's just say. That's what ledgers are for. So, I have a ledger
on that and what it is basically is determining the properties of something, not only of the properties
as we commonly describe something, but the properties of where they are and when they are.
Right? And this has been an active use, this technology has been actively used now for over
100 years on the population, unaware, right? So, there's only so much, you know, that we can get into.
But hey, if anybody wants to talk about time travel, I'm open for it, but maybe we'll do it on
another occasion. Yeah, because I would relish the opportunity to even be able to witness events
in the past directly, you know? And I've been told by more than one person that this is possible,
but you got to stop thinking about it that way. And there is, you know? Yeah, but we go back to what we
said. If you want to think about something, look, all right, I'm not going to say what religion it is,
like Christians, but they got this symbol, right? And it's not biblical, it's not historical, right? So,
so if you want to experience that, how about just starting what's written about it first, right?
If you want to learn about something, how about gather together what's been written about it first? And
then maybe go more direct, you know? That's the thing. Why am I the only one stating that when the
Christ was arrested, whether you believe in it or not, historically and biblically, he was brought
to Pontius Pilate who washed his hands of the matter and said to the religious authorities who
performed the arrest, I am returning him back to you, use your law. And then we know clearly that
the religious authorities of Judea are not Roman, and their method of execution is Mosaic law,
which is by stoning. And if you read the events as the people witness this is clearly not what
symbolism the people are using, right? So, I mean, how retarded is that?
Well, I approach that.
So, I approach that.
I mean, I approach that as, first of all, this idea of the cross, right? This is not a form of
execution used at that time. It's a no. So, actually, it was prior to it. It's not even, it was actually,
believe it or not, you're ready for this. Crucifixion was never considered execution, it was a form of
torture. You were put up there for three days and after three days, they let it, if you had
friends or family members, they usually took you down.
Yeah, but for three days, you couldn't, you know, do it.
But they didn't put you on a--
You was created by the Assyrians.
Yeah, but they didn't put you on a cross beam. They put you on a tree, usually.
No, actually, the crucifix that they're talking about is a role is an Assyrian form of torture.
It was never a capital punishment. Capital punishment is beheading or stoning.
What does it mean?
Yes, but the thing is, even if the Romans were seeking to execute somebody, they wouldn't have
used that. They wouldn't have used it in that form. The Romans didn't do it anyway.
It depends on who there was no argument because if we go back to the text, it couldn't be more clear.
Yeah, and the--
I'm just by let's say that I'm returning him back to you to use your luck.
Right, and next step is, as you said, mosaic law, they don't have that in there.
Yeah, by stoning. No, by stoning. It's very clear. It's actually details of that are given in Deuteronomy 21.
Right.
By the way, if you believe anything and you hold adherence to that biblical text,
you're completely deceived.
So the 99% of the people that have anything to do, that anything that comes out of there,
are completely deceived by it, it has nothing to do with 99.99% of the people.
It does state things that are coming upon the earth.
Yeah, they're there.
But when it comes upon the earth, you're going to go with it anyway.
So again, it has nothing to do with you.
It's a children's book. This is what the scripture, the biblical scripture is.
Very high order beings that were a billion years technologically ahead of us billions of years ago
gave us that as a children's book. And if you're an adult and you say you can understand that,
maybe she give it to your cat and dog, and they'll maybe own this because you're really far gone.
It's written as a children's book. That's why you don't find
99% of the relevant things that one uses in their lives in there,
just like if you went to a bookstore and picked up a book for four to six-year-olds,
you're not going to learn how to build, you know, fix your car with that.
It's, you know, if a member fun with Dick and Jane and see spot go,
that's the level of the scripture. That's where it's at.
It has to do with a certain group of people.
And if you want to be part of that people, you have to basically have a legions to this particular God.
Or entity. And he gives you laws.
Like Simon says, if you want to be one of my people, you do this.
And if you don't do that, guess what? You ain't as people.
So this goes with all the religions, by the way.
And these are non-imperial beings, by the way, which is another discussion.
This is a federation of human beings that are looking out for like,
we're like not even 2% of, you know, our genetics is less than 2% of what,
by the way, bouncing around like a banana and a monkey grove,
bass, backwards. This is a fact.
Anyone could look this up, by the way.
Genetically in the mitochondria, like we were saying earlier, there's information that goes back,
you know, all the way, you know, as far as you want to look.
Do you know that monkey genetics and pig genetics come after human genetics?
So that blows away completely that we came from monkeys.
Now, I've been to certain universities and courts and doctors.
I could tell you they definitely came from monkeys, but that's a different story.
So, well, there is an interesting divergence there where it does seem as though there's
maybe a heavier influence from one species over another among, you know, I don't know.
It gets a little confusing, but it does seem like maybe we're not all actually, as you, I mean,
we're universally, we're interchangeable.
We're extremely old, extremely old, it's okay.
You know what we're more like?
Do you remember okay? You got vinyl 33s, you got 45s, more of the little singles,
and then before that you had the 78s. Do you remember the 78s?
Yeah, actually, yeah.
Okay, I got some 78s, they're very thick.
Anyway, I pulled one out and I put it on a turntable and I downloaded it digitally into a file.
So, I went from like a 1923 record to having in a digital file.
Think about the jump because it went from 78 to 43 to 43, right?
So, you know, then magnetic tape to DVDCD and now I'm going from 78 right to
a computer file, holy crap, what a quantum leap, right?
That's how we are right now.
We are that version.
We are almost like a digital representation of what humans are.
What do you think we only lived to 60 or 70 years?
You know, you're not even about those 80/90s.
You're not supposed to do anything.
Yeah, but you know what's funny about those digital representations is that
they are as sophisticated as it is, it lacks a whole bunch of things.
A whole bunch of stuff has been removed.
Well, see, but that's where I was going here is that, you know,
it's de-evolution as opposed to evolution, it seems like because even though these things are like
your spaster and they can move quicker and you can communicate them, you can send them around the
world in seconds, right? You couldn't send a 78 around the world.
You were experiencing, yeah.
Well, you could, but you're experiencing evolution.
Let's say you work, let's say with telephones all day, salesman, right?
Your finger gets sore.
Every set's where they stick a pencil to dial or the old dial phones, right?
You know, touchtones.
Now you don't do that anymore.
You have a mouse. You have a different type of soreness so your body is going to evolve different.
Then what is it called? Carpet Tunnel Syndrome, the type of sad?
That didn't exist 75/80 years ago, right?
Well, maybe a tailor would have it sewing buttons all day or something.
That makes sense, so.
There is evolution, you know?
Like in other words, cheap shoes give people bad feet.
I'm serious.
Right, bad shoes.
So that's a form of evolution.
So there is evolution that way, in other words, biological influence change,
on a biology of something.
But essentially, okay, here you are.
Let me just drop another thing.
Do you know that most of the people on this planet, two thirds are synthetic humans.
They're not real humans as humans are defined.
What I mean by that?
At conception, people, it's funny how many people will know this.
You could look it up.
At conception, when the sperm meets the egg, there's a flash of light
when the union, when the conception begins.
It's a very brief flash of light.
It's in the millisecond, you know?
But it's within the frame rate.
If you have a microscope, you can see it.
It will be a little white yellow, blueish,
flash.
That's a download.
That is a ethereal download that determines whether the person is going to
carry genetics that are real or whatever.
Now, when you manipulate that flash,
just like if you're downloading something and the internet gets a hiccup,
you know, the download is bad, right?
You've got to do it over, right?
Okay, so there's a little download that happens at the moment,
the sperm in the egg meat.
And this has been learned in how to be interrupted.
And when that's interrupted in an individual,
it's recorded on the mitochondria and they're not a real human,
cosmically.
You know, if you hit them across the head with a baseball bat,
they'll cry.
If you don't feed them, they'll get hungry.
They sound the same way, but cosmically, from a spiritual point of view,
they're considered a synthetic.
Now, here's the interesting thing about it.
This could have happened to your parents.
It has to, it's not hereditary of the synthetic formation.
It has to be, at the moment, a conception has to be manipulated.
So let's say both of your parents would became synthetics because they were a manipulative,
they can have a real baby.
In other words, you weren't.
They didn't mess with that point when you were conceived.
You could be real, but in your genetics, in your mitochondria,
it will show that your parents were messed with.
So the people that, you know, the normies, the mask wearers,
the people that have to, you know, oh, I got to do what they say,
those are the synthetics.
And they've been, this is, this process started in very recently,
in the 70s and 80s experimented on very heavily.
They always blocked this kind of high-level technology by telling you,
oh, they did chemical and men, K, ultra,
they did this.
They always try to keep it on the chemical.
The more chemical stuff they try to tell you,
that means that they're actually messing with you on a higher electrical frequency level, more and more.
All right?
Just like nuclear devices.
Okay, so now I've got, now I've got a personal question because
I, I have been hearing people over the past few years, especially,
talk about the non-player characters because they're relating it to a video game.
NPCs.
And-
That's a valid, that's another way of disclosing what's going on, right?
Look, what's the difference between a normy and a conspiracy theorist is two and a half years.
Right?
Because anybody who's called a conspiracy theorist, which you know the origin of it,
of course.
is always, they're always right, but it doesn't matter because to these people,
that's why it's so easy to wipe out, says one third of the population will be wiped out.
Okay, well, we still, you could conceivably do that and not kill any real humans, by the way.
So when you're walking around on the street,
right, and you see people that have that blank stare because the, you know,
they say the windows are the eye to the body, you know, they say the windows of the eye to the
soul doesn't say that. It's the, to the body.
Do you know when you look into someone's eye, you actually see the, the optic nervous goes
directly to the brain.
Yeah.
It's part of the brain.
Yeah, of course.
So when you look inside someone's eye, actually, this was shown a lot in the early movies,
you can stimulate them to be happy or sexually aroused, depressed, but just by looking into their eye,
if you know how to manipulate that, it's an old, the mesmerized hypnotic stuff, right?
Yeah, today people will talk about neural linguistic programming. It's all based on this very same
principle that if you, and that is also because the eye literally does project a little bit of
light, whether people know that or not.
And if you learn how to control it, you can project what you like, obviously, and you can
cause an influence by interaction directly with that person's brain through the window of the eye.
Yeah, and it's so funny because you try and explain this.
The fetics are very susceptible to that and they cannot project.
Oh, they can't.
Here's the scary part.
You can have a woman, you can have a woman that you can see the child with and you both
could be real and the child could be a synthetic if it's messed with that conception.
Well, obviously, it has to be done fresh every time.
And it's done. There are satellites to do it. There's ground tech to do it.
There are no secrets, by the way.
There are no secrets anymore.
Well, I've had people explain to me that, and I don't know if this sounds right to you, but
the fact that we're constantly bathing in these
electromagnetic frequencies, that is actually part of the purpose is to disrupt this
this very unique thing that does occur at the moment of conception.
Incidentally, it has rendered a great many more people to be without it.
Sensibly, I'm thinking to myself, an electromagnetic frequency, which is pulsed at something
at the proper speed, can disrupt light.
Sure, but it's not an electromagnetic, the electromagnetic, believe it or not,
we're pretty, we're okay with it. It does heat up the water in the cells.
This is not a play on words. It's a magneto-dielectric, meaning it's more on the ether side,
like what Tesla talked about, instantaneous communication, right?
Versus the time delay. We're having a Skype call.
I've had Skype calls all over the world. There's no delay. How is that?
You see, they're using this tech right here under your noses all the time.
It's impossible, based on any physics, that we don't have a time delay, but we don't.
So that they teach you. By the way, you can't break the laws of physics and all this other stuff,
that's the same thing that the Catholic Church did in the 1500s, right?
So it's a religion. But here's the other thing.
I want to hear a little bit here. I want to hear it back to the good old Vinnie Eastwood days.
Back in 2011, he interviewed a guy called Donald Marshall, who basically talked about the
cloning centers underground in REM, which is a rapid-eye movement, consciousness transfer.
When you're asleep, they're able to take your consciousness and put it in the cloned.
Now, here's the thing. I revisited this because it's very important.
About five years ago, I was sending people articles, not online anymore,
that they did it. Remember all these archaeological digs in Egypt,
I don't know, five, six years ago? I think, well, no, actually less than that. It was 2018 or so. Yeah, anyway.
And this one article comes out. It was a scientific one. It wasn't on the mainstream.
And it says that they dug up a mummy and it was a clone. And I sent it to people and said,
"Oh, they're going to clone mummies?" I said, "No, no, no, no, no, read it." The mummy that they dug up
is a clone. In other words, the Egyptians had cloning technology. And they went over everyone's head.
Like, how could that be? Yeah. Very, very simple. Here's another example.
There's a short news clip. You could still look it up where they grow a second skin for
burn victims. They take some skin cells from you and they grow a skin in the lab and then they
go put it on the patient, right? So the news people walk in there. There was a new company and they
went from being nothing to millions and millions. So the first three seconds, it shows this table.
It's very crude. How do you make cells divide and clone? It's very crude. He's basically, he's got a
table that wobbles. Imagine it's just like a wobbling table. It's moving with a motor and he's got all
these glass flasks on it and the liquid is wobbling and wobbling. So he goes up to one of them and he
takes the skin out of the wobbling table and he puts it on a, looks like a cutting board and he
scrapes off a layer and he holds it up. This is what we need. This is how they do it. It's very
simple. So if you agitated tissue very, very at a certain rate with certain water, it will multiply.
This is a, so easy. You can literally do it in your kitchen just like we talked about. You can
grow gold in your kitchen, right? Oh, yeah. So, yeah. So, so the Egyptians had this, you know. Now,
the pyramids have nothing to do with this because the pyramids were built by others because the time
that they tell you the pyramids were built, they didn't even have toilets, right? So, if I said,
let's build some pyramids and these people here are crying about, we should build the toilets first.
We're going to build the pyramids first, right? No, no, sorry. They were very primitive. But the people
that were there, still amongst them, just like Atlantis, for example, you know, Atlantis has
shuttles to Venus and Mars, you know, back and forth and the northern part of Atlantis are the people
that are in Ireland right now. They sunk the continent with sunk and the southern part were the
blue people like the, in Krishna, you know, the blue people. Very simple and things got out of hand
very quickly there. Well, over thousands of years, but, but the advancement, this concept of
cloning, whatever they tell you, they're banning, you know, those a lot of laws we ban cloning is
what they're heavily into, right? Like, for example, they have the DEA and,
any drugs in the Western world, but that means they're heavily into it because that's what the drug
money is, what lubricates the banking system, right? Without the drug money, the wheels will get rusty
and stop, right? Not mortgages, whatever is the drug money. So you wouldn't entirely discount
Zacharias. So you wouldn't entirely discount Zacharias' sition is what you're telling me.
He's very light. He's like a lot of the stuff that I talk about introductory. It's much more like
the, what he calls the Anunnaki are hybrids of the Elohim. You're right. And no, I understand that,
but when he gets into the, you know, the, the, the, the narrative that is left behind by a thoth,
it's him and somebody else who put them together. Right. Which are very old humans again. Yeah. And
basically the laws that you see in the Bible that seem restrictive are to prevent you from having
sex with animals and male and male and female with female all the time and all that. Because
look, there are worlds out there where they did have the homosexuality. They, they eliminated all the
heterosexuals and they reproduced by cloning. If your heterosexual is a death penalty, right?
And other places, but so they didn't want that here. So they have these very strict laws to
prevent you from mating with animals. When you go back, you know, all the history they tell you
is false, but all the mythology is true. Like when you see half animal, half horse, the center,
you know, half animal, this is possible because our, our genetics are very valuable and pliable.
That's why, for example, when you read in the Bible, when they were told to go in and kill all the
animals also and the people is because they were having sex with the animals. You don't want to have,
you know, because sheep could bear, you know, anyway, and cows, you know, they have a sheep with
human faces on the, on you could see that, you know. So humans are pretty monstrous. And what I mean by
that is like Lord of the flies, you know, remember the book Lord of the flies, young children get
shipwrecked and end up killing the fat boy in like two weeks, right, for no reason. How many times have
we said you're on a violin planet? If you woke up this morning with your liver and your body be thankful
because in the middle of the night someone will crawl in through the window and want to cut your body
open and you'll see why you're doing it because I can because I feel like it. Right? That's why
predators do. So we're in a very self-induced mania of violence and that has to be, you know,
well, it has to be under control. And but at this point it's going to let go. They're going to,
that's what I'm saying. Your prayers are not, don't, they've been, if you think you're getting answers
in your prayers, it's been predetermined before you've even prayed already. It's already done. Everything's
in the credits, right? And when you're watching the credits of the movie, you don't expect the new scene
to come up. Sometimes they do that for shicks and giggles or whatever. But just a harking back to the
cloning thing that is so advanced right now. Give me an example. If you look at these politicians,
presidents, prime ministers or whatever, you look around, you ever see how their motorcades is
like minimal security, like a half, like a half drunk retired special forces guy in his buddies could
take over any motorcades. It's like minimal security. Right? Right? And kidnap any important person.
Well, this has been done before and they, and let's say they get the guy, the prime minister,
the president in the room, they're ready to call for their ransom money and the president,
prime minister explodes, boom, everybody's killed in the room. Well, and then an hour later, the same
prime minister, a president is doing a talk because it's not, you know, it's another copy, let's say.
So word gets around, don't bother kidnapping these, you know, high profile actors or high profile
people because they're not really real. They have a bomb in their head. And it's just like,
bank robberies went down when they started putting the dipax in the cash. So you leave the cash,
you get a mile away and then boom, the dipax blows up how, what, what's, how good is that? Right? Right.
You just wasted all your effort to get a load of people, still with blue dye, yeah.
So it's impossible to take hostages and it's no reason to assassinate anyone anymore because they're
already not real. So this is so, if you're just like, for example, when you tell people about
nuclear technology or all this, they still think like 1940 stuff, right? Well, that's all held by
DOE, Department of the two groups that control that technology is the Department of Energy and the
Secret Service. It's a department in the Secret Service called the Office of Special Transportation.
I love it how they hide things between them from obscure names, right? So anyway,
the problem is you have two different societies. You've got the surface and dwelling earth
in habit, hence which are basically equal to almost herd animals at this point, right? But not. But
almost equal in many ways, the way they act, the way they think and all that stuff, not much more
evolved than that, evolved meaning educated or cultured or their personal character. And then
you have another society that is not sharing that is incorporating a lot of the things that I've
discussed in the past five minutes. Right. Okay, so I have actually one more, I mean, we've got a
little bit over time here, but I'm sure you're okay with that for the moment. So you are, right?
Just double checking. You know, actually I lost you there. You know, I've been getting a lot of
hiccups every few minutes. Oh, really? For five seconds. Go ahead and repeat that. I'm sorry. I was saying
we're actually a little over time right now, but. All right, we're done. Yeah. We're done. Thanks for
hooking up on the dude a little bit of a recap. I think we put in a couple extra things there.
Get people thinking definitely did. Okay. We'll leave it at that everybody. So slightly extended
podcast tonight and a couple of little hiccups here and they're back and forth between me and the
Greek communicating for some odd reason. But a bunch of things in here. Yes, a recap for sure.
But yeah, you know, there'll be a treat for some in an irritation for most.
That that I I need to get a t-shirt that says that just says that a treat.
A treat for some in irritation for most. A treat for some in irritation for most. I love it. I love it.
That's how you know you're doing it right. There you go. Air okay, everybody. The Greek.
Support Chuccochillianchillie.com. There's no money in it. So yeah, that is the problem.
That's the biggest problem, I think. And you know, some people would say that, look, you're in an
age when you can be independently supported. But quite frankly, I'm on that business model too. And
look, I'm not going to complain, but I'm going to complain. Okay, because people want to support you.
They love you to death, but honestly. So you're listening and this is a very unsettling question.
Support the damn show. And I want you to do this because, you know, the Chillianchillie,
for example, in a few places where Greg Paliske get his is the stuff out. I mean, you'll still see
my violence in some of these outlets, but nevertheless, it's nice to be a regular on CNN and on MSDMC.
But no more. Revelation through conversation. Oh, chchillie.com.
(Music)