*music*
Get ready, get ready, go on!
We are sending a pass!
Well the big thing is the house, Chaco Jelly!
And it's been over many years of my PSK research,
And specializing in PSK and telling me things you didn't see in Bob's Law and the Multilapsa Foundation!
And Bob will get another global criminal operation in the 20th and 21st century!
US hazards, streets, courts, and tab!
Now I know the most decorated place in all of these!
*music*
December 10, 2020, allegedly, according to that thing we call a calendar,
and this indeed is the Ocele Effect!
So, we are originating from Ocele.com, but uh, you know,
what does that actually mean?
Who knows and who actually cares?
Meanwhile it is a friars day night,
according to that thing we call a calendar once again,
and we have a guest who is backed by popular demand!
Four people actually requested this guy out of nowhere,
I wasn't even talking about him,
and three of them were named Ed, I kid you not!
Anyway, the Greek I used to do a radio show with,
quite often, we called it Ocele in the Greek,
and uh, it was definitely something of interest for,
oh, what was it?
20 something episodes, and then we came back again!
I don't know, you know, we did this a few times,
anyway, uh, I had to invite him because you requested him,
you guys know that I will do that,
and you can request guests at info@ocele.com by email,
but other people reach me via Facebook and all those other things,
and who knows, sometimes I catch some messages,
sometimes I don't, this time I did.
So, the Greek is with me, uh, of course,
if you don't know who he is, settle in,
because uh, you're gonna get shook up, probably a little bit!
Just want you to know that!
And, phone lines are open at 319-527-5016,
now I am the only one controlling the board over there,
so be patient, you'll be put on hold,
and you'll be listening to the show, uh,
and when it's time for us to integrate another voice
into this sonic event,
we shall do so!
Once again, 319-527-5016,
now I spoke it clearly, slowly, and everything else,
nobody can complain!
Greek! How you doing?
Hey, everything good?
Uh, Ben, hey Ben, hey, move to Gratzi.
Hello everyone, it's been a while.
No, it definitely has been, uh, you know,
and I'm not even sure how long it's been.
I know it's been at least a year though, right?
Since you and I actually got together,
I think, last time we got together on
the stream that's being run,
or was being run, kind of just for when you wanted to do radio shows,
what was that called? The, uh, the uncommon radio stream, something?
Yeah, back in AFR, and then I did a lot of sonic,
we sort of did a, uh, a start-up,
one of these free radio things,
and it's basically just the, uh,
say my piece and then bow out.
I think, uh, you know, you've noticed that, uh,
you know, you tell people, you know, brace yourself in a way, you know,
uh, a lot of stuff we talk about is, uh,
common, you know, me commonly available or obvious,
but no one really sees.
So you just say it and walk away because, uh,
otherwise if people find out later and it pisses them off,
they'll say, "Wait a second, you knew about this,
and you didn't say anything, right?"
So you have to say something, right?
And then walk away because you evaluate the crowd.
But, you know, by the way, there's,
there's other people out there doing some stuff.
There's someone that did a Greekspeak.com.
He's, uh, uh, once in a while we get together,
there's like 10 episodes rehashing stuff,
and it's kind of a fancier website.
But, uh, I'm pretty much bowed out because, um,
you know, uh, you gotta look at your audience.
So, let's say you're a classical musician, classical cello player,
and everybody's, uh, have you metal headbanger?
The chances of you getting the talk to the crowd
and having any appeal to them is zero to none, right?
So, the thing is, uh, most of the information that I've always put out
is not opinion based.
It's basically all resource based, you know,
anything that I've said to anyone could look up usually.
And if you can't look it up, uh, I'll tell you,
it's not on the stupid rectangle, right?
You know what I mean by the stupid rectangle.
So, which has basically been set up, uh, you know,
people are talking about censorship a while back.
We know what the different private,
let me just stress you, too, is a private platform.
All these things are private.
All the social media, but there's no,
you have no freedom of speech there, right?
Uh, just like the courts are private.
So, make, make a long story short.
You know, the best form of censorship,
in other words, to drown out a particular voice
is to give everybody a voice.
Right?
Well, that way they drown in the noise, uh,
which is interesting because, you know,
some of the things that you and I talked about
on our shows that ended up on YouTube,
funny thing, I mean, I had my whole channel pulled,
I had to go through a battle with them to get it back.
I mean, it was this whole thing.
Um, you know, I never got in trouble for any of the stuff
that you and I discussed.
You know, politics or something that was alleged to be hate speech,
which was not hate speech, it was just, you know,
reciting facts, I'm sorry.
You know, uh, well, it's because it's where it's coming from.
It's very different.
Yeah, I mean, there's no malice behind it.
It's just stating what humanity should be understanding
and looking at before they act, you know, you know what I mean?
Well, I got to tell you that speaking of humanity and acting and,
you know, me observing these things as you well know,
I do take the time to observe the world around me
and I try and report on it.
But also, I do a lot of deep research.
I mean, last night we had brought new information
into the, uh, the JFK research arena
that has not been out there previously.
You know, and stuff like that,
I'm constantly trying to search for new and different information.
And, and I got to tell you, it's weird
because I saw this whole thing going on with Iran.
And frankly, I had already wanted to have Yon before this,
but when I was observing that circumstance
and thinking about the possibilities,
and quite frankly, I miscalculated what I thought
the American leadership was going to do in the very near future.
Now, we'll see if it pans out over the long term, what I think.
But, um, when I saw all that, you know what I thought of?
Was the discussions with you about a Syria?
Now, somebody will say, well, why would you do that?
Well, Iran is right there.
Great.
Uh, so, could you try and give people a, uh, a clue
about what I'm referencing number one?
Number two, Kristi Aphrodite was in the chat room.
I just noticed and said that she bets you, you,
you miss calling into her show to complain.
I don't know what that means.
'Cause I wasn't aware you were on Kristi Aphrodite's show.
But I might have called in and she was back in the AFR day,
uh, days perhaps, hello, Kristi.
Right.
No, I remember she was there, but, you know,
I didn't remember that you were on there.
I remember you with, uh, Vinnie Eastwood a little bit,
um, you know, and then, uh, you and I had a conversation,
and that led Danny over there to actually say,
you guys got to do a regular show together,
and that's how the Oceleon, the Greek thing was born.
But either way, um,
I, I, well, actually, without just real quick Vinnie went on vacation,
Danny asked me to,
then a couple of weeks later I said,
uh, let me, let me go see who, who, what asshole's taking his place now
for three weeks, you know, and then you're there.
I said, "Well, this guy's got a pretty decent voice."
And, uh, he, you know, in other words,
you know, when you turn on the radio, it doesn't sound like noise,
and I said, "Okay, let, you know,"
and I got in touch with saying, "Hey, I was supposed to be doing what you're doing."
And by the way, if you need, if you want to hear something, you probably haven't heard before.
And that's how I think the, the, that, that was the germination.
The, uh, enablement was definitely Danny and everyone else, you know,
that said, "Yeah, keep this thing going, right?"
So, yeah, they bonded more of it when we had the conversation.
So, no, I, I thought it was, it was actually, uh,
an interesting time period there where I was doing double duty.
I'd finished my show and then do the show with you afterwards.
Some nights I was tired, Greek.
I got to be honest with you.
But, uh, but then again, you know, it was an interesting transition to go from whatever it was I was doing that particular day
to, uh, to really going into some very interesting subjects that probably sound really, uh,
inane to a lot of people like water.
And, you know,
Yeah, right, like what's water, right?
Yeah.
Like we're talking about water, not like the politics of water either,
but just like talking about water.
Uh, yeah, they, because people don't absolutely nothing about it other than what they've been told,
even though it's right in front of them, and they're made of it.
Yeah, exactly.
That's basically the same.
That's the root and the moral of the story of everything we've discussed.
What's right in front of you that you know nothing about?
Exactly.
And you, and you use as well.
But anyway, let's, you, let's just dive in a little bit because, you know, we could go, uh,
really long and deep.
So let's maybe get a few things out of the way if you've ever listened to the stuff we talked about.
It wasn't just a theory.
I'm glad that stuck, you know, stuck in there as you said it,
but that wasn't the, the whole crux of discussing Assyria.
The, the, the, the reason for discussing Assyria,
A, SS, Y, R, I, A, not Syria, us, Syria, was because that was something to look for as being,
a precursor to what?
When you see a new country being formed in northern Iraq, which is going to take part of Syria,
and part of Turkey, and I kept saying there's going to be conflict with Turkey and Syria and Iraq,
and all that before it started.
I don't know if you remember that.
And, um, because the ancient Assyria,
geographic borders, let's say, are political borders within those countries.
The reason of bringing up Assyria in such a manner in repetitive fashion is
that is the precursor to the Middle East Union.
Now, it's not a union as people describe unions of countries today.
For example, the EU is going to be a loose Confederacy,
but it will, it will not be mistaken that the power base, the power brokers,
and all the influential matters of human society will be coming out of there.
That's what I mean by union, right?
So, you have to be that's why.
Yeah, so, one second though, that's why it came up in my mind though, Greek, because
the geopolitical ramifications of a conflict with Iran,
while the US is involved in a conflict with Afghanistan,
while the US is engaged in Iraq, whatever they're calling it,
the US is still present and engaged in Iraq, right?
So, while we're looking at that and the consequences of the moves in Assyria
that affect these people that we call the Kurds,
there's no Kurdistan, but we call them Kurds.
There are all-
Actually, there is a Kurdistan, it's broken up,
and there may be 50 different little loose provinces,
but go ahead, just like you have China towns,
and little Japan's and little Italy's like that.
But it's not like recognized as a nation, there's not a Kurdistan on the map right now.
Right, and the Kurdish people are what?
They're the meads, and the Iranians are who?
The Persians?
Oh, I understand that, but see when-
So, they're very some good.
Yeah, no, that's the thing, so I was considering all of this,
and somebody stated based on my attitude, because I am not for war in any way, shape or form,
I said, you know, really, it would be great to see the United States and many of these other
interloper countries pull themselves out of the Middle East,
and a lot of people said, well, you know, if that happens,
then there would be great deal of conflict, and I said, yeah, I don't think it would last very long,
because without all of this outside agitation,
I think what would happen is, wait a minute,
what the Greek was talking about regarding a Syria where you would end up with
loose confederation, listen, it's much more beneficial for us to work together,
than it is for us to work against one another.
We no longer have to compete for the Western influence, so on and so forth, so I said to myself,
actually what I'm thinking would be geopolitically beneficial
across a map is exactly the kind of thinking that if somebody comes to it in power at some point,
would lead in a very short period of time, yes, there would be conflict,
there would be issues to begin with, but I think very quickly that would be settled,
pragmatically, and you would be looking at something that I don't know if it would take on the name
of a Syria, but it would certainly resemble exactly what you were talking about if someone were to take up
my particular frame of mind regarding this, so that's why it came up, you understand?
Okay, it wasn't as simple as it was.
Well, that's just, you know, basically.
I wanted that you just said something that's important, which is frame of mind.
When every time you said the U.S., I wanted to interrupt and say, there was no such thing as the U.S.,
but there is such a thing as the Assyrians and the Iranians and the Italians and the
and the English and the Greeks and the Israelis, but there's no such thing as the U.S.,
now the Greek you're speaking in riddles or your absurd or you've gone mad, what are you talking about?
There's no such thing as the U.S., let me tell you.
The vein, like when you're mining, you're looking for a vein of gold or precious metal is better
than it being scattered around and sifting it, right? So you could chip at it.
The information attaches to these national veins, these national bloodlines.
The information that I'm getting regarding the future, right?
When you have something like what's called the United States, someone says I'm an American
and he's really dark-skinned and he's wearing a turban and he's speaking with a Bengali's accent,
but he's an American, right? Then I got another guy that has to have pasta fuzzul on New Year's Day,
right? And he said, what do you mean? What are you talking about? I'm an American, right?
Another guy, you see, he's out of the Szechuan province, right? He has a restaurant,
bring your own cat and you get a free egg roll. He's an American. Do you get my point?
Yes, I get my point. What's an American? What's an American? There is no such thing. They're all dead.
I mean, the indigenous people here that were supplanted before known history were genocide it off,
for the Native Americans. So this is my point. I'm not giving them, I'm not breaking your balls.
What I'm trying to tell you is the information of regarding the thing has to correlate,
in other words, if it seems like it's in code, the code has to be broken and the details of that code
have to always be applied to the information otherwise it falls apart. Right?
Well, obviously when I'm referencing the U.S., I'm referencing a very real construct, which is the U.S.
military, okay? Right. Which is, which is about what? 60% black in Mexican?
Oh, yeah, absolutely, but I'm saying 75%. So that's then you could, in history, this is important because
in the future history will not see that army, it will say it is a lot, it was a Mexican and black army.
Okay, give you an example. When you read about the Roman conquests in the Middle East, like 2000 years ago,
those were not people from Napoli. Those were people like when they came down through Syria
and other places. Those were Syrians that put on Roman uniforms and run to Rome and hire, but
are they the Roman army? Yeah, they are. Oh, yeah, they are. So the interesting aspect is this old
information that will be repeated in the man's final society, when you see, for example, a country,
like what's called a country like the U.S., that is an ideology. It is an agglomerate. It represents
actually the West. Let me just help you put this in more perspective. What most Americans say,
well, we're Christian, we're American, we're whatever, and they're Islamic. They're Muslims, right?
What people fail to realize is there is no Islam per se as it's supposed to be according to the
Quran and according to even older traditions. What you they call modern day Islam, except for the
post dunes in Afghanistan, and a couple of tiny little pockets here and there is formed in the 19th
century by several influences. One of the main ones is what's called the Anglo-Mahamid in Treaty.
That you see. So modern day, and I play with this all the time, when I see someone who I know is
Muslim, I'll go to them and I'll put up, I'll have fun with them and you know, they see this guy,
you know, and I say, "Hey, you're Muslim, right? Yeah, okay. Were you alive when your grandfather,
your great grandfather was alive?" And he says, "Yeah, I remember. I say, he was not really Muslim. He was
like you are today. He lived his life according to Taurat." And he says, "Yeah, that's right."
Well, Taurat is Arabic for Torah, which is the biblical mosaic law.
Think about that for a moment. And modern day Islam, that's completely been done, right? Because the
Quran doesn't have any law in it. It tells you if you want law, you go do what Moses said. So, so my,
it's just like, for example, when you talk about Christianity, yeah, they say it's pagan. By the way,
if you call Christianity pagan, that's an insult to the pagans, by the way. Pagans are far more evolved
spiritually than Christians are, but my point is, you know, because a lot of times you say
Christians pagan has to put down, if it was pagan, it'd be a hundred times better at least, you know? But
here's my point. The chief God in Christianity is the Easter Bunny in Santa Claus. Don't say no,
because yes, that's what I see. Thank you, by the way, Greek, because I identify as a pagan myself.
Okay, well, at least you have a conversation with a pagan because they know that there's more than
one deity. They know that you can influence these deities. They know you can do barter with these
deities. They know that there's no difference between science and religion, right? Yes. I mean,
all these things, right? There's the same, right? You manipulation of your environment,
right? Christians are like, you know, they have to, so I'm not harping on the Christians because,
you know, all the religions are fallen apart because they're part of the political system. They're
all basically set up by the intelligence agencies and intelligence agencies have existed for thousands
of years. You've already read the Jesuits, right? So, so my thing here, in order to decode the
information, you don't have any liberty to free, free form the application of the information.
Very often, like, you know, there's a typical saying, like, you have enough information to be
dangerous, but not enough to do the right thing kind of thing. You can't do that. You're, you're not
allowed to do that. So when you look at a body of knowledge and it doesn't quite seem
contemporaneous to the thinking today, in other words, it is written in the language and in the ideology
and the thought forms that people had at a different time, you can't take whatever information you want
and apply it to your modern ideology. You must maintain the ideology of that's held within the text,
otherwise it falls apart, right? So you with me? No, no, absolutely. So from there, from that point of
you, there is no such thing as an American bloodline or a United States bloodline. There is no such thing.
That's true. And to even put that even drive it even more home, you know, you hear a lot of these
patriots more on say, Oh, our founding fathers really, if they were so good, how many founding fathers
is more than a handful, Madison, Hancock, Washington, Jefferson, if they were so good, where are their
descendants? How come their descendants are in celebrated, because they did have children? Right.
Where are their descendants now? Huh? Oh, good question.
How come on Presidents day, great, great, great, great, great, grandchild of Washington, all these other people
don't come out and say, Hey, let's celebrate these people, this family line or Jefferson's on TV.
But anyway, yeah, well, anyway, Kennedy, you know, Kennedy was the only one, right?
It's weird because his cousins, his second grandchildren, whatever, whatever, they're all spread
out through politics and positions of power. It's very interesting to see what happened there.
And now the modern people in power, what you call politicians, kings, prime ministers, those are
just people that are actors that are going to go along with what's called the sovereign state,
which is neither sovereign, neither a state. It's a private corporation. Well, yes, but
a hundred years later, you don't see the descendants of the founding fathers really continuing on.
I mean, there was John Quincy Adams, but I mean, outside of that, you don't see successors
to presidents and things like that actually showing up again, outside of what? The bushes, you know,
the atoms, like I said, it's very rare. Go ahead. In the modern age, which is when I say
modern means past 1950 and 50 and then went to space age, right? And then now it's just the fucked
up age. But anyway, by the way, I want to correct you on one thing. When you talk about the Italian people,
there's a problem there too, because there really isn't a actual Italian people.
Yeah, well, you could say the Romans to a certain point and then you're going to have to say a trust
ginseng. Well, then you'll have to include the kingdom of Sardinia and Sicily, which Sicily was a
separate kingdom. Of course. Yeah. And if you go to Sicily, it's all the stuff is written in Greek. So
what do you know? Well, it's just like, you know, the Alexander the Great was Greek. No,
really, it's Macedonian. Correct. And Macedonians is very discreetly different. As a matter of
fact, they just resolved the 20 year quarrel with Macedonian Greece regarding language and flags and
all that stuff. So or trying to resolve, I should say. Yeah. No, I'm just saying. So that's an interesting
point. Yeah. So it goes back to familial bloodlines and yes, a family could turn into a nation. Yes,
it can, by the way. Well, that's why city states were battling with one another. And like I said,
if it wasn't for Mussolini and many of the people that were working with him at the turn of the 20th
century, there would be no Italy. So that was, I mean, I'm just, you know, speaking practically, the
Italy. Yeah, but there is a Roman, there is like if you if you, if you, here's one thing, if you lumped
in the Portuguese, the Greeks and the Italian that to one bloodline, you'd be 99% accurate, you know,
that. Yeah. No, I'm aware of that. That's the truth of it. But that's not the way it looks on the
map, like I said. Right. Right. So back to the Americans, when you, when you look at the, you know,
what the US is doing, for example, you know, the US is a corporation. I went, I've gone through this
many, many times and you could look all this up. For example, give me a quick brief from down because
this is very important because this is exactly what's going on in every UN country in the world.
The Revolutionary War allegedly happened by a bunch of lawyers you call the founding fathers.
The British king and the reason why they did that is because King George passed the bunch of
laws saying you got to leave the indigenous people alone, their heritage, their land and their
culture. And that means no expansion, right? You can't touch them. And the attorney said, no, we're
going to go after them. They did. Then the European says, okay, we got a revolution in France,
this, that, and the other we got Napoleon coming. We're going to make the Americans pay.
They settle in for a little while and they come up to Lincoln in secret. Yes, there are secret
meetings, people all the time. And they say, look, you're the central government, all the other
central governments in the world have access and power and money over their people. You don't.
So we'll help you. You just sit back, follow our lead. We'll start creating some sabotage and
propaganda. We'll make a war, get rid of the people that want to keep the country together,
and you'll have more power than imagine. And they also destroyed Lincoln in the process.
Which by the way, let's go back to the founding fathers with the US Constitution. That was a
seditious document, sedition against what's called the Articles of Confederation completely
ignores them from 1774, which there were five presidents before George Washington,
which by the way, George Washington is very likely killed in the battle of Brooklyn.
And they didn't want to report that. This is early on because morality would fall. So they found
a guy that was almost his doppelganger, except he didn't have any teeth in his mouth. That's why
after the battle of Brooklyn or whatever, this big scramble to put teeth in George Washington's
mouth, which is still famous today, right? But anyway, let's go back to the Civil War. So Lincoln
they take out Lincoln, they impeach Johnson after Lincoln. And then just like you know, you got
Homeland Security that came in right after 9/11 out of nowhere, this 150,000 armed force that
took over the airports and it's just like how the hell did that happen? Where did it come from, right?
Well, right after the Civil War, 1871 or so, they put in the Libra Code and guess what they formed,
just like Homeland Security after 9/11, guess what they formed right after the Civil War. Nobody's
talking about this. You could look this up as a matter of fact, the academics call it an anomaly
in history like no one knows, no academic knows where the hell is thing came from. You know what
that thing is? The DOJ Department of Justice and they strong armed grant and they said, you better
sign an executive order that we're going to represent your legal affairs and all of a sudden they
grew into a monster which formalized the intelligence agencies that you know as the FBI,
Secret Service and all that and none of that came through any kind of an organic movement that a
nation would. It was all imposed. Now in 1871 with the DOJ they also have what's called the United
States Corporation Act and they turned into a corporation not to turn into a corporation for corporate
sake but so they can bankrupt it later on which FDR did in 1933 and got rid of lawful money and
made all the put a lien basically allowed the private bankers to put a lien on everything in the
country including you. Okay this process if you condensed that that took about 150 years, condensed
that down to less than 20 years they did that in the Middle East at the turn of the century.
The whole thing the whole thing that I mentioned right? Okay and they also influenced their religion.
They recreated what's what's called Islam. Okay so this is the mindset that you have to carry through
when I say there's going to be a Middle East Union. Right. It's not countries, it's not yeah. No no I
understand. A loose confederation as opposed to and that's the interesting thing when you study the
articles of confederation you wouldn't have a lot of the headaches that we have today had they
remained valid let's say as usable as usable construct for what we call America now.
You know and I just passed you a chat room question I'm sorry if that distracted you. Oh no that's
fine but I figured I'll pass you the text while we're sitting here you can deal with it whenever you
like but I thought it was an interesting question so I gave it to you. You know it's just it's rather
fascinating to go through all this because I keep looking for the precise act and the record
does not reveal where the corporation was formed you know what I mean that's not.
You all this religious that's like the question I could read it real quick why is that there's
no country that the age of majority provide their citizens or subjects with a document to legally
be in agreement with their respective constitution and quotes by becoming a co-signer to the
compact I know no nation that does this unless a national idea or SSN is considered to be such an
agreement. Well the social security number is private government agencies don't use it so if
you're ever asked for a social security number that's not government that's an agency.
FDR told you under the administrative procedures act the government shut down but don't worry
we'll be running everything through agency right. So well the reason why they don't do that well
the Constitution is a vicious document and I'm not anti-constitution for I'm just stating
what it is if you want to be pro-antiate that means you have to act on some kind of ideology that you
comprehend out of it and I want none of it just you know now the the reason why they don't have
you do anything is they don't have to because you're talking about the the key word they're a subject
it's a fiefdom feudalism. But part of that process I think begins a birth where
you're reported to be born you're reported to the agencies by your parents that's what when
they fill out your birth certificate that's what they do that's when you get a number right that's
when the agent is in the lead into the history of policing the reason why they do that is because
the agreement that the government has with the the private financing cartel is that they have a
presumed lien on everything in the country the squirrels the cats the dogs the land the water the
people the people's labor all the ideas the patents houses everything has a presumed lien on it
and see that's where policing comes from when you look at all the problems with the police and
you know people don't know why well the police in in this country started in Boston and in
New York when the bankers had notes on pretty much about half the town including the government
buildings they went to the government said look we we got everybody everybody at half the people
here oh yes so we need our own police force to protect our stuff because if there's destruction
or damage to property how they're not going to want to pay the note on it right so we have to
protect our property and manage the piece so they brought in what's called police right so that's
the history of the police has nothing to do with the reason the police keep law in order is so you
don't damage the property that you owe the bank which is pretty much half the town they're the
policy enforcers which is why it sounds like police yeah well you could say that but you have to
understand again the history of it you know so and move forward but but again let's we've gotten
off topic because here's the thing the ideology is very important you know like what how people think
there's frame of reference what you know when you say something where does their mind go like for
example you and I brought this up many times and managed to skirt around what the word using the
word unless you use it properly the word nice when you say nice and most people's ideology you
mean something pleasant likeable or good but we know when I say we whoever we is that it doesn't
mean that at all so when we discuss things about the possibility of war what's going on the middle
east what's the US doing where you know politically let's you know let's maybe not be so political or
maybe let's talk about this that none of that means anything unless it's custom tailored to fit into
the ideology of the listener right so with that said let's just very often let's use the ideology
that we are aware of like you and I might have a conversation with some other people and we might
stream along in the conversation and we're using accurate you know terms accurately and we're
very careful to convey a thought through accuracy most people listening are not have not been that's
beyond their ability because they've decided it what things are versus what things are okay
you see so so from that point of view from like if we were to go on air this on Fox News we basically
have to say the two this is an easy way to distill it down each region has a concept of superpowers
right so some people will say well the Soviet Union or Russia in the US are the two great superpowers
and maybe it's just the US now okay well in the Middle East proper which in military and government
circles they reference it as southwest Asia okay they don't use the term Middle East that's a proxy
term for the media okay so the two superpowers there in that southwest Asian region are Israel and Iran
okay so if anything is going to mallow out or turn over meaning become violent it has to be between
the be either the support or the antithesis you know non-support of those two powers now we know
obviously that those two powers are both manipulated and manipulative in other words you hear about
the quote unquote Israeli lobby influencing the US and like half the people in important political
positions are dual citizenship with Israel okay now where is the Iranian influence in the US well
maybe not so much overtly and if we're on Fox News I can't say but since we're not I'll tell you
it's with the underworld where what do I mean by that if you go to Tokyo right now the underworld
there is well you have the the the Yakuza or the Japanese underworld but the Yakuza can't do anything
without who the Israeli underworld and the Persian or the Iranian underworld anything and everything
that goes through Tokyo goes through Israeli and Iranian hands as well as the Yakuza well that that's
actually why is that the well I'll tell you why it's important right away that's actually how the
Israeli underworld was built that's how what you know people commonly refer to as the Jewish mafia is
actually a reality they wouldn't even exist without the well the Jewish mafia set up the FBI well
okay I mean that's okay I don't sounds kind of crazy but I just put that out there to let you know
it's no small thing well it does because Jay Agruhubar I mean really did a lot of work there turning the
Bureau of Investigations into the Federal Bureau of Investigations so I mean I'm just saying there
was there was a lot going on there but in underworld terms though you know just like the the Italians
don't function without certain go-between certain conduits guess what the the Yakuza has no reach
outside of its region without what people call the Middle East and that's why they that's why they
they they feather their nest so well together exactly and the thing is I understand this and the
reason why I use the word Middle East by the way is because that's the most relatable term if
you start talking about Asia nobody thinks you're talking about the Middle East region at all yeah
but when Japan is just the top top right corner oh I know it but that's the thing you say
and all the actions on the bottom left so people don't you know they'll have that but but here's
the here's the continuation of this with Israel and in Persia being the two superpowers they also
have the what's called a super history for example all of the what they call accepted religions
Judaism Islam and Christianity are based on the same book essentially what you might say the
Quran also but the Quran has 20 references to reading the bible and doing what the bible says
the Old Testament right most people are not aware of that but go look it up you'll see
and that's the all based out of Abraham or Israel right well on the other hand right
Persia most of your sciences that are attributed to Arab culture like mathematics certain types
of medical things are didn't really come out of the Arab culture per se they came out of the Persian
or Farsi or Iranian culture you see now yeah they had spread prior to Alexander the great they
had spread their culture throughout the known world and when I say culture I mean that in its
true a sense meaning music art as in sculpture and painting poetry various forms of esoteric
education and religion well this is why I thought that even ended up on the continent of Africa
and why some people in Africa speaks for a farce which is you know not well advertised but it does
happen right they are the farce people and in the the empire that ruled that part of the world
which the Romans only could go to the Jordan River they could not go more east than that they
they you right everyone talks about the Roman Empire well it was not there there was another empire
there that that ruled and it was not centered in Iran and anyway the ancient the concept of ancient
empire and Persia go hand in hand and they have been let's say on the sideline business and they're
not Arabic by the way they're not Arabs right they're just like Afghans are not Arabs they are
Farsi of the they're a different line completely and when you compare their influence in history
with Israel's influence in history especially in the religious circles they're pretty much equal
you know in terms of what they've affected like for example first century up until the fourth century
the formal religion of Rome over the Romans was mythreism right and so they just switch the name
to Christianity later on or whatever but it's still the same so you know when they tell you about
Christian catacombs underground those are mythreiums well you know whatever so you're looking at
these two very deep culturally based power based cultures let's say that everything comes out of
what it's military political scientific artistic or whatever it comes out of those two countries so
basically you watch those two countries so you the the effort to to let's talk about what's going
on because of Iran in the US is notable but you also have to see I would say if the current events
involved Israel and the US or Israel and Iran directly it would be something to watch otherwise
it's not it's this is a precursor to the precursor and that's pretty much the whole thing
why we said a lot without saying much really but no I understand that but I mean it's just that when
I thought about the logical conclusion that somebody would have to come to eventually is that
it would be untenable to continue this program of intervention and interference from what we do
refer to as the US army and if that you know pin was pulled out of that particular grenade to use
a euphemism here I believe that many other countries would also maneuver themselves out of the
theater and you would find a region that would as I said before pragmatically begin to cooperate
and would lead directly to that loose confederation of states that we were talking about earlier
not necessarily states you know well you know here's the secret with the US military
and then most people are not going to like this but it has to be said because it's so freaking obvious
the US military is the worst army in the history of the world to confront another army
the majority of confrontations that the US military has is with the civilian population
they always avoid the military of that country and if you don't believe that and you don't know
it well you better look into it because throughout history they were known as terrorists
not in other words when you have an army in the US as we're going to war with you expect them to
attack your army but what do they do they go around the back and they kill all the women and
children right so the way you assess if the US has a military threat against a country the way
you assess the outcome of that accurately with an accuracy of 99% by the way is how well is that
a country that the US is opposing protecting their civilian population in other words if they have
sams you know surface-to-air missiles and police armed with M50 machine guns in the in the public
parks and on top of apartment buildings all that the US is not going to attack you see like if you
look at what they did to Iraq Iraq was not set up to protect the civilian population they basically
had a couple of army bases and they protected their airport to a minimal degree and that's it
Iran is set up to protect itself Japan is set up to protect itself that way many countries are
set up so there's no way the US can attack Iran on a full scale and succeed right as you see
in other things done in through history yeah that's why the ugly truth about Iraq is that uh you
know it the entire nation was absolutely devastated because it was in shambles you know what
what they started to do is systematically round up the citizens and uh you know suck them into
facilities and torture them i mean that's the truth of it uh trying to get information about where
allegedly these things were hidden because they were looking for you know where where is the setup
and there was none this was the problem you know well there was but it was an occulted setup that if
they told the public what was so dangerous no one would believe it anyway let's just say that
yeah but that's the thing is that the the population did not have the knowledge that they were trying
to squeeze out of them in these you know torture sites that's that's what really went down and then
what they did is succeed in angering the uh the civilians who by the way are better armed than
they are here i mean you know uh uh uh uh an a k is common in the household over there at least was
you know at that time so you know you're stealing our people we're gonna eventually strike back
and this became what they called an insurgents right wasn't even necessarily organized it was a natural
reaction uh and that's exactly how that went and still uh i i want answers as to how it is we get
you know the the u.s military as it is uh you know going in and destroying a a subordination under false
pre-tenses uh you know and and never actually being held accountable for it thank you very much but
back to a ron who is in time but i have to talk about that before it happened again
anyway because it has nothing to do with the there's a divine reason for all of this stuff and the divine
reason is that when you leave a place you you come back and you want it to see it like it was before
when you left it right that's like a very clich term right sure what i leave here and i come back
next week i want to see it just like i left it right kind of thing right right let's take that all
the way to man's society where no matter whether you're secular religious uh occulted pagan or whatever
most people what comes out of their mouth when you say where did man start well they're going to point
to that part of the world where how is man's society going to end that part of the world right and
and very often today for the past well since the cold war what they call the cold war will sit for
the past thirty five years or so everyone uh if you ask anyone where if world war three were to
happen again where would it start well after the cold war everyone would clearly say would have to
start in the middle east you see my point right and people that think so intelligent would say
magito but yeah go ahead which is just the mountain air that but that's here's the thing too i
try to keep away from biblical references for several reason one is you get tagged as a bible
bumper religious nut which i'm not and the second thing is if you start giving biblical references
directly you're deluding yourself first before deluding the audience because the reason why you're
deluding yourself you're delusional is because you're presuming that the audience knows what's written
in the biblical text and how the hell could they know what's in the biblical text if they don't have
any they don't have the biblical texts sorry to tell you but all those bibles that are printed are
not the scriptures those are king james bible is not the not what's in the ancient scrolls anything
that you have is not in there if the best you the best chance you have a figuring out was in there
is you better break down and start looking at what's called an interlinear and to make things even worse
you'll find out what they call the new testament which i don't know why they call it the new
testament is written in greek well those guys were not greek that was written much much later
and put and piecemeal out of the aramaic so if you don't know how to translate an aramaic word one
where you're going to translate it another and that changes the meaning so don't even bother
that's why chuck you've known me for quite a few years now how many times i ever tell them when
to go read their bible i do the opposite never put it away go away from it unless you're going to
dedicate you know it's kind of like telling someone yeah you need furniture go to the lumberyard
what do you mean go you don't they don't sell furniture at the lumberyard yes they do it's just not in
the state that you want it in yeah you're gonna have to put in the work to put that together exactly
that's right that's exactly how it is and you know and people are so still i mean you might as well
just tell people go like there's a piece of furniture called an electric chair once you buy one sit down
and plug it in anyway so the the the the whole idea is that how do you convey ideas you know the
software that people are running is crap there it's not it's you know like you look at windows it's just
a there's still running windows 95 you know in the background of windows 10 you know it's just a
cumbersome you know one thing one layer over another but but here's the thing let go back to the
middle east union there are so many details to give there and instead of telling people hey this
is where i got it just break it down and give them a summary so you i don't know you sound like a
fortune teller to them because of course it's going to come true obviously if you if you got it if
you got the information right but the thing is the the the jumping to conclusions idea every time
there's a hiccup in the middle east it doesn't mean these things that i talk about are going to
come together oh no i understand there's a timeline no please understand that i don't think that
way at all but i know you don't but when i thought this and i thought of what would be the logical solution
okay i'll tell you that too yeah the solution yeah to that is what you see happening no
no that's but but eventually see i i carry things on and where it is you can go you know you
if you're going to play chess Greek you don't think about just the move you're making you think about
the potential for the other moves and you think about every other pieces movement that could come next
if you're playing the game properly right so well it also chess would be in the middle it's more like
bridge and more like checkers okay checkers because the mentality is really low and bridge because you
don't play alone you play with partners no fair enough but i i go with chess because i'm the only
individual speaker and yeah and it's the me it's the medium point uh so the idea is though that i
think to myself many moves ahead so i imagine that if someone decides to come to their senses and you
know not act as though we need to uh do the proverbial saber rattling in order to accomplish goals
somebody might eventually come to a conclusion that would lead directly to a circumstance by which
the middle eastern union concept would not only be logical but would seem to be beneficial for
everyone who's concerned if they actually went through with it um you know so therefore i see
it getting closer to a time when it'll just be well of course we're going to do this you know the
thing is well well they just uh just to consider also uh what do what which culture really which you
might be pressed to figure out that there are no cultures that have not had a uh influence from
that part of the world in their past even the asian cultures you know which tend to hide that fact
um so the the danger of the middle east union well let me just say this one thing the the events
that are going to lead to the middle east union are going to be so brutal that while they're happening
and through their aftermath no one is really going to be thinking about the possibility of a middle
east union because of the brutality that's taking place and we're talking about like in for example
i've mentioned in israel the there is going to be a Palestinian state but no one in no Palestinian
in the west bank that means they're all going to be moved out of there and we're probably looking at
fatalities up to a hundred thousand put modern day Palestinians in a very short period of time which
will cost that prime minister his the israeli prime minister his life and also israel is going to lose
the capital city of Tel Aviv or why because it's the ancient city of yafa which was the capital of the
see the palestines so basically you're talking about major people it's going to be very rapid fire though
like it'll seem like the world is ending but it goes you know one day and then in a week it all goes
back to normal you see the other thing you're going to look for is a political rise of a new a
country called the new assyria right because when you bring back a country that didn't exist and
you maintain its old name you tend to put new in front of it like new york new jersey right
it right those are those are english places right you see and so new amster dem right so be the new assyria
the okay so these things are what you'll look for you're also look for a civil war type situation
in modern day aran where they're going to unify there isn't going to be a secular and religious
government because people don't know that there are two governments just like for example in the
u_s_ you have the head the house in the senate well in aran they have the religious government and
the secular government that's going to go it's going to be one well see that's it what's weird
about that greek is if you read the aranian constitution uh all aspects of aranian government
are already supervised and require the approval of islamic councils well that's what i mean yeah
that's going to be one there in other words you won't be neat supervision of a council because
it'll be the same it'll just be in other words no one you okay all right well be a bipartisan
don't be a bipartisan uh administration okay so okay so so these things are going to be very radical
and also you have to remember this is being influenced what i call the gods with plural right
and when they play around just like i mean you were saying chest earlier if if you happen to buy
you know a modestly priced chest set and you know you we take a break and we come back and the
dog peed and set the chest set on fire i mean you're not going to die over it you'll say we'll have to
get another one here in the closet it's no big deal right so to the gods hundreds of thousands of
people dying is nothing to them by the way if you know what i mean well why would it be quite honestly
i mean from the right perspective of a god per se again small g but uh you know it doesn't matter
how you say there's got plural and they're like they have a society and at the top they have one
and we're not talking about him he's the director but i'm saying that the gods that are going to put
this in in effect uh not talking about big deal here it even but here here let's be frank right
where these hopefully the audience is mature even the top uh g with a capital g like the christian
say doesn't care about most people he cares about his own people and he cares about people of his
choosing and who they are he knows right and how do i know that well i don't have to make this
self up you know if you want to scrap everything that's written about it in the past is fiction
that's fine but do you know it you know it's just like when you did your uh uh and probably still
our research on jfk stuff you have to look at everything and discern it everything even if 99%
of it comes out to be bs you you still looked at everything you see you have to look at everything right
oh yeah listen i mean i you know searching through hundreds of thousands of documents right uh you
you're looking for just one useful thing you know what i mean some time right so yeah so if you
look at anything and everything that's ever written about the gods even by these these insane people
known as religious people christians mausoleums ujans or whatever they all earn agreement all of
it and i've said this before anyone who looks at any ancient rits of all the ancient rits are
in agreement completely even if you look at the creation stories found in the bible or to the
accadian of the samaritan they're all in agreement all in agreement slightly different accounts
but in essence the crux is the same so uh if you to keep going back you know we're almost like of having
a semi-philosophical discussion because uh the ideology of just telling people there's going to be a
middle east union is not enough what people need to comprehend is this is not a political issue this
is a cosmic issue dare i say okay and would right you see what i mean by cosmic uh in other words
are influenced by uh forces that are beyond the surface and if you want to for example look at
how contrived the society is now whether because pretty much everyone has the same school system
medical system scientific system and all that right and money system this this the medical
system education system the religious system financial system is so evil and so deceptive it's
based on deception and the people that run it are so evil at heart and i'm talking about people
down the street maybe family members that work in it as well that you might have or know or friends
that is no way that such a plot such a social mechanism could have been hatched by human by humans
themselves right right so you know this is a something that's also been discussed through the ages
i think the only ones that have gone too far by trying to pinpoint a character scheme are the
the uh what they call the nostics right they've categorized they've put everything into these neat
little packages which just doesn't seem so right but even what they say you know that the one
that is activating and keeping things going is evil is correct as well but here here's the
to again go back to the middle east the reason why you're going to have the middle east is very
simple what goes around comes around basically what you're going to see is the revival of things
that are old you're going to see there and also being coined as new if you know what i mean
things that are that are so old and forgotten that when they reemerge they will they will seem
like they're newly discovered okay if that makes any sense so that seems to be a common theme in
recent history to me great so go ahead well if you need if you want to learn something new read a
really old book that you know it's very simple um i think we've discussed the reemergent goddess
religion which was one of the reasons of the department of justice by the way because when you say
when you say instead of saying the department of justice say the department of diana or the
department of marian or the department of carolina or the department of susan does that does that
what did i just give you all female names woman's names i said female because they could be names
of objects like ships right do you see my point so it's the revival of this goddess religion and the
goddess religion teaches that humans were at one point in a godlike state and when they were in that
godlike state they were either asexual or hermaphroditic so the way you promote humans to go back
to a godlike state is you promote male with male union and when the males unite they become infertile
and you promote female and female union the females unite and maintain their fertility and
procreate without the men on their own well and we listen to this and then that's how they're going to
that's how you're going to have a godlike being and this is an ancient ancient teaching if you go
into very ancient teachings you'll see this is not a cult of stuff this is this stuff that historians
have written about well right and that's why we've also discussed the mutilation of the male as well
which has become popularized in in recent years the transgendarism where you know it the encouragement
usually is the the male to female but of course they goes the other way either the mutilation
in the medical system well you're genetically prone to cancer so cut your breasts off right now
that too and anything that defaminizes over feminizes removes the male organ from the equation i
mean this is all what's being promoted but of course of course we're coming up to a break time here
and i want to go further on these subjects but we're going to take a couple of minutes
just to kind of reset and plus i got a bunch of questions from the chat room and we do have open
lines as well a 319-527-5016 and we'd love to you know get your feedback on what's going on here too
because well you know how you're going to get a question answered if you don't ask it the hotel
you're about to return the Greek is with me and the next hour is going to be even more interesting
guys you're you stick around
all street window dot dot dot goalt so the stock market all street window dot dot dot
perhaps you're the best with deeply perhaps you're not in deep enough maybe you're thinking about
getting started all street windows dot condo dot com michael swanson the brilliant author of the war
state understood these trends professionally for many years and now he gives you the benefit of his
knowledge all street window dot dot go there now go there now go there now go
remember that this is the boy from our hotel for the first
the only 10 years on the morning morning morning i'll go to the park and the ocelium pack
no here's redness from ocelium dot com
[Theme music]
Your head's out of air and seems to land
And since the sun has come up again
And all this peace is with the sun
A sun that has f, once upon a time in a world
Now your head turns out of air and seems to land
And as the sun has f, once upon a time in a world
Go ahead, Colin!
Yeah, this is sitting the truth about today's Aeophae Association
Right, well, what do you want to know?
Beauty Baker's wild claim, Oswald Girlfriend,
New Ruby and Barry, Cancer Reppens, Billy?
I imagine I could claim I have four wheels, it doesn't make me a wagon, but okay.
Oswald was on the kill team and I'm trying to present the motor of John Kennedy.
Come on now, has it wheel-eckerd on the day of Aeophae Association?
Go to amazon.com, Entert Judith Baker in her own words, you'll get the results for a digital copy of a book where Walt Brown utilizes her own words and the known evidence in the case to get at, well,
A different perspective, let's say.
You can get Judith Berry Baker in her own words from the author himself signed if you request it by contacting Dr. Brown at k-i-a-s-j-f-k at-a-o-l.com.
It's a fun book and it actually dissects the many, many fantastic claims.
Judith Berry Baker in her own words.
Thank you for all the great information.
[Music]
So we do return with the second hour of the O'Challee effect. I know there was a slight pause. Of course you're hearing this on podcast, you didn't hear that, but on the livestream you did.
I was talking to the Greek off the air and just, you know, a couple of seconds off on my intro, sorry.
Anyhow, back to it, we do have the Greek with us, which is a rather unusual circumstance, kind of uncommon, so to speak, for him to be on the show anymore.
But you guys requested, and I'm always happy to talk with him. I mean, I enjoyed doing the O'Challee and the Greek thing and all of it. I learned a lot.
And I felt as though it was, you know, something of interest. I know a lot of people did enjoy it, so I'm more than happy to have a conversation with the Greek anyway.
And actually, it's been a lot of time talking you off the air years ago.
And, you know, through different circumstances. But that's a story for another day. Greek, you got a bunch of questions that were asked from the chat room, which I copied and pasted to you, because you're not in the chat room.
And I think there's one more hang in there that's kind of a longer question, but I wonder if you wouldn't address the couple of those.
Who are the brothmins? Bronfmins? Okay, let's just put it this way.
If you're asking who someone is, before you do, figure this out and you're going to have to replay this, figure out where the time marker is and listen to this about 10 times what I'm going to say.
If you've heard of them or seen them, they have no power. Let me say it again.
If you've heard of them or seen them, they have no power.
The Clintons, the Kissinger, the Putin, the Hitler, the Stalin's, those are all actors. Anybody in anything you've ever heard of after Napoleon is all someone who said, yes, I will do the script.
Tell me what or whatever. And also, they know that if they deviate, they get a slap on the wrist. And if they deviate again, they die of lead poisoning usually.
Like JFK, right? Hot lead poisoning. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And that's basically the game that you play. And so you hear any of the Koch brothers, Rockefeller, the Rockefellers and the Rothschilds are the banking clerks for the owners of the planet.
Let me say that again. You know what a banking clerk is? If you don't know, figure it out.
The Rothschilds, the Rockefeller is all the zeeps, the Goldman Sachs, the JP Morgan's, those guys are clerks, clerks for the owners of the planet.
You will never find out. And never would the capital V who the owners of the planet are in this incarnation, at least.
They are very, very smart about keeping them self-secret because they stay there. The closest you're going to get to viewing anybody of what they look like is the next time you get an Alex Jones type video of who's going to the builder, burgs.
Look at the limousine driver, not who's in the back seat because every time you see a photo who's going to the builder, burgers, you have Kissinger and who's the Bozo that owns Amazon.
Whatever, in the back seat, look at their faces. They're definitely afraid of looking forward because the real guy in power is the guy who's the show for the janitor.
The guy who dresses up like the janitor at the builder, burgs is one of the owners of the world. This is how it works.
And you don't have to have more than a fifth grade mentality to understand this. You always hide.
Especially since Napoleon, because Napoleon decided to kick all the oligarchs in the shins and he woke them up the moment he did a self-portrait of himself as the emperor of Europe.
Because yes, Europe had emperors up until the 19th century. And the moment he did that, they all said, okay, that's it. We're going to go in hiding.
And that's it. And it's been that way. And the way that you see what they are doing is through the what they call the intelligence agencies.
Like for example, you want to consider it. Let me just put it out this way from a good source. The Bozo who owns Amazon.
All right. Okay. He gets a suggestion to do something with the way the company is going to go. And he doesn't like it.
And they get back to him and he still doesn't comply. Well, that Bozo is going to go look at his bank account one day.
And guess what he's going to see 0.00. And then he gets a phone call after he checks his bank account. Do you want to reconsider what we suggested? And he says yes, sir.
And then his bank account goes up to, you know, whatever, 100 billion. It doesn't matter. Be those bucks. Yeah.
And other, it doesn't matter who it is. That's exactly how they work it. And that's exactly how it's done. And the people who push the bubbeliever not the people push the button on that one was a woman that's in her 40s.
It's about five foot zero. A little tiny lady. It wouldn't even suspect her of being anything like that. So make a long story short.
Greek, are you saying that they took Bezos money away? No, there was never any money there. It just digits anyway. Right.
It's access to it. And every Trump is like that, too. They're all like that. They're all actors. The next. My favorite is the Ukrainian guy. They have. He was a comedian. And they wanted to put a porn actress in Italy. Remember. Oh, yeah.
I do remember perfect. Perfect. Remember back to the future. Who's the president future? All Reagan. The actor. You know, like Donald Trump, the president. You mean the TV reality show?
Guy, I mean, come on, guys. If you know them or you heard them, they have no power. They are an actor of power. It doesn't mean that they don't have any power to you because they're acting as the official. Right.
Well, that's the interesting thing that Ukrainian guy that my favorite clip of him is playing the piano with his penis, actually. That's that's my favorite clip of him. Just just say no.
You don't think they can go different ways. You know, you know, it's a. Again, if you go back to the policing and all that, not a very short lady. She, you know, one day I heard, you know, this is an neighborhood in this little. Another short lady.
He goes, I got a rooster here down the street because yeah, I keep calling the cops on them because I don't like that grew up on a forum and I hated the way they sounded.
You know, so basically, all right. So basically you're calling the cops on the guy because you don't like his cock. Okay. So anyway, yeah.
Next question. Sure.
Let's see. Okay. Where does the Prince of Israel come? Okay. Well, that's that's another discussion. The Prince of Israel. You know, depends on who the Prince of Israel is in his equal 46. That's a ladder prophecy thing.
Let's just skim on this for a while because they're not good. Deep at all. I mean, skim like even night and touch the surface. When people look at the biblical text, that has to do with the chief God of all the gods.
And it has to do with him creating a people through Abraham and the Christ that came was through Abraham for the Abraham's descendants and those who want to go into covenant.
Now, what the hell does that have to do with you? And if you say of nothing, you're probably correct. Has nothing to do with you at this point. And how do I know that's true?
Because that's why they put all the ridiculous Christian religions is like one or 150 different formal Christian religions. And then there's another 20,000 sects in Christianity.
I know it sounds kind of crazy, right?
And then they have Judaism, which is straight out of Babylon and then Islam is supposed to be based on the stuff that everyone else is supposed to be based on.
It's a big radical mess. What the gods are telling you is the promises that we made to the ancient forefathers and the Christ and the people and the prophets that's not for you.
But how do I know because the people don't have it? They have these ridiculous religions led by Peter files and Peter Fogos. You know, Fogos means to eat, right?
So I mean, it's, but it will be for everyone on the planet later when the planets redone when it's more a little more obvious because people don't quite get the point.
So let's go to the next one. Opinion on Zaroastrianism. I don't have an opinion on it, but it is a legitimate deity because you have to understand there is a cosmic or divine geography.
I think you and I chuck went over it many, many times. The gods, there are, there are at least 70 major gods. We're not talking about the head one now. And then countless, literally countless minor ones. And they take have geographic influence.
That's why when you look at Christianity in Europe, it's different than Christianity in Eastern Europe. It's different than Christianity in South America, right? Because it has nothing to do with Christianity to do with those of those gods operate.
Right. Mr. Zaroastrianism is all confused with some of the geographically aligned elemental entities, which are not gods, but are a higher order.
Well, the elemental entity would be like the street sweeper in your neighborhood. The gods that the people deal with would be like the mayor. Right.
The demons and the angels of that God would be like the police and that what you see on main street. You know, because you are a good way to organize it, sure.
Yeah. And the president is off plan is a way from all of it because he doesn't have to be here. They already have been given instructions and said they understood it.
Exactly. Okay. So that's basically how it is in all of its legit. But when you're told about leprechauns and fairies and all that stuff, they do exist, but not in the way that, you know, they're not on cereal boxes.
Right.
Okay. All these things do exist. And the beauty of living now is that you're going to see evidence of all these things coming up for those who can discern it. Right.
So when you see, you know, someone in Germany going for a walk in the black forest and he with his iPhone takes a picture of this little creature that doesn't come above his knee.
You know, that's a leprechaun, but it doesn't look anything like you've been shown on the cereal boxes, right. Right. So. Okay.
So all these things, I don't have an opinion on them. I know of them and the question is, do you know of them? And what do you know of them? Right. And that's the point. So go tell other people like we were talking about having conversations earlier.
Hey, I said my piece. What am I going to go? I can't go further. Right. Because the response is minimal. In other words, right. You know, you know, there's a, there's a level to where you put out information and people say they want more, but if they can't handle it.
And they don't know they can't handle it, but you know, they can't handle it. Why say it? You see. So I've said my piece. There's going to be a time in the future to start talking again.
But I think you and I both agree and others have agreed that the stuff that we even put out on a cell in a Greek is more than some put out in the past couple of thousand years.
All organized and easy for people and the truth of the matter.
You know, and you know, recently someone says, well, great. Who do you think you are? You're the only one that has the truth. And I said, well, did you listen to it? Yeah. Did you understood? Did you get what I said? Yeah. Well, now I'm not the only one that's right now. You have it because you heard it.
You see. So get it. The ego's got to go away. And if people can't see through the arrogance and the ego and all that other stuff that they want to formulate, then you have to go away because they're not getting it. And there's not you know.
Well, see that that's the thing is that actually I I used to object to one of the things that you said quite often, which was that, you know, it's not time to discuss certain things. And, you know, in different areas of interest, I have found that to actually be very sadly true.
And why do I say that because I've tried to disseminate certain pieces of information and it went really unheated and misunderstood by people. And then they came back to it a couple of years later and said, oh, now that makes sense. And I said, no, it made sense. Then just you weren't ready to hear it.
And it's funny because I mean, it's not about cosmic topics that that that I've done this, but about some very real things. And I found that yes, there is a lack of audience for some things that I could present.
Yeah, welcome to Planet Earth. Yeah, welcome to Planet Earth exactly. I know, but look, I had to learn it my way.
It was sort of like talking about the Samarian organization of spirituality and they go, well, Sitchon and it's like, oh, God, look.
You know, he gave you the problem with Sitchon also is the reason, okay, let me just say this. I never say more than 11% or 10%. Here's the 12% or 11% one more percentage.
When you start figuring out that everything that determines what everything is happens between the ears, it's not about flesh and blood and it's not about nuts and bolts. Like with the UFO people, they're looking for nuts and bolts. It's not about that.
The people that are looking for spirituality, they want to go out of their body. Well, you can't do it inside your body. What do you think you're your body? You're just just a container. You could, you don't have to leave it. You could do exactly what you can do leaving it in still in your body.
You see, everyone's attached to this material stuff. Right. They don't understand it. And you're being shown all around you that that's been done away with. Like, you know, there's no money, right. There is no money at all. It's all credit, right.
You have no medicine at all. Band-aids, pain killers and aspirin and antibiotics is not medicine. Sorry, guys. That's all you got, right.
You know, you have to, the religion, I mean, come on, Santa Claus and Easter Bunny is saying no more. Right. So, you know, I mean, the thing is, it's not about, it's not about what you've been told at all.
And to get to that level, here, here's one example. If you want, you know, the brainwashing they give you to change the path, the present with time machines and all that, right.
You have to go to the past, right. And you know, you change it in the past. No, it's not. You go to the future. You always go to the future. I don't want to get in trouble.
But I don't want to let's, I don't want the Skype call being cut down, but the way time travel works to influence the timeline is you go to the future. You never go to the past to change the present.
And they're like, wow, Greek, that doesn't make any sense. Good. Perfect. That means now you can get rid of the old mindset. The reason why you say it doesn't make any sense is because you're relying on all the bullshit you've been taught, right. The same with everything.
So basically you go in the future and you send the information back to yourself in the present, which is in the past. And you can do that all between the years also.
And the gods have been trying to tell you this for all their ancient texts. That's why all the most pertinent ancient texts have what in there. It starts with the p and ends with a y.
Prophecy. Why are all the substantiated ancient texts, whether of any culture, what is the most significant part of their eschatological meaning is what happens in their what in their prophecies. Why are they always telling you the future?
Because that's how you change the now. So you see, how can I get into a discussion like this when I still see people wondering about blood pressure and they don't know how to keep time because they're on the Pope's work schedule.
There's no meaning to it. So next question. How can you tell if you're favored by the gods are making your life miserable and you know why your life is miserable.
There's lots of people who know, I mean, there's lots of people who say their lives are miserable, but they don't know why. If your life is miserable and you know why you're being favored by the gods, what?
Right? Okay. And it's not because I'm says on my opinion, that's the fact. At least I know I go in and out of favor with the gods. Thank you very much because it's going to.
It's going to be the female feminized the male. This seems to be the agenda of a softer kind of population control, global population need to decrease or natural resource need to decrease. You pick.
Yeah, there's plenty of people like for example, there's plenty of room for billions and hundreds of billions of people. For example, there's over a billion combustion motors on the earth right now.
And one combustion engine uses in eight hours more air that you use in a year. So if you do the math eight hours times three is a day times 365 in a year right now just based on how many combustion engines are on the planet.
And it's like having over a trillion people breathing air on the planet. Well, and so you got plenty of resources. Yeah, the people are going to go. Yeah, but real quickly I got to ask you something here because I am stymied by this every time I see it where there's not enough resources on the planet. So this is what.
If you scientifically allocated resources based on what is necessary. Okay, like in other words, if I were the deity and could simply allocate resources all over the planet it will. There's no issue here.
There is no. It takes more than enough resources. In fact, to sustain three times the population on the planet.
It takes, yeah, take the architecture and the way you call the infrastructure of a city like what would you say major city New York Tokyo, you know, places like that.
What the cities look like where people live comfortably. If you built all of Texas like that you could house everyone on the planet just in Texas.
Yeah, if you built an infrastructure that looked like, you know, apartments and high rises and you say and they would live comfortably.
It wouldn't be a despotic nightmare, you know, tripping over people would be plenty of room for everybody on the planet just on Texas if you developed it properly.
Well, and you would have to consolidate in that way you could actually allocate a fair amount of land, you know, arable land even to the existing population and distributed it if it was just simply done in a scientific consideration as opposed to, you know, who's got advantage who has the digits in the bank account or who's in the right.
Geographical location, all that stuff. If you re aligned at all, it's easily sustainable. There is no issue of resources here.
Well, the problem is the distribution and the where to. Okay, I'm just I'm just staying the type of technology using also. Why do you, you know, if you breathe what comes out of a car engine, you're going to die. Why aren't you.
There's hundreds of pans on how to run cars on a water vapor. I'm not talking about oxygen and hydrogen, just water vapor. There's a guy right now pedaling.
He wants to go cross country in a bus that sucks moisture out of the air with condensers and he drives the bus cross country just with air based on that.
So so the point here is those things like global warming is a message, you know, it's it's a cosmically caused global warming. They're telling you.
Too many people, they're telling you only one out of 10 people is going to be here in about a dozen years.
And the thing is it's not the numbers of people. It's the quality of the people. If you reduce the earth's population down to 100 people only and you put a rabbi, a priest, a minister, a doctor, and a lawyer in that mix.
And 40 years are going to be just as bad of a ship poor society, piss poor society as you are right now.
So in the future, you're not going to have doctors and lawyers and ministers and those kinds of basically demonic personages as you see today.
Those those box patients will not exist.
Everyone, you know, if you have a body, you know how to fix it. If you if you live in a society, there's law. Everyone's going to know these things.
But I assure you you could take this to the bank. If you put 10 people in a room right now, only one of you will be alive in 12 or 13 years. Max only one of you will walk out of there and that has to be done out of necessity.
And what I've cleaned from the information is that they're not going to pick the best of the best. They're going to take a representative sample.
So the one that walks out of the room is still going to be a typical human scumbag, you know, that you see today down the street or wherever you go in the country or whatever.
There's still going to be typical in that the people that are going to rule over them are going to be a different type of people.
And that's for another discussion, which I think we've broached on you and I years ago.
Yes, we did. It's going to be a cross section is what you're saying. And that actually makes sense.
The survivors are going to be the typical human scumbag that you see today on the planet pretty much.
Yeah, but they're not going to be ruled by the scumbags you see being ruled today.
Got you. OK. Fair enough.
So and it's going to be quite interesting, but you know, and I have more detail on that, which we've gone over, you know, one of these things go down.
You're going to have about a 40 year period of before the dust settles and retraining and all that.
And the cosmic realm will be more open. You know, when you look out at the night sky, it's not going to look anything like it does now.
And you look out in the day sky, it's not going to look anything like it does now either.
Well, that would make sense too. Yeah. So.
All right. Greek thoughts on capitalism, socialism, communism, how credit is seems to be supporting infrastructure of all these.
Well, it doesn't well, all those are.
You could go down socialism. I don't even know what those things mean based on their definitions that they give.
A capitalism can be defined as when you're done using something, you destroy it. So no one else can use it.
Right. You over here of like the US pulling out of a military base and they destroy everything right.
They tell you to do that. Destroy all your weapons in the army before if you know you're going to be captured, right?
Well, that's why they oftentimes sinking trucks and Vietnam before they left.
Yeah, dumping things after rivers and whatever. Yeah. No, that's true.
And you know, it's fun about that. Yeah.
Is before you even answer the rest of it quite frankly, the things that are defined, people start to point to examples of,
well, here was when socialism ran something. Here's when communism ran something.
Here's what a capitalism, you know, a capitalism based society looks like every last one of those statements is a lie.
Because if you have a religion that the state supports, in other words, if you put up a religious building organization,
state doesn't run it over with a tank in three days, that state approved.
So if you're going to a state approved religion and you have an identification number and policing, you're under feudalism.
You're living, okay, I dare anyone to do this. Start researching what a sovereign state is.
It's not what you think it is. And I'm not talking about just the legal meaning.
On YouTube, they got a couple of these academic assholes, you know, professors.
And the one guy's interviewing, could you define a sovereign state and he's like, oops, I wish you wouldn't have answered me that question.
Right. And the definition of a sovereign state is an entity. It's a juridical person. It's a fictional corporate entity.
That does three things. It has, first thing is it has absolute control over the territory that it's marked, you know, incorporated.
The second thing is it provides military protection for that territory. And the third thing is it offers services.
I didn't hear anything about communism, socialism, rights, voting, freedom or anything. It has nothing to do with that.
Anyone that's in the United Nations is a sovereign state, which is a fictional juridical person.
It is the corporate moniker that the owners of the planet have divided amongst themselves all of the countries.
That's why, for example, when you see, like, maybe was the impetus of having the sonic, the stuff going on between the US and Iran and near Iraq and all that, well, guess what?
If you look at the UN Council, is any Iran a member of the UN Council? Isn't the US a member of the UN Council? Isn't the UN Council a club for the sovereign states?
It's supposed to be-- nothing going on. Yeah, those are state problems. Like, for example, in the football leagues, right? You could have one team playing another. They're part of the same league. No matter how much they beat each other up on the field.
At the end of the day when it comes down to business, the owners of those teams are part of a group. And those are the ones that make the decisions.
So what I'm talking about when we bring up the Middle East Union, the UN will not have the organizational power and the kings of the world, the ones that own that you read about, the kings that I can't tell people go read it, but it's in the text, talks about the kings of the world.
It doesn't give any names, anything specific. Those owners are kings of the world that you don't know and probably will never know who they are, are the ones that it's talking about are going to be influenced.
So, well fair enough. I mean, I always like to go to the much simpler, easier, relatable kind of thing where you're talking about the football teams there. I say, look, there used to be this thing called the WWF.
And there was a guy named the Iron Sheik and he would battle a guy named Sergeant Slotter. And the two of them were supposed to represent Iran. And of course, Iran would be the Iron Sheik.
And Sergeant Slotter, everybody attended USA, USA. I mean, at the end of the day, they're both paid by the same corporate master and they are both there to promote the same company.
And as for who their managers are, their actual managers, not the guy showing up acting like a manager, but as for who their actual managers are, you don't know.
So, well, at the end of the day, it's the bean counter reporting to the real owner. I mean, bring up WWF when you say that. I remember as a child, WWF. I stopped watching it when Bruno Sarmartino broke his back and you had George the animal steal Andre the giant and the crazy manager, Lual Bano.
And Bob Backlin was the champion forever, right? Yeah, that's right. I really had some guy. Yeah. And that's that's my WWF now because I'm in my sixth decade. I'm my 50, 50 year, which my sixth decade, right? I'm going to six decade. I think you're 60. They're not listening. Right?
Just like all the morons think, you know, we end to a new decade. No, you don't go into a new decade and the Pope's work scheduled to hit 2021. Just like you don't go into a new century until you hit 2001, for example, right?
But anyway, who's counting, right? Yeah, who's counting exactly? I mean, you know, I'm 47 years old by most conventions. That would put me in my fifth decade, though, because you're in your fifth decade. That's right. When you're born, you're in your first decade.
Of course, yeah, however, you and yeah, and we're all in our first century, still. If we are 101, you're in your second century now. So this is the way, you know, you know, this is what we call dimension or the concept of measurement.
And there's nothing worse than surprises. You know, there really are no surprises because if you have an omnipotent being, how are you going to do a surprise when they know?
Right, but you know, I was talking to someone recently, there's an ET race, an alien race, and they will never be attacked because they're precox.
They know everything before it happens. So you can't attack them, right? So if you plan on attacking them tomorrow, they already know that, right?
Okay.
So in other words, they'll never be surprised. And we never have surprises with these things because the ancients knew about certain things that were so important to write down and make sure that we get.
And it doesn't, you know, check your familiar with the prophecies you've heard of whether you've studied them or not, at least you've heard of this every culture has an end times prophecy, right?
Nearly every culture. Yeah. Nearly every culture has some concept of either a reset or an end of the world scenario or, yeah, absolutely.
And it's not a happy ending and they don't give you much about after that. It's all you'll be better after, but it's never a happy ending, right? Like the massage bar, there's a used to have back then, but even now, but here's the thing.
I think they still exist, Greek.
They still exist, I know. But not that I know firsthand anymore, but anyway.
Yeah, I understand. First hand, that's, that's funny.
Yeah, go ahead, yeah.
If you're right, use your left, you think it's somebody else. So stranger danger. Go ahead. That's right. So, so the thing is, okay, what happens after is not important because we're not that after point right now.
We're still at the before point, before the end.
And it's not the end. It's just like the reset. I like calling it the reset because what is a reset?
You know, you're still playing the same game. You just wiped out all the current, the previous score.
Okay, like if you look at a video game or something like that, but you will let's go. There's a lot of fat to chew and yarn to weave when you talk about, we'd bring up the Middle East Union.
So we're not going to be on here indefinitely. You probably got to be eaten up the better part of the second half hour. I'm sure by now.
But what I want to say is this, there are specifics regarding all of this and you could get the short of it, you know, the summary, the quick summary or the details. I can do both.
So the, but the most thing because I know how people think is what happened yesterday in a few days. They won't even know.
So they want to know the immediacy of things, right? So what you're going to be watching and looking for. Yes. This whole thing with Iran just happened and all that.
But it means absolutely nothing in the big scheme other than one little brick in the wall more, you see.
One more event to change the ideology. These are what you're seeing that what just happened with Iran before we get into the next thing to watch out for.
I have not mentioned specifically because it's an ideology changer is to start making you or maintain your focus on that part of the world and your ideology.
And the ideology changer for some people who don't get the hint if they haven't studied the events.
A recap would be that the salamony that general was killed on his way to do a piece negotiations about the situation in Iraq. He gets killed by the Americans.
It is what they're with being put out. So he's not really the bad guy. He was actually trying to do good and the Americans are trying to look like the good guys, but they're not just the bad guys.
The Americans are the super bad guys because they're killing people for doing trying to do good. Not one bad guy versus another bad guy. You see I'm not demonizing the Americans here because they've done enough to demonize themselves for the past 300 years.
But here's the interesting part about it is that little bit that came out that the Iranians are trying to do good and they're slaughtered by the Americans puts even more what.
The negative sympathy towards the Americans. Why? Because the possibility and the of the whole world focusing on the Middle East as something good is based on say the Middle East Union and the Americans means no Americans in this you see.
So the more that the Americans become demonized the closer you're going to get this is not really an event that was really about us in Iran more than it was about the US if you know what I mean.
Well right. And he said it's the precursor to the precursor because yeah.
Yeah. And also to get the West. Now the problem you're good. I've mentioned this before you're going to have more people pulling out of mainstream religions, but they're going to be in no man's land because.
No one is presenting in a conventional sense what really these religions are supposed to be based on our people's faith.
It should be based on if they're going towards that you know the Christian or Judea or islam.
You know there is no one that's coming out and saying look you're all based on the promises given to Abraham.
And this is really what happened. No one is doing that at this point, but the vacuum is happening people are going away from mainstream religions.
And the problem is when people start explaining what is in the ancient texts and historically what really happened from Abraham to the Christ it's going to completely destroy Christianity islam and Judaism completely destroy it.
And that's why you keep hearing over and over and over decisions are made by governments because by the way it used to be the president got the football.
You know the atomic football when you become president right for the nukes well now what you get is you do have access to that as well, but you get a second suitcase and the second suitcase you get as a video file something looks like an iPad and written files on what happens if the E.T.s decide to make themselves known when you get what is your statement going to be to the world to explain it you see.
So and the reason why they don't come out and say this one of the main reasons is because it's going to disturb people's religions.
So you see what I mean so this is all tied in together the fake E.T. invasion and all that you know just like they had the fake terrorism you know there is no Muslims and right unless there were Muslims working in the CIA you know it's a different story but you know.
So that you see all of these agendas so what you're going to be seeing is agendas to get you to focus on the sky E.T. or something right UFOs tick-tack Navy Nimitz bullshit right.
And from speaking to an older person recently not real but some less almost a year now the point is retired spook.
So the H bomb was declat was not declassable kind of is you got a lost alamos in certain libraries you get blueprints for the H bomb it's no big not a secret really.
Not anymore.
Not anymore no but the biggest priority see the atomic warfare was a priority but by the mid to late 80s especially with Reagan making all of his hints the biggest priorities the E.T. agenda right now.
So if you for example are abducted by aliens and you start flapping your gums on the internet and it seems credible you're going to get my lab they're going to send military.
Rangers through your neighborhood at night with gas they're going to put the whole neighborhood to sleep they're going to come in and take you out of your bed and question you with sodium panthenol you know truth share.
And if you're lying you're in big shit but they know if you're lying or not by your story and they want to know what did they look like the what did they tell you you know what they're you know whatever right.
So this is serious business I'm not this is not conspiracy this is fact what I'm telling you.
So this all ties into the Middle East Union because how many times the people that look at the Zacharias such and stuff well they say out of an unarchy or all this stuff it's basically ancient aliens if you want to get into it right yes that they do exist but they're part of the ecology and it's not like the Christians say they're all demons no they're not demonic beings are different than cosmic ecology because right.
So all of this stuff is going to start coming to ahead in other words people are going to be looking more to the skies but not you know for time keeping or worthwhile things but for these things and there'll be signs in the skies regarding this you know you've had the phoenix lights and other places in New Mexico City or 20,000 people saw you have full hovering for eight hours right.
You're going to see more and more and more of that you're going to also have to learn how to keep time because time doesn't work the way CNN or the government or the church tells you all major events happen in the spring summer and fall in the spring when something major happens it's a building a period when the summer happens it happens in the summer it's a growing period and in the fall it's a breaking down period.
Like for example 9/11 happens in the fall it's a breakdown the idea that you live in a free country and everything that was in the past no longer exists now you're in danger right from an unknown enemy that doesn't really exist right what happens then they went to Iraq and started the war they went to Afghanistan sooner but in the spring time was shocking off you see and that started that whole thing now for 20 years so again and I think the first Iraq war they did it.
The first Iraq war they did in January February something the winter time is a transition time okay so basically right now it's winter you see this thing with Iraq in the US I mean the event in Iraq with Iran in the US and it's the middle of winter now it's not a big event if it happened in the spring it would have escalated if it happened in the fall it would have really escalated to the point where the US but here's one way to analyze this Chuck and why I'm not impressed by what is in the news.
This is the base that I use let's say you saw the news from the past month and it was what they call August September right they killed everything that just went on the in other words the protests in the Iraq in Iraq at the US embassy is really when all I started right you're aware of that about a more than a month or two now right some more day yeah and it led to this what we see now including a remember even after 9/11
a week or two later they shot down two liners airliners again right you know you remember that I think there was a couple of different problems where they crashed one of them crashed right in New York I think I'll go away peach yeah okay yeah I was going to I was going to go back that days that's the exact spot almost like maybe like a mile from where it crashed to visit but but they said it wasn't a missile and then a token booth camera you know
you have a token when you press the marine marine marine park parkway they said oh that token booth had a little black and white camera that had the missile being shot and hitting the airplane by the way that's used to be on the Internet I don't know if it's on anymore so
the strange thing that happened the next day in New Jersey is that the lottery number came out for the pick three for both the night and the day exactly the flight number of that plane which was really kind of odd because people that normally would win you know 50,
$60, $100 on a box bet we're getting like two bucks because so many people played the number it was hilarious to watch people get angry about it but go ahead.
That's that's that stuff that's very makes for good son X maybe in the few years maybe for still around I'll do something about how all that stuff works right.
And how to manipulate it in your favor or your friends favor your family's favor but okay so they commemorated this event with an airplane crash if you noticed right also so my point here is this if all this would have happened in what they call September right now you wouldn't be we wouldn't be
we wouldn't be having this conversation it would be escalating and escalating it would be in the news five times a day and there'd be major major international movements because it would be breaking down the entire presence of the US in the Middle East but because it happened in the winter which is transition it's just transition it makes sense.
What I mean by all this time so in other words you notice how I look at when things are happening overrides what is happening you notice.
So what I'm trying to say is if the same chain of events from the Iraq embassy protest to the murder you know the all the way to the plain being shot on happen in September the shit would have really hit the fan to the point word of broken one or two of the blades off right right but the same exact stuff but because it happened now cosmically it's not that important but it is part of the transition and which reminds me.
Humans are agriculture I've told us the people professors and they say no I techies know I said look okay you don't think we're agriculture lock you in this office in your cubicle and give me your cotton blue jeans because they're cotton agriculture and give me your wool sweater and you're going to get no food no grain products no meat products.
How long are you going to be in your office be as a programmer three days before you start crying your agriculture like it or not an agriculture what are you doing the spring.
You plan what you do in the summer what you have summer harvest and you it's your main growth you hoping for rains you don't you right you your main growth takes place in the summer what happens in the fall your harvest harvest again you go out and take everything right what happens in the winter well you have your winter rye have a couple of minor winter crops you have root vegetables
vegetables things like that when the winter is when you put a new roof on you you you go travel you can travel because you don't have to be on the farm right well and you should have had your food stored up during your story up right you in other words you're not planting on story you've actually stored right you see so okay and now here comes spring spring also is you're going to plow you're going to prepare right and you have to plant just at the right time because if you plant too soon it won't grow if you plant too late it'll be too young.
It'll be too young and tender for the hot summer sun you lose your crop so simmer spring is very critical what happens in the spring the fall is your harvest it's what you take in it's a breaking down period you know you drive through the country right before like the end of summer you see all the grass all the corn is up in the everything the forms of people what happens when you drive through farmland at the end of September October everything looks like ripped to shreds right right real ugly means torn down and gone so this is how I see it and
and link let's just go back and just do a thought experiment for a while like when the twin towers came down if that happened in the mid summer or in the winter would have been no big deal okay you know buildings fell down we'll get these terrorists but because it happened in the fall it aligns with the tearing down period of all social you see I wouldn't say would it be no big deal at all but it would not have had the cosmic effect that it did at the time that it did
well I literally feel as though because it happened when it did it it it shifted the reality a bit I I literally discern a marker there in time that there is a post and pre-9/11 reality because it affected the whole world you know everyone went into the security thing and here's the thing you have to be vigilant and discerning back in the eighties I did some technical work and there was an engineering firm
and I told them that I ride my bicycle at the World Trade Center at night because I like jumping the park benches and all this other stuff that they have there in the center and he said to me don't go near the World
Trend said trade center they have nukes there this is back in 86 87 and like this crazy old man maybe the new cuz the cuz he told you the nuclear core looks like a bowling ball they had this big round bronze I was like oh maybe that's where the
new cuz I didn't know right so and then in the late 90s I read in some people say hey Greek has your credit score I'm like what do you mean what is
what I care about my credit score it's bullshit and he says well because you have to have a good credit score we're gonna have a security based economy
and in order to do well in it you have to have a good credit score a couple people told me that I'm like what the hell is he talking about
and then later on after you like holy shit I was told about everything in the coming world you see what I'm saying yeah but I didn't know what it meant you know I remember the only rich guy I encountered really in the 90s kind of told me this
about credit scores and I just kind of you know fluffed it off because it wasn't you know yeah there was some places where you could find something reminiscent of it but it's not like it is now
right because they want to do well here's a thing years ago you're able to get a checking account closed take all the money out of the bank right a check for 50 grand and go buy a warehouse of tires and you get it yeah
and then like a month later the attorney says well you know is a bad check oh I'm sorry that was a bad check give me back the checks I could write you a good one they can't because they already monetize your signature
see now you can't do that anymore because you know there is no money when you write a check for me checking account and you see the money let's say you write a hundred bucks and the hundred bucks is
debited from your account it didn't that hundred bucks ever if you got didn't go to pay for anything it was the signature on the other end that paid for it your own bank takes the hundred dollars on keeps it for themselves
I mean the level of fraud and theft that is going on in just every day banking is so beyond people's imagination because they can't don't want to think about it so horrific that it is
if they look at the fraud that's going even if you got two hundred bucks in the bank account you're being defrauded when you see it being lowered your own bank is taking it it's happening everywhere on the world with such prolific so prolific that people cannot imagine that everyone they're getting away with it with nearly everyone right you see so now with digital money by the way if you go on the cell phone and you want you can't do that you want to go buy 50 thousand you know worth the tires you punch in sorry you can't do it you see
You see, so the digital stuff has nothing to do, electronic
was nothing to do with convenience.
It has to do with boxing you in between the years.
Well, see, these are the greater limitations that are brought about.
And, you know those that think Bitcoin is some sort of savior, it's like, what is
the difference, it's another digital representation of value?
It's, it's not lawful money.
Yeah, right, well it's not even a lawful representation.
No, not even remotely.
So anyway, you know what we're coming close to the end here and unfortunately, I mean like I love talking you over time
But I got a producer
That's no right after that. Let's let's do it. And thanks for having me on us
See again, I wish I had a
Lissipius joke to tell you but we're at a time so well quality not entirely. We got a couple of minutes
I was just warning you then you know, you know me. I do things gradually man. Yeah, that's right
I don't just to put like aren't you done?
So anyway, I hope people got something out of ideology more than anything else in other words be why do you think what you think?
Why you see not that you whether you can think or not which is rare anyway
It's why do you think what you think?
Well, see that's what I want people to do more than anything is understand why it is they are
Faulting to their positions why it is they have these belief systems not necessarily question their belief systems
But question why it is they have them in the first place?
because they are usually foundationally
corrupt such a degree
That if they understood actually what their beliefs are based on
You know, they wake up tomorrow and just decide they don't believe anything at all
You know, well, you know what what they they don't believe in it what they okay?
What they think believe they believe in whether it's religious medical scientific doesn't exist. It's all fiction
Yeah, it's all fiction. That's why I say when I die I want this body that donated to science fiction
So anyway, no fair enough look
I'm not concerned with where it goes because it is just a container and do we think about you know
The container we got our salad in from Walmart probably not you know
Just a whole here's here's the thing and it's it's it's it's be wasteful
It's gonna be converted to food because let me just before we go off throw this out there
Chuck you didn't know me before I you know, I was tell years ago
I was talking about what they call the gay or transgender way before it started
I talked before about the tattoos being normalized in society and if you've heard me also talk about
Cannibalism being normalized in society. I think you've right be aware of that because when the
next few years the next thing they're gonna put on society is you have the right and free will and
environmentally conscious to eat human flesh and
It's going and you know Greek that's never gonna happen just like transgender bathrooms never gonna happen
Yeah, right you're gonna be right now Pepsi Cola, Frito, Lay and a handful of companies are using what's called fetal
fetal liver tissue that they get from abortions in their food flavoring and
There's been more than one occurrence where people have sampled meats from various fast fast food restaurants and found human
Flesh in there and if you have a taste for pork
You have a taste for human flesh and you're probably being fed homeless people at Walmart anyway
Well, and the other thing is look for that agenda if you're going vegan
You better stay away from corn because you know
We already have seen the patents for them introducing human genetic material into corn
Thank you very much. Oh, but the cannibalism talking about direct cannibalism. Oh, I know what you're talking about
But kind that they have at Hollywood parties and political parties see but but aren't we already talking about the precursor to the precursor again?
Right, but again and to finish up to finish up
I have some of these code and co-conservative patriotist and types of Greek man. Aren't you outraged?
With all these you know almost sexuals and gaze and all that being you know and let it society now they have privileges
is it no no no
People are too trusting when the state you know the sovereign state which is a corporation says you have rights and they start bringing in all this stuff with a
transgender and the gaze and all that and eventually the cannibalism people think this is going to change the future society forever nope
Because what one thing that I've discussed with you also chuck of people go back to the archives is the whole society after 2025 is going to go
Under a very strict political and judicial flip meaning
In short, I'm not upset at all the you know, I'm an old testament kind of guy
So all the gender bending and all the stuff that they're putting out there. I'm not upset that you know why?
Because all those people that are coming out are being put on lists. You don't think so of course they are they got your picture and
And when this thing flips and now it's unlawful to do that and you get the the chop you know above the neck for it or whatever
Guess what it's not going to be hard to find these people and we're talking a very big chunk of the population
You know comparatively is going to be overtly known and this is and I'm not saying I'm gonna do this or anyone
This is how the system is going to go no you're right and
Unfortunately, that's going to be the last word on this but again, yeah if you go to a celly in the Greek on YouTube
It's still there and also on my website the section called a celly in the Greek but you can hear a lot of this stuff that
Greek was mentioning
During the show that we discussed at length years ago already
but
Anyway, man, thanks a lot for doing this with me. I really appreciate it and we're gonna have to make it a little sooner when you come back again
Okay, all right no problem take care man. Absolutely anyway no matter who you are where you are remember this
I am merely a celly all of you are indeed the effect. Thank you and good night
Go ahead Colin
Right, well, what do you want to know?
Wild claim Oswald girlfriend to new Ruby and Barry and cancer weapons really I imagine I could claim I have four wheels
It doesn't make me a wagon but okay
Oswald was on the tilting and trying to prevent the murder of John Kennedy come on now has a wheel expert on the day of
Acetation go into her claim go to amazon.com
Entertuneeth Baker in her own words. You'll get the results for a digital copy of a book where Walt Brown
Utilizes her own words and the known evidence in the case to get at well a different perspective
Let's say you can get Judith Barry Baker in her own words from the author himself signed if you request it by
contacting dr brown at kisjfk at aol.com
It's a fun book and it actually
Dissects the many many fantastic claims Judith Barry Baker in her own words
Thank you for all the great information
All street window dot dot
Gold
Silver the stock market
Wall Street window dot dot
Perhaps you're invested deeply perhaps you're not in deep enough maybe you're thinking about getting started
Wall Street window dot dot dot dot
Michael Swanson, the brilliant author of the war statement, understood these trends professionally
for many years, and now he gives you the benefit of his knowledge.
Walls3Stream2.com.
Go there now.
GO THERE NOW.
No nuclear holocaust.
You know what uranium is, right?
Think of nuclear weapons and other things like lots of you know what uranium is, right?
bad things, things are done with uranium, including some bad things, nuclear holocaust,
you know what uranium is right?
I think we...
Nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust, you know what uranium is right?
Think of nuclear weapons and other things, like flatsons, you know what uranium is right?
Bad things, things are done with uranium, including some bad things, nuclear holocaust,
nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust,
nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust, nuclear holocaust,
[Music]