to kill the effect is sponsored by Wall Street Window.com and Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss
Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss Miss
And now, the most integrated voice is on media check or Shelley.
January 3, 2023, allegedly.
According to that thing, we call a calendar and this indeed is the show you were looking
for.
How do I know this?
Because you're hearing me say what I'm saying.
I'm going to be testing out my audio here as I go live, my mic is a little hot, so I'm going to bring it down a touch.
See what we can do there.
But this is an interesting tears day or Tuesday and the first broadcast of the alleged year.
Although, again, alleged is it actually the year?
Does anybody know how to tell time?
Does this sound familiar to you?
If it does, you might have heard a show called Ocele in the Greek.
You might have heard Greek speak before in other places.
And you might say to yourself, "What is he talking about if you haven't?"
I got the Greek with me tonight and I'll tell you, we did this little thing called Ocele in the Greek.
And recently, I've had a bunch of people looking for it because I had my YouTube channel taken away.
And somebody else who is posting and reposting some of those old shows apparently had their YouTube channel taken away.
And I don't think it's because of the Greek, but just so happens if you're trying to speak anything outside of the normal gibberish.
And you're going to try and communicate something that might be meaningful.
Tens to not make you very popular on the popular platforms.
Just saying.
But anyway, the Greek is with me and when we started Ocele in the Greek, I got to say,
"I started on the premise of, you know, Greek?"
There was this issue I have where communication has gone bad.
And immediately what did we have to talk about? Well, cosmic censorship.
What does that mean?
And by the way, I do have all the Ocele in the Greek stuff in the archive@ocele.com.
But it used to be out there in a lot of places that, "Well, it's kind of disappeared."
So we're going to get it back out there somewhere sometime.
And I might make my entire archive available for sale at some point.
But until then, guess what? Let's get an update because that was, let me think now, almost eight years ago,
when you and I did that for the first time, because somebody made a suggestion that it might be a good idea for you and I to talk.
That was Danny Romero, credit where credit is deserved.
Oh really? When did you speak to Danny last? Tell him to say hello?
Oh, I haven't spoken to Danny in years, but back in 2015, I think it was.
He said, "You know, there's this guy, and I'd not heard you before."
And he said, "There's this guy, and he's starting to tell me some of the things you said."
And I said, "Oh, that sounds like interesting, new, and relevant information. Let's get to it."
I mean, that's usually my attitude. But anyway.
Well, Danny just a little blast from the past. Hello, hello everyone, by the way.
Rainy Eastwood was going on, he was, I still around, I think, somehow, around or whatever shape you want to call him.
And he was going on a one month hiatus, and Danny said that I want to do it for a month.
They said, "Oh, no, it's no reason. I don't even mention it."
And I just didn't basically talk in politics and things like that.
So, a couple of weeks went by, and I said, "Wait a second. Let me see what asshole took over that role."
So, I checked it, and I hear you, and I said, "Wow, this guy's got a pretty good voice, more of a dominant tone that you normally hear on the alternative scene."
So, I reached out to you, and I said, "Hey, you know, I was supposed to do that job."
And then we got the talking, and Danny said, "Well, you two guys do something, and there we are.
And here we are."
Right, and then after that, you had an uncommon radio with Seth, and you know, a complaint came to me recently that there was an archive that contained Oceleon the Greek, uncommon radio, and some other show, I guess you were doing, where you were putting out, you know, effectively.
No shows, totally, hold on, I don't do shows.
Excuse me, that's for other people. Yeah, do sonic events.
Sonic events, thank you.
I forget my Greek speak a little bit, because you were... That's fine, that's fine. There's a clear distinction, it's beyond definition.
You know, definitions in the way we use words has an effect on the mind, right?
It's also like a filter.
It's also a form of coding.
It's a form of basic overall criteria under the category you mentioned earlier, communication.
I want to get in all that, maybe, when we start rolling into this, because I don't think I've explained the filter and other things and the effects on the mind, but it's in the code.
So maybe get into it.
No, no.
Go ahead, you're giving a little history there, which is good.
And you know, this is planet Earth, right?
So if you've been here for more than 15 minutes, you should know what's going on, it's not that complicated, right?
No, absolutely true. And I think we started to disturb people with terms like the dummy load and stuff like that, but again, people...
Oh, disturbing the disturbed, you mean?
Of course.
Anyway, go ahead.
Well, you would take that term, and they would take it to be offensive immediately without actually listening to what it is you were talking about, which is what?
Part of the course, normal, I guess, here on planet Earth, because no matter what you communicate and sadly, I'm coming to this conclusion lately, and I've been related to you that after, you know, a decade, basically of doing this, pretty much nonstop, I'm starting to feel like, you know, I'm not reaching those that I use to reach.
You're giving it away. In other words, I would take any criticism on this comment I'm about to make, but in other words, this is the criticism that we might get.
Every O-chelly, O-N-G, let's call it O-N-G, episode that we did, every Sonic event about two hours, was sort of topical, not really, you know, but yeah, I had a topic.
And whatever topic we covered in those two hours gave you more usable information than a four-year college degree on that subject.
So if you're dropping, you know, all college degrees are BS, by the way.
Get it?
Of course.
So, you know, you're giving it away and it can't be worth much, but those, look, 1,000th of 1% of the people out there are really people.
I think we talked about it.
The rest of them are products of each age that they're living in, you know, like, well, we went through the industrial age, space age, technology, information age.
That's what I mean by age, each generation.
And when you take into account that most people are basically as seen on TV people, if in other words, when you, when they engage with others or socially, their responses and the thought patterns are based on what they've seen on television, right?
Okay.
So you're looking at this particular slice of humanity that's been affected, corrupted, however you want to say, each generation.
And by the way, you can have someone who's 50 or 60 years old that's got two or three of those, you know, grew up with TV in the 60s, then the 70s, 80s, 90s.
And then now, and it's got four slices in there.
But, you know, so it's, it's pretty, it's not very good.
But we do have a lot more freedom.
The one thing that I wanted to also impart with, without saying it, and they'll say it now is that we are a hell of a lot more free than we're told that we are.
Right? And one of the, one of the proofs of that is the O&G episodes and how long they'll erupt on that disgusting YouTube platform.
And I've said earlier, by the way, years ago, I will never do a YouTube.
Or, you know, so if it's, many of my stuff, the sonic event shows up on YouTube, it's not because I put it up, right?
Right.
And I've kept to its all this day.
And I've seen a lot of people prosper financially and popularity with it and more power to them.
No, look, and I never prospered from it financially because I just put it out there, right?
You got to run with the scissors.
Yeah, I mean, I may have run with the scissors.
You got to be reckless in other words, you know, you're not going to do well in these plot, in these mainstream platforms.
You know what I mean?
We'll talk about that, maybe some other time.
But, recklessness, reckless, but not abandoned.
So, abandonment with the, recklessness without abandonment.
In other words, you have to take responsibility for your recklessness.
Kind of like the Alex Jones guy.
Yeah, and you also got to make sure that, look, you're actually paid and protected by somebody whose interests are met by you doing what you do.
That's always helpful.
And unfortunately, I'm independent, so.
Yeah, but we all are protected.
That's the other thing.
We all operate, I mean, non-material.
See, now we're getting deep already.
And by the way, just in my chat room, they have asked actually what day it is.
And it's funny because I answered a chatter answered.
And meanwhile, we didn't answer with the correct day.
So, well, it's not, look, there's no look.
Here's the thing, there is no truth.
It's all subjective because when you're dead, what's true and that doesn't matter, right?
So, when you're alive, you can't prove that you're alive other than moving around like a fish and whatever out of water sometimes.
But it's a matter of, if everything is subjective and there is no truth as one would say, right?
Because people lay down their lives for going to war thinking that why they're going to war is the truth and it's obviously false, right?
So, if you have people laying their lives down for lies, what would someone do for the truth?
So, you know, anyway, what I'm trying to say here is very simple.
And we can't prove objectively what's absolutely true or real.
But we can actually approach more than subjective and mostly objective show qualitative differences.
This is a higher quality than this is, right?
So, you know, even people who are not well cultured or exposed to much, you give them something that's a piece of junk and the same thing that's a fine manufacturer they could tell the difference, right?
Even the most dim, dim width, half, you know, half width.
So, would notice that. So, what the Greek speak, Sonic events are about, is a qualitative influence, giving the people listening the perceptible choice to make a better quality decisions.
So, in terms of time, okay, if you're on the Pope's work schedule and the wind up to, well, known as the clock or digital part, whatever, however you want to express that,
nothing else in your reality other than some loose social format of, you know, the Pope's work schedule, like when you go to work and when you do certain things and meetings, nothing works on that, nothing in nature, not even the weather, the bugs, the bees, the animals, nothing works on that at all, right?
So, if nothing in the natural world that pertains to your well-being, by the way, works on that, wouldn't you want to find out what does, and that's why you would probably consider what I call lawful timekeeping, and that's what lawful just means.
Well, lawful also has a little something to do with logic, because let's just objectively face this fact, your day according to the normal convention, right, about when the day begins and ends, wherever you are, it begins in the midst of the darkest time of the day.
So, your day doesn't begin with a marker like say when the light arrives, right? Well, it's just, okay, hold on, this is, this is again going to what we were saying earlier, going deep.
You hear about ancient texts speak, I'm not just the Buddhist Daku or anything like that, you know, meaning the despair, not just that, but ancient texts talking about being in the light and being in the dark, right?
Okay, that's not physical, just physical, it's also where things are sourced from. So, you know, you've heard me say this before, I'll recap real quick. In ancient societies, most ancient societies, everything that you did used and based your life on was sourced in the light.
All the materials you're used were garnered from plants, plant dies, resins, things that grew in the light, you know, animal skins, right?
If you did any mining, it was usually surface stuff or on a natural cave, you didn't blast the side of a mountain in half, right?
Okay, your oil was gotten from things formed in the light. Your timekeeping was in the light. So, the day started at high noon, the new moon was the full moon, right?
The beginning of the year is when the, you know, everything equalized in the end of the year is when everything equalized again, kind of like a racetrack.
So, if you look at what's going on now with this society, everything that you've come in touch with materially has some form of petroleum product in it, right?
Think about it. No, pretty much everything around you, if you just, even if you ran out into the street naked, guess what you're standing on? Ass fault, right?
Okay, so where's petroleum formed, right? In the dark and the light destroys it, right?
True enough. Breaks it down. When do you start your day in the dark? When do you start your year in the dark, very dark society?
Right. See? So, no, I'm not going to give what day it is. No, I'm not, because that should have been established already by more than just me on even the ones listening here. I'm not trying to be an ass here.
Maybe it should be researched a little bit further and find out what you think should be not you chucked, but whoever is asking or listening to this, what is lawful timekeeping?
And by the way, what I just mentioned lawful timekeeping is mentioned in every astronomy 101 class in college, by the way. They do go, they do go into that.
It's only five minutes for the entire four years of college, but it's, you know, how much time does it, right? You don't need to, right?
So, spend much time on it, because it's not important. And as usual, it's, you know, what do they spend time with? Usually what is legal as opposed to what is lawful?
Right. That's what is commercial. Yes. Legal is commercial. Right. Like I always, I've been speaking well, when I ran into people out in public and I know a conversation is going to ensue.
I say, well, how long have been on earth for? And if they don't understand the question or don't give me a positive response, I know I'm dealing with a moron, which is, I'm saying that affectionately. Right.
So, if you, you're right. So, so now you have to go into that mode, which is different than a mode when you're teaching a child. Right.
It's, it's a, in other words, it's kind of like when you open a toolbox and, and you see there's only a screwdriver there.
Well, it's going, that screwdriver is going to have to become multi-use now, right?
No, right. You'll have to want it. Because you only have one tool. You can't, now if you open the toolbox and there's a hundred tools in there, well, you'll see you've got a big screwdriver, a small screwdriver, you know, for a big screw, a small screw, you got to, right?
But if you only have a butter knife or a screwdriver, well, you're going to have to use that for everything, you know, you could use the back of a screwdriver to make a small hammer, right? To tap something down.
Yeah, where if you had a hammer, you wouldn't do that. So, so, you know, once you start dealing with these typical surface dwelling earth and habitat, by the way, that's another part of Greek speak, right?
Yes. Well, so, calling them people is actually more than most deserved. But anyway, and I'm saying all these things affectionately.
And from a higher perspective, not that I'm higher, but from a higher vantage point, right? So, you know, I've given that idea of wasting time, you know, when you're on the ground, and a four hour parade is passing by, you have to spend four hours looking at it to figure out, you know, jot down what everything you saw.
But if you're in a helicopter, you know, a thousand feet up, you could see the whole parade, and you could quickly write down everything that's down there, come back down, right?
And spend the other three and a half, three hours and 50 minutes doing something else. That's also the purpose of Greek speak to give a higher vantage point.
It saves a lot of time. So, anyway, back to the meeting people, how long have you been on earth? Because I just mentioned earlier, you've been on earth more than 15 minutes, you know what's going on here, right?
I mean, that's kind of facetious, but typically, you know, if you're talking to a species where their eight-year-olds are exceed the educational capacity of someone with five PhDs on earth, they would get it right away.
In other words, they would know based on what's called a travel guide, or in the military it's called a, it's called a, not a yellow book, it's called a, there's a book for it. In other words, when they're sending someone in the military to a foreign country, they give them a book with all the cultures and laws.
So, when they go there, they don't create an offense, right? International incident or something, an area book, it's called.
So, the other book for the earth and the travel guide is very, very simple. Don't talk to any of the surface-twelling earth inhabitants simply because anything you say will confuse the shit out of them.
Right? And that's from a higher quality perspective, you know, if you're a quality, you know, based-minded being.
So, it's pretty sad, but then again, you only got to put up with it for what? 50 years, 60, 70, 80, 90, well, you're thinking, you're going to live to 120 more power to you.
That's all you got. You don't have to put up with it for too long.
No, fair enough. And I mean, look, I try to do certain things regarding this. And the communication issue that, again, I started with was,
well, it's interesting because you attempt to adapt to the language of the natives, which is a fair and good thing to do so that you might be able to communicate with them, right?
Stop me where I'm wrong. But when you do that, it's fascinating to me that even when you make the best effort to comprehend their language and use it so that you can communicate ideas to them.
Quite often, it becomes a fruitless thing because even though you properly communicated an idea, it simply doesn't seem to be received.
They can't handle that. They're bread, they're bread on ideologies, narratives, and opinion.
Right. Ideas don't work with these beings here. Very rare. And here's, okay, I mean, some people might be scratching their heads. Why is this guy so bitter about this?
Okay. Look, if you feel like you've partitioned yourself enough to go along with what I'm saying, you're not going to meet anyone else like yourself.
You're spread out. Right. The reason why this is done cosmically is because if you get like five or six or ten people that are mostly on the ball, the what's going on and how to operate lawfully, you know what's going to happen, right?
It's it's going to create a rupt, you know, too much of a focus. It'd be no different than if you know a 300 foot diameter shiny mirror finished UFO landed in Walmart parking lot.
Right. It'd be no different than this. Like if you had a spiritually evolved being, I'm not saying I'm spiritually evolved, but I'm saying if my pursuits tend to be spiritually involved, I pursue those things evolved.
If you had a spiritually evolved being and you put him in the middle of the super bowl half time field, I assure you about one third to one half of the people would want to come down off the stands and beat that person to a pulp.
And if you ask them, why do you want to do that? They say, I don't know. I just feed. I just I hate this guy. I don't kind of, you know, I just got to do it. You see.
So here they tell you go to college and get an educate. There's no education in college zero at all. And if you think there is you need to do a little mental floss will clean up and wash your brain a little bit.
I know. Yeah. At all. There's no educate whatsoever. Very easy. Just look at their curriculums and textbooks.
What they're doing there is it's a right of passage just just as for example, certain countries, it's the mandatory military right you're 18, whatever you got to do a year and a half right in the military or whatever.
It's a right of passage in certain tribal cultures. You had to go out and slay your first, you know, whatever animal, right.
Not until you did that, you were not considered a man or a viable member of society. That's all it is. And to prove that is whenever you have any kind of a cultural medium film TV books stories put out.
The intellectuals are always shunned. They're called eggheads and the eggheads came from Germany in the 1930s when they were going after the intellectuals and they would go beat them up and the guys of the fucks would come back.
They had to go. I said, oh, they're like eggheads when you throw them on the sidewalk. Their head cracks open like an egg, right. That's where it comes from.
Well, you had revenge of the nerds, right. They always portrayed as a nerd even today. A geek or a nerd, right. Bad, you know, that never gets the girl always gets beat up doesn't do anything, right.
So they're all so the intellectuals, by the way. Again, I'm not saying that I'm part of that is just a, you know, observation.
You live in a society where people who want to advance themselves cognitively mentally and selectively are shunned and viewed as negative.
But on the other hand, you have higher learning institutions. Yeah, right. Sure you do. You see how it works. It's very, very simple.
So anyway, let's let's go on. What the communication part? Well, you don't mind. I find that part fascinating because, right, I do not possess any of these degrees.
And on occasion, I attempt and I must say attempt because it has varying degrees of success.
I attempt to communicate certain things, which are scientific, which are about, you know, the preservation of actual pieces of history.
And I communicate these things and quite often, regardless of the quality of the presentation, the information, it's got nothing to do with me.
But I mean, the actual information, the documentation, whatever, it becomes irrelevant because why I don't have one of these degrees.
I don't have the permission slip from the degree. It's more of a right of passage like someone who killed the biggest lion.
He could be a total, you know, whatever halfway, right? And he's regarded for the rest of his life as, you know, the lion slayer, right, because he slayed the biggest lion or whatever, the giant slayer or whatever, right, caught the biggest bug.
Right? So it's just a right of passage. That's all. But anyway, maybe I lean too heavy on the higher education part, but it says nothing that there is no, you live in a society. This society is completely fake, meaning that people have no sense of origin.
Their history is completely fake. Their money is fake. You know, it's based on credit, which is not money.
Their religions are all fake. Their philosophies are twisted and turned. Most of the medical technologies and medical industry is fake.
I think we've gone over that. And by the way, I think we did the second one we did was called a container. And then I included in many other sonic events.
If you've listened to a cell in the Greek, you've been forewarned about what's been going on for the past two years and what's really going on. And by the way, what, even though it didn't maybe seem like it was relevant, what's going to be, what's starting to happen in the past, let's say, month or two and going to continue for the next year is really going to validate it even more, meaning all the fakery, right?
But it's not going to be enough because there is no blood pressure. The pump doesn't, the blood, the heart is not a pump, right? You don't absorb anything through your intestines or your skin, the way that you, the brain, all these things.
So that won't happen until the next society is formed, which is not going to be for a while because when the mop-up crew comes here, you're going to have anywhere between four, well, it's going to be a 40-year period, a 70-year period, a 100-year period.
A 70-year period, a 120-year period of dark ages kind of thing. So enjoy yourself right now while you still got it.
And what's interesting about time and the time in which we find ourselves currently is that it is a bit different from that, you know, again, using the conveyance of the, you know, the communicate, the communicative tool of the calendar, right?
In the 2015 time period is different than it is now. And I note the change in communication where it's become in some ways, it's become a little easier to communicate.
And in other ways, it's become even more difficult, even more distortion, even more of a disconnect.
And it's more of a lot of the attempts, as I said before, to try and utilize the language of the natives, right? Their, you know, conventions even, you try and communicate. And it is still a problem.
Well, it's a different way.
I see it that way, sorry, because when you're dealing with the natives, it should have purpose.
Even if you're going out there to find a wife or a husband or something intimate, it still should have purpose to it.
And I've given this before example. I'm going to acquaintance somebody that considers himself a friend to the Greek calls and he says, "Oh, I want to come by."
He's on a cell phone driving around. And it's not too far away from you. I said, "Why do you want to come by?" He goes, "I want to say hello."
I said, "Well, you just did on the phone."
Right.
So let's have some more purpose. Here's an example. If you say, "I already, yes, I already did say hello, but I want to come by and give you a hug so you feel loved."
Yeah, I'll take that. I'll take that. There's no substitute for that.
And there's a purpose which actually requires physical presence as opposed to what they just did, which is like just said a little.
Over the bone.
Right. So in other words, develop the purpose first, right?
And then execute it. And it's like that with anything. And once you understand this, you can pretty much do anything here, but then you have to again do it with purpose.
Anything can be accomplished to a certain degree.
I always have discussions with people regarding business models. When they look at these billionaires or millionaires, I've met quite a few of the billionaires.
It would be, and they don't even know how they got there. Don't believe any of their stories. All that was predetermined.
It is, it is a big conspiracy. Cosmic one and Earth-based one, but not on the surface, but what you see on the surface is all strings being pulled.
Go ahead and try to start an Amazon or a Twitter or one of these cryptocurrencies, kleptocurrencies, I call them or whatever. It's not going to happen. All these stories are fake.
Every single, there are no self-made people. It is all predetermined before birth, even both cosmically and physically.
I can give many examples where people wanted to start a little UPS store or whatever. By the time they got up to their second or third business, the FBI crashed them.
And after they crashed their business, they apologized. It's like, no, you're not allowed to do that. Go ahead and try to start an electric motor company on your own.
What is going to happen? All that stuff is all predetermined. It's already scripted. They just put whatever character up there.
Cutting to a strange chase on that, one could say that what you're telling me is that the Calvinistic concept, that the only people that are successful have already been, now this gets a little touchy, but have already been determined by God to be blessed with that.
More than that. More meaning physical here. It's already been planned here by people that have been executing stuff on the planet. It is a conspiracy, but it's so big you can't see it.
It's kind of like the flatter thing you live under a dome. Yeah, that's possible. If the dome is so big, you don't notice it, right?
The whole solar system could be inside of one of those little snow globes and you know, it's so big, right? It's beyond your ability to first of all cognitively grasp it. Second of all perceive it. Third of all, why does it matter?
Like these things are all very, look, look, here's it's very much within that. There's no script. Like, you know, the little was a 13 year old high school girl more than a decade ago that showed all the presidents are related somehow.
Right. Even though it's whatever, it's if even if it's not you see, so you see it's all related. All these figures and people. So when I say you can do pretty much anything, it's within the context of what we've laid out in the past 20 minutes.
Well, right. And here's the thing. Like I was trying to get at the the African proverb with the elephant, I think is very, very relevant. And I bought this up to you before that, you know, if you're standing right on top of this thing, what is the elephant?
The elephant is this giant gray mass that really, you know, if you're right up against it, you're perceiving just the gray skin of said elephant. That's all it is.
Well, you're the other thing. If you respectfully the more the better you get to know that elephant, he doesn't seem so big anymore. Well, that's the other thing is because you finesse that, you know, just like, for example, if you've ever gotten behind the wheel of a semi truck with a trailer fully loaded.
And, you know, but they're out there, you know, and try to drive around the block, you know, someone who's familiar with it, it's no big deal. But you have to do it respectfully. You know, you can't make a right hand turn on a single side street.
You'll take out the front fenders of two cars, right? So I've just tried to move one of those around on a lot and it's not not easy.
I mean, because I'm not accustomed to it at all. Right. So you get accustomed to these things and also you get accustomed to the madness, you know, once you understand it, but you cannot approach things. You have to do it respectfully.
Same when you're dealing with the morns on this planet, the surface to all the earth and habits. You when you have a pretty good comprehension of them, you still have to respect it because they, you know, they're stupid people are dangerous, right?
So they certainly are. Yeah. So again, it does, it goes by really, really as you get older, your perception of time goes by faster. I believe it actually does. It's kind of like a spiral, you know, when something's going down the drain as it gets towards the center, it goes faster and faster, right?
So, you know, I'm in, I'm in my sixth decade, right? So I'm like, yeah, it's, I'm getting kind of tired of this stuff here, you know, this stupidity.
And, but it doesn't stop me from still existing, you know, so, but I know that it's not going to be, you know, I'm not going to be around that long.
Well, relatively speaking, a lot less time ahead of you than in front, you know, than, than behind you, so to speak, I'm, I hopefully, I'm more than three quarters of the way done with this, it is.
Well, that's what I'm going to. I mean, I've completed five decades according to their regular reckoning on the calendar, but yeah, I'm in my sixth decade as well. You, you and I are pretty close in age.
Yeah, so what I'm saying is it's, it just put up with it. It's not, it's not that bad, but it's, it's not good either. Like a lot of people always say to me, Greek, am I wrong?
I say, well, I don't think you're wrong, but you're definitely not right. Right? So that leaves it open.
Well, that's another thing again, back to that elephant. Now somebody who says this thing is a giant gray thing. They're not wrong, but they're also not right because it's not just giant and gray.
There's a lot of things to do. If you give it a name and you know, it has its own personality, there you have one of it's just another surface throwing earth and happy.
Well, true, but it's not, I mean, why do you think people love their pets so much? They call them their family when you get to know animals?
You know, it's like you might like to eat chicken, but if you're sort of like a heartfelt human and you raise chickens, they, you give them names. They come, they answer to their names.
They each have different personalities and you say, you know, after six months of raising chickens, you still want to eat chicken? They're like, "Oh, yeah, but not these guys."
Well, I've got to handful of dogs, you know, in the house right now, right? And in some cultures, they'd certainly eat them.
Yeah, when I see Vietnamese here, I ask them in Vietnamese, they say, "Uncomtac chau." Which means, "Do you eat dog meat?"
And most of them, well, I had one of them, my wife being witnessed, she says, "Not here." So he didn't say no.
He just means not an American.
Anybody get angry with that or?
A couple of times people just start laughing and they go, "No!" You know, especially the younger ones.
But I've said, "Uncomtac chau." And they say, "Not here."
Well, say there you go, respecting the custom of the locals, right?
I don't know if we have any Vietnamese speakers in the chat, but...
I do not know. I don't think so, but either way.
Well, let's just assume...
Yeah, I tend to allow the Greek.
But anyway, the whole thing about communication is this, "Yeah, I'll give you a personal story."
I was doing Skype groups anywhere from 30 to 40 people, after a couple of like two private calls.
And after about a couple of years, like, "You know, I'm not promoting this, I'm not doing a Patreon, I'm not..."
You know, I'm doing all this and like...
I know all these people that I'm talking to, none of them can communicate.
It just got stagnant. I was like, and I started evaluating.
And I was like, "Oh, the people that I'm attracting can't communicate this."
So it's kind of like pissing in a bucket or trying to lift yourself up and nothing it's not going to go anywhere.
You have to commercialize it based on the venue, right?
You get subscribers, you do membership, right?
So then you have something coming in, coming in, like what they call, you know, some intake every month on a regular basis that you could assign.
So you could say, "Look, I got all these subscribers in Patreon, people signed up, getting so much every month, hey, you know, every month, I'm talking donations, donations don't work."
You know, on a format, a membership or whatever, and this can be assigned.
This could be assigned to a publisher, you know, where you have to compensate someone to do graphics, to buy equipment, to further this on, right?
And I didn't see anything going on, on its own, organically, naturally, right?
So I said, "All right, I'm stopping everything."
So I don't do any, you know, try to stay more like in a recluse type of thing.
I don't... people... I still get emails you want to do an interview like, "No."
I said, "Why not?" I said, "You asked me if I want to." I said, "No, I don't."
Well, what's the purpose of the interview, right? What's the... And not being a jerk, you know, I'll engage them, but I'll say, "No, I'm not going to go out and speak in public."
I mean, that's why, you know, when we did the thing here, look, this is more like a loyal and hearty, abbot, and Castello thing, in a way, because we kept it light, right?
And it's kind of like an unlikely pair.
You know, well, I'm likely, because I looked at your archives, and I don't mean to be pejorator or anything, but it's not anything, and nothing, none of the hosts, and none of the topics, or anything, I would ever click on.
The only, you know, but I have a history with you when we work all together.
So I wouldn't go around like, you know, when people ask me if you want to do an interview, I look at what hosts they've had, and what topics, and I'm like, "You got to be kidding me."
No, this is completely different. This is something that is on a different, it's, first of all, the Greek-speak stuff is extremely rarefied, but on the other hand, it's a pair, it's an anomaly, because I never speak on anything that's more than five feet beyond your reach.
In other words, you stick out your arm, that's like two and a half feet, or so two feet, depends if your knuckles drag on the ground, whatever, and how tall you are.
Just a little bit beyond your reach, just half a step forward. You could probably grab a book, or a magazine, or see something, pull something out of your wallet, or look in the mirror, and everything that's encompassed in Greek-speak, from the dummy load all the way to the human body, and banking, and everything, but the gods, and the ancient text, is all, either you know something about it already, or slightly familiar, or have access to it without any specialized, doing any kind of specialized, let's just say, endeavor.
We have to buy anything, or seek something else. It's always about things that are in your reach, or you are, have been made aware of.
You've got to start there. And here's the other thing. All of these things that people talk about politically, with the medical stuff past few years, with the money stuff, or whatever, I've had the opportunity, one thing the gods have given me is a lot of access to people.
So when I want to study, let's say for example, the legal system, believe it or not, within a year and a half, I'm having that one lunch, or two lunches, with Supreme Court justices. I'm like, how the hell is this happen? How does this even happen?
John Fitzgerald Maloy, he's the guy who penned the Miranda rights. You know, you have the right to remain silent. That guy. He doesn't know anything about law. I'm serious.
So I'm studying how the police work. Before you know it, I got like five of them in my backyard because some of the incidents happen across the street, and they come over here to set up, and I make blueberry pancakes and cowboy coffee for them.
And I'm just, they don't know anything about their job at all. So, and then the same with doctors. I'm like, I show them, hey, there's no blood pressure.
You know, there's no absorption. Look at this. Look at this. Yeah, I know, but you know, they don't acknowledge that. It's, I just do what they tell me to do.
Right.
It's like, what the hell is going on? No one knows what the hell they're doing and why they're doing it.
So, so to me, those people that have taken the professional situations that I just mentioned are sellouts because any reasonable human will say,
well, I aspire to be a doctor and I go there and I don't learn anything about, you know, really what health is about. I think I should not, I should quit.
And you know why? I'm saying this because there is a very high dropout rate and they say the high dropout rate in medical, education, let's say, for example, is a sign of how good or difficult it is. No.
It's a sign of only the same dropout and the insane and the idiots go in. Right. The same with the law, the same with all the fields. Right. Okay. So the religious especially.
Okay. Political. There's no nutty of, that's just a show. Right.
So, it's all commercial, by the way. So, so I started thinking I said, look, we have a lot more freedom than we're told that we have.
Serious. And you are free to do as long as, you know, you don't agitate the people around you pretty much, you know, I'm saying this in a positive way to improve as much as you'd like or can afford to or want to afford to.
And that is the purpose of saying what I'm saying here, given I'm bouncing all over the place here like a banana and a monkey grove.
The other day I was, I cook with firewood outside, right. I just like the way it tastes and I'm very serious about cooking. I mean, people driven hundreds and hundreds of miles so I can make them dinner. But anyway, I'm cleaning small branches off of a log.
So imagine a log about, you know, however, thick and it's leaning down on the ground and I'm shaving the brand. I'm holding it down on my left hand and I'm cutting the twigs off of it, right, with an axe. Very sharp axe.
Well, the axe slides a little bit too far and goes into my left hand and slices my left thumb in a third almost in half from the bottom of the cuticle down to the palm split open.
I'm like, oh, wow, look, I just split my thumb and it was kind of serious because my heart rate went up really. You know, almost like a slight shock.
I did the Greek speak thing which I've talked about and what to do, right. And this is about a week ago. It's still the muscles trying to grow back and all this up. But if I take the bandage off and send a photo, you'll say I barely see anything there.
Barely, right. So most people, what would they do? I got to go to the emergency room.
Stitches, neurosurgery, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, if you want use of your thumb, right. So you do the Greek speak thing in three days. It's pretty much healed.
And then about anywhere between 10 to 14 days, the muscle to shoot and all that will grow back. What is that worth?
Right. By the way, I do have quite a catalog of people emailing, you know, my nine year old daughter, you know, the security doors. It's like, you know, this like a screen door, but it's made out of raw iron with a metal screen on the bottom. Sometimes they don't finish them. They're very sharp.
Of nine year old girl closes it on her toe, cuts her big toe open. They did the same thing three days later. It's almost completely healed. No stitches. Right. So this is a concept of becoming self-sufficient, you know, how the body really works. You know, we're in a biological vacuum, right.
There's no absorption. There's no none of the stuff that they're talking about, right. You can it's we've proven that very easily just using their own stuff. So.
So that's just an example and it goes on and on and on and on and on. Right. All the stuff you have access to. So the communication.
First of all, if you are highly skilled in these things that I that you hear on Greek speak, you're not going to meet either physically or sonically someone else who is also right.
That's that's that's a that's a promise actually written in an ancient ritz. You're spread like salt. He says.
And let's say in the western scriptures, right says I spread you like salt. What does that mean? Well, what is salt used for flavor and we know it's in the context of flavor because you says if salt loses its flavor, it has no use. You throw it on the downhill, right. Right.
So how do you salt your food? Do you spread it very thinly over so when you every bite you have one little grain or do you put a big lump in the middle and then when you put that lump in your mouth, what do you do?
Oh, you're going to spit it out. Yeah. Right. So you're going to be spit out. So one aspect for this is this is extremely rare, if I had information because it's so practical and true.
The true to the individuals that know how to use it. It's not true if you don't know how to use it.
Like for the longest time as a child walking around in an urban environment, I saw fire extinguishers. Right.
Yeah, you know, you know, from a young child to, you know, young adult, never saw one being used. So whenever I saw fire extinguisher, I always wondered, okay, there's not much to wonder about.
It's a canister. You know, when there's a fire, you grab that thing and you aim it towards the fire puts the fire out, right. Real simple, right.
So I had to believe what they told me about fire extinguishers, not until like in our early 20s, I saw one in use. Now I didn't have to believe in it anymore. I saw it in action.
You see the difference? No, true. I recall not not seeing one in use till I was about 30 and I had to use it.
But you had to believe that it worked before it was a belief. Well, that was the thing is I had to literally respond to a situation where it was like, this is the thing I go to, I went and got it and used it and had to look at it and think about how it works before I utilized it, even though I was told previous how to use it.
I had to think about it for a moment and make sure, okay, what do I do? I pull this pin out, et cetera, et cetera, right. And then you point the hose and you actually direct this stuff, you know.
So on and so forth. And then I also had to deal with the reality of recharge and get refilling it, but it's the belief if you eliminate. Look, if you want to put this society or any society to complete chaos, eliminate their beliefs and have them rely on what they know because they know nothing.
So, I know, I know, Al-Qaeda and ISIS definitely got the stimulus checks, the $600, $1,200 checks from the treasury. Oh, sure. So they stopped. Yeah.
So, so did you have a joke? Yeah.
I'm not joking, by the way, there were that. So, giving example on the idiocy here. So, okay, Chuck, I'm minus a foul.
I'm going to use regular people surface talk here, okay. This is not me speaking, but giving a analogy, very strong analogy that should make people really see how simple things are regarding money because most people do things for money and they think things are done for money. And I'll show you how ridiculous.
Not the system is because the system has a set of rules. You could look them up, but how ridiculous the population is. Okay. So, here's the analogy. Chuck, I have a bank account and it's minus a thousand dollars. Can I write you a check for a hundred? No.
I certainly don't want it. No, okay. Now, if you gave some, if I put a thousand dollars in there, can I write a check for a hundred? No, because it's a zero.
Yeah, forget about the fees and all the insulia rary things that they do. Okay. Alright, so, if, alright, so, so I'm at the minus. So, if you're right, go to the Treasury website. There are like 23 trillion minus.
Can they write a check for a hundred dollars? Well, they shouldn't be able to. No, no, no, hold on. No. This is based on the math and what the attorney general says in the school economics say and all this.
I'm using the analogy how they're all fraudulent. No, they're still constantly writing the checks. Right. So, if you gave the US Treasury 23 trillion dollars, can they write a check for a hundred dollars? No.
Not if there were 23 trillion in the exactly. Okay. So, what's going on? What happens is this is the magic part. This is, they, they do this because the people allow it. They tell you it's all based of faith-based money system. That means it's a religion.
Well, in a way, that's accurate because the fact is that people that have no idea how it works at all. That's very simple. This is how it works. When they cut you a check, which is just an instrument. It's a piece of paper. Let's say you go to the mailbox and it's let's say thousand bucks, right?
So, you get the thousand dollar check and you go to the bank, do I'm going to give the bank a can I deposit this and they're going to look at it and they can see no.
Because you have to sign the back first, right? Because there's a signature issuing signature on the front. They need an endorsing signature. Actually in bonds, you can either endorse a both signatures on the front.
Anyway, so the moment you sign that, the teller puts that in and with the comptroller part of the bank, it's, it's 10 to one. Let's say you make it easy. It's not, it's 10 to one becomes 10 thousand. That instrument becomes 10 thousand dollars.
You just create a 10 thousand dollars. You don't know that. So the third of that, well, they give you the thousand. Let's say you want to cash it, right?
I've done this before. Go to the, not with whether official check and I go to the bank, though, is this good? Can you cash this and they're like, oh, yeah, says yours treasure. Yeah, of course. There's nothing there. But anyway.
So it creates 10, it's 10 to one fractional banking. So they give you the thousand dollars, right? And a kick in the ass if you spend too much time there. So the 9,000 that's left over a third of it goes to the bank, a third of it goes to the government 3000. Remember, they just the cost of, you know, right of the paper.
Right. And the other third, whatever you want to figure it out, it goes to the federal reserve or whatever trust. So this is how they're funding their stuff by sending us. It's, it's most people. Right. They know if they don't have that, they, you see, that's why they give you utility bill to make you feel like your paycheck is worth something.
If you don't pay the utility bill, you're going to get your water, gas and electric cutoff. That's bullshit. It's all paid for. The reason they're doing this make you feel like what you're working for is worth something. You see, it's all a mind, you know, so anyway, here's the thing.
When they want to, when the government wants to fund something, it's so loose government, you know, it's kind of like, you know, when, anyway, you know what a franchise is.
You know, people say I went to Kentucky fried chicken, like, no, he didn't. And people say I went to Taco Bell. I said, no, he didn't. I went to such an a no you didn't. And so what do you mean what do you keep saying now? Let's hold these different places. Why do you say no? You didn't. I said, because they're all PepsiCo. Right. Yeah.
Yeah. The US government doesn't exist. It's so it's part of the, anyway, world economic, whatever. It's a franchise of the IMF. So here's the interesting thing. Whenever they want to fund something, they send checks out to people.
And you think you're getting a thousand dollars. That's why they keep it so low. A thousand, not useful. Like, for example, if you know anyone that lives in Germany, they were, or even Canada, they were getting two or three thousand a month. Right. Right. Right. So anyway.
So when they want to fund something, they send the their subjects checks and because they need their signatures, they can't create the need to have the the chattel agree to it. Right. So like if you have a ranch, you can even want to sell the ranch or sell the cows. You have to be able to put your hands on them. Like you say a thousand cattle and someone buys it.
They bet when they come to your ranch, they better be able to put their hands on a thousand cattle. You can't can't have ten cattle and say a thousand, right. It's not the deal won't go through. That's just how that works. The same thing with this financial stuff. You need signatures.
So this is the system that people endorse and by the way, I usually stop when I with the analogy of a minus a thousand in my bank account. Can I write you a check for a hundred. Right. If you give me a thousand, if I put a thousand, can I write you a check for a thousand. The answer most people say no.
So how the hell they gave you stimulus checks when there are trillions in debt and then the mind stops because it reaches the end of the road that they've ever been shown. Right. Right.
It seems like the rest of the road is an invisible paint and everything that I've told you you can look up in their own documentation. Right. A modern money mechanics federal reserve bag of Chicago. Right. Look it up.
So here's the interesting part. The way you make change. Okay. Okay. The way you make change. You see a lot of social leaders, right. And they usually get dialed lead poisoning. You know what I mean? You know lead poisoning right.
Of course. Okay. So the reason why they're not successful. The leaders that you've seen through history, civil rights, whatever is because they're trying to lead a bunch of idiots or morons. And you have to tell them like if you give them a broom, they don't know how to sweep. And even if you tell them how to sweep, you have to show. Right.
That's what gets the leaders in trouble. So true leadership. If you had a viable society. With just hint on what to do and the people would get it and do it without another. It would be a leaderless movement.
So then who are they going to shoot in the head or strangle or poison? No one. Right. They'd have to do. Okay. So worldwide strike situation. Right. And you know what fast trading is like.
They could do what? Thousand trades a second. Right. You've heard that with this been going on a Wall Street for a long time. Right. Micro trading or whatever.
Okay. The system right now is so reliant on what you do every minute while you're awake. That if you had, let's say, a third of the people on the planet just stop using banking. Stop using the utilities. Don't go to work. Don't buy anything. Just for three days.
That would bring this is most of this system, the middle part of the system to its knees. Right. Not protesting. You see. This is very simple to do. But by the time you get the information to the people, it's like pissing in a bucket. They don't get it. Right.
This is really relevant because there are a couple of situations here where we do have organizations that have created circumstances where there is no leadership.
And they're really seen as dangerous, seemingly to everybody. One. No. You can't organize it either. You just put out a public message. In other words, if, if the weather, which is total, baloney, by the way, because there are weather stations five miles apart.
Why do you have to predict that you could just give a real time every every five minutes, right? But anyway, what I mean here is you just put out the information in no organization and people will do it.
For example, bring up, you know, I brought up the Super Bowl Stadium. Have you ever seen the wave done in the stadium where the people do the wave? You know, it goes around. Okay. Where's the, you know, it's almost like a self organizing flow. Right. Because they're aware of it. And in the beginning, it's kind of rough. But then they kind of get it and they fall into it because there's no filtering. There's no blocks that have been put in place.
The thing that really kills it is fear. Oh, you know, it like, for example, I remember about decade ago or less, even maybe the time we were doing, oh, and G, the proper movement was reaching its peak.
You know, store rice and beans. And so I ran to some people as I said, oh, rice and me. I said, how? I see go to his living room. And he's got a 50 pound bag of rice and beans. I'm like, do you?
Do you write some beans? Well, I go, no, I said, well, if you had to, if you were in a situation where you really had to eat that, you wish you would wish you were dead. You wouldn't be able to digest it. You don't know how to cook it. Right.
And they would say to me, oh, when it time comes, then don't, don't come here. I was like, okay, sure.
But, okay, if you really want to be a hardcore prepper, you run a rehearsal. So what I suggest people do is if you're afraid that you're, you know, you're going to be in a situation.
Do me a favor. Do a rehearsal. Go out to the breaker box right now. Pull the power down. Turn it off. Shut off your water. Shut off your gas or whatever like that. And call me back in three days. Let me know how it went.
Right. How many do that? Well, not too many of them. Not too many. There was a small segment of the population that was actively trying to encourage people to do stuff like that.
At the time that we were doing the own G stuff. And it was very interesting to me because you, you, you had two sides of it and you had the very rare group that would say, look, you know, we do is we actually run this like a drill.
Yeah, but there should be no, see, there should be no group. There should be no, it should be innate and it will be in the future. Not this society. Not that this one.
You know, it's kind of okay. Let's say you have someone who's really tech savvy and they go back a few hundred years. It's not going to, there skills mean nothing. It's absolutely useless. Yeah. I mean, yeah. Oh, I know how to compute.
So the one I'm saying 99% of Greek speak is absolutely useless to your typical earthen habitant, you know, because they're, they're, first of all, I've been doing a study like I said earlier about the IC None TV for about two years now. I listen very carefully to people.
And the everything they say most of the majority of things that they say and the way they think is based on what, what form of television they were raised with the ones that were very heavily.
So and I would make a job every time you hear someone speak of say, oh, that's, they got that from television.
I'm waiting for them to say something that they haven't said, oh, we're done television. And that's just how we are. Right.
So you have to be very careful what you expose yourself to. No, certainly. And the thing is that by the time you realize what it is, you're being exposed to quite often. It's too late because your entire call and response reflexes are all based on this stuff.
Well, that's why I used to have a joke. What does heavy artillery and Greek speak have in common is to be the joke was what does banjo music and heavy artillery have in common. And it's once you hear it, it's too late.
Yeah, right. Right. In other words, because artillery, you know, if the shells coming in faster than speed of sound, it'll hit, it's not like the movies where you hear when the explosion happens. And then you hear the, the, the, whoosh sound, right?
No, but that that is. Yeah, the speed of sound is behind the speed of the, it's just the physical projectile will make us landing before you hear it. Yeah. It's just like a bullet. I've described this. I've been shot before, right?
And I did not hear that until after I was already shot. And quite honestly, I had to put it together because I don't know when getting shot.
The first thing, well, anyone has been shot and not going to queer you on it is the first complaint is it burns burns like hell. Well, my first complaint actually was that my leg was wet. Then it burned. Right.
Then it registered. I've been shot. You see, I wasn't even aware that that's what it was.
Right. It's not just like when I almost nearly chopped the finger off. I wasn't aware until I looked at it. So, anyway, where do you want to go with this? I kind of laid out a little mixed bag of a fave of what we spoke on. Yeah.
No, no, look, I appreciate it. And this, this makes perfect sense to me so far. I do want to talk a little more about the different organizational principles that I've seen. Now, you, you kind of objected to the idea that an organization and things would come about in an, in an organization.
I'm about in an eight way or, you know, in a reflexive way as opposed to somebody saying, OK, I've determined this is what I'm going to do and they, they actually do it.
I do want to talk about that a little more and take a little break here because we're at about the one hour mark, believe it or not. So before I will keep going.
Yeah, we'll keep going, but we'll take a little breather. All right.
Let people try to absorb what has been laid out so far, but there's a lot more. The Greek is with me here on a, well, on an alleged tears day or Tuesday.
Right. So anyway, and he didn't even tell you what day it was this time. So stick around. The Ocelli effect of return.
[Music]
Wall Street window dot dot dot gold silver. The stock market. Wall Street window dot dot dot.
Perhaps you're invested deeply. Perhaps you're not in deep enough. Maybe you're thinking about getting started. Wall Street window dot condo dot com.
Michael Swanson, the brilliant author of the war state, understood these trends professionally for many years and now he gives you the benefit of his knowledge. Wall Street window dot dot com.
Go there now. Go there now. Go there now.
The war state by Michael Swanson explains the great national transformation that took place and put the Kennedy presidency in the context of the times and reveals never before published information about the Cuban missile crisis.
President Kennedy would not have been assassinated if he had been president 200 years ago. His assassination took place in the context of the Cold War and the rise of the national security state.
Before World War II, the United States was a continental republic. In the decade that followed, it became an imperial superpower.
Generals such as Curtis LaMais not only wanted to invade Cuba, but knew that there were short-range missiles on the island armed with nuclear warheads that they could not destroy because they were on mobile launchers.
Their invasion could have led to a third world war and they wanted to go to war anyway.
The war state by Michael Swanson reveals why and will show you what president Kennedy was up against. For more information, the warstate.com.
Do you like history, real history, that you are never taught in schools?
Why? The Vietnam War nuclear bombs and nation building in Southeast Asia by author Mike Swanson with new documentation never seen before that will open your eyes to events that led up to this.
Why? The Vietnam War nuclear bombs and nation building in Southeast Asia 1945 through 1961.
Get your copy today at amazon.com. Why? The Vietnam War by author Mike Swanson.
In denial, the secret wars with air strikes and tanks by Larry Hancock.
Secret wars became a staple of US covert operations that are still happening today. Larry Hancock's book in denial rips the cover off many of them.
Using new files it exposes things about the Bay of Pigs that no one has ever written about before. It shows why it really bailed and why the United States did not learn from it.
And the secret wars became a staple of US covert operations that are still happening today. It also shows why other countries today are doing the secret operations with more success.
This is the book that puts what some want to deny into the light.
In denial, secret wars with air strikes and tanks.
Larry Hancock. For more information, go to LarryHiconHancock.com. Pick up your copy of in denial at amazon.com in digital or physical files.
Hi, I am Jesus Christ, the most credible spokesman ever. And I listen to the Achelia fact because Chappo Chelie has his shit together and it kind of thinks of me sometimes.
Let he who goes to Achelia.com get stoned. Much love. See you soon.
Hey, Colin. I'm interested in the truth about today's achelia fact. Right. Well, what do you want to know? Beauty Baker's wild claim. Oswald Girlfriends, he knew Ruby and Barry and cancer weapons. Really?
I imagine I could claim I have four wheels. It doesn't make me a wagon, but okay. Oswald was on the kill team and I'm trying to invent the murder of John Kennedy. Come on, now.
Has it wheel effort on the day of achelia's affirmations? We'll be in the work.
Go to amazon.com, enter Judas Baker in her own words. You'll get results for a digital copy of a book where Walt Brown utilizes her own words and the known evidence from the case to get at well.
A different perspective, let's say you can get Judas Barry Baker in her own words from the author himself signed if you request it by contacting Dr. Brown at K-I-A-S-J-F-K at A-O-L.
It's a fun book and it actually dissects the many, many fantastic claims. Judas Barry Baker in her own words.
Thank you for all the great information.
>> Laws. Streetree. >> Rando.com. >> Ralt. >> Soared the stock market.
>> Laws. Streetree. >> Rando.com. >> Perhaps you are invested deeply.
>> Perhaps you are not in deep enough, maybe you are thinking about getting started.
Laws, Street, Rando, dot.com. >> Rando.com. >> Like a swanson, the brilliant author of the war
state understood these trends professionally for many years and now he gives you the benefit
of his knowledge. >> Ralt. >> Ralt. >> Go there now. >> Go there now.
>> Ochelly.com. >> Use the stress by calling schools or anyone else who
happens to get on the air at Ochelly.com. Do not necessarily reflect.
>> Be use of Ochelly.com or Junko. >> And we are not responsible for any stupidity
with fighting students. >> Thank you. >> Revelation through conversation.
[MUSIC]
>> The second segment of the Ochelly effect here on a Tears Day allegedly and all that good
stuff. And I have the Greek with me and he is definitely giving us the clinic in Greek
speak. Reminisce and quite a bit of the Ochelly and the Greek stuff which I think at this point
only resides in my archive. I could lock. They took it down other places. I'm very certain
I'll be able to put it back out and all of that at some point. And who knows maybe we'll
just make the archive available to people that actually value it. More about that in the
future and what's going to go on in the alleged year 2023. >> Well, let me interrupt for a moment.
We secretly discuss possibly doing a reboot but not like before. So I'm putting that out
publicly. I don't know if you get any feedback on that. Maybe it's worth considering.
>> Well, I absolutely know that we would have people that would be very pleased. I get, as
I've told you many times, I get messages in between the time that you're on the show and you're
not. And often I have, well, you know, one friend from New Jersey, often requests you. So one
guy has been requesting ever since I had him on the first time just on my show. >> Sounds
like a stalker. >> Yeah, almost. You know Eddie. Anyway, you did know Eddie at one point anyway.
Maybe you don't know now. >> Yeah, there's plenty of Eddie's around but yeah, I think so. >> Yeah, good
eye from the same town in which I was allegedly born. Got it. >> Well, no, that's, yeah,
it's placed on the earth. You know, but there's a lot to say about geography and I used to
blame geography for a lot of the lack of sense that I saw around myself. But it's not geographical.
It's the entire world. So it's just slightly variation of flavor. >> Yeah, you know,
what it is, a different flavor depending on the region you're in. I mean, obviously stupid in New
York City is just as stupid in Atlanta, but it does have a different accent. >> Right.
>> So by the way, looking at the, just, this is like a loose conversation. So I'm looking at the
Chitango and some about the day here. Yeah, it's pretty close to the last one. Yeah, it's,
it's, I'm reckoning around the 28th of the 10th month, right? So it'll be the 11th month,
usually for the bulk of January, then 12th month and bulk of February and March,
around the first week of March will be the, the first day of the first month. So it also
about here, at least the CIA gave us LSD when they just say dropout. No, it's not about
dropping out. That's the whole thing. At least they brought it out. They, so one of the
comments here is basically to drop out the decks or stack, blah, blah, blah. Well, that's,
that's the initial, the initial flavor of it, but let me just interject something if you will
chuck, you don't want to drop out. There's something called administrative duties, right?
Like if you're around people that do business, run their own businesses, you know, I call
them, say we're going to go play some basketball. No, I got to do admin work tonight. Admin
means you're, you know, you're going to have to sit down, get all the bills for the month
together, you know, send them out, right? So they don't cut off your power or whatever to do pay
or whatever, right? Admin work, right? Because a lot of people run small businesses,
they wear many hats, right? That's true. Okay. So as I've told you before, right? I've worked
with everything from this independent circumstance that I'm in now, where I do not have a boss,
right? I don't believe I own a business. This is not a business necessarily, but anyway,
I don't have a boss, and this is all I do. Sure, but a little bit back to the thing here about
dropping out, I thought about dropping out at all. It's about finding people that will fill those spots
the best they can. Like for example, you don't want to do any banking. There's plenty of people
out there that will. Well, no, true. And that's the thing is that you're in a straightaway.
And in a straightaway, I used to work with people who wanted to get into flipping houses and, you know,
I'm like, do you want me to tell you how that's going to work out for you or do you want to revisit
this in a couple of years? And I'm like, oh, tell me how that's going to work out. All right.
You don't want to, whenever you're doing a landlord thing, and you're going to, especially multiple units,
no matter how good they look on paper, you're going to have problem tenant, right? One or many or whatever.
You get a management agency, you give them 5%, 10% wherever they want, and they handle it for you, right?
You don't want to be there beating the guy up for trashing the apartment or calling the cops.
You want the management agency to do it, right? So you get an admin to do it.
So, if you don't want to deal with the banking, there's someone that does.
Look, back in the days, the mob set up, they got into administrative stuff and took a smaller mob.
And, you know, like, Irish mob and all that. Right.
So they would start up these little front companies. The word got out that you can't do business the way you've been doing it.
You got to start a front company, you load up the front company, and then you crash it.
But the problem with doing it, they got into all the LLC stuff, so you needed, you couldn't just file paperwork.
They wanted like a person's social security, they want, you know, all this stuff.
So I said, where do we get? Who's going to take the fall? I said, look, you see the homeless guy here on the corner?
Right? He'll be so glad if you gave him a thousand bucks or two thousand bucks in a new suit and a shower to show up
wherever and sign all the papers. You know that, right?
Well, a hundred bucks in a bag of McDonald's, believe me, you can get a guy to get the money.
Oh, no, he got a huge amount. He's glad to look a lot, but he can't look too rough.
No, no, no, but I'm just saying. A hundred bucks.
I want to get somebody who's slightly not too insane and doesn't look too rough.
They've been out only for a few weeks or a month because if you've been out for years, you look too rough.
Have them do all the paperwork and, you know, whatever. You see, so there's always a fall guy.
There's always an upright, upstanding, administrative manager.
There's always a thief. There's always a liar. There's always a trustworthy people.
I've always said this before. You might trust someone and not like them or you can like someone and not trust them.
For example, you might like having drinks with somebody, but you wouldn't give them your car keys or your house keys.
There's other people that you wouldn't invite to have a drink with, but you would definitely trust them with your house keys or your car keys, right?
Well, see now, I've known plenty of people like that where it's like, look, they're fun to drink with. They're fun to go out to eat with, but I don't want to bring them anywhere near my family.
Well, whatever. You know, okay.
So you've got to be a good admin and you've got to understand socially. Most of the Greeks speak does seem reclusive and dropping out to the simple-minded, because when someone takes things too simply, there's nothing that's simple.
Right? In one sense, the overall scope of the matter is simple. Let me just rephrase that. It's not easy. Everything is simple, but it's not easy.
And when you see that what is making something not so easy, it's because it's simplicity run awry, meaning it's a lot of little simple things to be put together to make up that big, simple thing.
Well, good example. There's always people is about the quality of food, right? We talked about this many times, the quality of food, where it's very simple to say, look, avoid the GMO and the high-priced corn syrup, right?
Avoid that and you'll be a lot healthier. Now that's a very simple statement. Sounds pretty good.
Well, this more important.
Well, a little more to that, because you've got to live with the seasons and that's one thing. Well, I'm oversimplifying you. I'm just saying that you say that to somebody and they go, well, that's a pretty simple statement.
And then even you say, okay, eat seasonally. So know what's in season and eat according to that and also eat the things that are local to you.
Well, here's the thing. Within the season, you have monthly.
So for example, you know, as the moon is full and it goes up, you want to eat lighter foods, leafy greens. That's your time to have your sweets or whatever.
Sure.
When you get the dark moon, the energy on its way to the dark moon, right? It starts to go down. That's when you eat more root vegetable avoid sweets.
And then when it starts going up again, you lift up, right?
So when women are having a bad menstrual cycle, which is usually in the middle of the month, they need to avoid sweets and eat more root vegetable and they won't have such a bad cycle, right?
That's I'm using the menstrual cycle because of the cramping and all that, right?
So in the full moon comes around again. See so the so you've got the monthly, like for example, all of the really good farmers, all maniacs talked about planting what when and it went by what?
The moon.
Because of it, but they don't explain it.
You see, so you got to explain man, you got to explain.
No, I understand.
But I'm just saying that when you present a simple idea like that, it sounds very simple, but that requires a bunch of education, doesn't it?
But it's all within it's already it's already in front. It's already there. There's no sense in look, I knew this guy while back he was an IP guy intellectual property, right?
So you get on the call, Skype call, bunch of people talking about some material that you know, you need like $20 million lab to make.
And I'm like, this isn't going to help anyone here. We need to know about stuff we can go to the hardware store or find laying around that we could rework and that is usable and improve that this stuff you're bringing is doesn't work.
You need to have you see?
That's why I like you know, usually on Tuesdays, by the way, and Christie after Didey went in the chat room and she's usually on here on Tuesdays.
Oh good teller said hello.
I'm sure she just heard you, but the thing is that she talks about look, you know what? There is food all around you. There's plenty of things that are medicines and some of them grow right in your front yard.
Oh yeah.
Look, years ago, but then who are you going to talk to? And I say, look, this is what I mean. Years ago, I was trafficking high end water. We were making built a Victor Shaw burger device.
And we're trafficking water in California and LA under spring, two oh one of the places we're selling it at is a place called Rossum. They got busted by the feds for selling raw milk and all this other stuff. They're 10 years ago more. This is 2010, 1112.
So we're selling water out of there at 10 bucks or three quarters of a court, you know, a leader.
Let's say.
And people were loving it getting high off the water. It was really super high quality water. We were just taking top water and transmuting it to high quality spring water.
Well, the stuff that we covered actually in a private thing that's only in the member section of Shelley not coming back.
Sure, but the device I'm talking about is if you want one, you transfer 30 grand into a bank account. And by the time it's ready to be delivered, you got to give me another 30 grand.
It's kind of like getting a new like a used Mercedes or whatever. It's not another thing, but we don't take a very long time to build a very expensive.
But, but okay, so, but here's the thing. So these people are into the health and all this stuff. They know all this stuff, right?
So we're walking one day. This is in Venice Beach. I'm walking to the beach because it was just a few blocks from there.
And the leader of the group, you know, the store and all these other health freaks in a real earthy crunchy granola type people, you know.
Oh, you can't cook food. You got to eat it, Rollas. Sorry, we're crossing the median and talk about food all around you, right?
And in the median, I point down and I say, hey, look, and they're like, what? I said, what's that? And none of them knew what it was.
And I started pulling it up. So this is Birdock root. It's really good for you. And they didn't even recognize it, right?
And then we're crossing the median again. This is between the median, right? In the street. As a look at that, what's that? I don't know. It's Amaranth, man. You could eat the greens, the seeds.
So, so, so, another is be careful who you go. So, so here you have one of the most prestigious organizations teaching people how to eat well.
And they didn't recognize the wonderful vegetables that were growing in front of the sidewalk in the median on the way to the beach.
So, who are you going to, so in other words, you got to, like, for example, if you want to learn about the legal system, you can't go to an attorney.
No, no way. You want to know about the human body. You can't go to a medical doctor. No, F in way.
Right. Yeah. That's the point about the police, too, is that you want to learn about spirituality. You can't go to a priest or rabbi or a mom. No way. It's the wrong direction.
So, who are you going to go to? Right? Go to yourself. Crack it open, man. It's like, it's, it's, okay, here's the other thing.
A lot of people say that, you know, the GOD is within you. It's not. There's no text that says that, by the way. That's a translation in the King Jimmy, right?
What he actually said was the kingdom of heaven is beside you, but they put it within you, right? So, anyway, so everything that's, you get it?
If everything is beside you, right? You see, it shouldn't be more than what? Five feet apart. Like you could reach out two feet when you hold up your arm.
Just a little bit more. If you reach it, five feet is basically standing up, sticking your arm out and taking what? One step and you got it.
You see? That's it. What? Communication. Yeah. Communication. See, now, here we go into a strange area and we're probably going to take up the rest of the time that we're going to spend presenting this son of God.
And presenting this sonic event on this because as I mentioned to you during the break, and I always disclose this stuff, by the way.
You know, I talked about Antifa a bunch and I stopped talking about it. I've had people write to me, how can I not talking about it anymore?
Because nobody understood what it was. I was trying to explain, which is that there is this mechanism that is presented to you, you know, by the people that present entertainment.
And politics and all of it together because they're all the same media company, right? So, you know, your Fox Broadcasting, Fox News will also give you the Simpsons. So keep it in mind, right?
It's just it is the way of things. They're talking about this organization. Antifa does this and that and the third thing. And they kept saying that, you know, they're the anti organization to this or that or whatever.
Meanwhile, they're talking about a fabrication that is created. I mean, anarchists wearing uniforms. I mean, where do you want the contradictions to begin and end? Okay. Really.
And I tried to talk about what's really happening regarding this, which is there is a communication hub, so to speak, that exists. And that is actually what it is.
Not this thing that they keep telling you about on TV, because as seen on TV, I mean, even those products that are as seen on TV, Greek, right? Most of the time, they're not quite as good when you get them in your hands, are they?
They're not quite as miraculous. And, you know, the flashlight is not quite as bright, right?
But life is not really indestructible. You know what I'm saying? So it's the antifa. I think you want to model this, this you want to focus on the model of antifa, right?
Yeah. Which is the, okay, exactly the same as the Wall Street protests are on 2011 on the Pope's work schedule. What was that called? The one percenters are bad or all that, right?
Right. How many of them were speaking on the fractional money system that when you get a check, it has no value until you sign it, right?
Yeah, nobody. Nobody. Right? Okay. So the same thing with antifa. It, it, look, is, it doesn't matter if it's a dictatorship, fascist, communist, whatever, whatever, is it lawful?
Is it benevolent or is it unlawful, meaning legal and malevolent? Right? So that's, that's the, the, the, the straw. Like a lot of people you wouldn't believe past few years. Well, yes, you probably wouldn't. People ask me about Bitcoin. I said, okay, first of all, it's an intelligence operation.
Yes.
If you buy Bitcoin or engage in human trafficking prostitution or illegal drugs, you're supporting the intelligence agencies. Any time you see thousands of percent profit, it's an intelligence operation.
And it goes back to the Jesuits before that it goes back to the Templars, before that it goes back to the who were the, the, the, the salucites before that it goes to the Persians, before that it goes to the Babylonians, the same intelligence operational model.
And there's a reason why they phrase the opiate of the people exists, right? You know, just say go, go ahead. I mean, that model has continued to present.
So it doesn't matter what is like, okay, look, I have a personal story I could tell you from conversations with the Black Lives Matter and tying it into the, because it's loosely entitled the antifa loosely.
I don't want you to lump it up with the affirmative action. Remember that? They were saying, oh, we're going to title people because of their color or whatever it's too bad. And no, no, no. Affirmative action started.
This is from speaking with someone who was involved in structuring that in the 60s was American industry was becoming incestuous with middle-aged white guys.
You know, go look at, for example, documentaries on Ford Motor Company or the NASA or whatever in the 50s and 60s. You see all these guys with short haircuts, with pocket protectors, white guys, right? Middle-aged, right?
Everywhere. Okay. What they found out was American industry was getting stifled because of the culture of the middle-aged white guy running everything, right?
So they needed an influx of some new blood, new ideas, slightly different, just, and then they knew it had to be done culturally because they kept tightening the reins of education because this is back then if you wanted to be an architect and you showed you were competent in the field and can prove it with some testing.
They gave you an architect's degree or they not a degree from a college, but they gave you the licensing, same with a doctor, same with whatever or a lawyer. If you if you can prove they knew the law, they gave you the let's say quote unquote licensing and permission by the state.
Now they made it a requirement that you have to have a certain amount of college. Right. See before they, okay. So even that, they did that and they encouraged that back in the 50s and 60 because they needed some new blood.
Right. Didn't come. Didn't come. So the only way we're going to get it is by getting some of the Caribbean Latin, African, Asian blood in here. In other words, non, not white America. We need.
And white America includes also the German and the Swedish and we know we need some people diverse cultural diversity that will break us, break the train of thought that we have because that culture, by the way, we'll see things differently.
Different way. And that was the reason for affirmative action, not to unrighteously, unmeritoriously enriched people.
And certainly not to correct some previous injustice. That's just ludicrous. Nobody.
So here's the thing with the BLM and antifosal title instead of saying, well, we were slaves.
How about them saying that we have enriched your culture? Right.
Okay. Look at what the hip hop movement did in the 90s. Like before the 90s, it was ghetto and whatever. But in the 90s, you had, you go down to like white bread America. They were embracing big e-smalls and two-bock. Right. Right.
So I'm not, this is a bad example because I'm not, I mean, I, I mean, if it sounds good, it is good. I'm not a particular genre of any fan, a fan of any genre.
What I'm trying to say is the original idea for this multicultural stuff that was put into government codes in terms of hiring practices had nothing to do with unmarried, without merit bringing people in.
And merit of it was injecting a multicultural, multiracial, multicultural environment where it was right just white bread middle-aged white guys, you see.
Well, see, I had a conversation. This guy was a civil engineer who developed all the highways, which kind of a nightmare in Atlanta, Georgia. He was in his 80s.
He was about a decade ago and he was part, and says, nobody knows this. Here's the other thing. When you hear about corn-a-coat black people, you always culturally, just like when they show a doctor, they show a white lab coat with a stethoscope.
Well, when you hear about black people and where they live, they always show a ghetto or something like that. They never show the upper middle class neighborhoods like Cue Gardens,
or Queens in New York, or the Hollis Queens. They never show Marietta, Georgia. They never show, I mean, there's like dozens of upper middle class black neighborhoods, you know, like the Cosby Show kind of thing, you know.
They never show that. Right. Never. So.
But it's funny you keep saying white bread because it's very funny to me considering that the cuisine in America and the music and everything else.
If you were to extract and remove completely, you know, blacks, Italians, and Jews, I'll just pick those three groups. Guess what you got? Nothing.
I mean, really, anything that you consider to be, I mean, just the example of pizza I bring up all the time, which is funny.
Without this injection into the eco-spear, so to speak, of the cultural diversity, you've got a very stagnant situation without them and then later Asians and then so on and so forth.
Without these different injections of different things that are diverse culturally, you have stagnation, which is exactly the same when it comes to the technological advances, right?
Right. But the stagnation, if the stagnation is in deliberate, like in some cases you want stagnation so that the art doesn't get lost like in wine making, for example, or violent making.
Right. You know, the strata various, so they're not telling the people why it has its original sound because it's so simple. Right. And wine making, for example, if wire older, it's not really that the age of the wine.
If you ever drink like a thousand dollar bottle of wine, it tastes like jam, but it still tastes like, it takes some jam, filter it out, whatever, strawberry, grape jam and mix it with some wine and it's not that simple, but that's what it tastes like.
You know, it's like, why would you? It's the practices. That's what makes the age, right? So antiques, better, you know, that's the practice.
So some things you do want stagnation, right? In other words, you know, the best cheese, you know, Parmesan, Regiano. Well, but there's a different stagnation.
That's the same stagnation. They're not, they're not innovating. Yeah, but there's a difference between stagnation and maintaining a quality which has been reached by practice, right?
And if it needs, if it needs that influx, let's say, yeah, but that's better. Let's look at genetics. Right.
There's a guy as a YouTube video goes around the Antarondoc mountains where everybody's, you know, not everybody, but he interviewed interviews.
People that have been in bread and they're seriously retarded, right? So, so that inbreeding, you know, sometimes shouldn't happen.
Yeah. Wow. Sorry. There was a bit of a, I think, thunder roll behind me there. Yeah, hear it. Sorry. It was like this boom. And then there was a second boom. So I was just a little distracted there for a second.
But no, but that's the thing though is one something becomes too incestuous. There's a level at which, you know, homogenous actions and breeding and practice is good.
But this varies, right? And if it becomes too incestuous again, then we'll have stagnation. So at certain points, you need to engineer the introduction or the reduction of new information depending on the quality of things that are being produced, whether it's people or it's cheese, it doesn't matter, right?
No, well, the context matters, right? In other words, if you want to preserve something, you want to do it the same way, but you can't because the, you know, everything, the environment changes, right?
But, you know, it depends on the fine points that you're looking at. But look, you know, you got to, I see here something about 200, you know, I got cigarette and working well 200 years. It hasn't worked well. So I'll prop again to every time there's a new generation.
Here, this is how the social engineering works. You got to separate the children from the parents because the, the otherwise the children will be like the parents, not like a carbon copy of the parents, but pretty much a copy of the parents. So what you do is you create a rift, a generational rift, right?
And then it started in the, actually in the 1800s, late 1800s and, you know, remember, rebel without a cause, James Dean, right? The rift, right?
Yeah.
Between, okay, so you create a rift within the household, doesn't matter. In certain cultures, they separate the children from the household. That's the best way to change society because you can't teach something to a child.
And then they go home and sleep with the, in the same house and they have a different, you know, philosophy or ideology, completely different ideas and won't work.
Conflicts, so they know they can't do that. So they create a conflict, generational conflict within the house, right? And then one of those younger people are ejected from that environment, then they have more wherewithal supposedly and can rebuild society, right?
And this is just how it's done, but that system doesn't work anymore, right? Because there's too much information.
It's all distractions. You know, I think on the early Greek speak stuff, well, I spoke about what's coming as a Middle East union, but it's not, no one cares about that.
The reason for it is you're going to have a very conservative, quote unquote, move back to lawfulness and a very stringent, unlawful, it'll be lawful, but it'll be overdone, right?
You know, smothering. So this, this has started already. I don't know if you guys are paying attention, you know, on the subtleties of things that were banned and censored, let's say a year or two ago, or starting to be on, you know, mainstream media, right?
Like the, you know, the death from deaths from the, the shot, right? And the hoaxes that have been prepared medical hoaxes, that's starting to come out. And also being fed up with all this liberal agenda.
This is all planned, by the way, it's by the same people that brought you the liberal, right?
Of course.
And we've, I've talked about this and it's in within, by 2025 or so, you're going to be within the froze of an ultra conservative society that, that you will not recognize compared to what's been going on the past few years.
So snow, snow, big deals. Funny. It's great to talk about stuff that's going to happen in the future. And then you're still alive. You see it rolling up just like you talked about it and, you know,
and it seems natural to everyone, but it's clearly unnatural because you knew it was coming and you know the control mechanism. So,
well, right. I mean, quite frankly, if you listen very carefully to the early shows that we did, you could have predicted the past couple of years very easily.
Yeah, but here's the thing.
When you see it coming, the people, the people are just going to complain about it when it comes, even though you told them, right?
Well, that's what they do anyway. Yeah. Yeah. So, so, you know, so again, it's about the, it's about, I'll use the word individual or each, each, you know, select person, man or woman or being what they do with it.
And you structure yourself. Okay. This is how you, you know, it's about living life with efficiency. Right? So, for example, if, remember during the Obama years, we were supposed to go in a war and lock down or whatever.
You know, it didn't happen till 2020, right? So, if people that got caught up with the prepping, because disaster is coming and all this, if you know that it's not, you don't have to get engrossed in that argument.
You don't have to spend any energy in it, right? At all. That's where the efficiency comes from. It's not a, you're not going to change anything by knowing about it, but you will, you won't waste energy on it.
No, fair enough. So, look, with the last little bid here that I have you because we're going to end this around the two hour mark, not necessarily right on it, but around there.
I have this, I have this idea that you, you might be open to revisiting the Ocelli in the Greek thing, which would be fascinating. Of course, generally, you designed that. We had that.
Absolutely. It's not for say we'll be fascinating, not just informative this time. You know, I've always said I try not to share more than 10%. Right? Right.
So, let's do the 11, 12, 13, 14 up to 20, 30, 40%. Why not? It's going to be nitty gritty. And it's all done with, when I say people are more on, I say that affectionately, right? Because if you've got a better word, I'd like to know.
But it's, but it's not going to be on a venue. We could talk. I think the best way to do it is the way that behind a paywall and and give not an hour out 15 minutes.
And you don't just edit clips out. We do a 15 minute or 20 minute or half hour max segment on what you will get if you contribute.
No, that's how much contribute otherwise you're not going to get. And it doesn't even have to be quote unquote money, you know, credit because there is no right. You have to give something in return.
Oh, fair enough. Some exchange fair enough. I'm more than happy to explore this because, you know, I have all the mechanisms to do it.
The model has not quite panned out so well for me the past couple of years. And frankly, I even considered, you know, letting this go finally after doing this for 10 years because I feel like I'm kind of banging my head up against the wall, honestly.
But this would be a very interesting way to go forward and do the thing that I want to do here.
The whole key chuck is not the bang your head on the wall. No, I know, you know, unless it's a, you know, unless you're into that kind of thing.
No, no, listen, I'm enjoying it. I'm saying that it's one of these things that just seems to keep happening because I feel like I'm making plenty of effort to inform people about certain things.
Let me just say it this way. It goes down to one thing really. It's, okay, running with the scissors, new bad news travels faster than good news, right?
True. No. The other thing is you're not attracting people that are good at communicating. So in other words, if you have a listener base, I'm saying this publicly because it's just to help people.
If you have like 100 people listening to you and 99 of them can't communicate a thought even in their daily lives, how are they going to communicate what you're saying to someone else?
Yeah, well, I'm saying that it's not, they'll try to explain it to someone else and they'll just be like, I don't know what you're talking about or I'm not getting it.
Well, that's exactly the thing I've come to is that, you know, the majority and look, this is not to offend anyone or to put anybody down.
But the bottom line is the majority of my regular listeners do not seem to communicate with anyone else about the show.
Right. Anything is to attract people that are good at communicating. That would be preferable.
Right. This way the information could be, you know, and again, it's the information that is key. It's not about, you know, it no offense to you.
Right. The only thing about giving information to someone, anyone that helps their lives and they can't spread that, they have to give something.
They have to give something in return. Emphasis on the half, they have to give something in return because that's, you know, fair exchange.
Unless they're on the poverty level, meaning poverty is poor in spirit and then of course you want to help the poor.
Right. But when they get off that poverty level, then to go on from there.
See, that's why the Greeks, I never really pursued it. I've pursued other things in audio design and other forms of engineering that I'm working on.
But when I say audio design, I mean a way of producing sound that has never been heard before.
Like a small speaker that's under your arm that sounds more clear and more base and louder than a, you know, a large floor standing thing, right?
It's just some kind of different physics I'm using.
Oh, and some of your private Newtonian's. Yeah, and some of your guys.
It's not Newtonian. It's a can break the laws of physics, but Newton's been dead for a long time and there is a category called non-Newtonian fluids and non-Newtonian physics. Finally, not quantum garbage.
But the thing is I've never leaned on promoting the Greek speak. I've never done other than a website which is strictly for, you know, it's easier to go to uncommonradio.com and find the email. That's all that's on there.
There's no longer an archive on uncommon radio or anything, right? Nothing. There's just an email. It's just go to uncommon radio. That's where you send an email and that's it.
I mean, I'm not doing. I have other emails and stuff for other purposes, but, but the thing is if you're going to be giving information to those that can't spread it because this is altruistic.
If you know something that can help someone and others and whoever is receiving it is not spreading it to others, then it's kind of like just a single use thing, not getting anything back.
It has to be fair exchange of some sort. And that's why I look at all the models, like people that grow channels and immediately donate.
Here's my Patreon. Here's my Bimea coffee. Here's my membership because in, innately they understand that they should get something back for what they're doing.
And if they just put it out openly, they're probably not going to get anything back. So if you're doing this for a living or trying to doing something worthwhile living,
look, if you're painting houses or sweeping streets or a shoveling coal or shoveling shit or whatever, and it's useful to society or useful to people, you should get something in return.
No, this is true. And the problem with this, you know, a newer paradigm regarding the model of information distribution is that for the most part, there must be like a free level to it.
And then something behind a paywall, something that is, you know, for that exchange.
Of course. And it should be good. I've sometimes people email me things that are behind a paywall, they're remembering, like, what do you think of this?
And I'm like, I'm not, it hasn't very little value. Here's the whole thing.
I found that other than looking up, you know, how to change a water pump on YouTube, you know, it's very helpful because you've actually, if you've never changed a water pump on like a 2000 Dodge Caravan 3.0, for example,
it's good to watch your video, what to expect, right? At least you get something out of that. But the majority of what's on YouTube is just taking up your time. It's a dummy load. You know, do you want to just kill two hours or whatever?
So, oh no, the most useful stuff I've found on YouTube, honestly, is like, look, this is how you use your software. This is how you, you think your computer faster without downloading cleaning programs.
Yeah, stuff like that. Or even, you know, look, your computer has a problem. Here's how you might be able to address it.
Right. Stuff like that. Very practical.
Do you like it? Yeah. All DIY stuff. Yeah.
Yeah. But, yeah, but the thing is, there's something called medical advice and legal advice and all this other stuff. You know, when you study the laws on that, it's only those, you know, there's plenty of people in, quote unquote, prison for practicing law of all license or medical,
some of our license, right? And they've been tricked into that because the actual laws and codes are, if you've been licensed and lost your license or haven't renewed it, that those are the only people to be charged with those crimes.
But there's plenty of people that have been peddling, let's say, what's called legal information, especially in the Patriot community or with medical stuff that have gotten in trouble. They don't understand how that works.
So that the, and it's always misconstrued. And also, if you're speaking anything political, it's always going to be pro this or anti that, right?
If you're speaking about, let's say, what the holy rites of the world, they're going to think you're pro religion or anti-religion or the brand you as one religion, or I'm not religious, right?
So there's, so I think the category of putting everything under history, right? So if you want to speak about how to basically fix the human body, put it under medical history, or legal history, or whatever, right?
Because when you're watching a YouTube to get something out of it on how to fix your computer, that's historical because it was done prior to you watching it, right?
So everything is in history, even look, in order for something to happen, it must already exist because things that don't exist just don't come into existence and happen.
It already exists. You just haven't gotten there yet, right?
So everything is in history. That's why I said, when you, when you understand in the past prophecy, it's history of the future.
We write history of the past. Well, we don't really have any real history.
Right. But the what's coming is already happened, but not within our vantage point. Right, right? And you know, the thing is, look, I've already seen advice. Don't put this on Patreon or anything.
No, I don't think it needs to be anywhere like that. No, no, no, hold on, those things are necessity. Those things need to be in place because that's how society works. Like, for example, if you go to the stove and want to buy something, they expect you.
Through tradition to go to the cash register is something I pointed out was with someone at Walmart, right? Right.
And I'm looking, I said, look, I said, is that the self checkout, right? Waiting there to get some soaps and things like that.
And I said, look around the walls and I was like, huh? Why? I said, look around all this. Look, this is the exit. This is the entrance. This is where the customer services.
These are the counters. Look, look at the walls. Look, if you see any big signs that you must come to checkout first and quote unquote, pay for it before you leave. It doesn't say that anywhere.
You know why? Because everything's already been paid for. But customarily, you have to go to the cashier or the self checkout and process a card or get put some paper in the machine. And then you can get a receipt and walk out. Right.
Customary. No, where does it say in these big stores or even small stores that you have to stop at the cash register and do some kind of transaction before you leave? It's customary, isn't it?
Well, yes, do it. I mean try try to try to violate the customs. See what happens. I've seen a lot of people just walk right out. No problem. See, I've seen that too. And I wonder about it because I've also seen the other way too. You know, it's already prepaid by the way.
I know you choose your it's not stealing, but I'm not saying you should do that because the good customs, right, will require otherwise.
Here's the whole point in this. These customs should be avoided when they're totally unlawful, which most of them are.
But it comes to you come to a point where it's not avoidable anymore, right? Like in other words, you have to drink your own pee to save your life if you're stuck in a room somewhere for days and days, right?
Well, see, but here's the thing, right? I feel as though I must personally exchange something for value. If I receive something for value, right? Yeah.
So I feel as though it is an obligation of mine to not simply walk out with any regardless of what it is. I'm supposedly entitled to or not. Right.
How about that kind of perspective? I mean, is that not a problem? Here's the thing.
This is planet earth, right? So bars. I know it's very simple. Yes. The saving grace of the educational system is this.
Everything they're telling you about anything. Just reverse it and the reverse is true. That's how close. That's how accurate it is. In other words, right?
So even though, like, for example, all college degrees or a BS degree, right? You know that if they tell you what's this, the exact opposite is true. So they're very reliable that way.
It's not like a mixed bag. Right? No, it's not like your news or real pet. Look, if they tell you there's a pandemic, there is no pandemic. Right?
Not like the other terrorism. There is no terrorist. But your news media doesn't quite function like that. And not like the education system because they mix things together. It's not a one to one reversal.
I have it. Well, here's the thing. I found that the main. Well, you're talking about mainstream media is so bizarre in its thought pattern, which we didn't get into the filtering, by the way, in the coding. No, we didn't.
Yeah, that it's it's very coded. Maybe I'll jump into that real quick. Okay, sure. We can go over time a little bit if you know how does that be have sentinels, right? They watch what's going on. And like let's say you were security at a football game or a big public event.
You're watching the event. You might enjoy it, but you're also watching the crowd and someone who's well seasoned in security will know will notice things that potentially could become hazardous to the group. Right?
You know, I know that this is absolutely true because you're well well. Well, you and I have had plenty of private conversations. You know I worked in security. Right.
So you're watching the crowd very careful, even though there's a band playing on stage or whatever, right? And this is without all forms of security. So you're watching say, Oh, you see this right here. This is going to might turn into something we need to focus.
I'm watching packages. I'm watching things that are left on the floor. I'm watching all kinds of stuff that nobody's looking at when I'm working here. Yes, good.
Right. So imagine you have a way to label the status of the group and you do it through the language. So for example, let's use the biblical text or any religious text, by the way, works with every religion.
But let's use the Western biblical one.
They've changed everything around the perception of it so much that it's again, almost polar opposite, whatever you read, it's the opposite of what people think.
So you put out this Jesus character, J-E-S-U-S, right? Well, first of all, anyone who's got half a brain knows it's not an English document is written in Hebrew. So be Yahshua.
And the sixth book is the book of Joshua. Please call it Joshua with a J. Why didn't they call him Joshua's name was Joshua. Something's wrong.
It's really fishy to call him J-E-S-U-S. So when you put your security out there to watch the crowds, if everyone is using the J-E-S-U-S, that means they all fell for it and you're fine.
You don't have to hide anything. You don't have to redact anything. You don't have to propagandaize anything, right?
They already used it while using the code. They already read to that code which again involves the letter J which wasn't even in. Right, but let's say for go that and it's used as Joshua now and said, "Well, the why it's a J." That's fine too, but why not call him Joshua? Why they turn it to J-E-S? It's so distorted to make it so an eight-year-old with a mild awareness of the history of it. We'll see it.
Now here's another example. You have to pay for that. No. They got everyone saying, "How much did you pay for that?" Oh, I paid for this. Okay. No, there is no pay. You cannot pay. What you do is you settle. You settle. You do not pay. You satisfy or you settle. Did you settle that with them? Right, did you settle on that? Right? Okay. There is no pay.
There is no pay. So if they got everyone saying, "That's paid or I'm going to pay or you paid or you have to pay the security." Right? You know the security is is another thing, but let's say they're watching societies.
Oh yeah, these are all idiots here. They're fine. They're all subdued. Well, the term and insecurity literally when you're dealing with transactional things is to settle up. Right? That is not paying. You cannot pay. You settle with, that's why you have legal tenders. You cannot pay with legal tenders.
Or legal tenders to satisfy. Right? So even when we're examining loss prevention and leakage and things like this, these are all terms, by the way, used in you know, very short. Yeah, it has been settled. Right? Because legal say has no legal bearing. Right?
So it's funny. We someone once wrote a letter to an attorney and we mentioned a bunch of things and I said, "If you don't understand anything, if you do have problems understanding or difficult understanding what's in this document, you should consult a lawyer."
This is writing to an attorney because you know what I mean? It's kind of like a double and it's kind of like saying to a psychiatrist anyone who wants to see a psychiatrist should have their head examined, right?
But so all of these terms that are put out there that are completely non-sex-sensical in the context of late things work are coded messages for the security crew, security, what do you call them? Crew, security team, whatever.
That is watching to write in their log at the end of the day, are we having, did everything go smoothly? Right? Or are we having problems that we have to take care of? Right.
So when you have people in the religious circles using J.S. U.S. or G.O.D. Oh yeah, these people are totally, they don't know anything. Right.
When they have to say that they have to pay or they have debt, right? They don't know anything. They're totally fine. Right? You see? The medical goes the same way. Right? The blood, some people say, "Look, I went to the doctor and said, "Hold on. Before you tell me what he said, did he strap a cuff on you and tell you you have blood pressure?"
He says, "Yeah, he did. That's a quack. That's a total quack, which is standard, by the way. Standard is, can quackery become a standard?" Here.
Rat feces in food is monitored, Rat feces at food processing locations is monitored by the FDA. Okay? Right.
How much Rat feces is allowable at the location? Now, long time ago, they found that all the hot dog manufacturers not only had Rat feces at their food processing locations, but it was some of it also getting into the food.
They can't shut down all the hot dog manufacturers in Mary. There'll be a revolution. Right?
There's also an allowable level of... So they allow it? This is disturbing, too, by the way, just a quick point. There's an allowable level of human flesh in your hot dog also.
Well, if you...
If you've been eating pork since the 70s, let's say, I've been a whole old, you are definitely...
Let's say, you have human... In other words, there is no processed pork on the market that does not show human DNA. Put it that way. Let's go that way.
Let's make it to the extreme at this point. There's human DNA. In other words, you're eating pork, you're eating people, but it's usually in the ground-up version. That's very well-known, and it's left about just like chemtrails are left about.
So if you research chemtrails, it's all conspiracy theories, but if you put in a stratospheric aerosol injection, you'll find all the patents and all the groups that are doing it and all that.
You can find a lawsuit from what is in 1971 regarding chemtrails being created over the state of New Jersey, because it was creating too many artificial clouds.
And therefore, it's a stratospheric aerosol injection.
So, you know what I say, no pork on my fork, and there's a reason for it. Because it's so similar to human flesh that there are people that...
You know what a prank is, right? That's another part of the Greek speak, the pranking element. It's all about pranks.
The worst thing I've ever been hearing since I learned how the money system works is they're going to war for money. No, there is no money. That's nothing to do with that.
They're going to war because you want to go to war. You know, people do.
Well, that becomes terribly twisted. That is a discussion for, I think, a separate presentation even.
Okay, let's just a bit of deal and I appreciate you having me on because it's like a memory of things we've done that were done very well.
Well, I always enjoy this because quite frankly, every time, again, the little tagline I put on the website, right, revelation to conversation is meaningful to me.
Every time I have a conversation with someone who is, you know, in a different frame of mind, which is always a guarantee, right? Nobody's in exactly the same frame of mind that I am.
You know, here I go using all kinds of sloppy, ham-handed phrases, right?
I like doing this with you occasionally gets them upset and then he goes on a tear about something I just said that is really badly worded.
And we wind up discussing etymology and we wind up discussing the actual roots of things as opposed to, you know, the general convention, the conveyance that they tell you about.
For actual reserve banking, sure you've heard about that elsewhere. I mean, I love the presentation in that movie, a zeitgeist about it, you know. I'm sure you've seen that.
Yeah, but they look what they do in two hours was zeitgeist. We could do in 15 minutes and you'll get more out of it.
See, that's the thing is that a whole lot of this stuff that we have done and is now not available as it was.
Well, look, we can go on and on and on, but I recently, past year or two, been doing some private Skype conversations with someone that's important to me because, you know, I studied the ancient hybrach text and this person is from Israel.
And the reason they're important to me is when I bring up some ancient hybrach text, I asked them if you read this, if a modern day Hebrew speaker read this, would it be understood?
Are they still using in the, you know, in my litmus? This is yeah, or sometimes we'll see that word stop being used anymore, right?
You know, if you're reading bail wolf, it's old English, right?
So, so I'm trying to figure it so that person, but I said, how do you find out about Greek speak? And he says, well, years ago, I used to go to the office, which is Starbucks, you meet up with some local people, right? And they have coffee or walks of life.
And this person works in physical therapy and there would be an attorney there next firefighter or whatever. He just saw kinds of people.
Well, he didn't know about Greek speak and this attorney, a lawyer goes to him and says, listen, you got to hear this guy the Greek and I listened to him for, in 50, he did a 15 minute explanation on how the money system works.
I've never heard it explained so simply before I use it all the time. Really? So it was an attorney that heard this, that enjoyed it and conveyed it to someone who I consider a friend now.
Is that interesting? You just never know who is going to find out and, you know, use it or whatever, you know?
Well, see, that's the funny thing about lawyers and attorneys and, you know, people go, well, they must know the law and this and that. Actually, what they know how to do is tell a story.
Yeah, well, the attorney is not a lawyer because you can give, here's a proof of that.
Well, that's why I separate you. You can give attorneys and lawyers. You can give power of attorney. A attorney just means they represent you can sign for you.
Like, for example, I can give you power of attorney over the car, the house, the bank, whatever you can make me your attorney.
So to speak, I practice them all. No, attorney, right? In other words, an attorney is power of attorneys. It's all by, a lawyer is knowledgeable in the law and a friend of the court.
Attorney is just representing an incompetent or someone who is not available because they're incompetent, right?
Or even in the case of, say, a medical issue, if you give someone the power to make medical decisions for you when you've been put into surgery or whatever, they are technically your.
And there is no, the medical industry, there are no doctors, by the way, medical doctors are medical technicians. They're not really doctors.
And they are part of the legal system. I've witnessed this more than a dozen times in my life where I've asked certain doctors, why are they prescribing this with that when it's obvious as well.
And why don't we just do this herbal tincture instead, which is where it was garnered from with no side effects is, well, legally, I can't tell you that.
Well, legally, wait a second. You know, legally, what do you mean legally? I thought you're, you know, not this is about health and medicine.
So it's really the attorneys that are running every, well, the attorneys are the trustees for the bankruptcy, right?
So, and well, everything's bankrupted, you know. But people don't understand that all of your institutions are running on emergency status.
So, like every year they sign in every few years, the state of emergency, right? Politically, you can look it up. It's in the federal register.
No, that's all true. And of course, we have also covered that as well.
And I look forward to this. If you're very serious about revisiting this and doing the short term, I'm already seeing some interest. Some people would really love to hear some of these things again.
Also, an expansion of information because some years ago, again, about eight, according to, you know, that Gregorian thing, that calendar, about eight years ago, you and I are talking about things that were going to happen in about 10 years.
So it's right right right on her. And some things are happening that we discussed. In fact, if you go back to the medical discussion, I got to tell you that there's a pretty stark description from the Greek about,
theoretically, I said these things about viruses, they're going to use, they're going to bio-terrorism. In other words, that the powers that be or what you consider, the authorities are going to terrorize you with that.
Right. I've said it. That was very clear about that long time ago. No, you were.
You were. Indeed, I have carried with me ever after the challenge to many people. Okay, do me a favor. If there is something that exists, that's called a virus.
It does. It's just like litter. It's just like litter on the street. No, I understand. But what I have asked people to do is show me a photograph. You must admit, if something exists, you can photograph it.
Yes, or no. Well, in the other thing with the shots and the injections, I've been looking at that, always touting an NIH document, 900 pages long.
Can't find it now, by the way, I have it on a dead computer. Basically, it's 982 pages or something. You read the introduction and asks about the efficacy of, in, you know, immune boosting stuff, you know, basically vaccines.
And you go to the conclusion, 981 pages, and they basically say it's inconclusive. Why, what are you going to read in between? Right? But when you read it in between, this is what you find out.
Recently, I was out about recently a year ago. There was like a little thing set up to do the, you know, the shot. And someone was speaking and everyone frowned and said, "Oh, you're one of those anti-vaxxer nut jobs, right?"
Well, I walked up forward and I said, "Well, look, are you taking into account the blood type and body weight of who's going to be getting the shot?"
And they also have to take in consideration if they're male, female, and their race as well. Are you taking those things in considered? Because all the studies, that's how they do it.
When you get a shot, they have to know your blood type, body weight, male, female, right? Yeah. Black, white, or Asian. Because if you speak to an anesthesiologist,
it's very determinative there, regarding... And by the way, yeah.
Yes, Asia, here's the funny thing. Most anesthesiologists have no concept as to why anesthesia works, actually.
Oh, yeah, but here's the interesting thing. There is a 90-pound white girl with red hair and freckles needs an appendectomy.
Right.
And there's a 300-pound black guy that needs an appendectomy.
Okay, the amount of anesthetic that you have to give the 90-pound white girl with red hair and freckles will kill the 300-pound black guy.
So there is such a thing called medical racism, just like you won't find pro-Zak in Asia.
Because in places like Korea, Northern China, if you take pro-Zak, you die.
Yeah, it doesn't. Yeah, it doesn't. It's not... It's totally illegal there because...
Yeah, it literally just...
Yeah, so there is medical racism. So anyway, all the studies about things that are injected and all these immune, whatever,
if they're not taking a great consideration, all these things that we just... It's a one-size-fits-all hoax.
Well, it's funny. I forgot about that when recently there was a discussion about a K-pop star who was sentenced for a felony in Korea
because they had one of these SSRIs in their possession.
Now, I guess that their ancestry not entirely Korean. So this again changes things. I mean, even...
Well, blood disease is a cool reasonemia, sickle cell anemia.
They're the same thing. All these other genetic traits, we are... We're all the same, really, but we have variations.
But there are variations, but those variations that are related are related for a reason.
And the thing is that K-pop star got in all this trouble for having something that would be commonly in somebody's pocket here
in the United States. Sure, sure. But this is... And a pharma. In other words, it was a typical pharmaceutical here, but lethal on there.
Right, exactly. And you brought a K-pop star anemia. I bring that up all the time, too.
Anyway, look, I'm gonna close this out now. And I look forward to having more discussions with you in the future.
I certainly want to have another one publicly, for sure, maybe to announce formally what it is that you did propose to me privately.
And then mention here on air, because I think we could do one of those things that I think is extremely worthwhile,
which is informing people about the world around them, even if it is just that world that is within five feet of their reach from where the base of their body is.
Right? I think that that is extremely affected because... And useful. No dummy load-free.
Dummy load-free, which is interesting. Of course, I present sometimes opposition and commentary, but like you said, it's an Abbott and Costello on occasion, but if we condense it a bit, I think it's got to be...
It's got to be. You've got to show both sides and what's great about both sides are on the same bird anyway, you know?
Oh, there you go. The left and the right wing, it's still part of the bird. Up and down, inside out, left and out, all hot and cold, yeah.
For better or worse, that's what it is. And so uncommon radio still exists, but uncommon radio...
Just an email site. In other words, you go there and you just find the email and I'm very easy to access.
Fair enough, and we're gonna access you a bit, and hopefully, yeah, we'll be able to really put out some useful...
See, that's the best part, is the useful stuff, like you and I both agreed about YouTube. It is so great when you get a hold of a piece of information you need, and they show it to you on a video there, right? DIY, how do you do that?
YouTube University, man. YouTube University, not so bad, and quite honestly, again, a lot better than the PS you might get elsewhere.
So, we're closing this one out. Again, thank you, Greek. I always appreciate the Greek speed. Even if it takes me a little while to absorb it, and fully understand it, and I'm not even saying that I always do.
So, there you go. But we'll get there. Anyways, the Ocele Effect is done for tonight. No matter who you are, where you are, when you are, because most of you catch this further on down the stream.
By a podcast, I appreciate you, and I am Emilio Ocele, all of you are a GD Effect. Good night.
[Music]