You know how that rolls.
[Music]
Get ready, get ready for the end of your silly attacks.
On the big span of the challenge, Chaco Shelley,
and it's been known for many years,
applying the UK research and specializing in the intelligence
and the involvement in multiple assassination,
propaganda, and other global criminal operations
in the 20th and 21st century.
Your listeners are strange, fortunate to have you.
And now I'm now most integrated in all of me.
[Music]
Chaco Shelley!
[Applause]
November 30, 2018, allegedly,
according to that thing we call a calendar,
and this indeed is the Ocele Effect broadcast live from the facility
of Ocele.com, but also,
heard in a variety of other places.
And who knows progress with Apple just a bit?
We might actually get back in the iTunes store.
I'm not holding my breaths with those people over there,
but anyway, it is, it is Fryer's Day,
according to the Pope's work schedule.
But, you know, the fact that I noted that it was November
and that it's allegedly the 30th day,
and it's allegedly November,
and it is that thing we call a calendar,
seems completely appropriate to bring on a long time individual
who used to do a show with, called Ocele in the Greek,
a long time individual involved with these broadcasts
on this network and other places where I've been,
and I am extremely happy to welcome the Greek tonight.
Because, you know, after all, he shows up,
unlike Jefferson Morley, who did not bother to show up last night.
Anyway, here's the deal.
I told you what the date is, according to that thing we call a calendar,
but Greek held me out.
What day is it actually?
Well, I'm not showing up, I'm sonnicking up.
That's true.
There's no show here, and I don't know,
what day, well, we're already into the 10th month, you know?
And we used to, I heard you say, you know, we used to do a show.
How about we news to do a show?
But anyway, as new versus used.
But here's the interesting part.
This is an intercalary year.
Look it up, it's a big word for most people, intercalary.
But the first week of the 10th month is over.
Look, November, November means nine.
December, desi means 10.
Right?
September 10 means seven, octopuses, right?
So means eight.
So, live enough people.
You know, you've got three strikes, you're out, you're back on the,
you're back on the next inning because you're, you're struck out, three strikes, you're out.
Anybody ever talk about four strikes?
Four strikes you've done.
You're not coming back on the next inning.
That's why you got the four months that are listed in almost proper order,
even though they're still arbitrary.
You ever notice multiple choice question and answer tests or four, four questions, not three?
Right?
You ever notice you got a thumb in four opposing members, right?
You lose the thumb, you lose the rest.
But anyway, use of most of them.
So the thing is, no, the four strikes you're out, principle, doesn't mean you're coming back.
And this is always being put in front of everyone.
And then you're going to come back the way you are, the way you've been doing businesses usual.
You know, I noticed on the bumper you had, you know, what, criminal corruption?
These criminals are a corrupture, whatever.
They can't do, Jack, they can't do, like, stew knots without the people backing them up.
So who's the real criminal?
You wonder who the real criminal is?
Use of mirrors.
No matter, fact, use two mirrors.
Anyway.
Well, that is the beauty of it.
Some people come down on me a little hard for criticizing the leader, you know?
But the fact is that it just so happens that is the representative that does represent.
Well, the thing is, I'm always speaking on a basic scriptural term.
Like, for example, in a certain book of wisdom, it's as never cursed the leader of a people.
But you know what?
You don't know who is leading you.
Isn't that?
I assure you that.
100%.
Let's say 150% for the other 50% that you don't know about.
So because you're under what's called an administration, hey, you want to have a little fun?
We used to knew we knew us to do a show versus use, you know, new versus used.
Okay.
Go to Adam online.
Maybe I should drop this on on on what I'll do is I'm going to copy the link.
And I'm going to drop it in the let's see with my open on the other computer.
I'm going to drop the link on the O'Coli chat.
Which we do have a live chat room for the people listening.
We do have a live chat room at O'Coli.com, which goes along with all the shows.
And yep, you're putting a link in there.
I still think you're politically minded to some extent, which leads back to what's called federal government to some extent.
I want you to click on that link.
I just dropped on the O'Coli chat.
And you Chuck, I want you to just read the first 10 words or so for the definition of federal.
Just the first seven or eight words, maybe 10 words.
Sure. Now to do that, I'm going to take my mic out of the stand because no, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's because it has like 70% more punch.
I don't know why when somebody else reads it.
Well, would you like to write it with the secular meaning or would you like to start with the top?
Well, top federal to an adjective.
Go ahead, 1640s.
Go ahead.
Gotcha.
So, that's the second adjective.
1640s as a theological term, parentheses in reference to, quote, "covenants" and quote, between God and man and parentheses from--
Okay, stop.
Hmm, stop.
Well, if the secular took precedent, why wouldn't they start off the meaning with the secular, right?
Obviously, because the spiritual-- this trumps the secular meaning.
The secular meaning, secular, whenever you see the word secular, just replace it with the word dumbed down or dumbed up.
That's all that means.
So, on anything placed first in a body of written work is usually the most important key information.
For instance, if you look at a news story in a typical newspaper the way they used to print them,
what did they teach us in basic journalism?
You have to put the who, what, when, where, why, and how in that very first paragraph, you lead with the essentials of the information first.
Don't you?
I'd say so.
Go ahead.
What's interesting about this is let's go back to the Sarnix we did a few years ago.
Has it been that long?
Yes.
How many times have I said that your law comes from your God and all these countries have patron or matron deities?
And no one is addressing them because if you start addressing them, then you might try to figure out what's the root to the problem or the root to the solution or whatever you want to call a root cause of something.
How many times have we gone over that?
It's all a spiritual back thing.
So here you go.
That's why your patriotic, what does patros mean?
Latin and Greek means father.
Right.
Right?
So anyway, I think we've gone over how patriots, you know when you're, hang around with some patriots and you know what you're going to get?
You're going to get the, it doesn't matter what country.
You're going to get the language of stupidity, ignorance, hate, war, greed, you ever noticed that?
You're going to go, why?
Hey.
Yeah, these guys are, they don't like us, right?
Because we're this country, there's your hate.
War, oh yeah, we kicked these guys in the ass and we got to watch out because these guys want to kick it, right?
Ignorance, do they know anything about what even the definition of the terms that they're using are or their history?
No.
Well, this leads me to an interesting question in my own mind, which by the way I have some listener questions as well I want to get to before we're done here tonight.
But in my own mind, you know, considering that you brought it up, nationalism is one of these things that is being discussed quite frequently in a lot of circles right now.
And it seems to me as though people don't understand the meaning of the word nation to begin with.
And they don't understand the concept which is being placed in front of them, although they are continuing to argue over it.
What are your thoughts on nation and nationalism?
Well, let's fast forward without skipping it, but skipping it in a sense.
There's a guy called Daniel Estelin, E-S-T-U-L-I-N. He wrote the popular book, not the first book on the Bilderbergers.
I'm not endorsing him, he's very censored, but he's got, he makes some really good points.
What you see on the world political scene now doesn't matter what country. You have two basic factions that are based on the credit-based economy.
One is the conservative nationalism where economy, which is where you, each country had, protects its own economy.
Then you have the globalist liberal banking economy, which the whole world should just be under one economy, right?
So for example, the Trumps, the Putins, the former leaders in the Middle East,
these guys were all national, the old conservative, where you have terraffing and all this to protect nationalism.
Then you have the Clintons, the Soros, the leaders of Germany and France today, the political leaders.
Those are all the globalist groups that want to put everything under one umbrella, right?
So this is what's going on behind the scenes.
I like what he says, Trump is not a man, he's a project.
He needs to be examined like a dinosaur. He put him under a microscope and he sniff from a problem, look at him real close,
and you'll see that there's no such thing as Donald Trump. There's no such thing as Hillary Clinton. There's no such thing as George Soros.
There's an ideology behind all these political people and that Trumps the personality and character of the person, right?
So in other words, when I'm trying to say, it doesn't matter who's in power, it's what ideology they have.
You see, he's like the headhunter analogy, I've given that before, you run into a headhunter and he shows up with a bag of five shrunken heads and he says, "Hey, does a bother you've got five shrunken heads in the bag?"
And he says, "Hey, no one ever asked me that question, as a matter of fact it does bother me, and I have five shrunken heads in the bag."
And he says, "Why? Why? Because my brother, he's got twenty shrunken heads in the bag."
Now it doesn't matter which headhunter you ask, it's the ideology that shrunken heads me, you see what I mean?
So, there's one problem with this and I need to interject here for one very specific reason.
I think it's something that a lot of people fail to understand, including Estlun, who by the way I did offer to have on as a guest and now will not have him as a guest because he has fallen into this very bizarre trap in my mind.
And I'm not saying that I necessarily endorse everything.
Many, many traps, he's very censored.
But at that point, it doesn't mean you can't take one, you could walk into a really bad store or venue and it doesn't mean that everything is bad, you could pick something off the shelf, right?
Oh no, but listen, if you start going to every aisle and you can find five, six things of, you know, let's just say it's a food store, five or six things in every aisle or rotten, I'm leaving the store.
So maybe it's not worth going back ever.
Yeah, so that's the thing with Estlun that I see at this point is that in every aisle he's got a bunch of rotten products and here's why.
Yeah, I agree.
The issue and again, this is not personal. This is a matter of the information he's putting out and I'm objective.
You know, I'm trying to be objective about it personally. I don't even know him.
I've only interacted with him briefly. So I have no personal judgment about this man. I'm just talking about his information.
The logical trap that is eluding people who make these arguments very similar to his as well is that see when you're taking a look at the Trump Avatar so to speak, there is no consistent clearly defined ideology.
That's the interesting part about this. He has shifted over and over again. His history does not prove out that there is a consistency to the ideology.
Well, that's why I said he's censored, but good finish up and I'm going to I'm going to land the point. That's why I'm speaking on this.
Oh, yeah, no, absolutely.
Absolutely.
And that's true.
What we get out of Estlun can be condensed down a less than what, 30 seconds like I said, the rest is a dummy load.
But now I'm going to tell you why. Oh, sure, but but I want to make this point and then allow you to wrap it back around because I think it's going to work perfectly.
Here's what happens. See, and I'll give an example really briefly.
You know, there's certain shifting ideas here. He wants the FBI, which is totally corrupt and you know, undermined and completely ridiculous to go after his political enemies because that's a worthy thing for the corrupt organization to do.
Right there, you have a built-in counter intuitive statement, don't you? Okay, so let's put that aside and just assume that that's something maybe I'm just, you know, picking.
No, no, but it doesn't matter.
But you know, the FDA is even more powerful in the FBI, believe it or not, in firepower as well, believe it or not. People don't know this.
But here's the aspect of it. It doesn't matter which agency, the minute you rely on an agency, you fell for the trap and I'll explain that trap.
No, no, certainly, certainly, but outside of that, what I'm saying is that when you take a look at a consistency, when it comes to an ideology that can be sort of codified into something that could be related from one person to another, the inconsistencies are so numerous.
When it comes to this guy's actions, when it comes to the changing his position, essentially based on his personal position in the equation.
You see that you have somebody who is not part of a standard ideology, he's there to do a job certainly and he is definitely an avatar and I agree with those sorts of points, but for somebody to tell me that this guy is actually in truth a nationalist or someone who is anti-globalist is ridiculous.
And this is the thing about that equation that I think people fail to understand in all of the background noise of what goes on regarding reporting and analysis, which nobody ever really does anyway, but they attempt to or present it as analysis.
The fact is there's such an inconsistency here that it is difficult for anyone to truly articulate what his ideology is and he is not alone.
There is a contingent of individuals whose ideology shifts based on merely what is beneficial to them and that is the only thing that I can find consistent in their ideology in air quotes.
But please continue on with that point.
When I brought up the two, they are not in essence independent ideologies, the globalists and the Nashors, they are just two ways of what I call livestock management or policy, public policies.
Those are two public policies, which neither one is lawful.
If you take it down to the basic aspect, it doesn't matter which, whatever ideology you see in the world today, it is criminal and corrupt.
All of the points that have been brought up especially in mainstream and all turned out media are fraudulent points.
The reason why people are so ignorant is because the all the information that can help them solve what they think is a problem is in the public library.
If you want to hide, let me say it a different way. If you want to hide something, where do you put it? The public library, why? I am not going to answer. That is a rhetorical question.
You know why? Because no one wants to hear you. Everybody looks at each other and they have consensus reality. This crowd says this, I agree with them. And this is the truth, not that crowd over there.
Anyway, quick test for American listeners, it is very, very simple. Don't look it up, don't look at your phone, don't look at a computer. Tell me, where is your local library to where you are standing sitting right now?
The problem with that is the library is again, I am not against the feds or anything, but they are easy to pick up, just like the Pope or the doctors or the lawyers, because they are just so ridiculous.
It doesn't mean they are not dangerous. You could go into a tropical rainforest and see this beautiful, ridiculous bug that will kill you when it is venom. That is what I am talking about. There is still dangerous.
Now here is the interesting point. Everything that is discussed is fraudulent. When anything money wise is fraudulent. Anything health wise is fraudulent.
It is just a false, but it is twisted enough to seem like the truth, to a reality that is accepted by the population. Again, consensus reality.
The actual one speaks a lot on this debt principle. There is no debt. Now if you go to the library, let's say a law librarian, look up everything that is to do with monetary policy and law, you will see there is no money.
It is very clear that you could look at the Senate and congressional hearings, you could look at the history of the mid 1900s regarding central banking, and you will see that the entire thing is a fraud.
Now, meaning it is all based on credit. Now here is the interesting aspect of it. You are ready?
The problem with the Estlil and Trump or anybody discussing politics is this. When you try to hinge what they are discussing on a certain ideology, you will not find one.
The reason why you will not find a solid ideology other than what is a cultural meme, like this culture does things a certain way.
Right, no, I totally understand where you are going with this. You disappear, you have a coughing fit.
Here is why. Because years ago, let's just jump around here. Years ago, a conquest was done by an overt conqueror, and you had what is called overt empire.
The last bit of that was the Ottomans, the Austrian Hungarians, the English. Well, they found out that if you overtly conquer people, there is always going to be some kind of revolution.
Which is also a fraud because you can't have a revolution without substance industry and all that backing you up. And guess what? All that belongs to the empire anyway.
So they just have to change the way the window dressing looks. There are no legitimate revolutions, by the way. They are all frauds also.
That is a long thesis. It is a tall statement to make, but it is a thesis that can be proven if you do anyone who wants to either verify or deny that statement can validate either that it is true, that revolutions are fraudulent.
By looking at the concurrent history after revolution. Even the who wrote a song about it, meet the new boss, same as the old boss.
This thing about overt conquest, it seemed to not end up well, and it also depleted the conquerors.
So the best way was to behind the scenes divvy up the entire planet. Amongst the nobility that always has been in place anyway because they were looked up to anyway.
You see, you get what I mean? These people are not historical figures. Some of them are, by the way. And they were always looked up to anyway.
So they put the ball in their court as owners of the entire planet divided by various districts or whatever you want to call it. That is why when you look into several old institutions like not the UN or the League of Nations, they have ever heard of the Interpolimentary Union or Interpolimentary Council.
It is from the 1870s and it basically runs all of the governments of the world and it is the biggest most powerful group that no one has ever heard of. Look it up.
It is the Interpolimentary Union or Interpolimentary Council. And the American Congress and Senate and presidents says we are not a member on it, but when they have their meetings they have them in the meeting in absentia anyway.
So basically all of the world is owned by this old nobility and they have administrators because remember the thing is not to upset the apple cart.
So what they do is they look at like a part of the Middle East and they say, okay, these guys right here they like to live like this.
So we will let them live like that and we are going to, but we are going to, through many years and what we call policy and our administrators are governments, you know, they are all puppets in their government, the princes, kings, presidents, ministers, monarchs, whatever.
We are going to have them do, you know, using psychological tricks that we know have worked for thousands of years on the people like Higali and dialectics and things like that, right?
So, you know, they look at Russia, they do the same thing. Actually Soviet Union broke away from it during the Soviet times and to prove that the Stalin and Lenin took the Soviet Union off of the Pope's work schedule, are you familiar with that?
You can still find even the wind up toy they changed. Actually you could find the money bait. They had ten hour clocks and you know, ten hour, ten day weeks, you know, they got off the Pope's work schedule.
By the way, anybody on the Pope's work schedule is part of this empire, the world empire. So anyway, make a long story short here. You are being owned. That is why in any country you don't have money.
Now if you are a slave on a plantation, do you need money or is the plantation owner supposed to provide the for you, right?
Now on the other hand, if you have a plantation big enough, let's say over 10,000 people, it's possible they could have their little subgroup and have their little pieces of paper that they use as money amongst themselves, right?
That's exactly what's going on. So, but the thing is you can't let the people know that they are in this condition as being owned. That's why if you look at any deed anywhere in the world that you own property, it says you hold it in joint tenancy. What's a tenant?
You know, I was specifically discussing this with somebody off air just last night. Exactly this point.
It doesn't matter. Yeah, it's true. So the whole world, you know, who is it? This is a prison planet. That's right. It is. Like for example, if you wanted to make a logo of the earth, take a vision of the earth, visible, you know, image of it and put a chain around it.
And that's the logo of the earth. Like for example, when you look at the United Nations logo, you could bring it up yourself. Most people look at that and they're so brainwashed, they say, "Oh yeah, that's just the earth with the lines of latitude on it going around the right?" And then there's all of branches around. No, not at all.
If you look at all of branches, they don't, all of leaves don't look like that at all. Those are shafts of wheat, 100% image of what wheat looks like. What is wheat symbolizes food? And the world is not in the lines of latitude and longitude. Those are not lines of latitude or longitude. Those lines in the UN logo are the lines that you see inside of a sniper scope.
It's right in front of you. This is not like something I'm bringing, you know, this is not like Jordan Maxwell who, you know, crap. This is, this is stuff that you, anyone can see, you know what I mean?
So what they're doing is they're, they're weaponizing food to control you at this point. Anyway, why did we, why did we even bring that up? It's, it sounds conspiratorial, which it's, it's really not. It's really a syndicate.
Basically you're being owned. There's nowhere to go right now where, whatever, right? But the problem is the masses that are ignorant are so big that they could roll over and crush you. Like if you know anyone who's on, who, who, who's a rancher with like very large cattle.
Well, they say what happens to the cattle? They feed them. They could slaughter them, bring them to market or whatever. But if things get out of control, those cattle can stand peed and crush the rancher and his family and kill them off, right? Very easily.
You see what's going on? So you have the masses literally, you know, if you even from a scientific point of view, he said he got rolled over by something that had great mass to it. You expect them, you know, no, it doesn't sound too good, right?
So it doesn't, these people that rule the planet that put administrators in front that you see. Now it's very easy to prove this is true by what they're, by what they're saying and what they're not saying. Like for example, you have blatant acts of heinous acts like, as you might know, the JFK assassination.
If the US really had true enemies, how come those other countries intelligence agencies didn't come out who expose the plot? Wouldn't that be more effective than dropping bombs in all the city because it would completely discredit the government with no surviving with almost zero survivability?
How many countries have come out and said how 9/11 has been done or the fake moon landings, right? I'm not saying they didn't go to the moon, but I'm saying would definitely what they showed on TV was a fake.
Now here's the other aspect, discrediting a government to the point where it's in complete humility renders it into a zero survivability mode where if you were to drop bombs on the country, that doesn't render zero survivability mode because they could go underground and displace themselves somewhat.
You see, so how come there are no enemies because you're already all unified? It's even less, it's even we said join Tennessee, imagine apartment building where all these tenants hate each other.
Ultimately, you can't go blow up the next guy's apartment because you're living in the same building, you see? You're going to be doing harm to yourself.
So you'll see how Putin covers for Trump and Trump covers for Putin and Hitler covered for whatever and this guy covered. They all cover for each other because they're all, you see?
See like World War One was fought over money and World War Two was fought over fake money. And World War Two there were no winners or losers, they just stopped fighting.
People don't know this, but you could look up the history.
Don't forget about what's in the papers because if you read what's in the papers, you're going to think you're going to put the whole story together and I don't know, was Kennedy shot from the book to Pository Window by 19 Arabs with box cutters or which one was?
I mean, they could morph the story into that people will believe it, right? So you can't look at the newspapers. Like for example, look at what they call the stock market crash. What are they? What's the popular story that people were so upset they lost their money that they jumped out the window on Wall Street, right?
No, which which stock market crash?
Well, the big one is one, let's say the one in 29, the biggest one was in the 1800s, by the way, and there was subsequent ones every every 10 to 17 years.
But what they tell people is that that's not true. Anyone could do a little bit of research in New York Times still has articles where the National Guard had to be brought in because people who had their money invested with stockbrokers were going into the offices and throwing the stockbrokers out of the window.
Big difference. Yeah, that's a slightly different action than somebody deciding to take their own life because yeah, that's retribution versus depression. There's a bit of a difference there. Yeah, I know.
If you read the ancient rites, whether they're romantic scriptural, you know, deific or whatever, man is always shown as being a prisoner, be a slave or three a hostage.
That needs to be freed, released or ransomed.
You know, it is possible to simultaneously be all three.
But the pants pick, you know, what, you know, what he was a filmer when you, you know, it's like when someone wants to beat you up and they get you tied up and you got to pick what you want to be beaten with, you know, a whip, a wrench or a stick, right? Pick one.
Right. If you really want, you know, you pick the worst one. The ones could do the most damage to make the guy look bad, but it doesn't matter in the end because you're the one that's going to get hit.
So, so the point is right now, humanity, you know, if you jump around and because, you know, when you talk about like where do people come from and all that, even the evolutionism and the sciences religion, it has its own God, albeit secret, not too much because you can see it, you know, if you look into their language.
Do you ever consider that we were created by gods and they say, you know, in almost every case they're anthropomorphic?
But did you ever stop and consider that maybe we are their form of art?
Just like you have an artist draw a portrait with a landscape, you know, or make a sculpture that when that gods are dealing with us, they're dealing with us as if we're artwork.
Well, and what does an artist do but reshape something that already exists into something that's a little more aesthetically pleasing, which seems to me to be the story that's told in various, various scriptures.
Well, you could call it an account, right? Because it doesn't change.
That's fine. It doesn't change, by the way. I mean, that particular very narrow aspect seems to be universally, you know, from Babylon to what you call the Bible pretty much is there.
Well, the point I'm trying to make is if everything is not the way it's supposed to be or should be, according to even the gods, there's no explanation for it being this way other than we are nothing more than an art form.
Nothing different really than if you went to a carnival and you walked into the haunted house this time, but you know, but you just stayed in the haunted house or the house, you know, the fun, whatever, right?
So the point here is this, you got to be patient. The only problem is patient doesn't matter because you could probably going to die before you run out of patience because your life is too short.
Well, the other thing is obviously, you know, look, you could look at filmmaking as an art form and the people that say that this entire planet is pretty much a live action reality show might not pass you far off the mark because, hey, listen, if you were trying to make a TV show to entertain yourself, planet Earth could be fascinating enough for somebody who can keep a camera in every single place on the planet.
Why not?
Yeah, but, you know, the film is a good thing because you know, you got that's a good analogy. I always use the word in the credits part, right?
Yeah, right. You know, you know, in other words, time ended. So you're in the credits part in the credits unique because you show everything, especially, you give actually credit, you know, you can't an accounting of everything and everyone that was part of making the film.
And you also get to see certain aspects that weren't shown in the film and it's all done in a very short, compressed time. And you know, the other part that never discussed about credits is that's the part of the film when no one tells you to sit down and shut up on their running.
Right? That's why how many times like let's say all the people coming out right now, let's say on the internet saying that the Catholic church is nothing but a bunch of pedophiles, you know, you couldn't do that 30 years ago.
Well, as a matter of fact, today, even today in Europe, if you're on a public radio like terrestrial based radio TV and you say something against the Catholic church, a $5,000 fine.
I don't know if you know that you know, Italy, Spain, you know, these big Catholic cuts actually Spain is even more Catholic than Italy. But, but anyway, I do have no personally know that's true in Italy.
Yeah, yeah, you know, so the thing here is is what's interesting is that you got to be patient. You know, I will look, what's the best you can do with what you've got is really what anyone can say, right?
You know, forget about like, I don't have enough. Yes, you do because if you know anyone that you speak to that's not point blank. The first thing they say to you is do you have any money or anything to eat?
If you meet anyone and that's not the first thing they tell you they have enough to make do, right? Because it's easy to run into people such as you can see, can I have some money, can I have something to eat?
It's the first thing they tell you, well, that person doesn't have a lot to do it. You know, a lot, a lot to do anything with. They're on the most subsistent base.
But most people, you know, whatever, if you got food clothing and shelter on a consistent basis, can you make the best of that?
Right? And, uh, I mean, speaking, yeah, I mean, the best of it, but now as to what the best of the situation is in comparison to what it could be quality wise or two different things, but you can make the best of that situation sure.
Right. And also you could seek out quality and demand it. Now, the problem is that most people still think that they have what's called a profession, career or general interest of things they do or y'all, or a job, you know, a different
difference between a job and a job, right? Anyway, okay. There's no application when you get a job. Okay. So either way, so when these people that have specialized professions or a narrow type of, you know, living in terms of their interest, when they want to learn something about medicine, they go to these, the medical society and try to look something up or it might be brought into their house obtrusively when they're watching TV or, you know, whatever, in newspaper.
When they want to learn something about the scientific world, they go to the scientific community. When they want to learn something about law, they go to the legal community. Okay. All those groups that I just mentioned are complete frauds. Right? So what chance does this and that people don't know this? And most of them will murmur under their breath. Yeah, we know, but that what are you going to do is just what everybody accepts. No, that's not what I'm talking about. Like when I say people are morons and stupid, a lot of people say, well, yes, because, you know, they've been misled. This is the whole lit name. Like, no, no, no.
I'm just taking a cross section of word is right now. That's a fact. How they got there is not important. The fact is they are, right? It's like if someone comes in with a really bad bruise, it doesn't matter if you fell off a roof, a fell off a bicycle down the stairs, you got to treat the bruise, right?
So what I'm saying right now, it doesn't matter that they've been propagandized. Are there slaves and they're being owned by an ability that no one knows who they are, let's say, whatever the matter is, take a cross section right there, stupid. Okay. What are you going to do to fix it right this second? The next five minutes, the next hour, the next day, the next week.
That's what I like to speak on. That's why I always say no one is noticing even, you know, they want to talk about these far fetched subjects or even if it's something distantly far away. Why don't you start mastering what's five feet around you first?
And then 20 feet around you, right? Or whatever. You know, like people say, well, I'm in a relationship. I'm not happy. What makes you think if you get someone else, you're going to be happy because you're just projecting on them, right?
So, you know, the whole thing is that is the essence of the point, right? I mean, what are the Marines say? Who are, right? Everybody thinks that's something that they do. What is it? You know what that means, right?
Herod understood, received acknowledged. It's an acronym, right?
Okay, so that point, you know, when I go out and I speak, it's a hurrah thing. Did you hear it? Did you understand it? Did you receive the acknowledge? Like, let's go down the line. Let's go back with the legal thing.
Like you see a lot of that legal stuff in this. I don't know if you know, still the news with the FBI Mueller and Department of Justice. None of those people in the Supreme Court FBI Department just know any law at all, at all, right?
People think it has something to do with law. They're attorneys. I think we've gone over this before. If you're an attorney and you study the law and try to apply it, you'll be a used car salesman in a week. That's not allowed.
Anybody could do research and read all the laws that they have on all the acts. That looks pretty scary and it sounds like it applies to you. But go look at the definition of the terms and then tell me in the definition section of the law does it apply to you?
And the answer is a big fat what? And oh, it doesn't apply to you. Only very rare cases, right? You want to go to the medical community.
Come on, blood pressure, viruses. Come on. Are you joking? Right? So, you know, I've spoken a lot. You know, money people. I've walked into rooms with doctors, senior medical people and I started to give me a chance to speak.
And they either lead, they get a blank stare and they leave and I say, why do you leave that? I can't acknowledge what you're saying. They're not challenging. You're saying what I'm saying is wrong. They just say I can't acknowledge it.
Right? The other ones, they get sarcastic and they're like, oh, I didn't know I was going to learn that much today. Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Or any other ones will say, well, where did you get your degree? I can't listen to you unless you tell me where you got your degree.
Right? Okay. So, you know, like, for example, recently I had a discussion with someone who was a senior medical person and they gave me a very sarcastic thing. I said, you know, it's about doing research on diabetes. And I said, well, okay, it's called diabetes. But really, you know, what's going on is, you know, as people, what they call diabetes is very low on potassium in their bodies. The other, that's right.
It was like, well, you know, potassium is produced in the body by sodium intake, you know, and exertion like in a warm, you know, in a warm environment exercising, right? Like a construction worker working in the summer that takes salt, good high quality salt, their body will develop the potassium.
And they're not diabetic, right? You see? So people who are diabetic are not ex being active in a warm environment with high quality salt.
You get this iodide salt, which is poison, right? So I challenge anyone out there if you've been measured as being diabetic or whatever. And by the way, that production of potassium, but, you know, you take potassium, it just piss it right out. Your body will produce some of it, but it needs to be produced by the body, right?
And if you don't understand this, you could look up a man named Kervron, KERVRAN, who showed how the body produces these elements. But anyway, anyone who does feel like there have been diagnosed with diabetes or has it, not to the point where your limbs are rotting off, that's too late. Then it's like the car has to go to the junkyard. But if you have a high quality salt intake, like sea salt, you could put it a little pinch and some water and warm water.
And if you're going to have to be very active in a warm environment, you will notice that condition will go away in two weeks, three weeks, three months maybe, right?
So what does that have to do with blood sugar? Can you tell me? Did I mention blood sugar one moment?
Doesn't sound like I heard blood sugar or sugar in that equation.
Can you tell you when it gets cold, you get a virus or a thing? Wait a second, doesn't that render? Shouldn't you be getting sick in the summer because that's when those pathogens are more active?
Is the logic because it's cold out, you're going to receive a contagion of a microbiological thing?
Isn't that unintuitive when you compare that to the notion that it should render all refrigeration useless? Hey, let's put our food out in the heat because there's no bacteria.
We don't need refrigerators anymore. No.
No one's to put, why don't you put the two together? Okay, and if you look up virology, it's under the toxicology and the mitochondria that they're calling viruses are produced in the liver.
So when they take a blood test and say you have viruses in your blood, those viruses came out of your own liver. So how is somebody going to catch a virus from somebody else?
Well, I guess through direct blood exchange maybe. No, but well, then it's yeah, then it's maybe, yeah, right? But that's a different condition altogether again.
Well, if not too many people go around just sharing blood, they might share dirty needles and whatever, but then they don't get it from sitting on it. Anyway, I'm saying, you know, sex is another factor.
But still, yeah, that's different. So anyway, you know, here's the thing, there is advance, there is advance medicine. You know, you know, how to grow a limb back? This is stuff you guys are never going to get.
Very, it's a simple technology, although be it elaborate because you can't use the type of stuff, you know, technology, electricity and equipment that you have. But if you understand, you know, like let's say, for example, you know, a curly infotography is, you know, it has, you take a picture and it shows like the aura around your body. It's usually blue or rainbow colored, right?
You know, if you put your hand on one of these plates and move your hand off it and you process that plate, it shows like the image of your hand with this light coming out of your fingers and you can imagine that curly infotography, right?
Okay, so what I've seen it actually done with with with trees where you can cut a limb off a tree, you use the photography to take a picture of that tree and the limb is still in a picture.
That's right. So when people lose a limb, you've heard of like Phantom, you know, the guy lost his leg in the war and he's still it's still itchy because this is a great Phantom.
The main Phantom, this is a little bit mature all the time.
So what you do is you put the person if they still have that image, which they usually will up to 18 years later, if there, you know, happens at a young age, you put their body on one of these things that exposes the field and then where the field is, you just fill it in with material.
I'm not talking about filling it in with wood and plaster, I'm talking about biological material from the person's own body and you grow the limb back.
This is being done with teeth and things like that, but anyway, why get into this? Like for example, people talk about free energy machines.
What are you talking about? Joseph Newman already has a motor that if you make it big enough and run it fast enough, it will put out up to eight times more energy than you put into it.
There's no mystery there. Right, there's no mystery that you have to eat seasonally.
There's no mystery that the health of a society is based on a separation of its wastewater and it's drinking water. There's no mystery in that.
Right, it's all water-based. There's no mystery that if you look at what they call your legal society, there's no mystery that it's based on attorneys and it's based on a goddess religion and it has no basis in right or wrong or law.
It's basically livestock control. Right, now if you want, you notice that it bring up the religious because I think we've hammered those idiots long enough.
All of the religions are satanic, the mainstream religions. What you call satanism is not satanism at all.
That satanism is a revival of ancient gods, albeit they're very hostile and very nasty. Right, but what you call satan or the adversary is the one that controls all of your mainstream religions.
Right, that's why for example when you look at a Catholic exorcism of a demon, when the exorcist goes in, is he being defensive or offensive?
Right, an exorcism is an offensive act. You see, it's a fight. It's not because, you know, so anyway, and all of the memes and the cultures and all the stuff that have been in front of you, that J.S., U.S., hanging on across wearing a diaper or the guy wearing the guy with the blue skin or the other guy that didn't know how to read and write, yet whatever.
You know, I mean, you got all these really, none of that stuff is based on any of the stuff that you find memorialized in the texts or history, none of it.
So where does it come from? It comes from the ability to manipulate your imagination in large groups with a leader.
Well, so in essence, it's very, very, very, very simple. Be patient. The only thing is your life will run out before your patients does.
Let's say we were having this conversation a hundred years ago or 200 years ago. You're still only going to live most people 70, 80 years, 100 years or whatever. You're not going to see the end of this society.
Even though you were patient to the last, your last breath, your life cut, you see, interfered with your patients, didn't it?
But if you had an unlimited lifespan and you decide to just be patient, you will see the end of this society quite readily.
So fortunately, you're unfortunately your life will end before your patients runs out if you have that much time, you see?
So that's basically the reality. That's real talk. There's no reason to get into anything specifically other than things that people can apply to themselves immediately.
A lot of people are walking around with a big question where you see the fought bubble in cartoons.
I would see those, forget about light bulb because there's no light bulb in their head. There's no light. It's just question marks, right? Which is basically a dog's tail, right?
So you look at that and you see, well, monkey tails do that too. Most likely the monkey, but you know, I don't like comparing humans to the monkeys because what the hell is the monkey is due to deserve such an insult.
But anyway, so what I would say is start mastering what's around you first, like the karate kid wax on wax off, right?
You know, this thing that you're on, this Pope's work schedule thing, yeah, that's okay, you could read it, you put it in its proper place. It's a work schedule, right?
It doesn't mean you have to ignore it or you obviously we showed up because of it, right? You message me if you're a Friday, you didn't, right?
I said, I know what you're talking about, it's a normal creature, right? Start realizing the thing, you know, it's getting cold outside.
You're going to get sick. Why am I getting sick? You got to wash your hands because the bacteria really, when it's called out?
Okay. So these are some special bugs that get, right? Okay. So anyway, you see my point here? It goes on and on and on and on and on.
Why don't you start looking at it immediately around you and making that better, right?
But the thing is most people, I've seen a lot of, over the years, like I remember going to the library and seeing stuff before Jordan, that was up before Jordan Maxwell, I talked about the stuff that he did, right?
Or the stuff that was the other guy, William Cooper, you know, there's someone recently sent me a video of a guy on Johnny Carson in 1964, I was talking about stuff that would blow people away today in the alternative media, right?
So all this stuff has been around, but the thing is it sounds like a, they cover such a broad idea and what can they use? What is this person saying that I could use right now?
And the answer is nothing. It just sounds good. It might make good conversation, but you don't, you still scratching your head and you're wondering why you feel so shitty.
Not because you are shitty, but you feel shitty.
Right? Well, you know, that's why I always try to say, okay, what is it that we can do with this information usually at the end of a show I say, you know, what can we very simple?
Well, the thing is, well, I've reached my saturation point. I've been speaking long enough. I think eventually warning, just warning people about what's coming is really the main thing.
They're not the two censored, you know, there's a few people that get it. I mean, for example, I get a lot of people, maybe a handful of people and also people in the medical industry, for example, that they bring case studies to me on Skype.
And we're not talking, we're talking about people with 30 years in surgery, right? And I said, why don't you do this because the body is in a vacuum, this ABC or D and they come back to say it worked.
Very simple, like if you just accept that the body is under a slight biological vacuum, when you have a cut or a wound, whether it's your body or a car tire or bicycle tire, that's not you're not going anywhere because you're going to, you need that pressure, right?
Right? So when you get a cutter or wound, you look at it as a leak in a bicycle tire, you wrap that really tight. You want to put a patch on it, not like a bandaid, but it's very tight patch that, you know, stops any, usually if it's on a limb or a tire, you know,
if it's on a limb or something, you're going to have to release it every time minutes because your finger turns blue or whatever, right? Or numb.
And any cut, no matter how serious it is, unless you're flesh is starting to get jello, you're going to have extremely rapid healing. Even burns.
I've had searing burns on the fingers two weeks ago and I did that in two days later. It didn't even look like anything three days later. It was no sign of it at all.
If it was anybody else but the creams on the stupid, whatever, you know, concept they have, I'd say I'd have scars on my hands, right?
Okay, so in that case, if you understand the bodies under a biological vacuum, you can work with it, right?
If you understand, you know, just wrap it tight, very simple, but it's, that sounds oversimplified, but you know, there's more to it, you know, with disease and all this other things.
How about the treatment of water? You don't need this fancy water stuff. You got these idiots going talking about water for three hours, none of them on the internet. There's hundreds of guys got miracle water and all this and shows up with a plastic bottle and holds it up in the light at room temperature. You got to laugh at that.
You know, I don't care if you get in your water from a ditch. Keep it in the dark, keep it as cold as you can and watch what happens.
You do that right away, right? If you're religious in anything, start reading the book that they say, "Now what, you may not like it, that's all right."
But what they say, catch them on their hypocrisy, right? And then watch what kind of assholes you're dealing with because every time you bring up a contradicting point to what they're doing, they say, "That's your interpretation, get out of here, right?"
Same with attorneys.
How come in the definitions over here it says you're an attorney, you can only represent government officials or corporations or trust. What am I doing in your justice core? What are you doing here?
I got nothing to do with you. Where's the, you see, there's so many ways you could do, right? How am I supposed to pay taxes when there's no money, jerk off?
But if you're endorsing it, "Ah, yeah, if you all money to the heroin dealer, you're not going to get out of it."
You know why? Because he also owns the police. Right? You can't go to the police for it. Right? So anyway, and by the way, you know, police are right, when the banking districts, this fake money was established, they put policing.
Because the sheriff is the lawful. Sheriff can also deliver commercial paper, but sheriff was part of the English franchise, the police were put in, wherever you see police, that means that you're lost to that area belongs to the banks.
When the banks have enough mortgages, I think up to 30% they create a police district because they own 30% of the town, they got to protect their investment.
Well, they have to put out policy enforcers which, you know, sounds vaguely like police.
They're not legal law enforcement, they call them leos, which stands for law, but they don't know any law, they think they do.
Nobody, you could go right now to the, I don't know who the head attorney general is, he doesn't know any law at all.
Goes sit down with the Supreme Court people, they don't know any law. We're going to recite policy in history, they don't know law.
That's why I just said, they're policy enforcers. But what's policy for their owners?
Now people, I've been in, like for example, they say, how do they get away with it? Very, very simple, very, very easy.
You know, I mean, how do they get away with anything? Look Manhattan, they blew up three nuclear, 150 kiloton nukes underground, you're not above ground, but underground, and they got away with it.
I mean, they killed a shot Kennedy out of the book depository window, they had a clean line of shot with the magic bully, right?
So I mean, come on, they got away with that too, right? So anyway, when they show you pictures from man on the moon, they show the moon is a little tiny blue ball.
You know, you know, the moon is, the moon is like, what, less than a quarter the size of the earth, right?
So if you're standing on the moon, earth looking at the moon, it looks this size, now if you're standing on the moon, look at the earth, it should look four or five times bigger, right?
It's the same thing. Like if you're standing on a motorcycle looking at a school bus, you expect it to look, you know, if you're on a school bus looking at a motorcycle, 10 feet away, it looks small.
Now you get on the motorcycle, look on the school bus, over some of the school bus shrunk to the size of the motorcycle. Does that make sense? No.
Anyway, this is an off-fire way you are though. The same distance. No, if it's the same distance, I get your point, but what I'm saying is that, you know, you could see the earth is about the size of a marble depending on how far away you are.
Right, but the, so what happened was when they went to the moon, they pushed the moon out on other a million miles from a quarter of a million to a million to make the earth seem that small. It's so ridiculous, it doesn't make any sense.
It's right in front of you and the astronauts who weren't even pressurized. So anyway, you don't need pressure. But anyway, the point is, you know, the reason I brought up the moon thing, somebody sent me some emails on moon conspiracy stuff for two hours, I don't need to watch that.
This is your thing right here, nobody. Look at the picture of the earth. It's got a fill, at least when you're looking at the horizon of the moon, it's got to be one tenth of the entire horizon, which is pretty big.
And no one's picking up. It's like, what the hell are you people on? I'll tell you what they're on. The moon conspiracy people, the JFK people, the debt money people, the history, but they, they all part of a group, somebody put out some information.
I like what he's saying. Let's, you know, I look at this guy saying you like it. No, you don't. Okay, get out of here. You like it. Come on. You like it. Come on. It's like everybody's going to the bar. No one's paying any attention because you're all drunk.
Yeah, but see, math math seems to work. Let me ask you this question based on what you said. And then I want to add in a listener question, because when we look at the sun in the sky, this thing does not appear to be very large. It's kind of a tiny thing in the sky.
How far is the sun from the earth and how far is the moon from the earth? According to their math, well, that's about eight million, eight million for the sun roughly, and it's roughly a quarter of a million or less for the moon.
Right, but the sun is what 300 times the size of the earth? No, no, no. If you go to, if you do a comparison of the size of the sun and the size of the earth right now on paper, it's very easy to see why this and the distance, why the sun looks like it is from earth.
Oh, I'm just make a triangle to colon, right? No, I understand. I'm asking. I'm actually asking about the math here because that's what I'm saying is that based on the fact that the, that the moon is so much smaller,
but it's still closer. Does the math work or not? That's my question. I've got a math that mother nature doesn't have a, she's not a crack war with a calculator as Ken Wheeler says this is a simple, simple measuring, you know, like, for example, in high-end geometry, you do what's called geometric construction.
You use a stick and a compass to make all your geometric shapes. You don't measure the triangle with a ruler, right? You, you do a construction, right? You make an arc, you make a circle, you generate geometric forms using what's called construction.
If you, imagine right now, if you will, a ball, the size of a basketball, a little or a little bit bigger, that's the earth. And across the street, you're going to put a softball, right?
You can imagine that in the distance, you know, maybe 30, 40 feet. When you're looking at the softball from the earth's perspective, it looks like a softball. When you're on the softball looking at the, from the moon to the earth, is it going to look like a softball or is it going to look a basketball?
It looks like a basketball, no matter how far away you go, especially if, no, no matter how far away you go, if you haven't changed the distance, the perspective is the same.
If I take a camera, I understand that. And I take a picture of the moon, that same camera, if the distance between the moon and the earth hasn't changed, if I'm standing on the moon, taking a picture of the earth, it's a hell of a lot bigger, a lot bigger.
Well, of course it should be, but what I'm saying is, is not in the photos.
If you make a basketball the size of a house, but then you back it up so many miles away.
And when I change anything in miles away, everything is the same. No, okay, let me try and explain what it is that I'm asking you in comparison.
I think we're going off on a tangent that's not necessary.
No, I understand, I understand. How about this? Everybody do your homework.
No, definitely.
Definitely. I would like to see people do that because I'd love to see what the mathematical equations say regarding this because it's a fascinating thing.
It's used trigonometry to do it just like a surveyor. You use sine, cosine, trigonometric functions. If you look at surveyors with a theatillate.
Well, both of your eyes do trigonometric calculations at all times. That's what we call depth perception, okay?
So the math, that's the only math. You don't even need that math.
Well, I'm just saying that this is how can do it.
But this is one of those things that you have to consider is that the size in the visual field that is being observed of something which is very large. You back it away.
It becomes very small, even if it is a lot larger than you or anything you're standing on.
There is no bad, but the distance is a given. This is not variable.
Here's the point. No one's picking up on that fraud. In other words, the point is if they're on the moon photographing the earth, it's got to look a lot bigger, at least five times bigger than they're showing it. No one's pointing that out.
This is a basic geometric astronomical fact. You don't even have to use the planets. You could use any object.
Now, if you, if the moon all of a sudden landed on the moon and took the photograph, the moon was all of a sudden five to eight times further away, that picture is legitimate, but that didn't happen.
Anyway, the point is no one is paying attention to the simple stuff.
Oh, I was just looking. I was just trying to get a handle on the quantities involved here because I'm wondering if that's accurate what you're saying in general. That's all.
But look, if nothing, if all things stay the same, the perception stays the same also.
No, I understand that.
If you're standing on a big object, looking at a small object, and everything is the same, the distance between the objects and the objects themselves, when you're standing on the big object, the little object will look small.
Now, move your body over to the place where the little object is when you look over to the big object, the big object is not going to look small like the small object. It's going to look big like the big object.
It's like when you're on a cruise liner looking at someone in a row boat, they're tied together, they're not moving.
You can see, you look down, you see as a freaking big cruise liner, look at the little row boat, now you go in the row boat and you look at the cruise liner, all of a sudden the cruise liner is as small as the row boat?
No, sorry, that doesn't work.
No, I understand what you're saying.
That's what they're showing.
There is a variance, but there's a variance here where when you see the moon as we apparently see it in the sky, you have different conditions than what you're looking at for the earth.
There is a different visual condition, I mean, listen, in enough darkness, you don't see the moon anyway.
It doesn't matter, you wouldn't see the Empire State Building in a blackout.
It is large, it is still there, but you're not able to necessarily perceive it, and there is more than one condition besides just the juxtaposition between the two objects.
That's all I'm stating.
So I'd like to see what this looks like when it's entirely studied to see if that perspective is way off or if there is an explanation for it.
That's all I'm asking, you know, that's all I was entering into there.
And I think it's a pair of questions.
But anyway, we'll put it aside.
I do have a listener asking if you have any sort of thoughts about things like yoga and stuff like that.
I also have some interesting questions which relate to religious aspects. I would call them scriptural things.
And a few other random bits that people either written in advance or entered into the chat room as we're speaking.
Sure, the scriptural part is difficult because 99% of the questions are hinged upon very bad versions.
So if I'm asking you, for example, a question on the magic bullet, right, you don't want to address that because there was no magic bullet, right?
Well, no, see I'll see what it is they're referencing and explain to them what it is from the real evidence as opposed to the...
Exactly.
That's why scriptural questions are opening up a thing because someone will ask me what about this and say we'll go back to an internal interview or see what it really says.
And I'll consider it the answer is right there. If you know what came before it because scripture is cumulative.
You can't go, like for example, if you know mathematics, you got from kindergarten all the way up to PhD level math.
When you go to PhD level math, you sit down and you think they're going to start already class what's one plus one?
No, it's cumulative, right?
So, and also if you take kindergartners and put them in a PhD class, you could talk to them for an hour. Anybody got any questions? They'll raise their hand in the year.
What they ask? Yeah, you got any candy?
So, so, so, you know, the thing is you can have to understand this is cumulative, but we'll give it a shot in terms of yoga.
Yoga, the yoga, okay, it's like, that's like what about Tai Chi, Tai Chi Shuang, yoga, there's various other movements, you know, that exists.
This every culture has some kind of a physical therapeutic or physical movement, just like in martial arts, right?
You know, the Europeans have their own style, but it was squashed out, like the Greeks had what's called punkration, which is a Greek fighting like jujitsu, right?
So, to make a long story short, any of these healing arts are fine. The only problem is that they've been dummyed up or dummyed down, right?
So, the basic principle has been removed, so, but the bottom line is you have to judge it from your lawful perspective. Are they telling you to do something that's unlawful?
Right? You know, if you got a yoga instructor that makes sure that everybody, male and female in the class likes to do goddess pose and happy baby most of the time, that's not because he wants to, he's because he's stretching out your, your vaginal and anal muscles because he wants to get into it.
Make a long story short, you got to look at the character of the people that are giving you this information, otherwise you got to discern what's good for, good, good for you.
Take it like we said about Daniel Estolin in the store that's all rotten stuff.
Take what you works for you and go, right? But that means you're going to have to do a little bit of homework on your own before you investigate it.
But are they, are they, all these, let's say yoga, tai chi shwana, are they corrupted? Yeah, yeah. But the thing is, it doesn't mean you can't get a benefit out of it, right?
So, make a, make a long story short on that. I would suggest that anything that's group based, you're going to have to be leary of do a little bit of research on your own and try to find what it's history in terms of, so I hope that helped.
You know, there's a health benefit, but you know, if they start talking about blood pressure and viruses causing diseases, you know where they're at and then you might diminish their importance a little bit more, where I fully so, right?
So, no, absolutely, absolutely. But look, we're actually a little over the time where I usually take a break, so I'm going to do that.
But the Greek is with me here on this particular friars day and I'll try to get to the rest of your questions or see what we can do with them anyway. As we go forward here on the Ocele effect, we will be right back.
Gold, silver, the stock market.
The brilliant author of the war state brings you exclusive reports about the big changes upcoming in the markets.
Perhaps you're invested deeply, perhaps you're not in deep enough, maybe you're thinking about getting started.
Wall Street window dot com, dot com.
Michael Swanson, the brilliant author of the war state, understood these trends professionally for many years and now he gives you the benefit of his knowledge.
Wall Street window dot com.
Go there now.
News, entertainment and more, you will learn something children's Ocele.com.
[Music]
The second hour beginning now at Ocele.com, do appreciate you for tuning in whether it is later on via your final slide of choice, your applicable application, etc, etc.
Who knows maybe we'll be back in the Apple iTunes store shortly but for now glad to have you along and if you're catching this on the live stream also much appreciated there is an interesting conversation going on in the chatroom@ocele.com.
And I do want to thank all of you who participate in one way or another in this show.
Tonight we are talking to the Greek and trans resistor radio will be up next.
That ought to be interesting as well tonight but I got to produce that as soon as I'm done and where did we leave off?
Well a lot of places really yoga yoga none of these things that can help anyone are harmful if they're helpful but the thing is you know what is there a compromise in radio you're being led down right what are you being led down.
But you know giving example is you know anyone could do rudimentary research on what they call this satanic cult and when they abuse children or human sacrifice or whatever the report you get is a gender switch that men wear women's clothing and the women wear men's clothing.
Now how many times have you heard these people are behind the scenes running the world right it's not a joke and it's not a any a mild suggestion it's you know it's pretty true that they belong to these types of cults.
Why wouldn't they in quote unquote and times allow that kind of behavior to their people you heard of lgdp t x q y whatever it's all right now for men to dress like women and women and dress like men and they have rights what do you think that comes from the same these little cold groups that do you know.
You see what I mean there are all of all the stuff that you see that people are fighting over or may want to take lying down or see it as a demise of their society is nothing new it's just stuff that's behind the scenes that's now being put on the public because hey why can't we all be friends right.
Well yeah yeah. So anyway the thing is you know in other words anyone who's researched what quote unquote human sacrifice with these western so tiny cults will see lgdp t whatever as being an extension of that in the public doesn't matter if the public knows it or not right just like how many people in the public use a celebratory birthday cake how many of them know what that represents or even cares right how many right we talked about what do cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common.
Oh I think anyway very first discussion actually was yeah very first public discussion anyway was definitely that you know it doesn't matter I mean it doesn't matter that you're going to do you're going to say anything or promote the you know you know the real meaning of what it isn't get people to stop no because it's not in your position to do it you're going to get rolled over very easily right.
What you do though what's happening because of the spiritual side that controls this when you tell people it doesn't matter if they like it or agree with it or not what's important is you say to them did you hear what I said did you acknowledge what I said not whether you acknowledge it morally or whatever but did you hear and once the minute they say yes now they are guilty of it.
Do you get my point right the warning shot you know what's the purpose of a warning shot to be heard or not be heard to be heard and if you continue and you get shot and then there's a you know an entire entire let's say inquiry done in the thing they're going to say but he did fire a warning shot.
Well I'm probably going to get something from you but I do believe this is very legitimate this aspect of what we call law anyway this concept of men's ray of where you have to be aware that you are committing a criminal act at some point in order to be culpable for said criminal act that's right.
This is a spiritual concept actually and a legal concept.
It goes throughout the entire universe. Right. Right. Now here's the thing you know like you know what you know the biblical text Leviticus is where you find most of the law and a big chunk of it and why it's the law and the first chapter it goes something like this I paraphrase when you know the law and you see you know so your fellow man transgressing it but he doesn't know the law you can't hold him guilty of it.
But once you tell him the law now he can now the guilt is on him but here's the thing there's a certain point of culpability if you want to live in harmony with him if you even though he doesn't know the law this is an extra part that I'm adding just because he doesn't know the law doesn't mean that there's going to be hell to pay or some you know you might have you know if you have enough people like that that don't know the law and that you can't hold them responsible but you know what's going to happen your crops are going to start failing.
You might have an invasion you might have really bad weather you might get pestilence. This is when the gods are you know but anyway so what I see part of Greek speak is doing is just making it easier for the other side because anybody who hears me is guilty.
It doesn't matter if they like it or not or forget it. One point it's been checked off that these assholes heard it and it doesn't matter if they do anything or not you see.
It's like for example if the quote unquote alien invasion or the gods came to earth right now to clean up the society called the mop up crew right I don't use I don't use terms like the apocalypse or again I use the mop up crew right because I'm not giving a description I'm giving an explanation right.
You can describe it as whatever colloquial term apocalypse or again whatever but that's not the explain they're coming the mop to clean it up right.
I tell people look you know how do you feel about that I'm like fine look if I know they were coming right now.
You had say look hold up fellas come over I'm going to make some sandwiches and coffee so you got all the energy to do the jobs that you need to do.
You know what I mean because it has to be done.
And here's an interesting part I've said it on various sonic events you know what the number one agenda is of the controllers of the world right now how they're going to reduce the earth's population like a tenth of what it is.
Right for the United States you could look this up to plenty of war documents you could look up online by 2030 they want the United States to be only 20% of the population that it is now.
Without even factoring any growth you know so you want to reduce it down to like 20 million people or something right or whatever.
So the only problem with with getting that agenda done is you don't want you want the remaining the ones that remain to go along with you right now if you just come out and kill eight out of ten people in the US.
I don't think the remaining two out of ten are going to want to cooperate.
You have to get them psychologically primed and ready you see what I mean.
It's like the vaccine thing is a good one you know you know the vaccines like the lottery they put out a million vaccines and there's like 30 or 40 really severely tainted ones in the batch.
The control they're not controlled because you get a vaccine you got to sign paperwork they're easy to track so if the everyone takes the million vaccines and you get 70 or 80 people end up in the ICU the next day.
You know they know they know where they got the vaccine and all that they got the numbers and all that and say let's see what the public reaction is to these people dying from the vaccine.
That's why it's called the CDC not the CDP it's it's the Center for Disease Control not the Center for Disease Prevention you notice that there it's a control mechanism which which you see how the vaccine thing works is a psychological thing.
There's no such thing as an immune system that's your first your first prey anyway it's so ridiculous you know check your nurse I stopped being at edifying we used to do the sonic events.
I'd sit there and you'd ask me questions or I'd supply and go on and give all the reasoning I'm done with that is people are too ignorant they don't want to know.
It's not because I know and I'm smarter maybe I'm a little less stupid but the thing is right now those that know we'll see it and those that don't know that want to know we'll hear it and the rest stoo gots buff on glue right.
So I don't know can you do that on Google translate anyway I'm sure that you know so go ahead so anyway this is so simple and so easy to see that it's just freaking ridiculous that's how many times you're going to say set yourself apart from it right.
Well see now this brings up a question for me I'm not going to get to the list of questions probably tonight because there's there's a bunch of them and I think you don't want to answer about the queen of heaven and a few other things.
Yeah I can just shoot them by a real quick queen of heaven is a goddess look look these people can answer their own questions very simple I think we've gone over the biblical meme is very very very simple.
You know you got various creations of mankind it's right there is any historicity right so we think you remember you know shows man being made on the sixth day and they're made man and woman right off the gate and they're set out their job is to populate the world then on the seventh day the gods rest and on the eighth day in the garden of Eden they don't create man they form him out of soil they took from the earth right this is 2000 years later after the other guy.
And then they don't make and when they make this man they don't make man and woman they make one guy and is this job to go out and populate the earth no his job is to stay in the garden mode of the laundry the brushes take the garbage out right maintain the and all of a sudden he's by himself is okay we need to make a woman so we're not going to make a woman like you know we're going to just take a some flesh out of your body and grow a woman out of it very different and then they have let's say a pair of twins whose sons and one kills the other and he isn't put the death for killing him.
He didn't intend to kill him he was just angry at him he didn't know what it took to kill him right because if he intended to kill his brother he had to be put to death right but he didn't intend to kill him.
So anyway he gets sent out away from the garden to the land again and he says well what you know if they find me these people out here find me they're going to want to kill me right well what people what people well the people that were made on the sixth day you see what I'm saying so simple right.
So a lot of people say well there is a rehash of the story of the sixth day when you go into the garden of Eden really I find that the whole book has historicity to it.
If you're reading the first two pages of Genesis that's before the next five or ten pages which is before the next twenty pages this is all historically laid out in a timeline.
So you believe what you want to believe and I'm going to tell you what's in the text all right that's all because no one else is doing it.
I'm not saying no one else but you know since we got the opportunity I can say that right very simple so you got the flood these people are mixing now you got the really original people and you got and things get really really bad because the gods are you know openly interacting with man so they destroy the whole thing but location by location not all at once it's not like the you ever see the Sherwin Williams logo where they cover the earth with paint remember that it's the show of paint going over that's not how it worked but anyway.
When you get to the point they all gathered at one point this is a few hundred years after the flood and some many survived from before and they divide them up as nations and there's supposed to go out and live as different nations with a different patron and matren deity and each patron and matren deity over each nation in the world is supposed to judge and teach the people about the laws of the creator but they didn't want to do that they wanted to stay and babble on and build a temple.
Well that's what pagans do is what the pagans do is they have like an exchange system with their local God they bring an offering to their God because they want something done well that something could be anything right and the God can't resist the offering he comes down just like the genie in the bottle right me get three wishes kind of thing is one way that's but that's not even a gods of the gen it's a formal very low form so the people were trying to do that and like no you know you're supposed to go with these other gods
so okay we're going to just confuse you to the point where you can't come over here and make this giant offering temple and you got a scatter now when they did scatter and they did get a God over them each nation got a God over them those gods didn't do the right thing right it's like a mob with a has the boss and all the couples take a territory but they're operating independent of of the boss how long does that last usually
usually what usually the boss takes out those couples and replaces them with somebody that they can know exactly what's going to that's your history of the biblical text that's why in the end everybody's going to be under the you know the one that's supposed to be in these particular gods are going to be killed just like men you could read about insomnia that's the whole story of scripture so now you got the queen of heaven that queen of heaven is a very predominant figure in the middle east now what happened of course you understand that the druids
are really the remnants of the Babylonian priesthood you know everybody traveled all over the world right so they in the Catholic stuff and all that so the queen of heaven is merely a goddess right over a certain people and did she do the right thing no she's not so
fee up she's not wisdom but she was referenced in the in the text at some point wasn't she oh yeah yeah in Jeremiah is a white you know Jeremiah you know the tells the people look you're going to go to Kinesa because I'm pretty much kill everybody so you know you're going to have to straighten up he's like no what are you talking about you know would you get that he said we got it from
Yahweh's like Yahweh what are you talking about we're going to worshiping the queen of heaven look how for hundreds of you look how we prospered what are you talking about right so anyway you see your life will run out before your
patience does so make a long story even shorter the whole point is this it's it's your caught in between this is like again when the coppers and the boss are having a war don't you think some innocent bystanders are going to get in the way eventually right whether they like it or not
no guarantee it's called collateral damage right and in this case though you're not so innocent with the birthday cakes and the Christmas and the churches and the LGBT and the Pope and whatever federal
crappy got going on you know so innocent listen some of that allegedly non combat and collateral damage in a in a you know a typical
conventional war sensor not innocent either because in some cases they were supporting the you know the the the enemy who is also being
attacked in one way or another so I mean kind of very sensible actually that there is some collateral damage I mean is there
someone fortunate tragedies and involved there too as well well yeah but well here's the thing the gods are not protecting their own people because they're hostile to the people
like the u.s military when you read military documents and they talk about enemies domestic or foreign
the foreign part is the one outside of the border usually known as an alien but the ones that are domestic are the ones within the
border that's you who's not in the military you and until you go in the military now you're not a domestic enemy anyway that's if you understand the
Libra code and the civil war that was set up for that situation what do you think there's a military base unconstitutionally in every state I'm not saying I'm
against it I'm just telling you what's going on what do you need the what do you need the Navy for in Utah you know I mean come on the reason they got
a federal military base is in each state is because if there's an uprising well look look we think I send the police no national guard and then what so you know the thing is no one sees
what and they're like oh thank you for serving who is that journalist he yet something out of faith is a marine retired and he's so tell
he was in the Marines and they say thank you for your service as he wants to punch him in the throat because the whole thing was a fraud it was a waste of time in a fraud right you
ever heard of this guy I'm not a public figure I heard of a few of them if you're talking about a classic sort of example of a guy who
was was very disillusioned you talking about Smetley Butler or are you talking about no no there's a recent guy still around you
still around he does he does he makes years ago he was doing the tour yeah I think as a website and the decimal
alternative stuff I get right into him a few years ago quite a few years ago
oh yeah no there's a radio station I don't read the Marine and he talks about a very subject pot you know whatever is in the
news like everybody else right right they they bring them on as one of these sort of talking head figures every now and then they used to anyway
yes I got to yeah yeah so the whole thing is I mean beyond reality I mean I mean come on look I'm gonna say two things that
I'll discredit Christianity ready Santa Claus in the Easter Bunny come on you don't talk about anything else come on just walk away
walk away you know but look the food is good we have a good time so look that you know it's very the gods know that
and they keep you in that position what do you this leave directly to another question by the way which is a
direct one at you about this particular subject where I'd like you to pick it up uh you are this is exactly
as written you are on planet earth are you not censored as well and if so why are you not more censored
so that you are in line with everybody else we could have that question just answered itself right there
the the the reason censorship was brought up twice what is censorship is deliberate blocking or changing of
information so the people who are its representative doesn't see it so how about unchained you know how about you
change it in reverse right you know look look you know what the cosmic censorship is like if everything is
upside down if you turn anything upside down guess what now it's right side up like Jack Fresco talks about
the upside down world right when a in an old barn when a not whole was knocked out and the light came
across the herd of cows and you looked in the barn the the cattle where everything is upside down
you know the shadow box does that right your eye you know works that way in cameras you know you
you never work with medium format film when you take when you develop the film you look at all the
pictures are upside down because that's how cameras work right well yeah that's why you require two
mirrors in order to well a periscope yeah we'll reverse it again but you know there's many ways to
to look at it I mean the cosmic censorship I think we brought up the the idea that if you want to hide
something you put it in the library right and also even if they find it in the library they're not
going to look to define the language look when you're going to learn another language whether it's your
own or a foreign language you can read the words like if you read Latin script a Roman script you know
the ABC through Z you could read pretty much most of the newspapers in the world right doesn't mean
you understand it because why you lack definition right right now you you let's say you don't speak any
Italian or any Spanish or Portuguese you can read Chuck you could read the Portuguese
newspaper you can read it but you lack the definition of the words right so what's the so why bother
you just making sounds so even if people find the information they lack the definition
of the words that's your another key to look for the censorship look the ancient ritz talk about the
censorship there's various forms of censorship man has picked up on how to use it as well using
groups you know Gustav Lebon you put people in a group everybody who feels comfortable anything
that contradicts the group ideology is no good and they defend it or often become offensive right
right now from in terms of the gods the the ones that are benevolent are going to put a censorship
on you that's going to make what the more you learn and the more you see they don't want to make
you totally miserable so they're also going to show you the stuff that's beautiful that you can do
while you're being patient right I mean what's more pleasurable than a delicious meal
than a comfortable surrounding than a really comfortable bed and having someone that you love
and even physically interacting physical love erotic love a good clothes good shoes good food
right putting things in order even if everything is out of order putting them in order in your own mind
right speaking of putting things in order in your own mind another question which by the way
you're intuitively seemingly answering a bunch of the questions in my estimation that I have here but
one that you didn't is what is the starting point for telling time
same starting point for anything you got what's called law and I'm not talking about the what you're
told is law you better learn what law is law is a set of rules that give explanations of your
environment okay now first of all there is no time you know that but I'm not speaking of it in
the new age or point of view there are only events certain people that are responsible socially
and familiarly and and nationally or whatever you want to say it they want to record these
events right you have history we want to memorialize something right so you're going to have to do
like what you said in the beginning the when why where who and what right and all that so the time is
just the when right so basically what's lawful time keeping well one thing if someone tells you you
got to do something and the only way you could do it is by doing business with him over here which is
rico by the way is not lawful right so if you don't know what date is because you don't have a calendar
or you don't know what time it is because you don't have a clock a mechanical windip toy that don't
sound too lawful does it right so lawful basically anyone can access equally and also you have
here of the concept of reinventing the wheel why that's like saying hey why why are you going
through all this it's been done already and it's been done properly right so historically when does
the day start i'm not going to answer that go look it up historically when does the month start i'm
not going to answer that again that's right now that's a rhetorical question to those that are
willing to learn okay fair enough you know i dare i look i dare anybody go to an astrology this is
i'm not good we don't for for time you know i'm not even asking to trust me you could anybody could
validate this in real time if you're quick with a keyboard go to any college any university in the
world a community college or or ivy league put in astronomy curriculum and i want you to look in
their curriculum and find out astronomical timekeeping and they're going to tell you astronomical
timekeeping is also scientific timekeeping it's very accurate and they'll all say the day starts
a solar noon and the month is what goes with the moon but are being bad are being with done right
they're in their own stuff i got you one other thing here is let's see is there a way to attract
attention from or to seek the favor of benevolent entities well here's the thing that fortunately
the benevolent entities are far more powerful in addition than the malevolent ones right so they already
know it but the thing is if what do you get what do you give someone who already has everything right
if you were to bring an offering right i've had this before we were going to go to this billionaire's
plate you know house there's having an anniversary or a celebration and you you don't want to show up
any hand empty handed so like what do you buy a billionaire as a gift what do you buy him he's got
everything already right well you know you might seek to bring a unique object right unique something
something well how you know but either way you get my point what do you give to someone already
has everything is what well attention hmm right okay
and you know what if you study scriptures of any of any god they tell you how they want to they
want that how they want that attention or what flavor of attention you know and they tell you who
they listen to and who they don't look at there there was this thing on Netflix recently about some
Nordic it's like it's like a comedy drama you know think it takes place 500 years ago with the Vikings
right okay and in every time the scene changes they're like they got to sacrifice somebody to
woden and the guys like how do I get out of it and if I get out of it you know we still have to do
something for Odin or woden you know what are you going to do instead you know I mean this is this is
common I mean you know it's anyway I think I'm the only one of the few people to come out on the
what they call the stupid rectangle and in the beginning for years and years stress the point
that it's all based on what human sacrifice human sacrifice them a level in blood sacrifice
all of the gods require it by the way even the benevolent ones but not from humans because humans
are unclean anyway I'll get over yeah one also asks how do individuals labors fit into that
equation when it comes to I guess offerings to the gods are not labors also offerings to different
gods as well I think that question is also something that he was so but yeah
labor labor could be all the way from a woman in labor right which was defined as the ultimate
sacrifice by the way because I think we've explained that the most precious part of the body is
the genitalia you know for future generations you know no matter let's say you had a health a
society that was perfectly healthy with no genitalia they'll all be gone in 40 years right
so keeping the genitalia intact and functioning assures procreation right
so what's the fruit of the most important part of the body the baby so that's why they did the baby
sacrifices in short I'm just there's actually more reasons that you can get into but in short
that's what all societies have in common even today they still do it that's why there's a million
was eight million children every year missing not to be recovered or and or investigated
in on the planet it's it's probably more in the in the 15 million you know what you know the statistics
are skewed right of course so so anyway what the labors I mean that's too general of a question
how about living your life lawfully right well what does that accomplish how about that
and because actually not that much there's actually a proverbial you know like you know something
that gives a little bit of wisdom will insight in the book of ezekiel you're gonna go through
real quick this will help the person with the labor at the time to at the temple period the
elders there was a had convinced a bunch of people to do sun worship at the temple you know you wake
up in the morning add somebody invite me to do that once I didn't go I said that was so stupid
whereas the sun's coming up you stay right into it without blinking and you get that light and
you bow down to the sun and all that shit right every culture has some form of that so if you're
reading there y'all always says to ezekiel I'm going okay I'm going to send an angel to put a
mark I don't like what's going on and I'm going to put a mark on everybody who's protesting this
action right and everybody else I'm going to kill I'm going to send an angel down and I'm going to
kill all the other ones involved in this right so you ever know if you look if you listen carefully
even though I'm paraphrasing there were people who were living lawful lives that knew about this but
didn't say anything about it right did they get the mark of protection no the ones that saw it were
lawful and complained about it or protested about this happening in other words it's on lawful
or not right according to the previous agreements we have they're the ones that got the mark of protection
you see so and the last thing I have loaded up here is is related to Zacharias Sitchin
oh boy so I can only imagine what it is you're going to say about this but
it's just two levels to everything you anybody asks anyone who knows about Zacharias Sitchin so go
ahead right okay so I'll give both of those levels quickly if I can no problem by by the way I
have one of his books that are signed by him and I heard I was just going to coast to coast a while
back when he died I jumped up in in the morning and I told the wife I said hey you know that that
paperback they want me want to give us two dollars for it's signed by Zacharias Sitchin now it's
probably worth a couple hundred because the fuckers dead anyway good yeah probably probably got
up in value but actually this question is about Zacharias Sitchin's work on Babylon and the
interpretation of what seemed to precede what you what you generally refer to as the biblical text okay
so the okay the stories are a bit different in Zacharias Sitchin's work
regarding what Babylon allegedly preserved in its own language which has not been translated
properly or memorialized for public consumption what do you think that he's work in general all right
his work in general is for public consumption which is what a dummy load now why is it a dummy load
because 99% of the people that refer to the ancient Sumerian Babylonian accadian culture are not
referring to their historicity of that culture but referring to their works like a lot of people say
well Gilgamesh's you know the flood story and the god story and all this other stuff but they fail to
tell the public was unaware Gilgamesh was a commissioned play who was it was a work just like Shakespeare
99% of the stuff that people have access to about that ancient culture were cultural works
like Macbeth or you know or things like that they were not intended to be history even in their times
they were commissioned plays and acts that were to be performed for the king's court
big difference from being a historical record right number one number two what is to just let me
just enter this part into your explanation before you go into the second part what would you say
to contend that possibly the biblical text is simply one of these works as well that has survived
well it's the same one well because it's the only sure commonality i mean listen there's some
commonalities with Gilgamesh and the story yeah just like Shakespeare's Julius Caesar is commonalities
historically not factual some factual things well but it also has the only things with the biblical text
well the only thing about the biblical test is extremely accurate historically and geographically
and archaeologically where the other ones are not I mean right now so remember I said one of the
signs of this period is acknowledgement of the of the works of the creator and at which I
haven't I should have covered a little bit when I gave the quick history of the Bible like for
example right now scientific journals have picked up that there was a a very hot meteorite strike
that turned pottery into glass in the Middle East and the north eastern part of the dead sea and if
you understand that's the little true location of Sodom and Gomorrah not where they tell you it is
all the way at the bottom of the negate there right so they're actually the scientific whatever is
dating and acknowledging the destruction of Sodom right now in their own journals
all right but it's not you know they won't say it's Sodom but anybody who reads the biblical text
actually by description land description it tells you you could see Sodom from the area of Bethel
or Jerusalem where which and it tells you where it was in the Kikar meaning the flat plain that was
at the end of the river right where they tell you Sodom and Gomorrah is with those other idiots
all the way at the bottom of the dead sea where they're finding sulfur and all that other stuff
that's not Sodom and Gomorrah at all so what I'm saying is there's going to be acknowledgement
but the here's the thing the interesting thing about archaeologically identifying and proving out
the biblical text is accuracy is a very slippery slope for the you know the conventional wisdom
or conventional actually tumfulery and stupidity regarding religion and all that other in evolution
and all that other stuff right so but this is not for me to be a apologetic or defend you'll see it
you know and like I said earlier I have no interest in getting into a lot of the details but I will
point them out I'll try to avoid saying I told you so well an interesting thing though is that one
could say that one of these works was created based on historical realities not necessarily
adhering to the entirety of the story but you know you know the old phrase it's based on a true story
sure but the thing about let's go back to Zechariah's it's and and the thing he leaves out so many
points that are critical like for example the biblical talks about a hybrid race right and that
does exist in in both historical and fictional works of the Babylonians and the Sumerians
most the Babylonians came as really as Sumerians and Acadians right they talk about that a mixed
these people that you know they were bragging that they learned directly from the gods and directly
from their hybrids and their leaders were these hybrids right and those are the upkalu
and nobody talks about them they talk about Anunnaki well they know not people that were like 16 feet tall
right well they could be yeah they didn't have to be but yeah usually the upkala were hybrids and
the biblical text speaks of hybrids also but the biblical texts trumps the Sumerian text with its
accuracy and we could we that's a whole other thing that we can get into or I may never get into
in public because for me to do that it's actually a full-time job not a job to do a proper presentation
and I don't think I I don't seem interested I put it this way when you gain a certain amount of
knowledge it is his own reward right oh I understand I'm just you know doing my job or job here
the difference in a job and a job right so but but here's the the interesting aspect of all this
is that generally if you're going to take anything from the past two hours or almost here whatever
generally what the public thinks is right is not right at all it's wrong right and you see
well so what's been put out is explained why because as as I say all the time everything on the
planet seems to be mislabeled because every time I take a look at the meaning of a word and then
take a look at how it's being applied to something it appears as though it generally describes the
opposite of what the thing actually is all right let me let me let me go back to help out maybe if
there are biblical questions this might fill in the blanks and this is this has never been said
and any of the alternative I know of the consult dummy load anyway you know that firsthand by
having guests and stuff on that you know I'm sure you're like I'm not whatever you know
disparaging you or anyone but you know it's like we got to fill two hours this is not a two-hour
fill this is a two-hour you got to sit down with a you stake knife and you're going to hit a lot of
bone and what I mean by that is the aspect that I gave you earlier that mankind was supposed to be
divided into different groups that each have a patron or matron deity which you see now even today
what happened the creator did not take on one of these nations later on he says I'm going to come
down to your level meaning these other gods is lower gods and I'm going to take a nation just
like you just like a father who has all these children playing a game when he goes to play with them he
comes down on their equal footing he doesn't pick one up and throw them across the room because he's
the dad right he he's gentle so he comes down in other words in his will and he grabs a nation which
he created out of Abraham they're known as the Israelites and he's going to take them under and he
says okay I'm going to be like this you see all these other nations have gods now I'll be your
god I'm going to play like they do and so I have my nation also so that's why they're the quote-unquote
chosen people not because the other ones weren't chosen at the time the other ones were chosen to have
each corresponding deity you see right that's why people still are wrestling with the creator and you
hear stupid stuff like the god of the old you better you know believe in the god of the new testament
not the god of the old testament what are you talking about it's the same there is no new world there
is no you know it's like dividing the soot any of any literary work in an ad hominem way to suit your
agenda you can't do that you know that you hear that all the time with the patriots with the
constitution right they they only quote things out of the constitution that suits their agenda right
so anyway so basically in essence also the other reason why you watch
why israel is chosen because there are timepiece these things will happen when you see this happening
the israel over here then the next thing is this that's all it's just like we choose a timepiece it
could be the a stick in the ground with the sun or the mechanical lined up toy right or an hour glass
we can pick a timepiece you see well you know what's strange about that though is that there was
attempts to to found the nation state of israel in various other locations that has been in like
in the oblosskin russia yeah it was that was the first one that was formed in the thirties yeah right
it still exists today but but not i'd not capacity yeah but what's odd to me though is that
that this attempt to found said nation uh didn't seem to have a geographical preference when they
were doing it here i don't talk about this often because it needs to be explained not described you
could say that there's a nation of israel right now by description but i'm telling you it still
hasn't been formed because it's it's what's called secular right now you know the ball the uh the
the accords uh that the Rothschilds formed uh was the balford accord uh in all this right this is a
product of that this is still a private enterprise and i've explained how it will change when it runs
out of prime ministers you've got two or three prime ministers left most likely to i've explained
where that is that you do you remember right this is why i would return to your former judges which are
prime ministers right prime ministers prime judge and then you will be known as a righteous people
meaning as long as israel has a prime minister they're not going to do anything right they're always
going to be hated so you're going to watch i also gave the specifics you know if you read the book
of judges it just lists the book of judges when you get to the 14th judge or 13th judge at samson all
of a sudden this page is in pages dedicated to his story well the samson type judge is coming up
now when you remember in the book of judges you know he interacted very heavily with the philistines
killing a lot of them and there was a lot of intimidation back and forth right as a matter of fact
you heard a fire fox the the browser right well you know what it samson do he took two fire two foxes
he tied their tails together and set the foxes on fire through them into the field anyway somebody
knows what's going on right so anyway so the next prime minister you're going to see uh you know i've
told this people who get out of the west bank if you know anybody's palestinian you live in the west
bank get none of those people well very few are going to survive we're talking about hundreds of
thousands of fairly fifty thousand hundred thousand palestinians killed in the near future by the
israel could you imagine what's going to happen kind of a worldwide outcry is going to happen when
that happens the onslaught you know i'm not really sure uh uh well it's going to be very yes it's
going to be enough to topple the current government that's for sure well they have no problems with
hundreds getting killed you know in retaliation for allegedly who will be killed or things like that so
if killed about well the past 30 years over 10,000 or less than that and they've injured over
100,000 in the past five so now but what i'm saying it's a bloody bloody thing but what's what the
outcome is going to be is the gaza strip expanding all the way up to telev which is the ancient city
of yafa which was their city and they're going to be living in harmony and they're actually going
to fight together as time goes on and all this is going to happen very quickly we're that what i'm
speaking on is is you know within the next seven years within so um well here's a great question
uh because you started talking about israel i knew i knew that was going to do something that doesn't
matter uh they're they're hated and they're supposed to be hated until they're not well well but
here's an interesting thing that was brought up actually in a recent discussion with Jordan Maxwell
on the show uh okay go ahead which uh which is kind of an interesting uh piece of feedback we're
getting here um what about this position of a high judge in israel being called a nasi n a s i
and that's that's the day is them that well that's an extrapolation of what what you called your day
is and which is a mishmash of Babylonian mystic rights mixed in with midsirium rights,
Egyptian rights and some of the samaritan rights well i've been describing that these are the on
another series about how a lot of this has to do with a you know a god of the moon the the god
Saturn well Saturn is crono so Saturn is important because Saturn used to be used as a timepiece by
certain priests because just like we use the celestial bodies you know if you want to know when
it's noon how do you know when it's noon you put a stick in the ground right well you don't really
locate Saturn by putting a stick in the ground and have you ever seen Saturn through a telescope by the way
not the photos they have online or magazines it looks very its position is very different the
the rings don't go left and right they go up and down are you familiar with that reality yes
okay and that has parted something to do with it but make a long story short
Judaism is not approved of biblically you know that right especially if you read in the new testament
it's kind of uh the book of mark when the christ is told to go to the feast of tabernacles which
were one of the ordained feasts you know he says this is not my time this is an evil time this is not my
time in other words you're doing it on the you're not doing it on the right day and what you're doing is
that you see well what's interesting is he also says that the the old law has been abolished through
him too which you know it doesn't you never said that well that's that's what i'm saying that
that's not red it though it sits in there as one of those go read it go read in context again it's not in
there uh okay no no no and when law you have to it's very you have to be very careful when you say
law even today with these patriot idiots they always bring up is that statutory law or common law
you're noticed that i believe the word used is covenant but uh but but i'd have to look at the new
the new covenant new covenant now is about that you know you know what happens after you die in other
words a new covenant now is proven because in order to have a covenant which is you know a you know
basically an attachment right uh the long story made short there were two law forms going on at
the time you had the holocaue which was the protective law form that was taught to the people
to shield them like a hedge so they wouldn't break the law and that
transgress the law and eventually they forgot about the law and they studied and stuck to the what's
called the the hedge laws you know the holocaue which means to hedge you give an example of that
let's say the bible scripture says you shouldn't eat pork and they're like all they're all wondering
how are you going to prevent the people from eating pork well if we outlaw pork in the whole country
then they can eat pork right oh let's do that so now when people saw pork they said oh that's
outlawed in the country they didn't think of the script saying you should need it you see what I mean
so for example if the if the scriptures said be in by let's say six o'clock I'm using a
paraphrase metaphor they make a law saying you have to be in by five o'clock so if you're a little
late you're still before it you see what I mean so then people started looking at these other laws
to protect them from you see and they forgot about it that that's the one that's been done away with
all in other words all the insuliary bullshit stuff that took precedent over the real deal
fair enough so as we get into the last uh and by the way that's very clear when you study
with if you go if you read a short thing out of context it's not clear at all what I just said
well I just do remember reading that that that interesting area where it seemed to me to say that
the old law had been was was yeah that's why it's not so I'll go back over it and
well that's gonna take you well you have to do it when you go back over you're gonna have to be
cumulative because believe it or not early on in the biblical text it gives you hints about what
the law is about and how it's supposed to be administered and what will happen to it so now
you got to go all the way back to kindergarten but anyway well you know sometimes you need a
refresher to be able to fully grasp where you're going you know not necessarily here's another
suggestion for you and anyone else go find where you thought you read it and read it in context that
means go back and you know the setting you know go back you know read the whole you know aspect of it
few verses before and a few verses after like for example give it is a really good example you know
when you talk about specific end time stuff with Christians they say well no one knows the day or
the hour right you ever hear that they say that no one knows the day or the hour it's in the Bible look
are you familiar with that concept well yeah I'm familiar with that concept but also anytime I go to
read something that's exerted from something else I always go to the to the before and after because
usually if you're cherry picking you're forgetting about the rest of the branch you know and
you're forgetting about the roots and you're forgetting about the fields so all the Christians
like to say no one knows the day or the hour I know we got a few minutes but if you actually go
to verses before the question to the Christ was in a sudden say J.J.
yes you as or the question to the Christ was when will the sun the moon and all these things
as heavenly bodies pass away and cease to exist is the answer is the question and he says no one
knows the day or the hour when the sun and the moon all that will cease to exist but if you fall asleep
you'll miss my coming right you see the context answer the question wasn't about when the mop-up
crew comes the question was when do the heavenly bodies start to decay or fall away you see
okay you know years ago when I was younger and dumb raised to have a long and short list of all
these biblical misconceptions as a matter of fact they made the error of previous sonic events
always debunking a cliche whether it was secular or religious or biblical and it was just a waste of
time so anyway no fair enough and like I was saying you know we're getting toward the very last
couple of minutes here is there is anything you want to sort of say in closing to this two hour
sonic event that occurred here interesting one I actually found this one loaded with more
information than then we usually get to actually so I'm real happy with it and I hope everybody
who is listening has also gained something once again or possibly regained something yeah let me
I want to do a plug by the way someone is doing a just Greek speak dot com website it's not me I
can't say I'm not going to say I endorse it or don't endorse it just someone that's a like what I've
been saying and they've actually did a pretty polished website it's called that just Greek speak
dot com if you just do just Greek speak dot com it'll show up he asked me to do a plug if I speak
tonight because he thinks he has some articles and quotes and things that are ready for public
consumption I personally have the uncommon radio dot com which I have nothing on there there's no
reason like I said earlier all I have is the email to get in touch with me and that's that's what I
wanted to maybe get in the last minute or so and that's you know pretty much it and you know my
model has been why bother and the thing is you know how they say don't think too much but the thing
is how about just thinking a little bit right yeah I mean sometimes you heard oh you think too much right
well how about just think of what does that mean don't think at all right so
right and actually I'll provide links to both of those websites uh
within the podcast to make sure it's there for anybody who says oh well now I got to go back
and listen to it now I'll put it there for you no problem um the individual that is doing the
just Greek speak thing I was looking at that actually and uh notice that he's got a list of uh the past
sonic events with you and I on there as well because I was actually looking for an image online
and I came across it so uh oh yeah okay good yeah we did so I get still good things here we did some
good work together was a good good way to like spill the beans a little bit and here's the thing I
mean if you don't pat your own back who's gonna pat your back at least you say you did it first
no the stuff that we discussing you hear on greek speak not because I'm saying you're not gonna
hear anywhere else and it hasn't been said anywhere else period um and it doesn't matter where it goes
or if you do anything with it you know what matters though it's been said it's been done
well there you go because after all uh what I asked the question very early on in our
discussions why is it that you're bothering to say this because you don't seem to want a
bother to say this and then it's my bother well the thing is look if you're asked you have you know
you you do it unless you have a good reason not to do it right well fair enough but also you said uh
that at that time anyway the reason why I'm saying these things is because they're not being said
so I yeah yeah right if you do so because go ahead yeah because you can't be held guilty or
accountable later for knowing and not saying you know there's many old uh pair what is the
pro stories about that right so but right now you go on the what I call the the the stupid rectangle
and everybody's parroting the papa galo right in italian everybody is parroting everybody else
for quite secure so yeah well it seems like uh the majority do anyway I mean because
me cosmic censorship dummy load Pope's work schedule come on where are you going to go to get that
forget about it right well that you know that's that's the truth and uh we certainly have done that
and this one is also unique I think uh I think we're going to have to name this particular
uh episode and I'm I'm uh pretty pretty happy with calling it heard okay acknowledge
not receive and uh my father yeah you know I heard understood received acknowledged I think might
be a good title either that or why bother I don't know which one but either way Greek I want to thank
you all right papa for talking about the hour absolutely and uh I know that everybody got
something out of this the ocelli effect is done for this entire week now I got to produce trans
resistor radio coming up next but uh hey you know what it's been an interesting week and uh again
Jefferson morally pumped out on me so I don't know why that is all right Greek thank you again
I chop that anyway like I said trans resistor radio is up next remember this I am merely a
ocelli all of you listening participating donating doing whatever it is you can for this show even
just going into the chat room downloading whatever you are all the effect have a good night
(Music)
[Music]