Get ready for the immediate attack.
On the big stage of the shall, Chaco Chelly.
And it's been over many years, but why?
The UK Research is specializing in the intelligence agency involvement in multiple assassination,
propaganda and other global criminal operations in the 20th and 21st centuries.
Your listeners are streaming, fortunate to have you.
And now I know most activated voice in all the needs.
Chaco Chelly!
[Cheering]
On the 20th, 7th of September, 2018, allegedly, according to that thing we call a calendar.
And this, indeed, is the O'Challee Effect broadcast live from the facilities of O'Challee.com,
but also heard in a variety of other places, networks, etc.
Even occasionally on FM stations, randomly were being tested out there in the FM market.
So let's see what happens there.
Anyway, it is a Thor's Day, and I did not make it for Wodans Day yesterday because it just was not feeling up to it.
And besides that, there really wasn't anything to report yesterday.
But this is an interesting day.
Now, a lot of times I have carmined with me on Thursdays, but since he's only doing every other Thursday now,
I figured, "Well, drop something special in each and every Thursday."
And as far as I'm concerned, this is a special presentation.
Why? Because we're sort of revisiting something that we've already done.
Now, for regular listeners or long time listeners, you might remember when I was doing two shows,
not only the O'Challee Effect, but something called O'Challee and the Greek.
And, Jay, the Greek is with me tonight. How you doing, man?
Hey, Chuck. I'm doing, where are we? What is this? What's going on, right?
Well, what? You know, listen, allegedly according to the calendar.
Now, that's a funny thing, because I have started saying that after long conversations with you,
because the very first conversation we ever had, I think, publicly was all about telling time.
And, Jay, I think we've had about six other conversations regarding the actual accurate depiction of what time it is on the planet,
and, you know, the Pope's work schedule and all that.
We went through that stuff real early on and had to keep going over and over,
and over it and why? Because a lot of people just simply do not listen to what is said.
And, that is something you impressed upon me.
And, sad to say, you were extremely right. Quite honestly, I am often attributed to have said things that I didn't say.
People didn't hear when I did presentations where I've sat and painstakingly gathered together research to reveal something,
and I sit there for two hours, I put it out, somebody claims to have listened to it.
And then they send me remarks that show that they did not.
Well, you know, let's just talk it in the upper ear.
Upper tiers of society, the way that the humans are regarded as, it's basically all about livestock management.
You know, you've got the dogs, the pigs, the cows, the goats, the sheep, right?
So, you know, you've heard of references to animals, you know?
So, it's about livestock. So, I don't know, what do you want to start out?
You want to throw stuff in the trough, the feeding trough? You want to start off with the lawful timekeeping?
Well, no, not being sarcastic, I'm being accurate, by the way.
No, I know you're being accurate. It's better than talking about Georgia peaches, though, but anyway, go ahead.
That was the before-air discussion. Georgia peaches, but, no, you know what?
No, I don't want to do timekeeping. Why?
Because nobody's going to pay attention anyway, and there's about five people to do it.
So, you know what?
Yeah, the two-fim it. We'll look, look, September, let's just do it this way.
You know, time is just a recordation of events, which has nothing to do with most people, by the way, because, you know, anyway, you know, you know, what goes on in most people's heads is very...
Well, hey, that can't be true.
I don't like what he's saying, so it can't be true.
Well, if I don't like it, it's not true. What does he say something I like? Because that's true. Right?
So, anyway, you know, that's, that's heresy, by the way. Heresy is the Greek word for what you like, you know, it's being true.
So, nonetheless, the, you know, you've heard some of these new age morons talk about, there's no such thing as time, that's correct.
Time is a, is a reference point that's used to record events, like, you know, when do you want me to come back?
Well, soon, look how soon. Well, it's better if you say five minutes, right? Now you've got something you can, you know, you, you can not only use it as a form of measurement, you have rational communication.
Well, you have a mutually observable, something that you can measure by, right?
And, wait, it's a standard.
Yeah, it's a standard. And look, that's why you talk about the wind up toy, or the digital representation thereof, is, is something that can be mutually agreed upon.
And it's an objective, you know, why? Because my clock should run just like your clock, you know, and therefore we could agree that a certain increment of time can be attributed to an hour, five minutes, whatever.
So, it makes a lot of sense. I tried to say to somebody the other day when they were giving me this argument about time and calendars, and, you know, this is the real calendar, and this is what it actually says, and I said, well, you know, first of all, I don't think anybody's got it right.
But, you know, what kind of all, how would have I just started time when I'm having a conversation from day one, which would be the day I was born? That would be day one, zero into one, right?
Well, yeah, but the only thing about no one's got it right, but I could tell you who's got it wrong, meaning wrong, meaning where you're subject to the point where you're just subject, slave, subject, you know, whatever you want to call it, the same thing.
For example, right now the world is in a commercial dictatorship, and those that own all the corporate countries are laughing at everyone, you know, because they're focusing on politics and the bullshit science, you know, B.S. stands for bad science, like Jack Fresco would coin and all that.
So, the thing is, what the clock, we can agree on the clock, but what happens if, okay, how do we engage in clock? Somebody's got to make one, and then someone's got to buy one, right?
What if you want to focus on reference points that don't have to be made and bought? The sun, the moon and the stars never lose their damn clock, they never have, they never will.
I mean, actually, they will for a little time, that will be assigned to those that know. But when was the last time you bought a clock, Greek? I mean, realistically, a clock's just come along with things now.
Well, let's just say it's inclusive in things that you buy then. It might be included as part of the package, but then again, so is paint. It's not like you really bought paint, you know what I'm saying?
Well, yes you do, but it's still, let's go back to the point, it's a commercial dictatorship. That's why people are looking for political reasons, religious reasons, and all that. They don't understand the commercial aspect of things, right?
Well, here's the point I want to make really quickly before you move on. Yes, you're right. It is about a commercial transaction, but here's the thing, and I think people don't consider this too often, is that there is a package deal involved.
Now, the package deal that you and I can get is not necessarily the same as the package deal that somebody who's got an exorbitant amount of digital figures in their alleged bank account.
Credits. Credits. There you go.
Because there is, because there is no money. This is, this is a big surprise to most people because they've, you know, so good.
Well, my point is that everything is a package deal, and I think that a lot of people don't even recognize what's fully in the package.
It's almost as if they're ignoring the styrofoam because they're so fascinated by the TV, although styrofoam cardboard for other plastic came along with the TV that they bought from Walmart, you know what I'm saying?
And they might, they might miss the remote and throw it away in the batteries too and a whole bunch of other stuff because they weren't observant enough to pick up on what the entirety of the package that was handed them is.
Now, I just want to make that point really quickly, but go ahead.
But, life stock never is. The life stock is only concerned about the feeding time, the rest time, the sex time, the play time, you know, the package, you know, if you're right handed, use your left hand, it feels like someone else is grabbing the package.
But anyway, so, which I want to get to shortly, but continue.
Right, even though you wouldn't believe there's only like maybe 100 people out there that actually got something out of Greek speaker.
Overall, you know, the years of talking, speaking, I should say, it's more like talking, because, you know, talking and speaking connotes different, you know, priority also.
But, you know, when someone gives a talk, it's okay, someone gives a speech. Oh, a speech, really, you know, but anyway,
even people got a lot out of the lascivious comments, believe it or not, and you got it, you got to throw a little bit of that in, but here's the point of the matter is there is no point.
Bottom line is you're embedded in a physical body, right, and you're limited by it, right?
So, first go to what is going to make your physical body optimum for the level of optimumness that you understand or want.
So, that means good food, good clothing, good shelter. The best you want to afford or can afford. The rest of it is really BS. Either bad science or bullshit. Take your pick.
Now, let's go at the problem with just saying it's just about that, to many people, it sounds superficial.
But, on the way of pursuing good food, good clothing, and good shelter, you're going to learn about everything else there is to learn.
You see? That's the prize in understanding the simplicity of it.
And, by the way, if you go back and study any of the ancient masters and sages, did they ever give you some complex formula and some bullshit math, or did they give you like real simple profound stuff they had to think about, right?
Giving example, not that I'm in that group, but very often people write me emails, you know, like two or three paragraphs long asking questions. My response is four words.
And they email me back a week later, said, "Man, I wrote you three paragraphs, you wrote me back four words, and I had to think about it for a week."
So, in other words, you know what, that is nothing to do with being a master or a sage. It has to do with operating with a high level of efficiency.
So, you got efficiency, you got a human body, you got food clothing and shelter, and then you got that bitch called time.
And I don't mean a female dog, I mean that in a pejorative way, because the thing is, you're going to be on this plan.
And unfortunately, you're not going to be living in this shit society, not only in just America, the whole world for five, six hundred, seven hundred years like the ancient patriarchy, even though we're close to a thousand did, but you're only going to be living 50, 60, 70, 80, 90, right?
So, what are you going to do, take up your time? Right? Because you ain't going to change anything.
Right? And if you could change anything, you better figure out how you're going to do it by yourself, because you're not going to find anybody around you that makes any sense to do anything right.
You know? That's one thing that's missing from this very primal equation, where you're talking about good food, good shelter, and good clothing, right?
There's one thing missing, see, if that's all you had, if you had the optimal mobile those things, you're missing something.
And that is some time, it seems to be essential. Well, it's not just time.
How are you going to take up time? Well, it's a time, I don't know how relevant time will be.
Look, you have the optimal.
Hold on, you got the aging factor, right?
Oh, cool.
But then you got, oh, you, let's see, you got good conversation. You don't have a good conversation. Yeah, right. Good luck. How are you going to find that?
Wow.
Okay, the other thing is good entertainment, right? Really? You're going to get good entertainment?
Well, okay, okay, okay, that's, but that's my point is that there's still something else missing there.
Why are you reaching for conversation and entertainment is the connectivity between individuals, right?
What individuals? Well, individuals as in G, wait a minute, you have a one.
Is that, hold on, is that a qualitative or a qualitative question?
Well, that should be, well, the teachers walk out your door and grab anybody or quality individuals.
Obviously, if you've gone for the optimal circumstance in your food, your shelter, and your clothing, right?
And, you know, why would you not go for the most optimum circumstance regarding the company you keep?
That's right. Now, if you can't find the quality individuals, guess what you got to do? You got to make them.
Ah, okay. Now, there's an interesting point.
You got to make them quality. And even there, there's a QC, there's a sifting.
You know, when people are making things in manufacturing, you ever notice like, let's say you want to make the best chairs in the world.
You get all this lumber delivered to you. You're not going to use all the lumber.
Some of it's got knots in it, cracks, you know, right? Even you ordered the premium stuff, you're going to choose that down to the best grade.
Then you're going to start making your furniture. And even when you're making it, you might have some errors and you got to reject that one and start all over.
And some things are damaged in shipping too. I mean, you know, that's right.
Damage goods is a label, a good label for most people. There you go.
That's what the word average means, by the way, look it up at them logically. The word average, I'm just an average Joe.
Average means damage goods. I'm not making this is not my, you know, this is, you know, your ref, you know, anybody's reference.
So, so the thing is, you know, the other thing is to make an individual quality, that means that you have to know the aspects of it.
And they have to be willing to see them also because you're not putting a gun to someone's head, right?
Well, just like with telling time, you got to have some sort of mutual agreement of measurement about said things in order to, to be able to recognize quality, don't you?
Well, also you have to do it from a non-materialistic point of view.
Well, let's say you have an individual that wants to do it, but just doesn't get it, then we got this other bitch called Cosmic Sancership,
which, you know, I mean, I don't meet a female dog. I mean, that is a pyjard of something that's really shouldn't be there, but it is, right?
I guess that's a good definition of bitch.
Yes. So, you know, what's funny about that, by the way, is Cosmic Sancership is again one of those very initial terms that I encountered with you.
And I've got to say it is proven to be excessively true.
But at the same time, I'm noticing something.
There's a school, I have a school, by the way, and how to overcome that. It's private. I don't really talk about it ever on public NES Sonic Mination at all.
Why bother is my motto, right, bother, right? But I'll give a little bit of that.
Well, before, before you get over the Cosmic Sancership,
Well, I want to hear that for sure, but before you go into that, I've noticed something odd lately in the censorship. It seems to be cracking a bit.
I have to. Because if you go to death row and you ask people on death row, why are you here? They can tell you, yeah, because the judge, I got convicted for this, this and that.
The minute you go on death row, and someone says, I don't know why I'm here, they pull you out of prison when you throw the whole court thing again.
Because you have to be there through consent. And if you can't get your consent, they have you criminally insane. They get off of death row.
Right now, the world is criminally insane.
So you can't condemn them to a clean up crew. So what's happening? You have to break some of the censorship.
Let them know that their felt, a felonious behavior is ready to be dealt with.
Have them admit it, whether it's for 0.3 seconds, 10 seconds, or a minute, or a day.
And then let them go back to their cosmic censorship ways and even worse. And then you send the clean up crew.
Because you have documented that they've already acknowledged their fault and their flaw and their behavior.
Very simple, how the cosmic worlds work. And I say world's plural because there's various stations in that world. There's various hierarchies just like on the earth.
I like to, you know, the weaponized morons they call the military, right?
I'm not anti-military because they're just, I'm just being objective. They're morons.
And also, I know I've known Forstar Generals and I've known people in the military and they all agree.
But privately, publicly, they won't say it. So let's just be brutally honest here.
You have the grunt enlisted guy. Then you've got officers and then you've got various stations of officers that go up to the command, right?
Each one of them is a completely different society. Like if you go down to an Air Force Base or military base to have lunch, you have the enlisted mess, you know, looks like high school lunch with the trays.
Then you have the officers, a place where they eat, officers hall. And you sit down at a table with a white cloth and you're served with, you know, chefs, you know, people with chef hats, right?
Sometimes called a lounge or lounge, right? And I've eaten it both, right? And then you've got the higher one where you have, you know, the higher ranking and then it's even even better than just the officers lounge, let's say.
So those are like completely different societies. So when you're going into like the realm of the gods, which people, you can't have a discussion on this because the people are just too whacked out to even reference anything.
You see that there are a couple of odd references in the chat room, by the way.
Well, it's, you know, I don't know if you've been in there yet, but we do have the live chat room at ochelly.com, which, you know, you can get to through the listen, live button if you're hearing this on your smartphone or dumb phone or whatever it is.
Your tablet, your fondle slab of choice, whatever it might be. In fact, is you can get to a chat room. And there's a couple of odd things in there that were looks to me timing wise as though they were put out either right when we were coming to air or right after.
So they're random questions. Do you, do you want to address those right away or should we?
Oh, wait, I get back into the office. You know what I'm going to do? I'm going to make some coffee while we're speaking.
Yeah, you want some? Absolutely.
All right. So I might mute intermittently, but here's the other aspect. That's the primary aspect. Right? Then you got the secondary aspect, which is the material aspect that everyone likes to discuss.
Like, you know, whether you're discussing like medicine or religion or science, it's always, you know, material. They can't deal with the, the aspect that controls the material, the pre, the non material based.
Right? As a matter of fact, even one of the put downs or progardives that people tend to use against other people is like, I don't like him. He's too materialistic.
Means like superficial, right? You know, or, you know, whatever. It had no depth. Right? Kind of thing. So, so discussing things that in other words, the primary cause is like, like, for example, you've heard something called a chronic illness. Right?
They have this thing called chronic ailments, you know, the medical, the, the quacks do, right? If I translate that to English, all that means is they don't know the cause of it.
They can only treat the symptom. And because they don't know the cause, it keeps coming back. They're, therefore, it's chronic. That's like a very sly, handed way to say, we don't know what causes it. So we'll call it chronic, right?
Which makes perfect sense. Because as you know, it's up from continuous back pain. And it is because they do not know how to deal with it.
I went through the medical industry for quite a while. And you know, all I got there was addicted to some painkillers, which I'm not anymore. But that was, that was the best solution for masking the symptom that they could find.
And there was no way to fix it. You see, well, you get yourself a piece of quartz. Remember the crystal ball thing that people used to talk about in ancient times, oh, crystal ball through the future, right?
That's a big distraction. Here's some really clear quartz, which is very rare to find. Make a slit in front of it. And you could put the person in dim light and you'll see what kind of creature is hanging onto your back.
And then instead of addressing the pain, address the creature and watch what happens. The back pain goes away. You have to have a site for that.
Anyway, I never said that before publicly. Did I know you have it? You have not.
Yeah, yeah, there are more spiritual beings than there are physical. There are more unphysical things and there are physical things. That's an easy thing to imagine. Even so.
That's why the crystal ball was went down through the fame of whatever, right? But not that's not why because it, you know, it's, you know, for example, spiritual beings don't see, if you're, let's say, it goes to spirit and angel, whatever a god.
You don't see the world the way we do because we see the world. I know you have a little bit of a seeing, seeing a site challenge, but let's just roll along with this.
They don't see the world. They don't see green and blue and they don't see the objects like we do because we are seeing it through the receptacle of the eye, the organ tissue and all that, right?
They don't have material eyes. So when you show an angel or a spirit or whatever, let's say a red beach ball, they don't see it as a red beach ball like you do because they don't have a physical eye. Do you see what I mean?
Right. So by using other things to distort, not distort, but add the ultimate solid as a crystal form in front of the human eye.
Now it's both material and immaterial because a crystal is a very difficult material to define. You get to see into things that are quite interesting, not all the time, but it happens enough that you understand.
But here's once you understand that's level of science, you know, that's like the level of science that the Christians did away with, right? If you know what I mean?
Absolutely. I've which which is by the way I use crystals in in a lot of the things that I do on a spiritual level.
I've never heard of this using the quartz to deal with the back issue though.
Well, you got to you just kind of art that you could probably use a mirror also, but the mirror is going to be silvered on the back of the glass. You need a mirror that's silvered on the front or a highly polished metal plate.
Okay. That changes it again. Do you understand? Have you ever seen yourself in a mirror that's silvered on the front? You look odd. You look at it like, whoa, I've never seen such detail before because whenever you look at a mirror, you're actually looking through a given thickness of glass with the silver on the back, right?
That's distorted. That's not what you really look like. Like for example, if you all mirrors are slightly distorted and an exaggeration of that would be fun house mirrors, right?
But if you have a perfectly flat mirror that's silvered on the front, you really get to see what you look like. But here's the other interesting part. Once you understand this reality, you don't need those devices and you could just dress the spiritual side from the get go.
It's kind of like a really good mechanic. Like most people have a problem with their car. A cool mechanic, I don't know what it is, but a really good mechanic can hear a car going down the street and say, hey, that guy is power steering pumps ready to go just by the car driving by.
Right? Or that guy needs his brakes change. You hear that? No, I don't hear what is that, right? You see?
So in other words, what does that come down to? It's the old t-word called troubleshooting. You know, a good troubleshooter is really what you're looking for when you're trying to deal with the mechanics of something, whether it's a material mechanical aspect or a non-material.
See, that's where the, you know, you've talked, we've talked about paganism back and forth, but to be clear about it, you know, there's a big movement in that, right?
The paganism. That to me, when I hear people talking about paganism, I translate it to normal terms. That just means we're sick and tired of all the mainstream religions. We need something that works. That's all they're really saying, but they're just a zignor and as the rest. And I watch a lot of the things they do.
And I'm like, it's not about pagan or non-pagan or whatever. It's, do you know the truth? And the answer to that for most people is no, they're just searching because there's no, it seems like most people have discovered that there's no reward in finality.
The reward is in the search, right? It's like that stupid saying it's not getting there. It's the trip that matters. That's bullshit. That's anybody who rides the bus. Would you rather snap your fingers and be at work right away? Would you rather take that stupid bus trip? You see, of course, you try taking the, try taking the gray hound of Dallas. I'll tell you all about how the trip is not the part that never is.
That's why, for example, if you read any of the real ancient sages, I mean, none of the stuff is out, by the way, you have to really look for it. And if it's in a foreign language, you screwed because they never translated correctly.
But when you read, even let's say even let's use the standard biblical text, when you reach a certain height of knowledge, it's time to check out.
And if the other side really likes you, they pull you out. They retract you from this mess, right? Wasn't there a Disney phone about the little pig like that? You know, like imagine a pig farm and the farmer's daughter really likes one of the little pigs.
You think she's going to take it out? You're going to leave it in with the mess or she's going to pull it out and clean it up because it's so cute and cuddly, right? You get it?
Excuse me. So coffee's almost ready here. So what's cool, but on a personal level, I got to tell you something on a personal level, I have often felt that that there was a truth to this, this idea that people that are of a certain level of consciousness are often sort of just removed from the scene, especially right before something very, very horrible is about to happen that that affects like a mass group of people.
I've noticed that that people just seem to depart. If the superiors, if the superiors deem it, so if they deem it, that you need to go through it, then you go through it. That's either way it's fine because you leave it up to their superior knowledge.
But here's one of the things I wanted to get to with the cosmic censorship because this ties, look at what's it? What are these guys talking about?
The first key to cosmic censorship is just, I'm not pushing out of the way, but check this out. I'm not stepping on anything here, but just just do a hard stop and a hard right.
You ever notice how people say, I believe this or this is my faith? Okay, that's total bullshit for most of them. The reason why is because knowledge must come before faith.
Most people have no knowledge in why and what they believe in, whether it's mainstream religion, alternative religion, the sciences, political issues and all that.
Once you learn to flip that around, then you get to the point where you could start seeing through the cosmic censorship.
You've never heard of religious conversion. Let's say somebody says, "Oh, I want to be a Jew." You go to the rabbi and you say, "I want to convert you to Judaism." He gives you all these pamphlets and things you have to study.
I want to be a U.S. citizen. They give you all these things you have to study. You ever notice that?
Most people now ask, "I'm Christian." I don't know my parents where they just need to say that. The thing is what people believe in and their faith.
Also is congruent with what's acceptable and commendable in society. For example, in America, if you say, "I'm Christian, everybody pat you on the back."
Like, "Oh, this is a man of great faith. He's a Christian. He's good." Bullshit. There's nothing to know because if you knew anything about what the Bible was or a scripture or the history of the characters in Christianity, you would run away from Christianity with your hair on fire if you had to. Just to prove a point.
The same thing with all the main religions, including the paganism and including the Buddhism, including all this other stuff. All of it. It's just trash.
Most people find that if they pick something that they... I believe that this should be done. I'll read based on what?
Then they can't tell you. That's how you know someone is censored. Ask them, "What's your faith?" "Oh, I'm Christian. Why?"
"Sensor, it's a boom. Now you have to make a decision. You're going to start scratching a little bit, not scratching, but just scratch and say, "Hey, look, is this workable or not?"
Or is this one of them that's been subject of the state gone, a goner? Am a scientist. Oh, really? Okay. Sure.
You bring up a couple of points. You know what the best thing is for a scientist? Can you define a field? They can't. They tell you it's a wave.
A wave is not what something is. A wave is what something does. They tell you lights or photons, little particles, really?
You know, remember the incandescent light bulbs? That emitting photons, really? How can it do that? Aspholes and a vacuum, isn't it?
We mean the photon goes through the solid glass. No problem. Doesn't make a hole in the glass and it comes out and it keeps going. It's that small dick.
You know what are you talking about? I mean, all their stuff is rubbish.
Right? Anything more? What about a finite amount of space? Because, you know, if you leave a light on long enough, isn't it going to fill up a box?
You know, the power lines, the power lines, the electrons are moving. They should be no wire, no other thing left on the wires.
I mean, this is really stucquant. That's stupid stuff. And then you move on to politics.
And you know, I always hop on old people because they deserve, look, I'm in my sixth decade right now.
I'm over, I'm past the 50 plus mark way in the middle of it, right? So I'm putting, but to me, in my sixth decade, right?
And I still, you know, when I tell, I said, old people have no value anymore at all. Actually, they haven't for a long time.
And because I tell us to young people, I say, stop deluding yourself that you're going to see an older person and they got something smarter or wise or any advice to give you.
They don't. And if you find one, let me know. And still no one's ever called me, right? And most of them are dead. And here's the thing.
The reason with that is people say, oh, you need to, you're into politics, right? Once you go study what's already documented by the quote unquote government about the government, right?
Like reading someone's diary, you learn a lot about them, right? Because when you read someone's diary, and if it's a true diary, you're going to get to see stuff that they don't present in the facade when you meet them every day.
You get, you know what I mean? So when you get to read, for example, what the government puts out in their general printing office and various statues, various histories,
you get to see the side of government that you don't see on CNN Fox News and alternative media, right?
Okay, and people say, I don't have the time to do that. Okay, and then how come the older people that they're retired, they're on pension? How come they don't do it?
You ask, oh, it'll cure. Right? So for example, with politics, what people don't understand is, and actually, not getting into much is a guy named Demetri Callosov, K-H-A-L-E-Z-O-V.
And he talks a lot about the nuclear demolition of World Trade Center and a lot of the nuclear terrorism going on. He recently did some videos which I found to be very refreshing because it's just someone else saying it from a different point of view.
In terms of politics, what people don't understand is, give a quick, I'm going to give a one 60 second maybe 75 or 80 second minute and a half history lesson here, that's true, an accurate that anyone could reference.
What do people know about the Victorian era? Nothing, thanks for being honest. Okay, Victorian era was basically 1800s of the beginning of the 19th, 20th century, right?
Okay. Ghosts side of what happened there, and not about just gas lamps and stuff, it was really screwed up. What, what the people that rule the world financially and dust, really religiously and all that decided?
Let's make a real optimum system, just like in the Matrix, remember when you made a perfect environment that they all fell apart, they need the challenge, remember he said that, right?
Yeah, okay. They made the first one into a paradise and people couldn't accept it, it just didn't work, it's with the idea that the architect said, right?
Right, so people ask me, who are they, because it's like three hour explanation, I don't know exactly who they are, but I can narrow it down really accurately, who owns everything.
So let's keep all the countries separate, but we do want to make the people our property.
So, like for example, you know, you're here as someone as I crashed my car and I destroyed it, is you have insurance good? Okay, good, no problem.
So when they talk about people, we killed 20,000 people, do you have insurance good? No problem, they don't view you as people, if you view you as chattel as animals, right?
And it's because the way you act, you accommodate them too, they give you a chance to act like humans and you're men and women and you don't. But anyway, what they did during the Victorian era was they said instead of directly conquering people so they know who to point the finger at, let's create this corporation called a sovereign state.
And we own the sovereign state as private owners and we get all the people to sign up through government forms, their bodies and all their labor, you know, they have to register everything, birth certificates, they have to get licenses, they have to join political parties and they join our religions.
So these Christians, you know, I can't stand their fake values and their fake morals, they don't understand that that's a state religion. It has nothing to do with any particular God or any particular ancient writ.
The same with all the religions, by the way, just the fake morality is unbelievable. They don't understand that it's a state creation just like the big Mac is a creation of McDonald's, right?
So when you go back to it, what they do is they have the sovereign state. Now if you have reading comprehension, if you read the US Constitution and what I just told you is very clear in that, by the way.
But, you know, there's people that talk about NLP, neural linguistic programming and slave talk, that's all I see, it's deafening, right?
How many times have you ever heard, oh, we went to the moon, oh, we attacked a wreck or a mile, whatever. What do you mean we attack? Who's we? What are you talking about, right?
Okay, so this thing called the sovereign state and the sovereign state has to have a registration, a process, right?
Which is what you have. And it has to have a set of laws and management. Like for example, you could look up sovereign state right now. Academic definition tells you it does three things.
One is it has absolute control over the territory and everything in it. Two, it maintains order. Three, it provides services.
You got it? One, two, three.
Yep.
Okay, where does it say you have rights and votes and laws in there? No, where?
No.
That's all a charade based on what culture you have. Give me an example in terms of culture.
Like Americans freak out and say, you know, rights, I don't care about rights. Are we talking about Greek? This country is based on that. You know in order to go under rights that means you've transgressed or broken some law?
To go under rights?
Right? In other words, when someone broke a law in a very like anarchistic savage society, they just kill you on the spot.
People say that's not good because what if he was innocent? Yeah, I guess you're right. He has the right to a trial. He has a right to three hearts in a cut. He has a right to bear arms. He has a right.
You see how you see where rights come in? Let's slave talk. Right?
Give me an example. Let's go to a country where it's all headhunters, right?
So you run into a guy and we say, hey, you know, he opens up a bag and he's got five shrunken heads and you're like, does it bother you to have that?
He says, yeah, you know what does? He said, why? Because my brother, he's got ten. Right?
So these Americans that keep wanting more rights, I'm like, whoa, man, you guys are screwed. Right?
And I'm talking because I'm presuming mostly an American audience. Right? And then you go to any other country until you get to the point where people are free, they don't care about that.
You see what I mean? Which is basically the thing about laws do know harm. And also don't try to do border exchanges with demons. Right?
You know, that's like, for example, if you read like the higher aspects of the cosmic setup, what they call pagan cultures, especially if you read biblical stuff where they did sex, children, children and human sacrifices to gods and all that.
What the people were trying to do is like an exchange system with the gods. If we do this sacrifice, you'll do this for us. Right?
Where the higher lawful beings, you don't have to do that. You don't have to do an exchange like that because they already, it's like the thing, you know, I was invited to go and speak around some, while back some very wealthy people, powerful people in this country and privately.
And one of the people, you know, everybody was what they call a birthday, which I'm not into is, you know, what are you going to do? So what do you buy? What do you bring somebody who guys ability?
Now, what do you buy them? What do you bring them to impress them? What are you going to bring them? He has everything. You know, what do you give some, what do you give to someone already has everything?
I mean, there's nothing, but you know what I mean? OK, so lawful God doesn't do that kind of exchange on that basis. You see.
Right? So you keep progressing into the concept of lawfulness. You're going to lose your average man or woman because they have no concept of something like that.
The only place where you might have some free lawful people are some people in the mountains of Afghanistan and sandals.
Giving example, there's an army ranger that was here in the Southwest. Remember when they went into Afghanistan in Iraq, right? And he was in Afghanistan. He was a ranger. And what they did was they set up a tent and area for people to come in and register their houses, their children and their cars with the state, you know, the sovereign state.
And they all looked at them and laughed at them like, are you joking? You mean, if I register this, then I have to pay. OK, so basically my children, my car and my house is mine right now.
But when I register with you, I have to pay a use fee to you. Otherwise you take it away, right? And they're like, yeah, exactly like screw you, man.
That's what's going on in Afghanistan, not what you're, you see. But in America, if you set up a booth, come on. Oh, registration. Oh, this is so convenient. I don't have to do it in the mail. I could just do it right now.
Oh, yeah, birth certificate. Oh, yeah, we go right here.
You, they lack the ideology. OK, so what does this mean? Food clothing and shelter. In other words, you're going to have to live this through. There is nothing you can do to change it, right?
There's no political answer. There's a spiritual answer, obviously. They give you an example with the spiritual answer. You know, if you read ancient texts, there were 72 gods that were put over all of the nations over the chief god.
And the 72 gods are supposed to operate everybody lawfully, but they decided not to. That's why when you look at the dollar bill, it says in God, we trust they don't tell you which god.
Because that's the American God. Right. If you go to Persia or Iran or Iraq, it's a different God, but they don't, but they don't use the name.
Even the Muslims say, Allah, that's not a lot. It's Allah. Allah in our America or Arab cognate me. L means the and Allah. L, E L, A H, for example, or A L, A H means the God. They don't use the name. They don't know the name either.
I thought L was a specific deity actually to an area in Persia. Well, one time there was a deity that they described as L, which has nothing to do with.
Well, that's just a class of people. That's just like saying a Leo, a law enforcement officer. Right. Right. You know, a cop.
Yeah. But you got to realize you have to also discern whether common Joe Shmoos 3000 years ago. Yes. I'm answering for you. Right. Yes. Of course they were.
If you look at the common Joe Shmoot today or whatever, the stuff that's put out by whether it's the priesthood, the people in control, the owners, the kings, to the obvious, to the group of people known as the commoners for public consumption is garbage.
Low level stuff general none of your business. Most of the higher level stuff is need to know basis again to the military, right. Do you need to know the launch codes for the S whatever, anti whatever rocket system. No, because you're not going to be there. So it's a need to know. Right.
If you're carrying a rifle, all you need to know is that rifle. Right. Exactly. So the so the more people we tell, we come start compromising. So the stuff that's put out for public consumption now.
And public consumption. I mean, your highest universities. If you really want to have a laugh, by the way, I've had a recent Skype discussion about medical and law.
And I said that they don't teach this anymore. Either medicine or law, you know, how the human body works or real law. And I said, I'm going to read you some car some college curriculums. And I was reading the curriculums, you know, for medicine and law.
And they're like, what are you reading from? Is that like some bullshit community college? I said, no, that's Harvard, man. Right. And people are Harvard. You see, again, it's like the headhunters, right. The culture. So you have to kind of look and see what the culture is is based on. So for example, let's say you're an America and you say, what's your religion? How do you do job?
What? How did no job? That's no good because in America, they don't believe in a, how did you judge? In America, you have to be a good Christian. Oh, good Christian. Oh, that's great. You see.
So because the culture, except do they know anything about it? Nope.
See, I have this odd argument with somebody about this, too, where they were pushing the whole, you know, if somebody's a Christian, then they're obviously a good person kind of thing on me.
And I said, well, you know, that's interesting because as I recall throughout my life and you know, here we go, I can only report what I can observe, right.
I've observed over and over again, plenty of criminals who basically would describe themselves as Christians in one way or another.
It doesn't matter because it's the headhunter thing. You know, it's the culture. You know, given example, like if you, how many times we, we discussed religiosity on O and G.
And if you read the Korean, you don't find any law in there because it tells you to go do biblical law in five different places, right.
How many Muslims do biblical law? None because actually if you follow the Korean, there's no way you go back to yourself and Muslim.
Now, Christianity is easy to demolish actually that you know what cheap sweater? You ever see like a really cheap sweater and you put it on and someone says, look, there's a thread here and they keep pulling it and then like they pull it for a minute and they have the sweaters gone.
I'm actually keeping that. Okay, Christianity is a cheap sweater. There's one thread you could keep pulling on because people have no knowledge of anything is what's their symbol?
They show you a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper with long hair always. That's the, they wear the crucifix, all that stuff, right.
Right. Okay. If you go to the biblical text, there's two places in scripture that give you a direct order of how that happened.
When this man was arrested, he went through the various Judean authorities. Finally, he had to be brought to Pontius Pilate because they were occupied, right.
It was the occupying force and he said, this man is innocent. He's not guilty of what you bring him here for, right.
And if you keep reading, well, reading, what a concept, right. Remember riff. Anyway, okay. What does he say? Because no one's read it.
Well, what he says is I find that this man is committed no crime. And I turn it back over to you to deal with him with your laws.
Exactly. And then he says in another place, he says, I know you have a law.
Well, okay, I'm paraphrasing here. Yes. You exactly. You have a law and he's talking to that to deal with him.
He's talking to the Judean authorities. Not to the authorities, right. Who are in the crowd, but who are supposed to be submissive to the ruling authority, which is him and he watches his hands of it literally.
Right. Now, washing the hands means two things. One means that he washes his hands of it to the pagans. Kind of say, oh, yeah, that means I'm washing my hands of it.
If you know the law, what does that mean? In the biblical law, it says that when a body, a dead body is found and we don't know who killed him or her, the elders are to come out and wash their hands.
So he that was a symbol of the law. Well, we know that capital punishment. Now, we're not.
If you go back and this prescribed and also the Judeans protest that they said, how are we going to use our law and procedure? How are we going to use our law? Is I making an exception?
Now, why were there Romans present? Very simple because they're the occupying force. Let's say, for example, the US is occupied by the Chinese. You're going to have Chinese police and Chinese military, right?
Okay. Okay. And all your government buildings and all that. Now, let's say you want to do the fourth of July. You think you're going to start shooting off fireworks? No. You have to get out from their permission from the Chinese. And now when you do your fourth of July, pull the raid, what kind of police presence you're going to see on Fifth Avenue? You're going to see American or Chinese police presence?
No, Chinese police. Exactly. That's why the Romans cast lots for his clothes because they were told how it was going to go down because part of the law is anything that hangs from a tree is a curse to be burned.
They knew all that stuff was going to be burned. And we know that we went out that stupid. We know that under the Judeans did mosaic law and under mosaic law, capital punishment was lapidation for stoning.
Right. And we're not that stupid because the book of Deuteronomy tells us that the high crime you nailed to a tree. And we're not that stupid. We know what kind of a tree it was.
You know, so the whole thing falls apart very, very quickly. That's a good, that's a good thing. And the thing is, you know, people say, oh, this guy's anti-Christian. No, no, doing your favor.
You know, you got to, you got to like wise up and man up or woman up or something. Wake up because if you don't wake up now, you're going to be woken up later when you don't like it so much.
Right. So and then you hear all these other stories about all this. It's just ridiculous. You know, that's every, every concept.
I think we've gone into metaphors of the Buddhists, the Hindus, all of them. They're all idiots, all of them across the board.
You know, so what happens here is you say, well, how come everyone partakes in these major religions because they're state religions? It's a form of patriotism, which is a disease, by the way.
Like Jack Fresco. So you know, when another one someone says I'm patriotic, these people are patriotic. Look, before you even go there, you know what you expect? I'll tell you what you're going to hear.
You're going to hear the language of war. You can hear the language of hate. You can hear the language of ignorance every one of them. They each have their own different way of expressing those things. Ignorance, hate and war.
You know, that's interesting. That's your second reference to a depressco there. Is he still alive, by the way?
Oh no, he died in like 102, man. I don't know. He really, really wanted to live the long time. I need to give references so people have somewhere to go because they're not going to understand a word that I'm saying anyway.
No, I understand. Yeah, let me throw it in the context, though, in case people forget this is the guy was in one of the zeitgeist movies certainly.
Yeah, but there's the thing the people listening and you and other people myself are far ahead of fresco. He didn't know anything about the gods.
He didn't know anything about cosmic censorship. He doesn't know how the money system works. He doesn't know about the sovereign states. He doesn't know how the human body works.
No, but he had a very plain idea about what was wrong with what was going on. He's a tool. He's a tool in your toolbox. Yeah, I mean, definitely.
No, when you need a screwdriver, you get a screwdriver. When you got a hammer, well, you get the Greek by anyway, joking. There you go.
When you really need to do some damage, you get the Greek speak, but anyway, okay, so the concept here is very, very simple.
Be objective. Get your reference points together. You've been lied to and you know, recently I had a messaging thing with someone and I made a statement. He says, good, I'm glad that was a lie also.
You know what they told me before on it because good because the safest way to have consistent thinking is to think that you're always been lied to about everything.
And when I messaged him that this wasn't so, he says, well, thank you. Thank you. Now I know that I was lied to about that too. Thanks. I mean, it's consistently. You know what I mean? That's how you keep your sanity.
Well, see, that's an interesting point though, because it is difficult to discern sometimes what is a lie and what is truthful.
I mean, obviously there are empirical ways to prove certain things and you know, listen, somebody tells you that they can flap their arms and fly. You know, okay, so if you can demonstrate it.
There are three ways to do the lie thing. First is the way the babies do it. Why did you stop using that organ? Second is by study and time, you know, put some time into it and the third is being objective.
And by the way, it's not about shooting the messenger, but you can identify the messenger. You know how they say, well, you can't judge a book by its cover. Bullshit! If it's big, thick and yellow, it's a freaking telephone book, man.
I could judge that shit from a mile away or maybe like a hundred feet, right? Of course you can judge a book by its cover. But not always, right?
I mean, you know, going to a law office, for example, you see all the codes, all the books look alike, leather bound, right? That's different, right? Okay, so, but even listen, even things that appear to be leather bound or crap too, I mean, I've seen that. Of course they are.
Yeah, there you go.
I mean, look, you know, here's the thing. You hear about this goddess religion and I know most people hate what they call the scriptural work or the biblical work. They hate it and even whatever.
But, you know, there's a goddess in there that's like a mouthpiece and, you know, she's kind of, you know, hostile and aggressive towards men.
And meanwhile, you got this document called the Constitution to establish justice. Right now there's this morons, I don't know, there's a thing, the Supreme Court in America, right?
You know, you could go, anybody could go look this up. There's over a dozen places where what they call Supreme Court justice is say the Constitution of the United States has nothing to do with the people like they think it does.
Let me say that again, where you got it? Well, I got it. You can say it as many times.
The Supreme Court justices already have admitted on their record, which is the interesting thing to say Supreme Court because it's not a court of record. It's an appeal court. But anyway, that, I mean, people are so stupid. I mean, it doesn't matter.
But those jokers even tell you the Constitution of the U.S. is basically got nothing to do with the American people like they've been told or they think it is.
In other words, the Supreme Court judges or justices, it's ridiculous. Anyway, those clowns are saying we're not going to step on the propaganda.
We're going to let the propaganda go because these people are so stupid, they have a choice.
You see, but make a long story short here.
What is justice? It's always personified as a woman in either battle garb or subtle garb.
Bearing some kind of a weapon and she's blindfolded. Now, when I stowl guard, in ancient times you'll find her literally in battle garb. She's not blindfolded.
Meaning she's got shields and swords and all kinds of shit. Armored braiding.
Yeah, yeah. And recently she's blinded, right? So how are you going to look at evidence? That's why every people go, "They don't want to look at..."
Can it be any more plain that you're worshiping the goddess religion? And the other question is, what do you know about the goddess religion? Nothing thanks for being honest.
Most people don't know anything about historically what the goddess religion is about.
Anyway, what do you do?
What are you going to do? We're actually winding down the first hour.
We're actually winding down the first hour, right? Where generally I do take a break. I mean, if you were really on a roll and you were going to keep rolling, I would have just let you roll until you wanted to take a break.
But we're coming close to that time. So what we'll do is take a break here in a minute. But this is some fascinating stuff. Now before we do, if you don't mind, I'm going to just throw the little pieces from the chat room at you in case you're not looking at it.
No, I'm not in the... I could, but go ahead, throw them out. Let's read them, read them out so everybody else could hear them.
First of all, are there gods?
Oh, are there men posing as gods? Is a question? Another question here. Now these are all three from the same... well, three comments from the same person actually.
What are the three bloodlines? I guess of a man kind, that would be... there are... there are three bloodlines. There's probably more, but there are three major ones.
And let's just say that would take more than an hour just to give the background. And I would suggest that you've been lied to about everything.
And do you comprehend what's being said in Genesis and do you comprehend what happened after that? And the third thing is that it's a secret.
But can we classify them? Oh, yeah. We can classify them. And are there men posing as gods? That's the state's wet dream.
And the shareholders, those who own all the governments in the countries, that's their wet dream. How to get someone to pose as a god so all the more uns can follow?
Well, see, but that's the thing is that... It's a political dream to be a man to pose as a god. But in a way, isn't that really what's already happening because...
Well, we'll stop the, you know, of the dedication and the... the... the... veneration that is granted to a lot of political figures and systems and everything else.
I mean, literally, you know, there are people to call themselves atheists and basically in my estimation, they worship the government's structure.
Well, yeah, you get your law from your god and the state, you know, they supply you with one. But, you know, the atheist, like I said, you've heard me say it.
Greek, I don't believe in that because I don't have a god. I said, well, then do you follow the laws of the state? And they say, well, yes, I do. Well, then the state is your god. And April 1st is your holiday.
Anyway, well, yeah, but that's the thing is that it seems to me as though in a... in a... I'm trying to think of the word here, it doesn't matter. In a very interesting sort of way, what has supplanted the activities that would normally be directed toward a god or an actual deity,
are often being directed toward, you know, men who have achieved a certain level of power. Like I often remark about the fact that people think that rich somebody who has, you know, a great deal of credits in their in their accounts means that they are of a higher quality as a person.
Oh, no. That is not even close to true.
Look, I was around someone who was in an oil magnet, a billionaire actually, I'm not going to get any more because he happened to be related to the secretary of state. Did I just say that? Anyway, axon people, but he was eating a thing of cottage cheese, right?
And he says you want some and he's not a very clean eater. He has a kind of over a shirt and stuff. And I'm like, no, so he goes up to the fridge and he scoops out some tuna salad and he throws it in the cottage cheese and he keeps eating.
I'm like, oh, this is so gross, dude. This is so disgusting. I know that sounds like a very base analogy, but you know what I mean? No, I totally understand.
It's like, no, that's nothing to do with it. It's almost at this point. It seems random, doesn't it? You know, the rags to riches or riches to rags, whatever it is, but I'm telling you random.
It does seem random, it's not random though. It does seem random because here's the thing. We won't use names here, but I'm just saying in general, somebody thinks that it just, I hear it all the time from people. They don't actually say it, but this is what they mean.
You know, I got to like translate because everything is, is so censored still.
Well, the thing is it's like, look, look, here's a, give you advice after the show. You want a good show. Think of it as livestock management. Whenever you go into the public, right?
Whether it's a guy standing on a street corner, he doing a Hollywood movie, alternative media or Fox News. In the back of your head, you have to think about livestock management.
What do you know about livestock? They got the group, right? They get hungry. They can hurt each other.
Well, right. Well, you don't want them in your living room. What you do is you create a space for them to be, right? You make sure to get a supply of something you can feed them.
You don't want pet on your ass. You don't abuse them. Right. You don't abuse them or at least you don't abuse them so they get caught.
And then after you've got them nice and comfortable and pinned in, then you do what you want with them pretty much.
Here's the thing. The reason I like speaking anymore is because it's kind of like throwing stuff into pick trough.
The pick doesn't really care. It's just something to eat. You know, and you know, you know, the earth is a cross between an insane asylum and a pick farm.
And if you don't know what I mean, you've never been to an insane asylum or a pick farm. I suggest you visit both and then you'll be like, oh yeah, this is exactly what's happening in every society, in every country right now.
Yeah. In one way or another, I have observed both places. Greek and food. Yeah.
What they need to start, what people could start looking at is what something is, not what something does. Let's take the pick.
Give them a bath, dress them up, and it took Ceto, if it's a female and a fine dress, and take them to the debut tom ball.
And the pick is opening the doors and singing it. Everyone's going to say, look what this is doing. Look, it's so well mannered.
Yeah, but I come in and say, well, that's what it's doing, but what it is, it's a pig. It's a pig, no matter what, like, member of the circus, the circus bear.
Oh, look how smart that bear is. You take that bear and you put him in his natural environment. He's an idiot. The other bears will be like, what's wrong with him?
Yeah, but still he'll eventually be a bear.
I do this a lot with relationships, sniffing with people, or a problem with relationships, I meet the buzzer, she's a pig, she's a dog, she's a cow, she's a goat, using the animal, the characteristics.
I just see that right away. Well, you might have had a good time with them, or I'm not telling you what they do. I'm telling you what they are based on how they were groomed immediately.
Now, whether the relationship lasts six months or a year or 10 years, if that's a pig or a goat, it's a pig or a goat or a dog, meaning the characteristics of those animals, right?
Not when you're young, whatever people use to them. I'm not talking about pejorative. For example, it's funny.
I know what your mind is left.
For example, a goat is very agreeable, but they eat anything. I tell goats what birthdays are based on. They're like, oh, that's terrible. Human sacrifice.
Then a week later, they call me, would you like to come to a birthday party? The goats are always agreeable. They'll sit there and agree with you.
If you tell them something pleasant, they'll say, oh, that's so pleasant. If you tell them something that's nice, they'll agree with you.
And then they go off and the opposite is true again.
Most people are goats, right? And then you have the pigs, which are dirty and they're violent eaters, very violent, you know, when they eat.
If you put your finger in a trough, when the pig is eating, it'll just take your finger off.
Yeah, they got like 250 pound clamping pressure on square teeth.
So then you've got the pig aspect, then you've got the dog, right, which guards, right, and shouts, you know?
And still very primally travels in packs when you let them. Right. Yeah. Like wolves do.
But they eat feces, they eat vomit, you see? So, you know, and then you've got the sheep. Now, which is somewhat efficient, honestly, because there's still nutrition in there.
Copper of fire, yeah. Most people are coprophied, yeah. Copper means, you know, fecal and fire means to eat.
Also, you know, you take that into account. But here's the other aspect of it. The sheep, you know, they call them sheep. That's a wrong term.
They're mostly goats, pigs, and dogs. But for example, a sheep, if you've been around a sheep farm or whatever, when they eat, when they graze, they take out the root where goat only eats the top, right?
But also if a sheep is very particularly, if you give it feed that is improper, it gets sick.
So a sheep or a lamb type person, if you let's say make them aware of a certain holiday or certain system, they will never go back to it because it'll make them sick to do that.
Right? You get it? So, no, I absolutely have to say.
So you want a sheep in that, if you'll say that's weak and follow, not really because if you've ever really been around sheep, they have these things called rams. Have you ever been around rams?
Sure.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, right. Yeah, not for a long time, hopefully.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I want to say they're friendly. Listen, they're not very friendly at all. They're very powerful. I wanted to see short, quick story because I was born under the sign of aries.
I had this fascination where I wanted to go and see rams. So I found a place where I could.
And even in a pan and even when they're, you know, seemingly somewhat domesticated, not very friendly fellows, not at all.
And the courageous because they've got really big walls. Well, then the walls.
They charge into things first and seemingly without looking, but they're looking.
Let me tell you something. They'll think about it before they once they start charging, it's all over, but they'll consider it before.
So that was so important is that they know which direction they're going in. I mean, it's not like they're doing it blindly.
But once they do get going, that's the end of the story. They're going to stop when they're stopped.
That's what I observed about them.
Yeah. In essence, there's no, you can't, you can help. Here's the thing.
You can't help people, but you could help them along. You get my point.
You know, people say, how do we make this better? So say you, you know, forget it. The site isn't need to be improved. It needs to be scrapped recycled.
You go to a recycling place. What are they? They munch it up and crush it down to its bare things, separate it and then rebuild it into something else.
It's the only real solution that there is, but you can help people along if someone needs a little, you know, this doesn't mean you're going to be helping them.
See, that's what I do as best I can. I help people along. Right.
They're not, they're, they're unreadbiltatable. But that's the thing is that even when you take on a singular project and you want to like assist somebody and, you know, whatever you have, no matter what your level of resource is, it's, it's like, I need to say this, but it's like nobody is capable of being rehabilitated.
So to speak, you know, right. They're unreadbiltable. There are a few and they're going to be some more in the future.
You know, they'll be pulled out of this mess. You know, it's in their minds, you know, the cosmic censorship and they'll be able to isolate themselves and be recognized.
But no, it's going to, but you know, when the whole thing is flipped and done, it's going to be, it's going to be great and it'll be well worth it, you know, the crap.
But at the same time, you know, it's, it's, yeah.
There's a difference, you see, I know you're doing, you're still doing the show and all this, right? You have to stay, you have to stay in what people are used to, right?
In other words, if you're, if you're doing a show and you're talking to headhunters, you can't veer off the shrunken head subject and, and heaven forbid, you say shrunken heads are bad, you'll be finished, right?
Now, this is very different from what, let's say, the Google and the YouTube censorship is, that's just a matter of showing you that you're being controlled. That has nothing to do.
Because there's no one in any media at all that is saying anything viable, you know, I mean, you know, take that however you want to say it, Chuck, take it.
But, but the thing because there's no explanations, a lot of descriptions, you know, like when the economy goes bad people immediately talk about a diabetic, but no one is talking about the source, right?
Whether if there's a health epidemic, no one talks about how the human body works, right? Everyone just grabs on to what's in the media because that's what the culture accepts, you know?
And that's what, for example, the censorship is based on, you know, who is popular on the fringe, we're going to screw with them to let them know who's boss.
But they happen to, I think, leave a lot of the stuff that's just real hardcore alone because the people who are really hardcore aren't speaking, they're not doing anything.
You know, they're not doing YouTube's, they're not doing elaborate, you know, promotions and all that, they're just sitting back and waiting for this, you know, knowing that like we said earlier, this is not fixable.
So if you know the situation, if you go to a society of headhunters and you know, you can't fix them, you better stay talking about what they know, which is shrunken heads, you know?
You can't, yeah, like, you know, just a, you know, I'll toot my own horn. Greek speak is not for this society.
Right, you can't tell people, look, you're being pranked by the banks, there is no money, right? You know, there is no money, right?
Or, you know, that you don't absorb anything, right? You're not a filter bag, right? Right? Right? You get it? You know? Or, you know, all these religions are state functions, you know?
That's why when you talk to a preacher, the two old beef patty specialist, you ever see one of the, how they speak?
Yeah, with verse, so you know, no, no, no, this is not, this is the wrong, wrong planet for what I call triple T rating, you know, truth rating.
Yeah, I totally understand it. And I'm going to say it a really low voice truth because you can't, because everybody, if I told the morons of hijacked it, you know?
Well, see that, that's the problem though, is that there is a reality in front of us. And I keep having these conversations, right?
Oh, I'm having one with you tonight, but I mean, this is what I'm doing is having these different conversations to try and get through the, you know, time, not just the time, but also to get at a couple of nuggets of the reality.
Oh, yeah, you know, yeah, a little bit, but the thing is there's no audience for us, be honest, like we say, right? There's no audience. And there is an audience, but it's so few.
It doesn't dim a show. It doesn't deem promotion. It doesn't deem whatever, you know, it's just like, put it this way.
There's so few people that could handle the truth, right?
That the higher forces know who they are and they will get it out to them anyway somehow, but it's not going to happen. You know, like the internet by the way, all this media stuff now that's easy.
You know, that's just a beta test, like someone on a, on a stage, one, two, three, that's not in microphone test. Yeah, the reason this is happening the way it is is to get these devices in everyone's hands so they could get audio and video later.
It's the later is coming pretty quick, by the way. So yeah, well, it does seem as though things are beginning to move now, finally after.
No, no, here's the, here's the thing, you know, people say, Greek talks about the end of life. Well, not really. It's really the beginning, you know, but here's the thing.
One thing that people don't know that the main main problems that humans are going to notice, you know, where they're going to be more than just slightly inconvenience is only going to last about three years.
Right, and that's not for another decade or so, a little let me know around a decade less, maybe.
So that's when it's going to start, but in the meantime, what you're being built up of is a different mindset, different form of centralization and also opening the mindset to the non material world.
Right, well, I'll tell you what, we're going to continue this in the next, well, it's not quite an hour left, but the Greek is with me and guys, this conversation is going to get deeper, I assure you.
Stick around, you'll kill you back to the right path.
[Music]
Young man in the front row? Spit that dumb out.
Thank you.
Hmm, cherry flavor.
And now the moment we've all been waiting for, my guest tonight is a man whom we all know and have grown to love over the years.
A man who won the Nobel Peace Prize for making the world's largest cherry flavored yellow, shooted and a great man of science.
I give to you...
[Music]
And now, whether you want to hear it or not, you're telling you like it is.
Your host, Czechoteli.
See, you always got to have a bumper where it's just loaded with a bunch of crap because that's how you get people's attention.
Anyway, we're well-passed going deep into the second hour with the Greek here.
We went a little long in the first hour, but obviously I don't want to hold him back any longer because it's been...
Well, let's see, it's been a few months since you've been on with me. I think earlier in this calendar year anyway, you were on with me.
I don't know if I'm really on. I tend to tone it down. I could say I'm off.
I mean, you don't really want to hear me when I'm on, do you? Anyway, I'm just joking.
You never can say... You know, you and I have had some interesting conversations that were not on air about a lot of things.
Now, here's the pony part, guys. I actually had in mind I was going to talk about the spiritual connotations of sexuality and this kind of thing.
That's easy.
And I'm thinking that the Greek could probably fold it right into the last 45 minutes here.
That's really easy, but again, are we going to address what's for public consumption?
And the livestock, we want to get down to the nitty-gritty that ties all of the human history and brings it forward.
Well, it's an interesting thing. I would love for you to lay down the nitty-gritty. I'm not sure how many people will hear it even if they don't say nitty-gritty.
I mean, from human history, bring it forward or the stuff that people are used to hearing that you get anywhere else.
Which one?
Obviously, look, I don't like doing the stuff that everybody gets everywhere.
All right, so let's get... It's not nitty-gritty. It's just real. You could figure it out on your own if you don't like it.
If you like it, you still got to figure it out on your own.
Well, that's the whole thing.
Because I had these recent conversations with Jordan Maxwell. And quite honestly, he has stated this over and over again that there is just sexuality that is absolutely scattered throughout all of these different practices, fates, everything is sex.
It looks like.
On the one hand, I started getting emails about this where it was like, yeah, that's true. That's true. That's what's there. But on the other hand, it's like, well, you know, if it wasn't for sex anyway, we would mere.
Well, that's the point. Maybe Jordan Maxwell turned in a tune in and learned something. And here's the aspect.
Sure.
It's very, very simple.
Even from an animalistic point of view, they have the desire to procreate. Why? Well, it's not just... If you look at some animals, for example, maybe if you're on a farm, they only take some like a few seconds or a minute.
So it's not a matter of pleasure. Some animals don't enjoy it. It seems like the cries and all that.
There is this natural thing to do that, right? Even plants do it, by the way. Not that way, but there is a male and female aspect to the polarization.
All right. Now, with humans or mankind, I hope Jordan Maxwell tunes in to hear this.
What you will find is they have the ability to plan. And because they have the ability to plan, what the help from the gods and other influences?
The idea of the word inspiration, that means it's divine. It's put into you, right?
Okay. Now, what's interesting about that is that when mankind in history, no matter how far back you go, they always thought about the future. Future generations.
That's why many of the laws restructure a certain way, laws of inheritance, authority, etc. You get it? Right?
Of course. That's why monuments, everything in humanity, the mind, the future, and what future generations will see.
Exactly. For generations. So how do you get? How do you get those future generations, Chuck?
Through population, right?
Yeah. Okay. So, so where do you have? What's population? The two, the, the, the genitalia coming together.
And then, of course, the act, whether it's ritualistic or personal, ritualistic, meaning, you know, the sex temple where it's open.
Or it's personally, you know, where it's private, right? Either way, those organs have to come together. Okay. So, and when it comes to the ancient philosophical thinking, this was the common thinking as well as the priesthood,
if, if the two genitalia have to come together to have a future generation, what's the most important organ in the body for the future generation?
So, genitalia of the man and the woman, isn't it? Okay. That's why you see all the phallic and gynec symbols through ancient culture. I mean, for example, if you tour Scotland, Ireland, Northern part of England, you'll see these carons which are stone carvings and stone markings on farms. And they're like giant penises or vaginas. Right?
Ancient ones, they go back thousands of years or even, you know, pre-Christianity, let's say, right? When they shut that down. Throughout ancient cultures, you'll see various phallic and gynec symbols. There were street markers in Rome.
Street markers in Rome would be a giant penis pointing. And they took, of course, they, you know, don't show that, right? No, they don't.
But even when you take a look at some of the modern, you know, the modern discoveries allegedly, you know, ancient art and you take a look at it, all of it, a bunch of it has to do with basically a sexuality in one way or another. There is always this constant promotion of sexualization, which is odd because some people object to it in the modern age and say that, you know,
because they're juvenile, even even the person you see are discussing as a juvenile mentality, right? Because they can't see the origin. See the, what's the difference between a mature mentality and a juvenile mentality?
The juvenile, I give you a juvenile, they just want it. What they can just tell you what it is based on what it tastes like, not what it's made of.
That's why you get away with all that artificial crap and children's food where an adult that has a mature pal, you give them something, you know, it's taste terrible, even though it's supposed to be this.
A mature pal, it can taste not only the taste, but also determine what it's made of.
Like a juvenile will say, this is taste good and a mature person will say, oh, it tastes good because of all the MSG in it.
You could taste the MSG, let's say, right? Some people can. I had that experience not too long ago with a much younger person who basically, you know, said, hey, try this.
And it was supposed to be like great flavored or something and I, I could not identify it as great flavored.
I said, well, I can tell there's sweetener in it. I can tell.
So I assure you throughout for the past at least 130 years, because you got to go back into the bullshit that most people are bringing forward from the new age movement regarding this.
There's been no mature discussion publicly at all, period zero.
And I assure you of this of the topic that we're discussing right now. There is no one period that sees it mature in a mature way, not because it's just the way it is.
You know, I could just tell you because it is. There's a juvenile way. People will say, oh, this sexual stuff.
Yeah, but can you tell me about it? Don't tell me what it's doing. Can you tell me why it is or what it is basically from a historical and current perspective? And the answer is no.
It just doesn't exist.
Well, no, it doesn't.
And the weird thing is that there were all of these artificial kind of ideas that were given to it, you know, like nudity in itself is not necessarily sexual.
And, you know, like that is something that again, there's a difference between the juvenile and the more mature way of looking at something, you know, simply because a painting or a photograph is of a naked person that does not mean that it's absolutely sexual.
Now, if you're an immature person, naked as a sexual boom, you know what I mean?
And immature can mean you could be 90 or 80 or 70 or 60 and be immature and that's all I see. Oh, no, that's true. I'm not describing it to a chronologically.
It's not chronological. And the thing is there's a lack of any discussion. You can get a financial commentator that's a senior and I could tell you they're just juvenile or a medical commentator.
Well, there's a propensity. It's been shut down mature is bad. You know, it's kind of like this. It's like everyone's chasing their tail meaning when you're young, you can't hardly wait till you grow up and when you're old, you can't hardly wait to feel young again, right? Or be young.
So no one's ever present. So let's just go do a recap in order for future societies or future generations to come. You need the genitalia to come together to make the future.
So that to make the future generation. So that's why the genitalia is so important. So because it's so important, let's just blast it out there so the gods know that we know.
Okay. Now let's take this all a little bit for the to a little more mature, which no one is discussing.
When you make, let's say, have this exchange, you see it in many cultures where they have an exchange with the gods that bring them a sacrifice, right? You don't bring like soil tissue or mediocre stuff to a god.
You bring the best of the best to a god, right? Because you can't hide it. They know, right?
So what is the fruit of the most important part of the human body? You know what? When the important most important part of the human body for future generations is the genitalia, what is the product of that?
It is a baby. So the baby makes the according to the ink, a lot of these ancient cultures, the most apt sacrifice to a god. That's why you see the child sacrifice.
And I'm serious and look, what we've just said in the past 10 minutes is nowhere to be found in such a simple term that can be conveyed.
And no one is discussing it and it would be who of anyone to think why it's not being discussed because maybe it's a planet full of morons, but anyway, okay.
So it's very, very, very simple, right? You see, now just because something is very important, does it need to be flaunted and shown all the time?
Well, I think it's in bad taste, whether it's now or back then. This is not open for personal opinion or whatever. When I say bad taste, it's beyond more than what I think is bad taste.
Because believe it or not, philosophically and religiously and academically and culturally, and most parts of the world outright over, you know, just in your face sexual organs, fallican genitalia, guinex symbols.
It was considered bad taste outwardly, right? You will find it in most of places that were aloof places that were dedicated to that.
Like for example, if you grew up in New York in the 70s, you know, you say time square to someone in the 70s and 80s or 60s, that was dedicated to what?
42nd street, prostitutes, pornography, etc. Right? Right? Right. Right.
It was dedicated usually to that and also some lower cultures. Like for example, if we talk about head hunters, that gets a little more esoteric, but along that line.
So the aspect of sexuality now, okay, is what do you know about the legal system, subjugation and slavery? I think we once talked about slavery is a legal condition, right?
You understand that if you don't understand, I'm not saying whether you like it or not, it's legal. You could sign, in other words, if you're free, you can become a slave. It has to show how you became a slave, whether it's by word, by witness or on paper.
That's why they get freedom papers when you get, right? Okay.
So slavery, that's why when you deal with authorities or leos, they don't care. They always have to identify you as property first. If they can't, they have a problem. Right?
And by the way, just a little bit on the leos law enforcement officers, do you know the banks put them in, right? That's why even today when you look at small towns, they don't have police. They have sheriffs only, right?
Only the big cities have police because they came in when the banking districts were formed. After the governments became privately owned, they broke up the country into districts.
Like America or United States is broken up into 12 financial districts, 12 banks over them and the major cities have police. And the reason why you have police is so the banks can protect their interests and create order because they own everything.
You can even old movies, you know, you go to New York, well, you know, Aster, you ever have Aster, you know, the Ionese landlord of New York, you know, so of course he has his police force. Right?
That's why if you there's a couple of case presidents, presidents, if you go to an administrative court, you have problems with the police and you go to administrative court, not justice court, with the state. I'll tell you, look, I know you've got a problem with the police of the state or whatever, but they don't work for us.
The private contractors did.
There were no police in America until the late 1800s. They started in New York, Boston. Guess where the financial capitals in the US were?
New York, Boston. And so if you have police in your area, that means that you are hardcore banking district and there's a banks have no money.
They're just managing property. That's why you put there's nothing done about police violence.
Because no one, you're just property. So let's go back to if you're just property. This is a most people will never understand what I'm saying about it.
But they're not law enforcement people anyway. They're policy enforcers, which is by name. But you, but look, there's a chair, care. See, you're just property. So law has nothing to do with you. You only go under rights and code and policy applies.
You see, what do you do? You have a policy if you have a private situation. You can have a policy where you've decided that this is proper behavior. It doesn't necessarily mean that.
That's why they have, well, that's why they have a problem with quote unquote legal legal immigration because they're not signed in as property and they're over here using their property. And if they work and you give them a paycheck or cash, they could go to international court and say, look, I did work for this guy.
He gave me these fake money. Stealing, but once you get them to sign up to be legal, nah, you just waved all your law. Now you go under rights and you know, you got a serial number and now you're fine.
And all the other idiots think it's that's the way it should be. And that it's the way it's going to be. That's when you read ancient texts. It says, and the slaves will be freed.
The bonds you ever read in ancient texts is the end in the end times and after the end times when the gods return, the bond the people those that are in bondage will be freed.
But right now people are so stupid. They're like, I'm not in bondage. We're talking about, of course you are.
Okay. So let's go back to bring it back to the future. When you when you were a slave, let's say they teach you about the black American slaves or whatever in America or any.
Do you know when you're a slave that you go under the religion of the master? So let's use the black American thing. Let's say you were a tribesman in West Coast of Africa and you had whatever rituals that you did, whatever gods you served.
And you're brought over to Washington's plantation and he's a Protestant, whatever Christian. Guess what you're dubbed. Now you are Protestant because you're his slave. Right?
You see that's why like again with the pagans now like America is wicked and Norse form of Christianity right? You because they have Christmas and right you understand the calendar is you know all this other stuff right. The names of the days.
So it already is pagan. You know. So okay. So now I recognize those every single day. It's like, it's moon day. It's Wotens day. It's thores day. It's tires day. Yeah.
Give you example there's a chicken chain not going to mention its name chick filah. Anyway. And they they they're proud what we close another one hobby lobby. We will close on Sunday for worship right.
That because they're very you know whatever orthodox Christian or whatever you know fake morality stuff right. The workers there. They have to go along with that they're like no, no, no. It's all right to work on that day too. You see.
So everyone that's why I joke around and I'm like, oh look at all the people they want those born again chicken sandwiches you know anyway.
Yeah. Yeah. Or you know the hobby. Oh gonna get some born again balsa wood you know. I mean this is how but this is how it works like if you are a slave in a Muslim country.
If you're picking sand okay or olives or lemons or dates you better say your muzzle if someone asks you and you know what your children will be.
And what you call Islam today is basically a creation of 19th century English and French colonization right.
They have no the modern day Islam is nothing like it was a hundred years ago or 150 years ago at all. At all people don't know that I mean there's a so anyway.
Okay so the modern people now you know I gave the analogy of these corporations that are owned by these Christians right.
Okay. The people that own these countries like you have zones right like you know all of North and South America except for Uruguay has the same owner.
Right. That goes over to Western Europe is a group that owns those countries you know those sovereign states.
Okay. If those owners decide that they're going to put a certain brand of sexuality or give permission to certain sexual practices you better believe those countries will accept it.
You get it. So for example let's let's talk about the sodomites and the lesbians or the gays homosexual rights.
That has you know what that is that's just now the state gives you permission to do that because in the past if you did that you know there were sodomy laws and other laws against it right.
But now the state is giving you permission to do that you have the right to do that because it's wrong you're still but you have a rights and accept right you see.
You just doesn't mean that it's right right lawful you have to understand when you're given a right to marriage same sex that doesn't mean that it's lawful.
It's not just the state is giving you permission to do right it's like you know what the definition of legal definition of a license is permission to do something that's on lawful otherwise that's the definition of a light look it up I'm in my opinion.
So you get marriage licenses to begin with isn't it?
Yeah that goes under which used to be on the internet it's anymore it's called the uniform slave codes of 1750 because in 1750 in America they had a problem when different slave codes in each state.
So what was really punishable in one state was not in another so if the slave went you know the slave says oh I want to leave and go become a slave over here because it's easier for that.
Yeah different laws in different places like you know there was actually a set of laws governing the treatment of slaves and things like that.
It's called uniform uniform slave codes of 1750 that I think the 12 states or 11 states signed up on and included in there was the birth certificate if a slave is out of a child or offspring it's to be put on a birth certificate.
If he's going to be on a carriage he needs a driver's license because he's driving the carriage and if he's going to go more than 15 miles he needs a passport and he also needs a license to carry guns and weapons.
That's why the international line and how many miles is it set 15 miles off coast you know that still they're using those codes.
Now I was showing these codes online more than 10 years ago now they're not online at all you could search for you won't even find it.
So your passport your birth certificate and all your licensing and all that stuff comes from the uniform slave codes which were adapted from the Victorian era.
I don't understand why people can't even just look more than just a hundred I'm not asking you to go back to ancient times just go back a little bit more than a hundred years.
What do you know about the Victorian era?
Do you know that they used to it was very common medicine which is another discussion took it was called corpse medicine or necro-farma which was they would take they found that if you dried up dead human bodies and gave them the people that had medicinal effects this was standard by the way.
There would even chocolate coat human dry dehydrated parts and give them the children.
This was in other words the Victorian era is an as a cross section example of when the sovereign states came in do you remember the movie soil in green soil in green or people remember.
Do you know that if you're a pork eater if you have a taste for pork you have a taste for human flesh did you know that instinctively.
Why do you think they promote that.
That's why the ancients didn't promote that there you know there was a was it old dickens book is not too long ago dickens right 150 years ago some of his writings you know one of the characters introduces a son he says is my son he I'm teaching him how to eat pork and the woman was like this isn't a western society you know.
So you know there's no possibility to have rational conversation so let's just tie back the sexuality when you're forward thinking socially because you know the ancients thousands of years ago knew they still have thousands of years to go.
The only way they're going to have future generations is by preserving the genitalia of the male and the man and the woman right and that's why you saw that when something is important you flaunt it right or you show it.
So that's why that's the root basis of your sexuality and also ties into the root basis of human sacrifice specially child sacrifice right because that was the fruit of those things and this is by the way it only took a minute to say that you could have you could try to study this subject for a year you won't get that.
Because I just distilled down several years of study and simple plain speak that anyone can get of course no one will remember it because that's just the way human minds work you know there are the most people have a bad case of amnesia and schizophrenia.
You know which is interesting because a question came up in the chat room and this you know it when you use okay.
Does spilling your seed make you unclean is the exact question I wanted to read it.
Yes but you have to understand what that means and for who for your common human right now no if you're living under a certain lawfulness it would make you unclean which the term to ma presuming that's from scripture let's say Hebrew scriptures to may it means unclean but it also means unfit.
And but it because you're talking about a time especially which can happen at any time when you could be in the presence of a high form of God at any time right and because they determine it so it is so giving example what that really means from that perspective and just like any unclean thing whether it's yourself or being offered Chuck if I knock on your door right now and say we're going to go meet let's say
the emperor of North America right and you're in your cut off sweats and a holy t shirt and flip flops you can say well let's go or you're going to go try to find your cleanest dirty shirt and look proper and slick your hair back or something right look good you want to put on your best right.
So basically when you read a lot of these ancient rites regarding gods you when you were going to present yourself to a God even through prayer because that's a form of communication like for example right now you and I are on skype doing the ocelli effect I'm presenting you myself to you sonically right if in other words that could be made unfit and if I had something buzzing in the background you say dude we're trying to do show here that's too noisy right right.
Okay so that unclean state with the gods prescribe as being unclean is that is noise interference to them not to you you know what what is it you know great you get it yeah absolutely.
Remember how we went early they don't have a physical body so for the simplest analogy I give this to young people is when you're looking at let's say a red stop sign with the white letters it looks that way the red the shape and everything to you perspective
because you have a flesh eye that organ is translating that light to your mind if you're a god angel or spirit being you don't see it that way I assure you for sure you don't see it that way at all.
Now obviously they're able to train if they were going to communicate with you they would tell you that red sign because they're operating on a higher level they could use that as their communication but there's no way that any god or spiritual or angel or demon or whatever can see the world.
And see the world colors and shapes the way you do because they don't have flesh eyes well and you know that look even with a deviation from the from the typical I can tell you that that's true because I described you certain things that I see that if you alter the eye you will see differently just like a lens.
Yeah well exactly so what what happens is there there's a lot of different ways if you change the instrument that you're using of course the results different.
You will get a different effect you'll get a different effect you'll get a different impression say so for your interpretation.
Yeah they're seeing life for what it is not for what you take for granted so when you read any ancient writ and I'm talking about of a high caliber not stuff written about ancient
wets like religious crap you will see that the if there's a prescribed deity in there they'll always prescribe a condition right you know what I mean there's a prescribed condition like this is good this is bad that's a prescription right right of of a condition right and very often it's understood by humans because they're limited to their fleshly what you call it when you receptors you know what perceptions right you can't say that you're not limited most of the day
your fleshly perceptions of course you are the only time you're not is when you have your imagination and the thing is what's in your imagination is also based on input you got from fleshly inputs can you get input that is not flesh bound and that's where the knowledge base and the wisdom base and study comes in right you wouldn't believe how many times I've had discussions you know with several people and this one older lady I have to say she's older she says I don't need any I don't need to get any information from a book
wow I was like can you say that again because that's like so stupid to say it again because I don't believe I just heard that and has nothing to do with it being a book it could be on a DVD it could be on a magnetic tape it could be scratched in stone the thing is you're getting a communication
well see a great deal of what I learned is is is bisonic interpretation that's the best I do I do a lot of that because it is extremely taxing to my eyes right to read certain things you know there's two that if you give me something to listen to I seem to get a lot more information from it then if I were to sit and read it right it's just I'm quite accustomed to doing it that way
I prefer audio books okay you know things like this and and also I pick up on information that a lot of other people seem to miss in these presentations audio is the way to do it as a matter of fact I think we discussed the nature of historic libraries
right you took your material and read it in a booth a little booth and they and that's where the conference from started because if you wanted to read 200 pages you brought some friends with you and you passed it around
right and if you walked into an ancient library you would see hundreds of little booths depending on the size of the complex and you would the whole place would be just vibrating because each booth would have a different you know they're not in unison right so this is very different now what they did was it's they you know the power spiritual and physical behind they they knew that that was critical important for retention and the effect on the minds of the shut it down now you go to a library and read out loud what do they tell you
yeah right constantly that means that you're finished in terms of the the motor software on that was around for thousands of years so but now it's back why because now you can have a mini television in your pocket you know aka a stupid phone smartphone whatever with headphones on an ebook we're back right sonic
hmm right you see see so things will re re occur but differently so instead of you reading a parchment or pulp which is paid you know parchment's animal skin pulp is paper or reading off of something now it's pre read in the in a thing looks like a mini television because you can't forget about the television so we didn't we didn't want you to forget about television so we made it so small you put it in your pocket now can't tell me those little smartphones don't look like little TVs
right you know how things are still around to hunt you right and we're going to plug you with the way your ancient forefathers were with information even though it means nothing to you and it's superficial because you've been reduced to livestock willingly
right but it's important that all these things are in place see that's the weird thing is that it I said I listen to something that that takes ten minutes
okay to listen to and present it to somebody else and realize that they are incapable of absorbing the information so what you mean someone or livestock was a difference if you know any someone let me know because I haven't seen any
someone's in a long time well by someone I certainly mean you know what I mean no I do know what you mean because if you know someone there is a who is at our
stoffenys who was the ancient philosopher in ancient Greece who allegedly he lived in a clay vase it was big enough you know it'd be like a tent you know someone could live walk
into a big vase and they did have them that big you know clay pots and he would go out in the noon day sun which is the brightest time of day with a gas lamp on you know an oil lamp and we put in people's faces
in at noon time you know bright sunny and this guy's crazy he says hey dude what are you looking for is I'm looking for a man you know mankind like instead of the livestock that you guys are right kind of thing you see I'm coming from that point of view so no I understand but what I'm saying is that I share you know with someone a piece of audio that I figure
since they do speak the same language that I do they should be able to interpret the information that is contained within it and it's it's really fascinating it's like predetermined how much they're able to absorb what it is
there completely unwilling to absorb and there is a prescription for this and it's just I mean you mean that you're talking to people who are censored because you could come out and say it are they censored or are they not censored and
are willing to up them upgrade themselves well some people are embracing greater censorship and some people are starting to see wait a minute something's not right here you know that there's this seeming split that I'm seeing emerging and oh yeah but it's going to be but here this is always happened like for example do you know that when evolution and Einstein
was announced in Paris in the 20s as being the new standard there were riots in the street because it was bullshit are you aware of this well you know I'm aware of the idea that it was supposed to be a Jewish plot to confuse Americans well this is really Jewish is yeah but so I'm going to avoid when Freud was coming over you know
the statement Freud on the ship he says now we're bringing the plague to the American psychiatry right well because sometimes the penis is a penis but right now but psychiatry is you know for is sick if you know I know I know quite a few some I have more than two or three psychiatrists and my life and they're very poor character and deranged people themselves and they're you know they're the people that are considered entitled you know
well I know it is the pseudos I told somebody this last week or two weeks ago and they they got really upset with me I said it's a pseudoscience at best that has a couple of useful elements in it that you can apply and utilize when dealing with people but otherwise it's really just a twisted sort of I disagree with that I'll tell you why in a in a in a disagreement in a universal sense okay you're correct within the culture that accepts it like the headhunters
the cult the head hunter culture accepts the shrunken heads if you speak out against it now you're the one with the problem right and if you don't have enough shrunken heads you got a problem you see so with the psychiatrist you know but but you could look this up but what is it last year was a DMG whatever their manual that they put out the American psychiatric society put in the 26% or 28% of Americans are psychologically insane or unfit.
You know basically one out of three right well I'd have to say it's 99% if not more but that doesn't matter you know I mean either way that you know what it's just bad taste again but you know we didn't discuss the sexuality with all the stuff the politics the psychiatrist with the goddess religion I think you maybe we should bring that up because this is something that is not being discussed by your friend or or any place else either
I'm going to bring up with the purpose of the goddess religion is because this is a esoteric beyond esoteric and you're not going to get this from studying new age stuff from the 19th century either on a superficial level and it's absolutely necessary because we're entering a time where there is this normalization of mutilating the individual in order to create something other you know I'm not a he I'm not a she I'm a Z now you know publicly you mean publicly that was all that's that's that's not the
way she would see for let's talk about let's say the gaze or the Sodomites of the lesbian or whatever that's always been around but now it's public more public in your face right certain things when you say mutilation will be are coming in like the the actual surgical sex change tattoos like if you had a tattoo but more than 30 or 40 years ago like is he a biker is he a criminal is in the Navy right it wasn't normal certain things like that yes you know
like back in the day they didn't really have the wherewithal to do sex
changes like they do now at the drop of a hat you know basically in
other words if you just get a gang of doctors they could chop you up and
splice you together with antibiotics hopefully you'll heal and you got an
outy instead of an any or any instead of an outy you know what I mean right
but what's in place you know
when I talk about these things most of them have been in place and I've not gone
away they're just going to emerge and one of them that's been emerging for
a hundred years is the goddess religion and I'm not talking about what people
think I'm talking about you know I'm not talking about what not about what it is
not how people relate to it like like for example if you go online you put
in goddess religion you got all these middle-class post-mensural women saying
oh we got to get the goddess going back you know you don't talking about right
all that's a good thing
absolutely crazy the power of the goddess because it's a feminine thing it's the
yeah they don't live with the type movement people yeah right and
little if doesn't even mean what it is little Laila Laila means night is another
that's a whole other well that's what they've adopted as a symbol and they
state that you know yeah that's why I call it the middle-aged post-mensural
thing they either take that on or they take on because they take a class on how
to be an interior decorator but anyway yeah so none of this so what you look
around I'll tell you what you're not going to find him not gonna hear anywhere
this is it very simple the goddess religion in secret has always been teaching
this and this is inspired meaning you know how you have demons being a plenty of
Hollywood by the way there's some movies a Sherlock home movie I caught recently
where the lumenati types were evoking a demon right I was like wow I don't
you know I'm moving I'm talking about about 10 years old less than that a couple
actors in there and the whole thing was to get rid of the parliament in the
and or whatever and like this is exactly you know these these things are can be
evoked right you know demonic evocation and all that stuff right so this has
been going on in private but the god the goddess religions teaching in private
has been this I've said this many times I'll say it again humans at one point
were in a god-like state and now they're in a fallen state which by the way you
know there is no fall of man there's an egg there's an excising of man right but
anyway when man was in a god-like state there was no definition of male or
female you were just a god and you were either both male and female or none as
sexual you were hemaphroditic meaning you had both in any in and out or you
were asexual right I remember once we had a caller having a problem with God
having a penis right I'm like it's it's not a matter of making stuff up it's a
matter of are you educated or not right but anyway make a go back to the the
goddess religion when mankind was in a god-like state you get a you there was no
male female there was either you were both or none so the way you get mankind
society to go back to a god-like state is by promoting male with male union and
the males become sterile and effeminate and you promote female with female
union they retain their fertility and procreate without the men and when they
procreate without the men you will have the hermaphroditic asexual being that is
the teaching the core teaching of the goddess religion right that's why
medical science got into all the screwing around with test two babies and all
that is nothing to do with good science right I mean they're giving you cocktails
of poison that's another thing of the goddess religion the farm I dare anyone to
look up what pharmacopia means or pharma I dare you what's it means poison right
if I were looked it up you know I can you get the energy yeah the
energy I'll show you that that's what it means poison period just like gift you
know why do you give gifts at Christmas and birthdays birthdays in German gift
means poison so anyway so this is the the teaching of that goddess religion that
no one has picked up on I mean that's speaking I mean you could go on the I call it
the stupid rectangle right it's funny when I tell an academic go on the stupid
rectangle they're like what are you talking about it says that an iPad is put it
down walk away what does it look like oh shit I know what you're talking about
now okay so no one is just you could search you could study and have talks and
interviews and read books for the next ten years you're not going to get it all
distilled down to that why because not time yet that's on a neat to no basis well I
got to say it's really funny because anytime I try and introduce this concept of
the ancient goddess religion into a discussion I get you level it I get you know
nobody wants to hear it nobody well you should you should try talking to people
instead of livestock okay on this way wait wait wait wait okay maybe you think
your doctor do little now I don't know that's up to you you think you could talk to
the animals anyway I said that I think I sent the point home already right yes you
did yeah I got you but you just over here he's trying to talk to the animals
all right but but listen I'm gonna keep making my attempts you know to oh go
ahead it's it's called throwing a marshmallow or brick wall but but but eventually
oink oink bark bark move move see what I mean try try that I think you'll get a little
further I know but I can't do that way you know you run into the Christian types
they'll tell you oh you got to read to all beef fatty special sauce was yeah you're
see how they throw verse yeah okay so anyway this is planet earth you know
today I was out in commerce and I ran into some people you know cashiers you know
I said here is she's like four dollars fifty cents here's four notes and some
coin up you get money for it some days because what is it I'm money I'm like how
long you've been on this planet you've been on this planet for more than an hour you
know what's going on over here she like froze you know so well you make people
nervous when you tell them something that you see hearing I didn't say she was a
people I said there was a cashier there she looked like a corn fed heifer okay
anyway you know the do you remember the the old is a mechanic I went into a shop once
and he had a poster he was it really anti cigarettes this is before you know he
had like signs on a chain like that's absolutely no smoking on the premises I was
like oh wow okay so anyway walk into the office and he's got these posters and it's
like a pig or a monkey or a cow the cigarette hanging out of his mouth it says they
look real funny with that you know how do you think you look you ever see that
poster anti smoking poster they have the animals with cigarettes is don't they
look really funny like that you don't look you look just as funny with a cigarette
out of your mind right you know no I never lose posters but I remember as
the Osborne tell in a story about his dog looked at him funny and that's what made
him decide to try and quit smoking was because the dog was looking at him like what
are you an idiot that's okay well yeah all right well whatever but you know but look if you look at the headhunter culture they had that is part of
machoism you know the James Dean t-shirt rolled up and what's hanging out of his mouth right yeah I know that's what that's what started my long term addiction to
it doesn't matter that's the head on to see so the thing is when I say I ran into a mechanic you know it's like what form of
bipedal you know you know you know because he's up on he's not on all fours he's on two's right so once you relax about see if you're not if you have
was a Saturday life thing decreased expectations like if you have no expectations how are you going to be disappointed
if you run to someone let me know Skype me email me something hey Greek I ran into someone meaning a man or woman a person a
people a real people let me know let you know they're out there somewhere well you know what I know this I know that
that I am definitely not I don't seem to be on your level okay when it comes to this but at the same time I know I'm not on their level either
either way it's a level take a minute and define level it's a very strange thing level you know looking at the kingdom you know they
talked to us about the kingdom of heaven let's look at the animal kingdom for a moment I'm not part of that I'm just not I
really am very much separate most of the time outside of you know when I get together with people over the electronic
conveyance outside of that I mean I don't even interact with but maybe three people a week you know I mean that's it
all right if they're people then you've got three people around you shit man that's a hell of a lot of people
around you in this world well you know I consider the four-year-old a people I'm sorry okay yeah you know he's yeah it
slowly learns that he needs more shrunken heads I mean depends you know depends on how you would if he's four you better you know here's the thing
you ever notice how they have I talked about the kids culture that goes all that that doesn't go away you can't have
move says the cow embosses the lamb and here's the choo choo train and then where do you where do you stop and where do you stop that it continues
it that it go read the curriculum at Harvard University for physics or medicine or law it's the same move goes the cow bog goes the lamb
it doesn't stop once you start on that foot that's over in other words when you see the animals when they raise their young do they go let's
give them a little pup the mother dog is a given the puppy book because it's different than the dog book no in other words there was a time in
human culture by the way a more let's say evolved society where there was no children separate culture the children
emulated the well thought well educated adults there was no separate culture you know by the way when did this
kids culture come out 50 60s you get it yeah why you know you know yeah you know the end time the end started 2000 years ago right people
don't you know they don't get it you know but anyway well that's why it's not the end it's the beginning see if you're in the ends for so long you know you
you just know you should be tired waiting for the end now you're waiting for what the beginning well I got to admit that I am waiting for a serious
change you know there there is something you're getting a sir you're going to get it in the next few years there's going to be a
rearrangement of geopolit because right now for example all of your leaders that you're the you know the officers that are put in front of you
obviously even if you don't have more than a third grade education you could see they're not very smart any of the world
leaders right I mean if you're okay all right so that so the reason like let's just take America for example the ever since Kennedy they've been
discounting the office of the president how do I know look at the characters that have been sitting in there they want to the
owners of the country want to get out of your mind that the president is capable of doing anything and now with the current president that's a perfect
example you know of what's going on of course you know they put someone it by the way I have no interest in politics but I have an
interest in being objective I don't know if you know anyone that's been in New York in this in the 80s and 90s and you brought up
the TRU MP guy very negative anybody it was a New Yorker you brought up the TRU MP guy you were like oh that guy's an asshole
what's every that's the thing I lived there that's time yeah at that time you know and that was said it's perfect but because if you're going to if you
want to get the people away from worshipping that office you have to give that so many characters over so many
generations that give them a bad taste in their mouth right no pun intended but but here's the thing that people don't
understand and then they never will is that it has to be subtle and they have to go along with it based on you know what the various
techniques that they use because you know if you if in other words if the people that own the countries and control
society think that they need a sophisticated plan to brainwash the people they're wrong you got to keep it
really simple and you got to keep it stupid otherwise people won't be attracted to it
you know what that is the end of the normal broadcast time your right though that is exactly right you got to keep it simple stupid because that's the only way that stupid people are
going to understand it there you go the Greek has been with me for two hours I don't know if we'll continue on past the
break but if not guys no matter who you are where you are remember this I'm really a jelly all of you are the effect the Greek
interesting discussion on a Thursday I promise you that much and who knows maybe you'll continue to figure out
what the hell is that jelly?
you are about to be in part of one great day the eyes of the world are upon you the wholeton players of liberty loving people everywhere watch with you
we're going to come right back with Greek so stick around if you're on the live screen and if not you can have
a message in the apperex section on ojelly.com so there you go hang around