* никто suется*
Game 30, Game 40.
Game 3, Game 50, Game 40.
Attack!
The biggest thing is now the Czecho National Radio.
It's been up for many years to plan the UK Research as specializing in the intelligacies of the Parliament,
and multiple of salvation,
and not again another global criminal operation within the twenty to twenty percentories.
Conversation speaks.
History is the market and tax.
Now I know, the most integrated voice is all these.
*the sound effect of the voice*
The O-Cali!
September 30, 20,
20 allegedly according to that thing we call a calendar,
and this indeed is the show you were looking for.
Guess I know that because...
*laughs*
You found it.
Anyway, still do have a little bit of a cough.
It may interrupt me on occasion here, but...
It is what it is on what they call "Wodans Day Wednesday the middle of the week."
Now, this is the time of the week that I usually try and do something different,
and gotta be honest with you, it was a great timing that I happen to be able to catch.
A guy I used to do a show with called O-Cali in the Greek,
and I'm more than happy to sit down and have a discussion with him just about any time,
because it's always a good time to see through the nonsense,
and not everybody is acclimated to Greek speak.
*laughs*
And we discover that incrementally, you know,
a different time periods on YouTube for sure,
when people discover the show that we used to do.
Comments still come in, I try not to pay much attention to them, but occasionally,
they do pile up a bit, and they range from the extremely disturbed,
sort of, upset, usual cesspool of commenting,
to, you know, "I'm so happy I found this."
But anyway, it's always fascinating, always interesting to speak with the Greek,
because I gotta be honest no matter how I see the world,
which apparently is not like the other upright standing individuals that are called humans.
*clears throat*
The Greek sees it in a completely different way,
and quite frankly, it's always a clarifying experience.
So, happy to have you along, Greek.
I gotta say, it's been a little too long, I think, since the last time you and I spoke.
I think it's what they used to call January.
Now, I'm not sure about exactly what day it is quite frankly,
because there was something off in my calculations,
and a few other people enjoyed this miscalculation along with me trying to reckon
what I would call real time.
Well, lawful time.
Lawful time, okay.
It happens to line up everything's lining up, like the Pope's work schedule,
and lawful time, for example, new time.
I'm reckoning around the 30th day of the 7th month, like September means 7, right?
So, it's lining up with the Pope's work schedule.
I know, like, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy at the tabernacle this year,
and it lined up with Maybon.
I don't know if you're familiar with Druid festivals.
I know this hardcore Druid guy, I know it's telling him,
"Today's the last great day," and he says, "Yeah, I know," and he says, "it's Maybon."
I said, "Really?"
So, that's lining up.
Anyway.
Lawful versus unlawful, legal versus whatever.
Why bother?
Okay.
All right.
Where do we start?
Well, where do we start?
I got a...
We start with a joke.
Okay.
You ready?
Sure.
Presidential debates.
That's the joke.
There's a joke.
Okay.
I know the punchline this time, Greek.
Isn't that amazing?
That is the punchline.
The punchline is just the thing itself.
Well, that's most of the planet seems like, really.
I've got a lot of...
Yeah, you know I've been talking about legal and lawful.
I'm not concerned with anything legal or illegal.
Unless it's a sick bird, you know, an ill-eagle.
Okay.
And about clarity, you know, you have those that see
and those that don't see or not see, get it not see.
Anyway.
So anyway, I would suggest that the reality is to be judged on if it's real or not.
Right?
Okay.
If I bring you a coin and I tell you this is a silver coin, you could take it on face value
or what I say or you can have it tested for its silver content.
Right?
Correct.
But they're both real.
In other words, if you don't have it tested and it's a fake silver coin, it's still in reality
a silver coin, you see.
So, I've got counterfeit bill.
You know, counterfeit and fake news is, right?
So, reality must be tested.
Correct.
Right.
So, when we test it, proof it, we come up with something very different.
As a matter of fact, the results of proofing something cannot be relayed back to the Nazis,
you know, then people who don't not see, right?
Because the information gap that is created by simply providing the information of the proof
is so, so large and so discrepant to what they're used to, that it doesn't make any sense.
And thus, the proofing is irrelevant to those that don't see.
I think we've said, by the way, go back to the Oceleon-The-Greek stuff.
That's probably the best reference stuff for introduction to Greek speak and pick up those topics
and what we've talked about.
By the way, there's a website done by someone else called GreekSpeak.
It's a double E, double E, right?
SpeakSpaldWithWEE.com, justgreakspeak.com.
And if you want to get in touch with me personally, I have the dormant, uncommonradio.com website,
the only thing you can activate there is the email.
So, that's my own personal, and it's not active for various reasons.
Even though it's a pretty kick-ass domain.
So, where do we go from here?
Well, okay, where we've been?
A couple things.
Where we've been, right, so I want to go back over something you just said.
Listen, I advise people to go ahead if you can access the archives are available out there.
For sure, I know there's somebody out there trying to sell them, but they are available for free if you look.
Anyway, so you could go back to those shows we did, but something you just said is very interesting to me about this ability to see and not see.
It's relevant to the time for sure.
I have noticed that the information gap is not something that is static.
It is widening, and it's fluid.
Yeah, well, see, but I am noticing the increase in the gap, okay?
So, that's where I'm going with this. There may at some point be a contraction, okay?
But I can only talk to you about what I'm observing, right?
And the fact is this gap is growing.
It is growing in dimension in my mind, why?
Now, I question whether it is a linguistic issue, and if there is a failure to communicate because the communication is confounded.
Or if we are seeing because it seemed to me like we had a moment, more than a moment really, but a period of time where that gap wasn't widening.
In fact, it seemed as though all of a sudden people had awareness of things around them for a little while.
It was very brief, not like what you and I were talking about when things would come together and people would understand everything quite well on this rock.
Okay, not like that, but a very brief time period where it seemed as though the comprehension, if you will, was actually elevating a bit.
And that is absolutely come.
Okay, so I'm going to come up for a second.
That must have been the last time I got hit by an asteroid because short of that, I can't see it.
Well, let me discuss the way the cosmic censorship, which is beyond that.
In other words, there is shutdown by a cosmic divine force, which is the shutdown.
So, but yeah, go ahead.
I get you, I get what you're seeing what let's say to cut to the chase, do you have a temporal, a temporal data on when that happened?
Do you think was it a year ago, five years ago, 10 years ago when I would say it was about four years ago and I did not take note of it until recently because of the tremendous contrast.
It was almost indesernable, like as if let's just imagine for a second, we think about the cosmic censorship as a computer program for a little while.
The program was not fully functional.
It seemed like about four years ago.
But now it has not only been updated and repaired, but incrementally appears to be growing more intense.
Because I see a failure of communication here on the most simple of levels that used to be a given.
I have troubles quite frankly having conversations.
Maybe I could help, maybe I could help you out what you're trying to say, what I'm getting.
Please.
What I've been talking about timekeeping is around 1998, which was the beginning of the seventh millennium.
But with a five year grace period, let's say 2003 on the Pope's work schedule, till about the early 2030s or less, when I say early 2030s, I'm talking 31, 32, 33.
You are going to have a thousand years of events in human history compressed into that time period of about 40 years.
Let me just say that again, a thousand years of human events compressed into a time of about 40 years.
So it's very concentrated, so you don't have time to think, time to perceive, you just have time to what? Go along.
That doesn't mean get along.
That just means go along.
But nonetheless, I would suggest that the nature of our existence as humans, as we've talked about external input, is voluntary.
Not because we're here, we've volunteered to be here, but because without talking about the Greek fates, the aspect of fate in many cases has many branches and is voluntary.
I think the last time we spoke, maybe two of the last times we spoke, I said the number one priority of the every administrative government in the world is population reduction.
How do you get rid of the majority of the people in the world and have those that are remaining be compliant and willing to go along with what's next?
Well, what's interesting is that in most countries, especially the West, 40 to 75% of the people that put general population at large is willing to take an injection voluntarily.
If you know what I mean, voluntarily.
So why do you think in the US they're letting them not taking the guns away?
Because it doesn't take much to take a simple to human to convince them to go out and shoot his neighbor.
So what I suggest is when you compress this time parallel to what is going to, what this time actually represents, don't try to make sense of it.
So if you do explain or proof what's going on, it won't make sense for any rational comparative basis that you can compare it to other things because it's unique in that way.
But if you do understand how these things go by what's called the ancient prophecies and also just rational thinking and studying reference material, which we might want to talk about, not the reference material, but what is referenced and contrary.
You'll see that it's pretty easy to do and it's also once you realize you're being censored cosmically.
Now you know what you can focus on shipping away at.
So that's what I've been trying to do with Greek speak and that's why, like for example, I don't, I'm not a public, I don't go out and do stuff.
Even though I recently did a Freeman interview by request and the website is dormant is because the reality as proofs will not make any sense.
No, look, I understand where you're going here, but this is interesting because you're actually bringing up some questions.
Now I've gotten questions from listeners recently.
And by recently, I mean over the past few months.
Actually, all during this year since the last time you were on.
And again, you know, noted on the Pope's work schedule, that would be sometime in January.
So since then, I've been getting questions one by one here and there related to current events and you know what is the connection and I never attempt to speak on your behalf.
You understand.
I've always said I will attempt to bring them on and see if he'll answer the question.
And so I'll have an interview.
I'll answer everything that's asked by most of these people.
These are things that we've been taught about, you know, since we were children in one form or another.
And quite frankly, the fact that it is here, I'm yawning. This is not a surprise.
Okay, even in the very dumbed down version of what, well, hate to do this, but what they teach you in the organized Christian faiths, which I'm well acquainted with.
You have a very dumbed down version of this.
Every Bible is a children's Bible basically to you.
All right. And these ideas that, you know, at a certain point, there would be this problem with linguistics I was talking about was already something that's been done before.
The fact that there is a disease. Now, I don't know if it's a virus, but of course people wanted to ask about that because we talked about viruses on this show, you know, the show we used to do.
The sonic events that we used to partake of, participate in, excuse me, not partake of that way other people could partake of.
You know, it seems strange to me, but a lot of people think that this COVID-19 thing is something new.
It is, COVID is COV-ID stands for Certificate of Vaccine ID. It's like it's an addendum to the real ID and it was implemented privately in 2019. That's what COVID stands for.
It's, you can't catch COVID-19 anymore. You can catch a birth certificate or driver's license or, you know, a gun license or something.
There's a coronavirus we've discussed before. Let's just warm up on the topic. You ever hear someone say, like, this food is high in cholesterol, wrong.
Colestial is something the body produces under certain conditions. There's no food. There's no food that has any cholesterol in it.
It's a virus as, it is not believable that you can catch a virus as such because all of the referenced documents since the beginning where, and all the way through all the postulates and research that has been done on it, it is something that forms in the body, just like all the other things that can be observed in blood and lymphatic system.
It is something that forms when the body is under extreme stress. Physical and emotional is exposed to toxins and as exposed to high levels of electromagnetic radiation and high levels of ionizing radiation.
The latter being nuclear, let's say, events, right?
So you can't catch a virus from someone any more than you can catch cholesterol from food or a red blood cell from someone.
And they are not the cause of disease and they seem to be present more often than not within people that have a certain classified disease.
Let me just say language is coded as in a code. Sometimes it's in the code is so obscured that they jump a little too far, too fast.
Like, okay, you're the blind JFK researcher, right? Is it or not true that in Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, they had published in newspapers at Oswald Shot Kennedy about eight to six to eight hours before it happened?
Well, the actual event, no, but what they did have instantaneously was an entire background on Lee Harvey Oswald and stuff like that.
That was able to be printed immediately. Now, I'm being very careful about this in a time in which you could not transfer files instantaneously as we know them today.
They had what would amount to the ability to do that based on what was published and the amount of time it took to go to press and actually produce a newspaper and everything else is also remarkable because it seems as though information was instantaneously spread throughout the globe.
Or it was already in the hands of the publishers before the event. That is the only two conclusions one could come to based on the timing that it was produced.
Now, I'm being very specific about this. Sure, sure. You don't want to give it any any. Maybe I was too liberal with that. In other words, there was there signs of four knowledge.
Yes. Okay. Like, for example, everybody knows that 19 Arabs with box cutters don't vaporize towers. No matter what they fly into the tower. Right.
You could look at just about everything that's put it like how many times have you heard like a financial collapse? Well, it's a credit based economy.
It's all credit. Right. So how they know how how can you have a financial collapse in a credit based economy because it's credit. Right.
Well, I know I'm into it. If the credit holders, the people who control the system credit, your access to credit. Yeah. They deny your access to it. Well, you have a collapse. Don't you? Right. I was explaining to someone and they actually did a little forensic work on it.
They went about three quarters of the way, but that was enough. Recently, they did a trillion, two trillion, whatever stimulus where they sent every one, $1,200, right? Check.
And I said that they don't have to two trillion or a hundred trillion or five dollars or anything that send anyone. When they send you the check, you're going to sign it. And when you sign it under various monetary acts, that $1,200 appears. Right.
But it appears at a rate of 10 to 1, so 12,000 appears. They give you the 12,000, right? So those 10,800, whatever leftover. The bank gets a third of that. And the rest of it, the other 7,000, 8,000 goes to the Fed or the people that allow the system to work that way.
So they don't have anything to give you. They approved the funding of that, but they don't have anything. You go to the treasury or wherever, Federal Reserve, whatever you want to call and say, let me see the money you've got. They have nothing.
The banks, the gold, silver, heroin and all the other stuff they use is just commodities. So this is very easy to discover. Actually, you could look up, you know, any financial institution, not what's being taught about.
It's taught about them or reported about them, but their own information tells you that no one has any money. It's all credit.
So this goes on and on and on. But I had done on the Greek speak, I think, a week into the Corona thing. And I said, well, it was really funny how the Federal Reserve reacted on this before anyone else. Right. So it's a Federal Reserve virus, if you want to be more literal as an technological term virus.
When you throw a virus into this computer or something technological. Now what's happening is I've discussed this not in length, but you know, as humans, we make tools and with the reason we make tools is because we want to develop or further certain techniques.
So when you hear about technology, you notice people don't talk about technique anymore, but the idea of technique and technology that the TECK part is almost the same word and meet it.
It's a Greek term. So when you develop a certain technique and you want to further it, you might need better tools and then you focus on making better tools.
But when you forget about the technique and you just focus on the tools, now you forget why you're making the tools, you see.
So this is where you're at right now. There's no more technique. It's just blatant technology. So technology in a sense that the tools have taken over.
So yeah, and the interesting thing is how this is still a secret. You know, I recently speak to people in public and they say, you should write a book and they say, well, anyone who writes a book is presuming that whoever is going to read that said book has reading comprehension.
Right. Why would you write a book if you knew not presumed, but you actually knew that people lack reading comprehension. It would be a waste of time.
Right. So this is what's going on. It's the same thing. In other words, you don't have any money because it's a waste of time to have real.
You don't have any law because it's a waste of time. Look, I've spoken speaking of all they had that lady pass away recently.
And she's gone public. That's a preem court justice. Ginsburg. They asked her about her job. What would it's like to be a justice? Oh, all I do is work with bar members. That's my job. Now the bar association is nothing to do with law. Right.
They have the appearance of it. So you go, you go to a priest or a rabbi and you know, you show them the book that their religion is supposed to be based on. And say, we don't go by that. We go by our church or temple traditions.
Right. Well, in those traditions are developed through a society, which is, you know, here it is. You have a legal society in air courts. Well, there's developed for a society to accommodate the people. Right.
For example, if you landed on an island or a planet full of savages and barbarians, is it easier to change them over into being civilized or is it easier to find out what they usually need and make it and sell it to them? Right.
The second part, find out what barbarians are into and you just manufacture and sell it to them. Well, you know, they're ready to go, right?
No, I understand. And that ties right to the thing you said about guns before because it's pretty interesting. I constantly am confronted here in the, in the alleged state of Georgia with people who tell me that, you know, there's those people who want to take your guns. And I keep trying to tell them, relax. Nobody wants to take your guns actually.
You are useful with a gun. Right. And I now am armed by the way. But it's only because I do not trust the thought processes of those around me.
So for defensive reasons, something I had never done regularly. Once I stopped being a criminal as a kid, I actually have, you know, possession of a firearm of a few of them.
This is not normal for me, but you know, how it is if you are, you know, in Rome, you do as the Romans do. And it's best that you do sometimes because that's the only way you're going to be able to defend yourself against the nonsense, which may come your way.
Well, you have to remember, okay, captivity. All right. When, when you look at animal statistics, for example, a straight cat, a straight dog average life two to four years, right?
But we know that if you have a pet dog or a pet cat and if you just pet them, love them and feed them and got a water ball, they're going to live between eight and 14 years. Right.
So you hear about people only live to 25 or 40 years ago. It wasn't because of distress, health and other things like that or disease.
It was because they, they try to live lawfully with honor and dignity. So if someone insulted someone, that was usually a death offense. And if you do old to settle that insult, the survivor then would be chased down by the surviving family.
And then they would die. See, so it was very, so in other words, I asked people said, how many times have you been insulted or have you insulted someone by the age of 21?
Many times. And while each time that happened, that was a potential life threatening experience. Do you know that in ancient times, or even up until you see the Westerns?
How many times have you seen in 19th century America movies, which are accurate in this sense?
Guys insult each other in the bar. They step outside. They have a duel in the sheriff standing right there. It doesn't do anything right?
Well, you and I have both lived in the New York New Jersey area, right? And fact is only 30 years ago, you could handle things by, you know what?
We're going to deal with this and you could potentially die in a fist fight. That was normal at one point.
Not if the, not if the state agencies were present. So now you're under captivity. I think I've gone on several things I've gone over how the, what's called America, the United States of America got into this mess.
What the civil war is. It's very simple. You know, the world is run by secret societies, which are societies that keep secrets and they're not necessarily the Freemasons and Knights Templars, but the Freemasons and Knights Templars were involved in this.
They went to Freemasons went to Lincoln and said, you have a country here that could potentially feed and provide resources for the entire world as we know it. Do you know what you're sitting on? And he's like, no, you know, I'm just an attorney from Kentucky.
And they says, well, we'll show you how to do it. And the Knights Templars backed up the Southern states with very advanced armaments and artillery.
You've studied the, you know, inventions of certain weapons that are still considered modern were advanced by the South, right? They were superior militarily by and every means.
So they basically got the federal. What Lincoln was sitting on to instigate a war. Right. So all of a sudden one night of fort blows up and it was a fort that wasn't really populated. And they, that was the cause of the war.
The South was far more superior, but there were of course the plan was not for any South to the South or the North to win the plan was for to create enough chaos and decimation that the sent you can create a central government that'll spread out and maintain order through chaos.
You see, so once they subverted the South internally, then they approached Lincoln again and they had already figured out he's too much of a simple to understand what to do. They had to get rid of them.
So they got rid of them and then you had the incorporation of the government and that was done deliberately in 1871.
Then you brought in the mystical side, which was even if you look up the department of justice, it's known as a historical anomaly even in mainstream circles that you could look it up right now on a Google search, the Department of Justice history.
They every all the historians call it a historical anomaly because no one knows who started or where it came from. Ha ha ha.
And then after that came all the intelligence agencies and all that that's when they put in the justice, the ancient goddess because the free the free mason's templates, whatever they always every occupying force or power base always puts in their religion as well, right?
Well, and to hint at something that I know you're not going to speak about publicly, but I will hint at it and see what you have to say anyway. All of the blood spilled on this land during that time was more than just the result of a conflict.
It was actually a ritualistic behavior that was part of the let's call the esoteric nature of what was being put into place.
I think people are able to recognize that you know we talk about it, you know the battle of Gettysburg and how many Americans died and you know more people died during this than any.
Okay, but for reason this was done well if you draw if you draw lines between all those points you form pentagrams right yes you do yes you so and I don't think a lot of people see that on their maps quite honestly, but that is a reality that I don't see any historian anybody who's looking at this not even the most alternative of individuals.
You know not even the the I hate to say this not even the Jordan Maxwell's will touch that if you have more than five people listening you got it.
You're not you're not you're not going deep enough, but here's the thing also Chuck blood is the currency of the gods plural the plural gods even the most time it was you know he sacrificed his own son which no matter how you look at its human sacrifice well his son as a human in human form let's say.
But the and also told Abraham to bring a sacrifice as his of his son which was normal he didn't complain right the middle text is loaded with the concept of a human sacrifice actually.
Right right and it's the because blood is the currency of the gods in the level of the the higher the order higher order beings blood is of higher value.
So one thing that people don't understand is you know again proper divine economics right so that would go under divine economics the other thing is the ability to procreate children themselves because they represent the fruit.
Of the seed so we've gone over that I think before that's why you have all of the most important in the occult most important part of the human body is not the brain.
But the sexual organs because without the sexual organs the human race is finished in one generation.
And you see that's why you have all the guy Nick and phallic symbols it's even in scripture there's one I think in one of the later new testimony says there are organs in the body there are more important than others.
Right I think it was a show or Paul that said that meaning without procreation in other words look at one what what's the big complaint about GMO crops that you can't get seeds right right.
What's wrong with that well you're going to eat this year but you're not going to eat ever again right so okay so.
Divine economics that's something you could do in another find a I don't know it's a cell in someone else and do divine economics maybe we never did one like that but.
No but it would be useful I'm just you know throwing out the hint at this that this is something that could be understood if one wanted to explore it the material is available I'm just saying this is not hidden knowledge really it's just not pronounced.
It's not out front you're not going to find it easily but there is a very much something to the idea that blood is currency and I think that is something that.
For the god for the god yes yeah and when you're when you're going down that road again because of the state religions.
I think I'm the last time we spoke we spoke about Islam is not what people think right the Islam that was practiced a hundred fifty years ago was based on Torah or Torah the current islamic world is based on the Muhammad in Anglo treaties.
That were done in the 19th century the sharia law and all that extremism and all that stuff and I think we haven't discussed is that Islam was created to block Christianity from spreading because it was the same time that the crusades were going on 7th century.
It was very well known that Christianity was a state religion to subdue and dumb down people right so it was a good thing to block it at that point but then it of course got co-opted as you see today or in the 19th century you haven't missed any so all of the you know if you look at the bond religion of the east you know like you have all these westerners that are you know they look at Judeo christian ethics in Islam and say I want to go with the Hindu.
The Buddhist stuff and they get into that that's the same thing it's a co-opted it's a very recent the current Buddhist Buddhism Hindu practices are again co-opted they're not the religion is really the bond religion.
So you have no choice at this point but to become academic and stature not an academic but academic and stature meaning you're going to have to know what you're getting into based on what was written about it in earnest before you came to this planet.
No there is a need to separate the concept of what people generally consider is academic from what you're talking about the you know it's not about the degree I don't see me member of an academy or having a degree that is absolutely ridiculous you know I catch every professor I spoke into hundreds of professors in the past two decades and everyone I catch them with their pants down some of them literally believe it or not the few ones.
Cute ones years ago but I always say you know the American education system is been is is in shambles and it's irreparable it can't fix it and any education really passed the sixth of the eighth grade is useless and they all say yeah pretty much and their college professors so I said oh and they catch themselves are they kept I said so what happens they graduate from 12th grade as you literates and they go to your school in your class and all of a sudden they're magically you spray some pixie.
You spray some pixie dust on them and they're magically competent good luck with that yeah yeah it doesn't work I wanted to go touch back to why the the the pandemic or this whole Corona thing is was done now.
Well that's that's the key because again I do see this this is an interesting concept because the idea of compression where we have a lot of events occurring simultaneously.
Nothing well by the way you won't notice that there's this compression until around the the the 2020 one and a half remember remember we were doing this in 16th 2017 2016 2015.
Yes and I said that this around 2018 this spring it's going to start but it won't really be defined by you know three and a half years which would be 2021 and a half in the summer of 2021 but as it gets closer to that point it will define it.
Well and that's the weird thing because I am noticing some of these things being signaled before they arrive.
Oh yeah it's not because you know I'm a soothsayer okay the signs are obvious it appears to me.
Well what's not obvious is how they're going to do it but what they want to do is obvious.
Yes exactly which is why I say you know as we approach only days away from this event that's going to occur here in the United States where you have this selection process which is is not an election although.
It doesn't matter I wish they would get away from all that and you could do it digitally like 1984 it's purely ceremonial.
Yeah whether you have what they call a republic a democracy which is not a either or a dictatorship or whatever they have in Iran all of that is ceremonial.
None of that in other words if you've ever seen the person or heard them they have they they're not in power they have the power as a as a corporate official in other words the president would be like the manager of a restaurant chain.
Right and your local officials in the state the governors would be like the waiter of the waitress you know they can they have certainly way yeah they they could kick you out of but they're not they're not it's not their restaurant.
They could be hired and fired at any time they're not in power if you suit Taco Bell or Kentucky fried chicken you're going to get PepsiCo attorneys.
Right.
If you know what I mean no of course because it is not necessarily the front name it is not the front people that you get to deal with that are actually in charge of the thing itself you know at the end of the day will yeah but here's the thing around the 2025 2027 period you will be very clear what I just said the PepsiCo attorneys will let you know that it's all owned by Pepsi what I mean you're going to have a one world leadership.
By default in other words.
Okay what's going without talking about the the pandemic and all that if you don't wear a mask that give you a fine and if you look at the ticket it says public health code whatever it's not because you didn't wear a mask it's just some various sundry code because the law enforcement doesn't know any law they they have a little crib sheet a little book and they if you look through it which what are we going to put on the site you with which violation that's all right.
They don't know what's going on and they don't want to know because they're just they get a paid what's called a paycheck right which is not payment but just a paycheck so this goes all the way from the the guy on the street you know I call them pawns or grunts or whatever all the way up to the people that are exposed which are making fools of themselves so if you remember meaning like if you look at for example the major fools are like the governor of California New York they're all getting big criticism right.
From their own a constituents let's say so what I'm trying to say is if we hearken back a few years and I kept saying there's going to be a Middle East union in an order for this to to relegate a world a central world power you're going to have to raise the Middle East you know into a higher civilized factor than it is now and you're going to lower the western world into a lower civilized factor so they kind of even out right.
Well this is a sham I this is one of the questions because you're talking about this right now I want to enter it I'm sorry to interrupt but here's the thing you know that recent sham of a piece deal that was had there between Israel and the UAE which is another fabrication of various other countries if you don't believe me by the way one of the countries was was the first to put the image of John F Kennedy on a silver dollar that was a charge are wasn't a big deal.
But it was a big silver coin I think it's five rupees but anyway charge are is now part of the UAE but that business deal right there somebody did ask if the Greek thought that that was the beginning of this formation that will be okay.
Okay it's going to be very fast when it happens literally it's kind of like you know an independence day where they wake up one morning all the ships are there right but they were detected weeks before.
Right.
Okay kind of thing I'm not that's just I'm using film analogies because they you know they tend to be up front in people's conscious.
This is another thing I'm going to say you have a small group of people or organizations that run everything there are no national enemies in other words Iran is not an enemy of the US and Iran is not an enemy.
Israel there is North Korea is not an enemy of anyone I mean look the Americans what they couldn't get the Americans off of Cuba Guantanamo Bay come on.
They're all good friends like and I was I was very cautious and reserved once I was out in the west coast in a meeting and there was a member that were of the Persian or the Iranian mob.
I wouldn't say he's very high ranking but he was high ranking and a member of the Assad pretty high ranking and they work with the Yakuza in Japan.
And I said Israel and Iran are not enemies are they started laughing their ass off right you know of course because it's the under the world you know you can get rid of the government the underworlds it's the underworld that runs it so nonetheless there are no enemies whenever they tell you you have an enemy like China or whatever it's there were no enemies since the 19th century.
So what was World War II Greek well you go figure that one out we just talked about what battlefields and blood mean right so what you what I would suggest is when this Middle East Union comes about you will have an am
amocity genuine animosity is developing and it's going to be very different because what one of the things that I haven't done is I'm not going to be a
lot of things that I haven't touted as I should have maybe I'll start doing it now with you here.
What is going to empower at least the the middle what is going to empower this loose Confederacy of nations what I call the Middle East Union that's coming around 2025 and beyond with with let's say everyone else is conscious focused on what's going on in the Middle East and almost taking orders directly and indirectly from the leadership there is that the people are going to be so fed up.
With their lives in other words how things have been going meaning also from what they understand from history and religion that they're going to be asking in unison for divine help right.
And the people the group that is going to be let's say usurping the position in the Middle East will offer it and the people will go for it.
You see I don't know how more clear to make it because you know even the most staunch atheist on their deathbed how many times have you heard they cry out to a God right on their deathbed usually they'll still profess atheism their whole life but they ask God for help you know like there are no atheists in it what do they call the military when you're in the hole in the ground.
Oh yeah there's no atheists in a flock of the flocks. Oh yeah right the same thing there's no atheists on their deathbed you see this is how the population is going to be but I brought up the shameful administrators you know how like you should read about comode to blossom all these other people knew some or whatever these governors are being touted as you know being bizarre and whatever that is going to shame and also with Trump and all these other guy call them Trump and Putin.
You know what Putin is. Yeah I got it. Yeah okay so any of it. Trump and Putin all these other people they're not leaders there are managers at a Taco Bell but the manager at the Taco Bell could have you arrested can he not.
Oh yeah sure yeah okay and and then sent into put into a cage you know which is basically a prison you know no one has been in prison legally or lawfully in the past 80 years right they're all there for other reasons and there's not an attorney general in the world that will deny what they're doing.
They're all in the world that will deny what I just said in private but publicly say other things. I don't know because I spoke into plenty on them about it.
You even had I don't know if you remember justice book in the 80s one of the congressmen were asking if you're made justice of the Supreme Court what are you going to do about the growing prison population what did he say?
I'm not going to do anything because everyone in prisons volunteered to be there right and they cut it right there right well you mean I volunteered.
It's true. Yeah it's more than you think it's pretty bad it's a religious system it's theocracy so here's the point if you have all these leaders that are shamed how easy is it you see to break so you bring okay when you have discerning levels okay meaning like a step something looks like something is higher or lower than the other thing.
Well you have to bring the higher one down and you have to raise the lower one up right and then if you you could you could have the lower one be the high one if you take the high one and lower it a lot right if you take to if you just if you have something that's tall and something that short if you just address the tall one and reduce it to one tenth its height then the one that was previously short next to it will tower over it without even making any adjustments to it you see right.
So what I'm saying is you're going to have the western society brought down and the people that are pretty much look like they're packing dust in the Middle East are going to be brought up which is very easy to do with construction and trade practices these days in other words.
The way cities are built right now you can have a metropolis built in less than a year and a half anywhere in the world right.
So so be on the watch but this is not until the twenty twenty five but what I'm saying is that this raising the Middle East and lowering the west will be very evident by what you call twenty twenty one by the summertime.
What like I you notice I see back in twenty fifteen I'm saying the same stuff it's back it's on track you see no it is I would say that one thing that we did not cover though at that time is is something now here's what I take notice of it's not a listener question I've got a couple more of those by the way one of them is by your reckoning what year we actually had because they've adjusted their idea of time.
Well lawfully well lawfully what year we had yeah Adam Adam was the one that that everyone keeps time by by the way and you know year 6000 was nineteen ninety eight so it would be you know since the year counting is now it's the year six thousand twenty three roughly but I would say six thousand twenty two because the great if you go to the Gregorian calendar remember they shot it back a year like George Washington has two birds.
Right seventeen twenty two and seventeen twenty one right.
Well you look that up and also during the break look that up no yet and if you attempt to have a conversation about birthdays with someone from the Middle East enjoy that because they don't have the same concept of when to count.
Because you count from the one seriously because the day you're born the day you're born you're in your first year so on your birthday you're the next year right.
Right so honestly there's a one year differential between the way people in the Middle East count birthday and the way that we would count a birthday.
Well here's an example I'm in I'm fifty five but I'm in my six decade because when I became fifty one and I'm in my six decade right right okay so I tell you so I hold you I'm in my six decade they think it's sixty because they're not listening I'm in my first century so were you.
Oh absolutely I'm forty eight so really you're within that first century in other words you're still chomping away at anything a century offers so when you're born you're in your first year because even though you're alive for a day or two you're chomping away at that first year right.
So is that year is complete now you're chomping away at the second year so you're actually in your second year.
No I understand that's why I'm in my fifth decade but I'm forty eight.
So what they you know like for example even today when I watch something on television you'll have a host and a guest you know how they sit back at a night show and they swing they cross their leg and they show the bottom of their shoe their soul.
Yeah that would be that would be censored in the Middle East cannot show or in other words showing the bottom of your foot or the soul of your shoe on the Middle East television is a kin to showing the Middle finger in Western.
So they blow out here mostly.
And they would blow that out or they would edit it or change the aspect ratio so would raise above that you see so when you look at how they keep time or they're then now we're getting into the customs but mathematically or arithmetically it is correct to say that you're in your fifth decade I mean my sixth decade when you're born you're in your first year arithmetically mathematically it's different you know the difference arithmetic and mathematics arithmetic is counting like stuff you use in your life.
And you're not counting like stuff you use in commerce but mathematics is a fiction like legal or whatever right right right I understand and like they say black holes exist because we have the equations.
Well mathematics or subject to customary changes arithmetic is arithmetic right and they could tell you this equation proves that even though it hasn't been solved or can't be solved if welcome to Einstein.
But anyway yes the big the big anyway with a capital N yes well listen I got to do that because I mean you move so quickly.
Then I've got to catch up here in there and and stop for a second to to figure out where to pivot to because there's a lot of information actually contained in this conversation already even though it's not used to a dummy dummy load free conversation that's all chucked well you're spoiled now that's true.
I when when you and I would get together more regularly this was something that my mind caught up with a lot easier but I assure the listener that if you were to rewind this and go back a bit you'll you'll find probably information that you did not catch the first time I take a couple of listens actually.
But anyway you and I are doing this live so I don't have a list of superior information is to put this unpackaging years ago superior oats or superior you know well not do you remember because I'm speaking back to the 1930s is stopped by the time world war two came around because of rations right.
Rations you know if you to the quality world war two just all it did was adjust people's palette to really inferior quality products right you were just happy to get sugar of any quality because right because they told you how to be rationed most people don't know that just like now for example there's a different type but if you looked at a lot of products they're called superior this superior that back in the day I mean 100 years ago and then you have superior information in there just not used to superior information.
I'm not saying I'm superior I'm saying the information I provide oh heck yeah it's way superior.
Well and it's fascinating because the decline of all things is something that we covered also in those earlier sonic events and you know the decline in quality has well you know stood stood the same I mean really things are still declining in quality which I find interesting although the speed of information is not.
Speed of information is increased the quality of it has decreased there seems to be more of it it is abundance but a lot of it is garbage and gee that seems to be just like what the food is what the products are that people are manufacturing you know everything is commensurate with everything else as far as the quality of the time mostly now that's not to say you can't find things of greater quality which was funny because one of the things I want to close it up.
One of the things I want to close out the hour with was a question that was asked about an event that you and I did that's only in my member section on ocelli.com I think and I don't know if you ever took it anywhere else but we talked about water.
And you gave some really interesting information which I have tested repeatedly which is correct about water and how to handle it so that the quality of it is at its best and stuff like that so now a listener took that and and and listen and follow the instructions that were given.
And you know increase the quality of their water by storing it properly and stuff like that and they have another question related to how people freeze food.
And what you thought about it because they wanted to know is there a better way to freeze food considering the fact that you know if you freeze chicken twice it's no good you know if you freeze it thought and freeze it again.
So well let me let me I see where you're going on the quality of freezing.
Unless you have a two stage freezer which means a two stage compressor double door where it goes down to minus 70 or better which is dangerous by the way.
You're going to get what's called freezer burn because I think below 30 degrees or 20 degrees Fahrenheit or 18 or 21 degrees Celsius water starts to evaporate faster than it does at room temperature or just as fast so you have all that freezer burn.
What I suggest is what I learned if you're going to freeze anything you know if you buy certain quality things in freezer sections are called ice glazed have you ever seen that before like ice glazed chicken parts or whatever I don't think I know what it is but yeah go ahead.
Well let's say when you buy organic chicken breast and it's ice glazed it'll always taste better and last longer than the ones that are not what they do as they freeze them on a conveyor belt they missed water on it so they has like an eighth of an inch layer of ice.
So when that starts to it increases the shelf life in a freezer that is in the standard minus 20 minus 30.
I also learned this really young we were trout fishing and one of the guys just took a bag and put water in with the fish and said what do you do that is when you throw it out basically you know it's like the day you froze it basically freezing the fish in a block of ice right so it doesn't dry out.
So what I suggest is what I do here for example sometimes I'll get some organic beef and you know 150 bucks for a chunk of beef you know is is pretty pricey and you're not going to eat it all you know you could you could try be eating beef for quite a few days you want to you want to quarter its license freeze it.
What I do is I put it on a cookie sheet and in the freezer and once it gets hard after about a few hours I missed it with some water spray it with a mister water mister and then I put it back in wait 15 minutes spray it again I got a nice ice glaze on it then I wrap it in a plastic wrapper wax paper and put it back in the freezer because I don't have a two stage a two stage freezer.
It's called a medical freezer they usually have double doors on them and there are some restaurants that do have them by the way they're very expensive to run and they're very expensive to buy I haven't I have never seen it in anyone's house I've heard of people wanting to get one after I recommended it but I have not witnessed one yet just like I have an witness you know how they say it's a man's world how many times if you witness to your own someone's house.
Fair enough why do we have to why do we have to aim you know why do we have to write why do we have to put the seat down if I'm the man of the house I want to urinal well I would think it's utility because you know you can use that one for both and therefore you know one one space one appliance basically.
Yeah actually I had someone of quote unquote high net worth a built the most expensive house in Tucson his wife was very dominating and I and I fixed that real quick by told him put a urinal in it was a 8000 square foot house at plenty of bathrooms and one day she pulls me to size I know you you convinced him to put this year and one of my supposed to do well with it when he's not using it I said put a flower vase in it.
Why not because he wasn't used he got so used to because they have so many bathrooms but here's the point is we're not as practical in these utilitarian in other words the majority of the people especially Americans freeze a lot of their food right if you go to if you go to a bonafide I have like a Chinese refrigerator you ever go to a Chinese person's house or career when you open their fridge there's nothing there's not it's empty except for some drinks and some condiments everything is fresh right you buy you go to the house.
You buy you go shot like you've ever been to a Chinatown how crowded it is it's because people don't store food they buy it every day right right.
Right so you if you want to be utilitarian ice glaze your food I don't know if there's any YouTube universities on that maybe or if it's small enough just go ahead pour away if you have like frozen french fries it might benefit better you know from the spring or just you know don't leave them in the freezer too long but if you have a precious piece of fish.
Like on occasion someone would send us salmon from Alaska.
Fisherman. Right and it comes in a styrofoam box wrapped in Alaska newspaper with dry ice you get the picture.
Yep. Yeah and if it's a big thing you know I don't want to eat salmon for a week so I ice glaze it.
I have a colony of cats I take care of and I go to Walmart and buy a 10 pound bag of fresh chicken parts for six bucks which is a lot cheaper than the canned cat food.
Right and I just laid on a cookie sheet and I ice glaze and throw it in the bag it doesn't stick together and all that and feed them fresh chicken well it's kind of funny because I actually got my hands on a second freezer which I keep it a much you know I keep it at maximum deep
freeze and I get it cold enough yeah well the freezer burn you got to get into the minus 60 minus when below minus 50 minus 70 is good but you know what happens if you touch it minus 70 will freeze an eighth of an inch of your skin solid
immediately and it will break off and you will be left with a wound right. Well see that.
Yeah actually that's that's one of the problems with this is that even though it is not quite at the level you're talking about you know the temperature.
I do actually have trouble I got a handle things with gloves or oven mitts you use gloves yeah right when I take it out of there because and usually yeah there's a pair of gloves next to it because it is that cold but also I use that technique you're talking about where if something is contained in ice.
It's better off it just it doesn't go bad in the freezer basically.
I don't have a lot of food that I store over a long period of time but it's just because I can't go I mean where is anything fresh I'm in making Georgia for God's sake.
Fresh food but also if you if you're by the way if you're a hunter I do recommend freezing to get rid of certain parasites like tricanella and Mary other worm that worm bodies that might be in the meat.
For example the standard high quality sushi is always frozen because there's lots of parasites in fish now right.
So you want to freeze it because the the worms will will will you know the certain parasites will perish or die in the freezer what's funny I ended up with the freezer because somebody having to bring to me to me to ask me you know what to do because.
There you go free that would freeze it that's what I did it and I put it into that deep reason I said look what it's going to do is now make sure you pulled all of the you know if you use buckshot or whatever make sure you pulled it all out of there.
But other than that you know if you've got those contaminants out of there this process here will actually destroy a whole lot of other things that you could be worried about.
And you know so I had that much of the formula in my mind but but I didn't want to answer that question because again you usually have some ideas here that I don't and again you did.
Now the ice glazing concept I never noticed that any food was ice glazed in in the markets you know but but doing it at home yeah I do that at home.
So same kind of certain high quality products are that are come frozen and state their ice glazed so you don't get freezer burn.
Well and see that's the thing is I never noticed it but you know in fact is that I treat the food that way especially I mean I don't treat every piece of chicken that way some of them it's like listen I'm just going to use this soon.
But if it's something that is you know organic and therefore was expensive and you know maybe came fresh from a farm that's exactly how I handle it.
Anyway we're going to take a quick break Greek and get into some other things now this next hour might be you know I don't know how you want to go we'll see.
But anyway I'll be right back like I've always been going so okay we'll see you on the other side.
Exactly. Anyway stick around I'll be right back with the Greek on Ocele.com.
[Music]
Ocele.com.
I thought you remember the time when Benjamin Fullford said that the Asian secret society was going to dispatch ninjas to take out the Illuminati to change the entire world for the better.
That ain't never going to happen.
That never did.
It never did.
Yeah because there's a lot of false promises.
Fools.
I do assume.
We better not say be polite but there are no false promises at the Ocele.com radio network.
That's exactly it.
It's to the point white to the point and this would have straight to the point of telly.com.
Listen now.
[Music]
Uncle do you remember that time when Benjamin Fullford said that an Asian secret society was going to dispatch ninjas to take down the Illuminati?
Oh that's interesting.
Yeah in the cartoon.
Yeah did that ever work out too good?
No.
It didn't it didn't.
But here on Ocele.com radio network things work out a bit better don't they?
Much better.
I mean it is clear and understanding about the programs, the programs, a much clearer, getting live, people into it.
They really have a good conversation going.
Much better.
Much better seen.
I say forget Benjamin Fullford and his ninjas and listen to the Ocele.com radio network.
I agree.
It's straight to the point, straight talk and I like that idea.
Ocele.com.
Uncle do you remember that time when the year 2012 was going to create the apocalypse end of the world?
Right.
And I thought it would come to the end.
Did it ever end up that way?
No.
Yeah.
Like we say, the only way to end is when he is ready for a team.
That's how it is.
If you want the real truth about 2012 you better listen to the Ocele.com radio.
Radio.com.
Yeah forget John Q.
John Q.
Doesn't know what he's talking actually about.
But we here at the Ocele radio network sure do.
do you understand and understand where it's actually coming from? potele.cai.com
I'm getting people.
I know most integrated group is the only.
All of us.
I see Google mall.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, the second arrow of the O'Cilly effect begins now.
And of course, this is a unique show because I have
the Greek with me.
And it is a rare occurrence now.
It used to be much more regular sonic occurrence
when we did O'Cilly and the Greek.
And then rebooted the show briefly,
kind of did a part two and ended it.
And I'll tell you, it's still relevant, still interesting.
We're referencing a lot of it tonight
because the majority of any questions you might have
were probably already answered five years ago.
By anybody's reckoning.
So there you go.
But it is interesting to look at the world around us.
And I want to address something and just kick it
over to you and then you can go in any direction you want.
But this again is all for me this time, not the listener
or listeners who have a contact to me
and ask me various questions.
But the thing is, I do note that there is a change
in these past few years.
And I didn't quite articulate it properly
in the first hour when I was talking about certain things
and is it a linguistic issue, is it a communication issue?
And of course, cosmic censorship is still in play.
But there's something else beginning to happen,
which is different and is slowly but surely having
the knob turned up if it were volume on an amplifier, Greek.
And that is this, I call it the agitated apathy,
where yes, indeed, we're hearing again.
And this is a, you know, everything is a regurgitation
and something from before.
Civil War 2.0 is coming, get ready.
Tension between people has increased noticeably
in the past few years.
It is getting more confused, OK, more incoherent.
And yet people are aggravated now.
The laziness of most people, I think,
is what is preventing them from doing a lot more damage
to their neighbors than they already do.
I think that is one of the key factors that is preventing
some bloodshed, but I think the right push, you know.
You like to mention movies?
Well, remember the Joker character, right?
And the Christopher Nolan Batman, who said, you know,
everybody is on the edge and all they need is one good push.
I think people are beginning to emotionally
and psychologically, seemingly walk closer and closer
to that edge where that push is not going to require much effort
for them to jump over the cliff.
And that cliff, it not even a jump, they're just going to fall off
of it really.
And I think it is because they are insisting
on being aggravated, agitated, and, you know,
some people say it's mind control, but it seems
to be a general consensus of hostility that is growing.
Now, we're not in an extreme level,
because I don't believe, you know, the things that they tried
to promote via the different entertainment outlets
that they call news.
OK, have the country was not on fire, even when they were trying
to show us how the country was on fire.
That wasn't true.
But the idea, the tension, the strife, if you will,
that is being promoted, I think is succeeding, sure.
But there's something else at play here.
I think hostility is being, again, slowly turned up,
much like that boiling frog.
I don't think anybody's going to jump out of it,
but eventually things are going to get cooking.
What are you talking about?
Well, yeah, and no, you haven't seen--
if you think you've seen it, you haven't seen anything yet.
This is like the small little hump in the rollercoaster ride.
You know, when they send you out of the cabin
or wherever you load up into the cart,
what most people have in common is they take up space
and they give off heat, right?
So they're space heaters.
I'm not against the space heater liquidation.
If you told me the Earth's population was reduced down
to 100 people, it'd be fine.
But the problem, or if you left it as it is, it's still fine.
Why?
It's the quality of the people.
So let's say you brought down the world's
population to 100 people.
If you have one attorney, a priest, a rabbi, and a doctor,
these are standard trained, you're
going to be exactly where you are right now in 40 years.
Exactly.
You haven't done anything, right?
You can take the seven or eight billion people and upgrade them,
but the thing is, I believe that they're irreparable at this point.
It's not a direct condemnation.
It's a tangential condemnation.
You know how a car, when it's totaled,
they give it a salvage title.
You could still rebuild it.
I'm not talking like that.
I'm speaking on, they're not fixable.
Because it's divinely-- they've been divinely altered.
That's the divine economy talk.
But yeah, they're just taking up space.
You've got to realize that gods are numerologists and numerics,
and mathematicians, and arithmetic--
arithmeticians and mathematicians.
They don't do-- they rely heavily on counting--
accounting, accounting, and numbers.
So why are there so many stupid people in the world?
And ignorant and apathetic?
It's because of the numbers.
The quality aspect that I'm speaking of is different.
For example, you're not going to meet people
that have honor, dignity, lawfulness, and morality anymore.
And if you don't have that to me, you're already dead.
Scripture talks about that.
Why don't you let the dead bury the dead?
So yeah, I'm in total horror and shock when I leave where I live,
the dwelling, and go out in public.
It doesn't matter where I go.
I'm in horror and shock by looking at people.
How they behave to each other, and not how they behave to me.
I try to be a silent bystander.
It's just an absolute horror.
And it doesn't get any better going from one country to another.
So what I'm trying to say is space-heater liquidation
will not begin until the late 2020s in earnest.
But you're going to have some of it now.
And what does that have to do with your question?
Not much, but this is what I can't answer it directly
because when I study and think, I do it in 10-year,
100-year, and 1,000-year swaths.
So when you say you've noticed recently, that's irrelevant.
The reason why I say that it's irrelevant is because this
is how people were two or 3,000 years ago.
Not much has changed.
Right.
Well, fair enough.
And me taking notice of it doesn't necessarily
mean that that's when it started.
I'm sure that we are talking about a 10-year time period here, though.
More than-- well, let's not forget.
Let's just say the 10-year time period is not really
relevant when you're doing the general perspective,
because remember, at one point, when the people--
they will not say they're looking for divine help,
but they will sure fall for it when it's offered,
they will be promised a golden age.
That if they do these things, we'll put humanity on a new foot,
and it will last for 1,000 years, let's say.
They may not say that exactly, but a new golden age.
And they're all going to fall for it, you see.
So when you say 10 years, it's not really relevant when
these things begin, because now everything will be wiped
and they'll look ahead.
In other words, I haven't said this publicly before.
I might as well.
You know, a year zero is going to be declared in the near future.
Let me say that again.
Well, I don't have to say it again.
You heard me, right?
Oh, I heard you.
I heard you--
Think about what that means.
Well, what does that mean?
Well, you have to think about it before you answer it, right?
Remember, put your mind in motion before you put your mouth
in motion.
Let me just say-- I've never said this before.
There's lots of stuff I haven't said.
And I can't hold on.
Oh, this will be ready in a few years.
But, yeah, declaration of year zero coming up.
Not next year.
I can't give you a date, but in the 2025, 2026, 2027 period,
to declare a year zero is a big, big deal, isn't it?
Well, I'm wondering if that is only
going to be a small part of a customary release.
Sure, changing the times, yeah.
Yeah.
And the thing is, I think probably even though it's
kind of a shocking statement you're making to some people,
I think that that's going to be the least shocking thing
about that time period.
It'll be-- it'll be least shocking because it'll
accommodate the rest of the ideology that they've already
absorbed.
Right.
See, and that's the weird thing.
I enter the last question, by the way,
because I just clicked over to my email,
and I see that a listener who asked a question
is listening right now.
So it's kind of an absurd question in my mind,
but I'm going to ask it anyway and let you deal with it.
OK.
They referenced the fact that I have often said,
I don't see why it is.
People are trying to make out Barack Obama to be an anti-Christ,
to be an anti-Christ, not be anti-Christ.
But some people, the anti-Christ, OK?
And this concept of the anti-Christ
is pretty fascinating to me because I read it differently
than a lot of other people do, but we'll put that aside.
Well, let's just use this maxim, meaning something
you should know, even though it's not easily written,
or just you should know.
Whenever you borrow a term or a concept from a particular source,
you must always look for the definition of that term or concept
within that source.
It's usually given.
Yeah.
So when you bring up anti-Christ, that's
in the biblical source material.
So the biblical source material, plenty well
defines who, and what, and where, and the identity of the anti-Christ.
So putting that identity on Obama or what
have you does not fit the source.
And now you don't have-- in other words,
that's where the people are operating without license
and without right.
In other words, if you don't exhaust the source
that you obtain the term or concept from,
you are now unlawful in your application of the term.
No, I understand.
But there's something further in this question, which
is related to our current times as opposed to--
because Obama is not in office at the moment.
So the thing is, when I look at this idea
that there is this ID concept to what's
going on regarding medical and all that,
they wanted me to ask you about what is the reality of the possibility
that we're looking at the rise of that figure now
because it makes sense with the idea that you're not
going to have to comport with certain things in order to trade.
You're definitely looking at somebody who speaks out of two sides
of their mouth very much like is described in the biblical concept,
anyway.
Not necessarily the same.
Let me just interject this.
The anti-Christ will be a political figure
in a position of political power, but he will be a political,
meaning not of the systems that you're used to seeing someone stand
amongst.
He will be fluid and free to move in those systems.
In other words, the UN National Federal Capital high corporate
positions, he'll be moving in and out of that, but he'll be a political.
Right now, he's about 223.
Actually, he was born a couple of weeks ago, around 1998.
He's of usurian, not usurian, usurian, ASSYR, IAN, descend,
but he will claim to be Judean.
That's why I tell people, don't even bother reading the Bible
because you're not going to understand anything in it.
I'm not telling people not to read the Bible because that would be
suggesting they stay away from high source content material,
right?
Because it's got sources in it as well, but in other words,
if you listen to what I say, when I say that, don't even bother reading the Bible
because you're not going to understand anything in it, meaning you have to
approach it with reading comprehension.
And one thing that is really off limits to most people and hidden
plain sight is what's called the book of Revelation.
If you're a Christian and you could read the book of Revelation five times
a day, every day, for 50 years, you're not going to understand anything past
the word the.
If you subscribe to any religion because it's coming from a different level.
So in that book of Revelation, it states that beware of those who claim to be
Jews in the King James and are not, right?
And people use that on all kinds of, how are they want to use it?
But it doesn't say that it's Judeans.
So that book of Revelation is very specific to identifying many things,
star charts, how the earth, what the earth is really is about, and what mankind is going to
get into.
The long-time period that these events will occur?
It's about divine law.
And you got to understand when you're getting the King James Bible, someone posted a video.
Actually, I thought it was funny to me.
And it's basically like reading a 12-year-old book report on the Bible.
There is no...
I have of King James is a door stop.
The New Testament is very difficult to get into because it was written in Aramaic then
a hundred years later in Greek.
Then into Latin and the people who translated into King James wanted a Greek version, they
couldn't find it.
So they took the Latin, translated it back into Greek and then translated that into English.
So it's a copy of a copy of a copy.
So you have to understand the law to put the things in the right perspective and you have
to understand Aramaic.
There's no source online that I can cite about doing that.
You're going to have to find someone who is of usurian descent and you're going to have
to go back and look at certain things.
But let's just not get on that topic.
So let's just state things that we can factually attest to based on studying the source of comprehension.
Okay.
The sticking point of the question though is actually about Donald Trump because he would
be a political and seem to share some of the characteristics that he's not of usurian
descent and he doesn't claim to be of Judean.
There you have a differentiation right there.
So I just want to make that clear that I asked the question.
I'd like it to be us 23 years old.
No, certainly not.
I'd like you to roll into that though with the question asked in the chat room while you
do this explanation if you don't mind.
What will we, let me see here?
What's going to be the events leading up to year zero is the question in the chat room?
Yeah.
Go ahead.
More of the same of what you see now.
Just stressing the human condition, which you can take a lot of stress.
In other words, it's going to get to the point where you're going to start killing.
We've discussed this five years ago.
I said people are going to start killing each other for no reason.
Look at various agendas that are going to be put in place that might take some people
by surprise, but they're going to be willing.
Everyone's going to willing to go for it.
Like one of them is the pedophilia agenda, the other one.
These are agendas that have, besides the homosexuality and other things that have been put
out.
But the pedophilia, which has already been put out big time, and petrasty and all that,
into the cannibalism.
For example, there's no such thing as laboratory meat.
You know they want to feed people laboratory.
There's no such thing.
It's reprocessed human whatever you want to call it.
There's no such thing as laboratory meat.
So the cannibalism agenda, on and on and on.
And around year zero, there's going to be a turnaround and using, let's say, a more draconian
approach or hard-handed approach to old classical law form overused.
You know what I mean by that is, law is good, like water is good.
But what you can drown in water, you can drown people in good laws.
So yeah, you're going to see these agendas coming around.
I will also restate what I've stated, been stating for past two decades is you're going to see
lack of adherence as well as abandonment of the, what are the major religions?
Judaism, Christianity and Islam.
People are going to be walking away from that and they're going to be walking away for many
reasons, right?
Well, statistically that's happening now.
Right, but it's going to be on the increase and within a year or two it's going to be
pretty major increase of that.
So for lack of a better term, we're going to see a noticeable exodus from it.
Oh yeah, okay.
Yeah, to the point where there's a place called Align Light on 6th Avenue in Manhattan,
I know guys started it years ago, it was an old church and they turned it into a disco.
Great club actually.
They did not just the disco, not just the disco, but they used to see on the men's.
I'm going to head on it.
So I'll rent it out and then you could have bands play there.
You sure could, but yeah, I don't even know so around.
I think it's 16th Street and 6th Avenue.
Yeah, it was a church before that, but I remember it well in the 90s played there even once.
Got to turn the Vatican into that make of great disco.
Oh, imagine the possibilities there.
Anyway, yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, I could go.
I mean, so you're going to see a lot of the ancient stuff that you've never so ancient
and so hidden that you don't know about it revived.
And when I say you meaning the public at large will not know it's a revival, they'll think
it's something new.
So what do you know about ancient culture, like the real quirky stuff, like real odd customs
and real odd religions, especially based around not the divine, what people call divine feminine,
but certain goddess religions, certain goddess religions, right?
Right.
I always find that rather funny by the way.
The people that tell me they ascribe to the feminine goddesses and I'm like, yeah, you don't know
which one.
You don't know who you're talking to apparently because the each have a corresponding demon,
like the Shiva you read about it in the Hindu piranhas, a piranhas and well, that's a very
formative, constructive goddess, but she has a counterpart demon that's also named Shiva,
right?
That's a destroyer.
So they all have that counterbalance aspect to them that, I mean, justice herself is even
Yahweh has a destroyer.
Right.
Of course.
But then's a destroying angel down.
Yeah.
No, they all have the counter, right?
And the funny thing is the intent, they believe that they're tapping into an intent, which
is this divine, warm, fuzzy, positive, "Oh, would never do any harm."
And I'm like, wow, you just really have no idea.
Well, let's see.
The emotion, it's like the candies, what is those chocolate candies with a hard shell on
them so you don't get it all over your hands.
Yeah, right.
They take these demonic practices and ideologies and they coat them.
So it just melts in your mouth, not in your hand kind of thing?
Yeah, exactly.
No, I know what they're swallowing, you know?
No, I see that and it's just so strange.
And anyway, back to what we're talking about here, which is where we're going in the next
few years.
More of the same.
But not as such, meaning it doesn't necessarily have to be a pandemic.
You will have the corresponding degradation.
In other words, you know when you hear about the disasters we've spoken about in the past
that you read about in biblical terms, the asteroids and the famines and the plagues and
all that stuff, that's all ready to go.
It's just that it's not ready to go until the morality, the lawfulness, honor and dignity
of mankind goes lower.
It has to go a little bit lower.
And one way to judge whether honor, dignity, lawfulness and morality are on the rise.
Or on the descend is to see people's desire to seek the truth.
Sounds kind of, I'm not being sarcastic.
So the less people desire to learn or seek what's true, the easier they, there are morality,
honor, dignity and lawfulness drops.
The more they seek the truth, the level of honor, dignity, morality and lawfulness raises.
When I say the truth, I mean the real objectifiable truth.
Well, so what do you think?
That's pretty easy to predict.
So if the people start seeking the truth less and less, guess what's going to happen to
morality, honor, dignity and lawfulness?
Well, I think it will go down.
But that's not coming in the future.
That's why you know.
It's coming.
In other words, I give the example of laboratory meat.
Do you think they're actually going to make meat in the laboratory?
It's just like genetically modified organisms.
They don't know what they're doing.
What they do is they find similar organisms and they modify them by applying toxins.
Right?
Here's an example.
When you hear about, let's say, genetically modified oranges.
You know, you have an orange tree of various types of oranges.
You know, I mean, not just the orange fruit.
There's many types, right?
You know, there's such thing as a decorative orange tree.
When I first had knowledge of that, I was in the Seagramps building in Manhattan once
and they had an orange tree and they picked an orange.
It opened new.
It's just something.
Oh, great, great.
You got to watch your electronic interference there.
It was a decorative plant.
Now the insects are not going to attack a decorative orange plant like they would one that
has a nutrition bearing flesh inside the orange.
So they're just cross pollinating and doing all that other stuff.
So when you hear genetically modified crops, this is an experiment some people are reporting
on.
You know, when you buy the seeds for that are genetically modified that they don't produce
seeds, you buy more seed.
Terminated, if you can keep.
Yes, but if you can keep certain perennials alive, I mean ones that I think I'm not using
the right term there, the plants that can go beyond one year, they will again sprout seed.
So you have to be very patient.
But it's not a way of doing it though, it's not conducive because you end up losing a
year.
It's an interruption in the cycle.
So again, I would stress, I'm not going to stress, but let's say the underscore in air quotes,
the cannibalism agenda, right?
And I'm not talking about like when the Supreme Court did row versus way the abortion thing,
that was not because of women's rights.
They don't care.
The rights is a terrible thing to entertain.
So they can supply their friends with a steady supply of baby parts.
Well, and in fairness, look, the truth about that is when it comes to, well, you know, that
denies them.
That's not true at all.
Here's the reality that they don't care about rights.
If you have an, and the other thing is those that are striking it down, if you have enough
money, guess what?
You don't have to worry about that.
It's a private procedure between a doctor and a woman.
Yes, but my point is when it becomes public like that it's code.
Yeah, I understand.
But I'm just saying that it's irrelevant on both counts.
It's funny.
But watch out for stuff like that, right?
So when they tell you abortions, okay, it's not because of women's rights.
It's because they have friends, you know, they take marching orders.
And Supreme Court, by the way, is not a court of record.
It's actually pretty low.
It's an appeals court.
It always has to go back to the district court or a court of record.
So, but it's all part of the religion.
I mean, it's pretty, pretty sick, if you ask me.
So all of these things is-- who benefits?
In other words, he'll bow no.
All right?
Keyobono and Latin?
Keyobono, yeah.
If you look at the-- the Nuke-- they dropped on Lebanon
a month or two ago.
If you want to know who dropped it, who is--
from a brand name perspective, it was the French.
Well, how do I know?
Well, because the French leadership is sticking their knows
way deep into Lebanon since that happened, right?
Meaning not that there really is a French government,
but the brand known as France is moving in--
do you see what I mean?
Right.
Well, in that brand functions on this concept
of control and destruction of colonies.
So if you look back at the history of them attempting
to insert themselves into the Middle East,
it makes perfect sense.
Now, I don't know about the evidence for that,
to be honest with you.
I haven't seen the evidence for it.
When I saw it, it certainly looked like not quite a nuclear
explosion as I've seen it on film before,
but it looked like something else.
And--
Well, the thing about calling it a nuke is based on the yield.
It's very easy.
There's a pact-- an unwritten pact for the past 40 years or 50
years--
to not do anything atmospheric anymore.
The 20,000 nuclear experiments is
a 90% of them are underground, so that's how they use them.
In other words, they're not supposed to detonate on the surface
because it's too obvious you have the double flash, right?
You have the detonation and the reaction.
So they're always used underground,
but the way you figure that out is based
on the immediacy of the environmental reaction.
But I call it because it's very inexpensive to do--
but now that they've got people used to the biologicals,
I think the last time we spoke in what's called January,
and you brought up the possibility of war
starting because of Salmani being killed by intelligence
agencies to spark off a war, let's say.
I said, no.
I said, the wars are going to be done using biologicals.
Do you remember that?
This is the story that started.
Yes, I do, because what happened there
seemed to me to be exactly the kind of thing
that usually starts a conflict.
But it didn't.
Surprisingly to me, it did not.
And I think the reason was that it couldn't be sold
to whoever makes that decision that this was a good idea at the time.
Right, and the only people who can defeat the Persians
are the Greeks, and the Greeks are in no situation
to fight the Persians.
No, they have no--
that's impossible at the moment.
So-- That's not going to happen.
So it's not going to happen.
It's very easy.
It's going to happen before--
Well, the other relevant thing--
Well, hang on one second.
One second, the other relevant thing
that you brought up at that time when we talked about that situation,
because I do have a memory, is that you said
it was the wrong time of year.
And what, using that idea and taking a look at the time of year,
and what it is that you naturally do in a Greg--
You know, a Greg--
A Gregorian, correct.
That's the word I was trying to get out.
In a Gregorian sense.
Yeah, you're supposed to be harvesting,
guess what, around now.
We-- Yeah, harvest is now, but the winter is transition.
The harvest is now, the fall, correct.
The winter is transition.
When-- see, in the winter, you're done with your harvest.
You have your winter crop, your winter wheat, winter rye going,
and you might-- that's when you build your barn,
your fixer wagon, or go on a long trip.
No, I understand, but when you take--
And you apply-- No, I get it.
That's what I was going to say.
When you apply that figuratively to what's going on,
of course, it was going to be no war then.
That would not have been the time to harvest this kind of thing.
I think what we have seen is an incremental increase
again in that tension across the board.
I don't see anywhere where things are getting more peaceful,
and I don't care about that business deal again
that they made in the Middle East.
That is irrelevant.
It's just another business deal.
OK.
Well, it's a historical-- you know, you have fake news.
What about fake history?
If the news are fake, isn't the history a compilation of news?
Well, on one level, it is, but it is also
the record that is recorded by individuals.
When you look at the concept of historiography,
it is more than that.
But indeed, the individuals who write those histories,
do it with particular agendas.
And I don't care if you're talking about Joe Cephas
or whoever the hell is keeping track of it
at the Pentagon at the moment.
There is a reasoning for why the history is written the way it is.
It is always subject to revision.
And quite frankly, there is the concept of the need for revisionism
on all of these histories, which--
listen, I agree to it-- there are things which are not known
at the time of the history that become known later.
So this is why, by the way, the French had the concept
of perspective that you had to have 75 years
between a historical event before you got a realistic writing
about it.
In ancient tradition, it was 100, yeah?
Yeah.
And my next point is that in ancient--
the reason why they see histories written 100 years
after the fact is because that's the way it was done.
That's why I mentioned Joe Cephas there and people like that,
because sometimes they were writing about things
that had happened a century before.
And people say, well, how do they know about--
well, that is the way history was written.
So you have to look at the process by which the history is written also.
And again, subject to revision at all times.
So no, I'm aware of all this.
I want to get back to this thing about Lebanon, though,
before we ran out of time, because that was the final question
I wanted to ask you.
Because you and I didn't get to speak around that time.
It has fallen out of the headlines.
There's no news about it.
Basically.
Right.
But you do note that the French definitely got
involved in investigation.
And that is a key thing whenever you take note of who gets involved
in an investigation after a major event.
That's usually the person that's responsible for at least part
of that major event.
That's right.
Yeah.
So I want to get into this a little more, though,
because Lebanon is a little more significant than the modern concept
of what people say about it.
I mean, we know about the history and the different conflicts.
And oh, well, the people behind Hezbollah and Bovon,
it was just a government screw up here.
I found that hilarious, by the way, that it's just--
the government has become so ineffectual
that this is what happened accidentally.
I can't quite buy that.
Well, forget about when you say government,
use the word administration, which is just like a traffic
cop, let's say, or something.
It keeps things moving.
Because there is no government as you're
taught in civics if you are old enough to have taken that class,
which they don't teach anymore.
Which I know what you--
Yeah, what you will be looking at in the future
is an decentralized power base between southern Iraq,
like what would be the Arabian Sea there,
like the land of Er, if that rings a bell for anyone,
southern Iraq, like south of Babylon,
to Babylon, Jerusalem, and the Levant of Lebanon.
Those three areas are going to be a decentralized power base.
In other words, there's going to be a lot of action, both overt
and covert in those parts of the world, which right now
are very still, except for the Lebanon condition
that we just talked about.
Right.
No, that's the Jerusalem is another major point.
And all of this is based on divine consideration,
not secular stuff that you see.
Well, let me ask you why, because the way I see it is,
is it just related to the fact that these are historically
relevant spots on the internet?
OK.
And that's--
Yeah, we're chosen a very, very long time ago,
like pre-historical.
Yeah, see, that's the thing.
No, why?
I've always wondered this, by the way.
Why?
It's a mess.
If you look at the map of the world,
and you do a cross-section, especially the flat maps that
go against the wall, just do a cross-section.
The major mass is Asia, Africa, and Europe.
They're all connected, except for various canals.
If you do an X through them, from the top right Russia
to the south, bottom left of Africa,
top left of Europe, to the bottom right of India,
you'll see the X crosses right in the middle of those three
places.
It's also prophetic as well.
Point of convergence, though, at center mass,
based on the land mass that was known at that time.
That's Asia, Africa, yeah, which is the major of the Earth, yeah.
Yeah.
OK.
No, fair enough.
That's simple question.
Well, in essence, I get it from prophecy, biblical prophecy,
which there are many other prophetic writings and rites.
I call them holy rites of the world that are all in--
they can be harmonized.
But the reason I mention the biblical narrative
is because it gives the most information.
Well, indeed, a previous--
allegedly, in history, previous to this,
you have many other seemingly divinely inspired texts
that did contain some of this information as well.
Now, I don't know if it's a lack of preservation,
or if it's a lack of information that
was available to previous peoples or not,
because that's a good question, I think.
It's not that it's never available.
Yes, it can be.
Having a book even 200 years ago was very rare.
Like, if you went into a small town, what's going on here?
They'll say, well, we have a butcher and a baker.
And this guy here lives across the street.
He has a book.
Wow, he owns a book?
Wow.
I mean, that's how rare they were at one point, right?
But on the other hand, if you had a secret,
and you wanted to make sure it was kept secret,
you make a million copies and put it in the public library.
And no one will ever find out.
This is true.
Who even knows what a library is among people
that are younger than us, Greek, honestly?
So--
But here's the thing.
I wouldn't focus at all on the things
that people tend to focus on.
Do the opposite, and you'll be better off.
You should always increase your honor, dignity,
lawfulness, and morality.
But also increase the level of food, clothing, and shelter.
There's a really great future that no one knows anything
about that's coming.
I mean, no one meaning the corporate, no one.
There are plenty of people that do know, but not that many,
meaning they're in the hundreds or a few thousand.
They know what's coming.
And it's going to be wonderful.
And it's going to be such a wonderful surprise
that I think that all of this crap, recent or not,
will be forgotten.
Right.
Well, and here we are, like I say, I do feel
as though this is an interesting time period
because the transition will be evidence within the next few years.
I just-- I wonder about the difficulty of the road ahead.
Oh, it'll get very difficult because it's going to test your--
well, how do you say the level of tolerance
or the robustness of the human, both spiritual and physical?
The thing is, they're both-- humanity is both weak, spiritually,
and both physically weak as well right now.
And they're going to be pushed to the limit.
And most will not make it.
When I say most will not make it in this--
in this, what we call reality now, the reality that's set up
by the corporations, the state, the secret societies,
the religions, your education system, all that.
Yeah, it's in very-- you're in very bad shape.
But you're resilient enough, ultimately.
And you have friends in high places that will eventually
help the general humanity.
99.9% of the people are going to come out fine on the other side
in the real reality, which is a reality of consciousness.
Here's the interesting thing.
It's all about raising-- when I say honor, dignity,
lawfulness, and morality, that's a consciousness thing.
So it's what happens in your heart and your soul
and your mind, which is your spirit.
And that affects your soul, your metabolism.
So if you read ancient texts, especially the biblical text,
what people don't understand is that it's one cohesive document.
There's no old and new.
And it seems limiting because of the quote unquote laws.
But once you do those laws, there are disciplines
that raise your consciousness once you do them.
It's kind of like the wax on, wax off karate kid.
He didn't understand what that whole discipline was about
until he was made aware of what the discipline was about.
And here's something that I've been discussing more in private.
I call it the existential threat to the universe.
And what I mean by that, I'll preface this this way.
Let's just follow this scenario.
One day, everyone goes outside no matter where you are in the world.
And you see these huge spaceships, right?
And it just scares humanity so much that all the countries
put down their weapons and they stop fighting
and they get into peace agreements.
We can depend on the state scenario again, basically.
Yeah, a week after that, all the ships fire on the earth
and kill everyone on the earth, except for one guy.
And he says, well, you guys present themselves.
And guys says, why did you kill us?
We made peace on earth.
He says, yeah, well, we didn't--
we made you to be a warlike race.
So we can take you and bring you out here
into the universe and fight wars with us.
But since you wanted peace, we had no use for you.
So we wiped you out.
Where do you read and where do you not read that the gods are not
warlike?
They're always warlike.
We're being--
I am suggesting that we are being bred spiritually,
as larva goes to the next metamorphosis,
what I call resurrection reincarnation, what have you,
the next level or the afterlife, let's say,
to be a warrior class to protect this universe
as we can conceive it from an existential threat
of beings that are not created and are not gods and are not
human.
They are a totally different life form.
And if you got this information now,
you would just scare the pitons out of you.
But you cannot get the briefing on this
until you go to the next level, in other words,
until you get into what's called the afterlife.
Well, right.
I'll end with that because that's a real fantastic approach
to what all this means.
But you've got-- you know why I said that because no one else is.
So--
No, and fair enough.
I recently slipped on a show.
And because I was asked about prayer, basically.
And--
Stop right there, prayer.
Stop using the word prayer because it evokes religious
sediment, which could be negative in many cases.
You know what prayer really is?
Good.
Telepathy.
Anyway, well, just think about that.
True.
But you're practicing telepathy.
I interpreted it to that level.
And taking a look, I take people's words
and I have to reinterpret them because they
use very blunt instruments and prayers as a blunt word.
And it evokes a whole bunch of connotations that don't belong
to it.
But in the practice that a lot of people
would understand as prayer, I know who I'm talking to.
And I know I'm talking to the gods of war.
And I said that.
And I got a little bit of crap for it.
What do you mean of the ancient pantheon,
these people bought?
No, no, no, no.
Well, they're God, actually.
Right.
That would be Yahweh.
No one uses that term.
And that term has been hijacked.
And that name has been hijacked.
Which is why I don't use it.
I don't use it.
But the thing is, I also know.
The aspect of telepathy, depending
on which circles you roll in is valid or invalid,
but I believe is more accurate than saying prayer.
But I know my telepathy is going to the god's poor--
correct.
OK.
And I also know that I am passing whatever it is I can pass to them.
I know that I am definitely addressing the gods of war.
I know this.
And--
Well, let me put it this way.
If you're not a god of war, you're not going to be around.
Well, there you have it.
Because there is a war of the gods also, which is--
that's the divine economics concept.
Economics just means rules of the house.
It goes beyond finances.
So typically in academic circles, especially in the 19th century,
if you look at certain treatises, the economy of such and such,
it meant how that culture functioned.
So what I would suggest is that increasing one's consciousness--
and I don't mean in the new age-- the new age
is bringing up the context and the subject matter,
but they fall flat on their faces when they
try to resolve it in any rational way.
You know, I say the new age movement at large.
But you'll notice in the new age movement,
they talk a lot about consciousness, right?
And that's what this all is about, because that comes first.
The ether, consciousness, the mind is the station
from which everything else emanates from.
And that is based on a form of aggression
that cannot be understood right now.
It's a form of dynamics that cannot be understood or comprehended
right now.
But it doesn't mean that you can't lean on the subject matter
in the way that it's been presented for thousands of years.
And it's not the way that people think about it now.
No, and it's certainly not this very--
I don't know what to call it.
Again, the new age is sort of generality
that you see regarding this.
There is indeed a way to elevate consciousness,
and you already spoke to that.
It is through the actions.
Through honor, dignity, morality, and lawfulness.
Right.
And that is not necessarily easily achieved.
It is a bit of work if you're accustomed to the customs.
So--
Well, you can't do it without knowledge.
True.
And martial art, for example, when I recently
been on Skype, I'll talk about martial arts.
And a lot of the things that you do here are true.
But you have to practice all of your waking hours, 12 to 15 hours a day,
every day, for a few years to be able to walk through a wall.
But the moment you walk through the wall
and say you've achieved it and stopped practicing for three days,
you can't do it anymore.
You see, so consciousness is on the same thing.
It's something that you adapt, like a higher operating system
where it becomes natural.
You don't have to think about it because it resolves itself
through your actions.
But without knowledge, you have nothing to resolve.
Most people don't know what lawfulness is.
And there's no need for it because they
forfeited their position to.
In other words, the condition of the earth,
humans are a commodity.
Right.
You're no longer men and women.
And commodities like doorknobs, nails, bananas, whatever, right?
Don't require knowing the law because they're just a commodity.
So, yeah.
When you break out of that, you'll realize--
here's an example.
You could look up a sovereign state, which
is neither sovereign nor a state.
Like the Federal Reserve is neither federal nor does it have reserves.
A sovereign state is what everyone in the UN is or most countries
now are.
And it's a juridical fiction.
Right.
It's a corporate entity.
And that has owners and shareholders that have everyone
subscribed to that system.
But if you look at all of the laws,
they've left all of the lawful laws in place.
You see?
Because they're almost--
you know, the people who own the world
or think they do, or it's been granted to them
to be in that position, like to have fun also.
They eventually do like to see some people that will go
and approach what's lawful and present it if they need to.
The pawns don't.
Like if you run into a regular attorney or a doctor
or a cop or a priest and you bring up what's lawful,
they're going to think you're crazy.
But as you go higher and higher and higher in private,
never in public, they do honor that.
Meaning the people.
You know, as you go up the wrong.
So if you bring up lawfulness or what's right,
or what's in the law, for example, in the American laws,
or whatever country you're in, they've still left,
they've still left laws in there that are pretty good.
And actually, you'll notice the things that people
are quote unquote charged with really doesn't apply
to them based on definition.
But if you're getting finding yourself in trouble,
you're dealing with too low on the totem pole,
which I call the pawns.
And just to interject, one of the things, one of the reasons
they did the the pandemic with the virus thing,
because I think I've talked privately that contagions
are only contagion.
You know, we've talked on the container, nothing
goes in or out of the body, right?
The body has to reproduce it through induction.
And there's plenty written about this.
It's just not acknowledged as it should be.
In other words, if you have a pandemic or a disease
that's contagious going around, you have to have the same format
as the person who is carrying it to be subject to that infection.
If you change the way you're formatted, let's say,
I have something called, or anybody can make
a acquiesce argentum, which is a silver solution,
or even soda.
If you take soda, you know, baking soda and water, anything,
if you have a certain diet, right?
You will not be subject to that infection,
unless it's extremely virulent, like the type
that if you contract, it kills you in a few hours.
That's different.
So the reason why they were able to pull this off,
as they did, is because you have these medical practitioners,
by the way, they get a doctor's degree,
and they get a state license, and they open up a local practicing
clinic, right?
You've seen them all over the place, all your life.
And their whole mode is to-- they don't know what they want
to do.
They have no inspiration, so they just become a doctor.
And they know that if they fill up their office
with appointments, they get $150 to $500 per head per day,
and it's easy money.
And occasionally, if they can't diagnose someone,
it's a writer prescription, because that's all they can do,
is they say, oh, you need to find a specialist,
because you have some viral infection.
And they brush off people that they can't diagnose
as having a viral infection.
And they've been doing this now for almost 30 years,
and people have been buying it.
So you can have something that's completely very simple,
allergic, because of toxin, or whatever.
And they tell you it's a viral infection.
Oh, and everybody agrees.
So they plant.
They created fertile ground for the virus
to be the new bookie man, based on these worthless medical
practitioners known as local doctors.
Well, fair enough, believe it or not, we're almost out of time here.
And I believe it.
I know you don't mean to say that there is not a actual contagion.
It is, but it is not as described yet.
Not as a contagion.
Let's just put it this way, and this is for sure.
It's never some vial in a lab or whatever.
The people that actually know how to do it are mostly dead.
They kind of sequestered the information 100 years ago.
And the way you create a pandemic
has nothing to do with laboratories with frozen samples.
And I'm not going to discuss that publicly ever.
So--
Well, there you have it.
And the Greek, I say again, always unique.
And I'm not just trying to rhyme, my friend,
but this was a fascinating two hours.
And I appreciate you taking the time to speak with me
because a lot of information has been packed into these two hours.
So anyway, guys, I am really a celly.
All of you are indeed the effect.
Please support the network.
What else can I say?
I'm not a good pitchman.
But if you gained something from this,
it would be a hoove you to exchange something for it on occasion.
Anyway, have a good night.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(music)