If you're chilly effect, it's sponsored by wallsthruido.com and listeners like you.
And now, the most aggravated point is on media.
Check or Shelley.
January 23, 2023, allegedly, according to that thing we call a counter.
And I'm going live a few minutes late on the stream, but of course if you're catching this further on down,
via your final cycle of choice, your applicable application, you don't care.
And besides that, is that actually the day?
Is that the date? That is what they call it on the Pope's work schedule.
Uh-oh, this sounds familiar, doesn't it?
Why am I talking like this? Well, I've got the Greek with me and we're going to discuss publicly.
Something that's going to be available privately very soon.
And I'm really excited to discuss this with the Greek.
Virtually no preparation outside of the five, seven minutes that we just spent off air talking about it.
But a new project we're going to do and those of you that kind of missed Ohchelly in the Greek might have gotten a little upset that they took it off of YouTube because it went away with the rest of my channel.
And a couple other people posted Ohchelly in the Greek stuff and their channel's got taken down too.
I don't think it was because of Ohchelly in the Greek, not at all.
But it is what happens. So I'm reporting it to you.
Anyways, yeah, that's not really available except through my website or really at this point only through my archive.
Yeah, there's some people that have got recently someone downloaded in Europe.
He said he was he's splicing and dicing. He's got 750 edits out of all the episodes and said you've got the episodes all 40 hours.
You know what? I got them all on a file. One of those upload cloud things.
And he says, you know, you say 40 hours. I said, yeah, it's about 40 hours. It's 4040.00 exactly.
Yeah, think about the synchronicity on that. I mean, when do you get all those random episodes together?
And it ends. I said, it's about 40 hours. No, it's 40 hours exactly to the second zero zero zero four.
I was like, whoa, okay, because I like that number four, right? It's a middle of seven, right? So neither of us.
I have them, by the way. I have all of them. I don't I've never listened to them ever. I can't stand the way.
You know, something about echo. You know, when you hear stuff, I mean, I don't know if you like the way you sound, but I don't like the way I sound.
It's amazing. I'm still doing this with anyone or speaking.
I hate the sound of my voice. I've done more than 2,000 of my own presentations, right? And I hate listening to them even the few seconds I have to edit them.
I don't like my voice at all. I love my presenters. I like the sound of your voice. But I can't stand here. I hear myself by cringe. I don't like it.
Now, while they think is also there's the printing option. I have someone has 75 pages of transcripts and sort of rewrites that were sent to me also in a book form, believe it or not.
And I've gotten emails that are in excess of 25 to 30 pages like treatises on just collections of what I've said all grouped together.
So there's plenty of stuff out there. There used to be that can't. I mean, actually let me take that back. There's not much out there at all.
But there's stuff that can be put out there. It's just a quick guide. You know, this is for people who want to see the world for what it really is.
Not for what they think it is or that's the operative word thinking. But what they've been told and raised in, you know, it's nothing that's not like that at all.
So if you want to see things the way they are, not because I know how they are, but I have a certain knack of getting to cutting through all the stuff very quickly.
And sharing it with other people is the way to go. And also a lot of people have mentioned this in the past with you Chuck is I'll go out and I'll start speaking in a public market or something.
And I'll have a crowd of people within five minutes around me if it's not too busy. And always someone in there will yell out, hey, why don't you write a book?
I'm like, no, because if you write a book and publish it, what you're doing is actually presuming that whoever reads that book has any comprehension.
Right? Well, yeah, that's the trouble. Look, let me just run this by you because I didn't get these different treatises that you did, but I did get one in a PDF form that they they titled Planet Earth for Dummies.
Yeah, I think you shared that a little bit. I didn't look at it, but yeah.
No, but it was interesting because it was not just you and me, but the shows you did with Seth, the reports of and a bunch of different things.
And he, you know, he sent it to me just out of courtesy says, well, you know, you're you're mentioned in here. So I figured I should send you a copy.
But I don't think he distributed it very widely. No, but hold on a second. Let's go back. It can't be. It couldn't have been me because I don't do shows.
Well, no, it wasn't. Okay. Now here we go. It's a sonic event. That's for sure. Right. Very important.
You know, the thing called the legal society they wrap you up with words, right? Oh, yes. And the that's what all these secrets, you know, the secret handshake, the secret symbols.
Well, they overtly the legal society overtly pulls that puts out they tell you it's legal ease, but no one cares, right? So they.
Well, that's the significance of it. That's why they're treated so harshly. You know, they've been so but but look.
Words are very important. You know, and I've never stressed that. Right. Because I don't think I'm impeccable in my communication, but I'm a lot better than most in terms of communicating what I want to communicate.
You know, in terms of the subject matter, you know, that we could take a particular subject you and I in one hour dissect it or or pretty much in part more.
You'll more useful information and you'll get in a four year college degree, right? On whatever subject it is.
So it's that's not words. That's really putting words to stimulate thinking and making people aware of their surroundings.
But when I say words, I mean the actual word itself, the way it sounds and the way you read it and the way you understand it has an effect on the mind.
And your mind has an effect on your mind is what interacts with the environment, right? Like people say, well, you know, you see with your eyes and hear with your ears.
No, you see with your brain, right? You see with your mind and you see with your ears and magicians know that, right?
The ledger domain, press digit, digitation, they know that if they make a flamboyant motion, you're going to look there and then they make a subtle motion to produce the trick, right?
So that's not with the eyes because you see all of it, but you don't pay attention to the subtle part is where they produce the trick, let's say, right?
So it's always, you know, you hear with your, you know, most people that have eye and ear damage, not all, but most it's actually they examine the actual instrument known as the ear and all the accompanying components and the instrument known as the eye and all the accompanying components and there's nothing wrong with it.
It's fully functional within tolerance. It's really happening in the mind and the brain.
You see, so that's where the words go directly to it. Words bypass senses. So maybe we'll save this for a sonic event and well, here's one thing.
One thing that we do with Ocelli and the Greek stuff is you ever notice that whenever we bring up any subject, I always, always, always, every time make a practical example that is fully tangible and accessible to the listener.
Oh, of course. Like, for instance, we use the, you know, we show people etymology online and say, look, I mean, since you're talking about words for definitions. Yeah, for origins of words, right?
Because a dictionary is diction, how to pronounce the word. It's not the meaning of the word that changes. See, they did the dictionary because they wanted all the plebeans to pronounce the word similarly, but the definitions change.
Like, a good one is ground zero. Ground zero is a technical term that has to do with nuclear or atomic that nations, right? So anyway.
But the vernacular of ground zero has changed over time and has become adapted to mean different things. Right.
So for a very good reasons, right? Because it was a slip. The reason it was called ground zero initially, you know, down there in Manhattan is because that was point that was actually used.
Not in common parlance, but because someone was asking, what are you guys doing here? We're here. We can't talk where it ground zero. And then they blew up from there. It was actually used in its true technical form. Right? The inspectors that went there.
So, so, but the the common examples are, for example, when we talked about the container, the human body eating seasonally, you know, or when you have a wound or whatever, it's very practical, very, very, very practical.
So this is super practical stuff. And what I'd like to get into is, you know, I always say never share. I always give this as advice to never share more than 10% off the bat. What you know about something. Right?
Because someone's going to want to act like an asshole and debate you on whatever you should never debate either. Right?
Once you once you understand what you want to do with the information, which is use it to help yourself and help others. You have to help yourself first. Right?
And you give up, you know, more and more as the need and the situation arises. And there are many situations arise. You know, you can be a teacher and use it as a vocation, but then you have to get something for it.
Or you can just do it to genuinely help, but for altruistic reasons, but not too altruistic, because if you know what the world is and you see the world for what it really is. Right?
You will, you will tone down. You'll actually be much more conservative and much more conservative in a sense that more efficient.
Like, you all these people, by the way, that you hear out there screaming, "I'm mad as hell, I'm not going to take it anymore."
And they're complaining about the corporations and the politicians. They don't see the world for what it really is. They see the world through the lens that they were raised in. The collective, the masses, right?
And the other thing is you know what the world really is. You will not be mad. And by the way, if they told you they were going to make the world a total hell and everyone's going to start killing each other, you'll say, "Fine."
And if you say, "They say we're going to make the world a paradise," you'll say, "Fine." But either way, whether you want to make it into a total disaster hell, overtly or total paradise, I want nothing to do with it.
You see?
Well, there it is, the other option. You know, people started to use the metaphorical instruments of the red pill, the blue pill, you know. And I objected to that.
Oh, hold on. Hold on. Take them both. Take both of them, man. It's cool. Take both at the same time.
Well, there's that. Or how about this option? I don't want your pills. You know?
All right, but look, if you did, okay, yeah, of course. Obviously, you don't want to be in that situation like the castenate on Don Juan. He says, "Well, if you think you're so aware of all that, what if someone..."
He's to be suppressing the old man. He's saying, "What if someone in the distance has got a high-powered sniper rifle, a high-powered scope, and they've got it trained on your head and they're ready to pull the trigger? What are you going to do then?"
He says, "I would never be in that situation. I would never think of that, right?"
So it would never be in a situation where I had to try to take a pill. But it's very simple. It's kind of like the pessimist and the optimist is the glass half empty, and it was a glass half full.
Well, did you ever entertain that if that thought that if that is an issue, the glass is too big?
Mm-hmm, right? Because if the glass were a lot smaller, you would never entertain as it have full or have empty because it's to the top.
If it were half the size, it would be full already and there would be no debate.
Exactly. There's no issue. So the thing is, it's not whether it's half full or half empty to see what one's perspective.
You engineer, as you approach life as an engineer, above that, and you say, "Well, either question is denoting that you're complaining about the size of the glass."
Not what my perspective, you say?
Well, yeah, because the perspective is irrelevant if you say that the glass is half empty or half full.
One is a pessimist, one is an optimist. This is the training, you know, like the bullshit they put out there.
But if you say the glass is too big, does that make you a pessimist or an optimist, you see? That's a neutral position, isn't it?
Well, is that a neutral position or is that someone saying, "Look, if the glass is too big, then perhaps your problem is you wish to shape the things around you instead of accepting them."
And that's what everyone does anyway?
Well, there you have it. There's the punchline. I wasn't going to get to it right away, but there it is, right?
That's what you do anyway.
That is the issue.
If you're happy with the one size fits all, they've got plenty of those.
Well, see, and that's the thing that always bothered me. Why, even though I've done plenty of my own sonic events, right?
I've always been pushed by the listeners, and I listen to them.
I always take into account what it is they say, but they're always at me about, you know, you need to debate this. You need to confront this.
You need to, and I say, "Well, I am not really interested in the argument. I'm more interested in sharing information."
And the best information, the best quality information I can get on a particular subject, on a particular, this is what I try to do.
And this is, indeed, what I have done. And it's very odd.
You know, well, look, that's the same thing. The blue pill and the red pill. You brought it up, right?
The blue pill is you just go on, and the red pill is you see what it really is, let's say.
And then later on, we find out it's even beyond that when he meets the architect, right?
Because the architect's home that what you think is real is still is designed.
But this is the interesting thing. You do both because you can give quality information on what most people are harping about.
Oh, we got bad politics. Oh, there's chemicals. Oh, the wax or an anti-vax.
Oh, okay, that's the blue pill stuff, right? The red pill stuff is, of course it makes sense that you have this or this.
Because look, you see, historically, they told you why it's going to be like this. There's someone I know that lives in North Carolina about 10 years ago.
He went down to Congress with some other people. He has some credentials.
And he went to Congressman's office. You know, when they're in session, they're there for like a week or two. They show up every day in their office.
And they didn't know any of the codes and stuff. What, you know, definitions. They didn't know any of the major congressional acts.
They didn't know at all nothing. They were just sitting there, you know, whatever they watch CNN and whatever the scene and brings up is and they have handlers.
Tell them what the thing can say, all right. So that would be red pill. The blue pill would go to the congressman and ask them about what CNN says, basically, or Fox or whatever.
But everyone's talking about why, why did you approve this and, you know, or why did you do something about this or that? Yeah, yeah, that's the moment you started dressing what they're doing.
You missed the point, right? Because they're not, they don't exist. They're just placeholders. You know, it's kind of like someone I know I frequent this hardware store and they're always getting new employees and they're much older.
In the retirees. I've been in his two years, especially their older, aren't they? Yes, yes. And, and when I say, teach history has it, you know, it's all fit. So you worked in fiction, basically. And he says, no, and I just, you know, basically gave him an earful in 14 seconds.
15 seconds he was turning red. But basically, if you look at history, I've looked at history books from the 19th century. Right.
And, you know, it was, yeah, I lived in New York City. I had access to the New York City public library. And even then in the early late 80s and early 90s, when I would spend hours and hours every week there, I noticed books being taken away back then. Right.
So, although you must say that, that a public library like that in New York was quite, quite extensive.
You know, as compared to, you know, I was able to sit at the same place where Nikola Tesla sat. And do that because they had a little plaque here. This is where Nikola Tesla would come and pull as I said, I'm gonna sit here.
So, you know what I'm talking about in the New York public library, the one with the lines outside, you know, on 40, 40, and 40, and 50. Right. Right. They filmed that movie.
Is it the thing about the natural disaster, the like, you know, the winter bomb coming through and freezing here? Yeah, well, it's right by Brian Square Park there. Right. Right.
You know, they have a bathroom in Brian Square Park. It's a beautiful marble bathroom with flowers in that park. Across a quarter of a million dollars a year to maintain. If you use that bathroom there, it's beautiful. I never used it.
Oh, it's the outside. It's in the park anyway. We can start talking about stuff that might be irrelevant. But here.
It's important. Okay. The other thing is, can you communicate it? Do you have a good memory? And do you see the difference?
So, go back to the hardware store. Retire. They used to teach high school history.
Yeah. I basically said to him in the next few years, you'll go to college level history and you'll open it. It'll just be a picture of Daffy Duck and making mouse.
That's where it's at right now. It's all just so bizarre. It doesn't make any sense. It makes sense. Like if you went through a book, you know,
you know, didn't have anything of blank cover and you opened it and you saw cartoon characters, it makes total sense. Right? Because this is just a book of fictional cartoon characters.
There's nothing they get angry about, right? But the minute you write this is history on it, well now you have a reason to be pissed. Right? You see?
So, I don't mind that what they're printing in universities, forget about high school. That's junk. First of all, I stopped my education at the eighth grade, meaning through the public school and private school system.
After the eighth grade, I just went, "Lala, I didn't pay attention to anything at all." Enough to get by. I knew it was damaging. It was total crap.
This is, you know, about 13 or whatever, but I didn't go to the eighth grade, by the way. I went from 7 to 9. But anyway, they wanted to get rid of me.
So, but that's, you know, a general, if I say eighth grade, you get a picture. So, you don't need that. But here's the thing.
The moment you take that book of cartoon characters and fictional stories and you say, "This is history," you still shouldn't get mad. You know why? Because all these history books, they just say their history, American history, your P and history of World History,
do you see the book on the binder, right? But you know why you still shouldn't get upset? Because it doesn't say true history, does it?
No, it doesn't. And the fascinating thing about that is what I call "historeography." Right. But it doesn't say true history. So you still don't have...
So when you turn on the TV and they tell you "grounds zero now" means this, it doesn't mean it's a true meaning, does it?
Well, that's the thing about this. I want to actually ask you a question because here we go. "Historeography." Okay. Now I know I'm using some of the words here that, you know...
Yeah, it just means the writing or pictures or written somehow about history. It's about history, the history of history in other words, right?
Yeah, the writing of history, literally.
So what's interesting to me about this is, look, if you and I were to go back in time and open up a history book, okay, during the same time period, because I finished the 12th grade,
but only because I thought I needed this high school diploma, you know, and also they told me I couldn't. So these were two things that motivated me to do.
Oh, no. Hold on. If you're 13 years old, you get a GED and you're done with it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I know. But I have to wait. I tell people all the time, get them out of this. Just get a GED equivalency at 13 and get the hell away.
Well, I would have been better off, but I did finish up to the 12th grade. So if you and I were to go back to the time when I was in high school and open up a history book,
it is not written the same way, even though let's just say they were describing the 1960s or they were describing the 1860s or the 1760s.
It's irrelevant. It is now written entirely differently if we go to that very same classroom today and go ahead and take a look at their history book.
It's a different history. The history is now different.
Columbus held the ocean blue in 1492. When did it make it to the history books, not until the early 19th century, the 400 years, almost later, 300, such years.
So what's what happened a hundred years ago is not going to make it into the history books for another 300 years, but it won't matter because everything's going to be shut down and lost.
And very soon, by the way, meaning, you know, within a decade, right?
Well, even the French, even the French with their literal terminology perspective used to have this idea that you could not adequately write about a historical event until 75 years after its occurrence.
Sure. Sure. In Rabbinical lore, it's a hundred in the Judean Jewish culture.
Right. It must be one hundred years. One hundred years according to their calendar.
Right. Which is very tricky about falsifying, too, because if you look up the Hebrew New Year, what year it is, it's 300 years off because they need to hide certain things.
Right. Right. But I'm just saying according to their calendar, it ends up being a hundred years.
But either way, you don't want to use a calendar. You want to use lawful time. Well, but there you have it. And there goes the very first lesson, I think, that we went through the very first, a sonic event that we went through, I think, was just that.
Oh, look, September seven, October is eight. No, of them is nine, Dec. 10 January 11. So it's around the 18th day. And we go by the moon, does the month, the sun does the day.
The equinox, which is a measurement at night, does these change of seasons from one to seven. Right. And this is what, by the way, the cockroach is the birds, the whales, the plants, the oceans, they go by what I'm saying. Right.
So if you completely, you know, the materialist will detach from that and go, you know, the, there's more and more people that are talking about what a scam, the calendar is, right.
And more and more people are doing about what a scam, all religions are. Right. Well, there's even someone talking about the Catholics and the Protestants are very different. I say, OK, I know they're very different because the Catholics say Santa Claus has got a size shoot 10, 10 size shoe.
And the Protestants say he has a size eight. But if you tell them that there's no Santa Claus, what happens? Then it's like dumping the water on the which of the West. They both disappear. You see. Right. Right.
There's no, you see my point. What size you're going to argue? What size shoes? And most people say Greek. That's not what they're arguing, but I know. But look, nothing. There's right.
It's as relevant as, OK, because they're arguing exactly. Thank you. You know, it's it's like telling you, you know, that look, I believe the tooth fairy can fly. You don't.
You know, the tooth fairy has to take a bus. Well, you know, what is the difference between the years. But here's the thing you can't go quote unquote in the bait or an argument with these people, whether whether, you know, red pill, blue pill or the Catholic Protestant, whatever, whatever.
Politician, on, but unless you know their stuff, you have to know their stuff. Right. So the thing is you don't detach and say that's not from you see a lot of the new age is, oh, I don't know any, you know, they don't know anything about these systems of the world. They want to do this.
They want to do this, are you fairy stuff? And you got to know both. So you got that's what's it. Take the blue pill take the red pill, right? And we talked about how these things work. In other words, when you take something into the body, you don't absorb it, right? Your body has to recognize it.
And then it goes to work on it. So if I do any of the secrets of the universe in Sanskrit, you can't read it. What's the point? You know, I mean, it's just when it comes down to you know, the secrets of the universe are written in every language.
But can you piece it together? There you have it. But what I'm saying is if there is no chance of comprehension to begin with, there is no point. So you got to find a common way in order to relate these things to people.
That is, that is, that is always the trouble, something. And I got to tell you it's gotten strange.
As as we discussed years ago, and I was thinking about this, I think we started what year did we start according to, you know, the Pope's what they're around 25 eight years ago, let's say eight year, whatever you want to figure it out. Yeah, I was like, what fall spring.
It's fall on the fall of eight years ago.
And we were seven and seven years and six, seven months, something like that. And the 2015 is what the date on some of these things are.
The thing about it is those conversations back then, even with the common say parlance of the of the day, do not match up anymore because there have been all these shifts like you were talking about now they've given you a new definition, they've given you a new meaning to.
No, but if I hold on a second, they, they do match up in a prophetic way that stuff that we discussed there that I gave very stark warnings about have come true.
Yes, well, that's where I was going is that regardless of the fact that and it sounded to some people and I heard from many people about this, you know, especially one guy that, well, I'm not going to mention his name actually.
I don't know if you can.
It's a vocat, but the thing is this guy said to me at the time, this guy is trying to start a cult. And I said, not I don't think so.
You know, I listen, it's possible I could be what I'm trying to do is find other like minded people so my life gets a little easier.
Well, it does instead of getting up at three in the morning and thinking about something for three hours, I could say, hey, I could go back to sleep because tomorrow I'm going to call so and so I will have a little talk about it.
Well, right.
You see what I mean? And that is, but that is that is the process and but it's so a cult would be like that star Trek episode where they go to a planet and the guys there alone and he makes robots to be his friends.
Something like that.
That's a cult.
I suppose so. I mean, maybe it's well, there's a lot of star Trek stuff we could go into.
I don't want to go to any culture easy to form.
Yes. All these and these whistleblowers and all these guys, you know, they say they're whistleblowers and many things, you know, and whatever they're easy to get you can pull a lot over the
pull a lot over the public's eyes and get them in a belief stuff very quickly and adamantly and take their money or take their wives or whatever.
But that's, you know, then that means that you are doing it because you're part of the world like the people that are wealthy are at the top of a shit heap and what they get as a prize is a polish turd, right?
So, you know, that's that's essentially what the cults do.
Right. But what I wanted to get out here is is this other problem that has emerged and the funny thing is if you'd listen to those early episodes, not you Greek obviously, but you.
Anything to us anyone. If you listen to those early episodes, you would have heard the warning that we were going to enter a time where just the act of communication was going to become challenged.
And it has happened in, I mean, you know, not yet.
Oh, I don't think not yet. I think it's already happening.
No, not yet. Yeah, the censorship is not it. There's going to be okay.
When it's going to get worse, it's going to get shut down the internet's going to shut down just like some kind of, you know, accident, they're going to blame it on something, of course, I'm going to be ridiculous, just like the pandemic thing.
Oh, I want to go to the internet, but let's slow it down a little.
Because I want to get to something else. It's not about the internet. It's not about that kind of communication.
What I'm saying is that the ability to simply observe something and mutually be able to say, look, this is what this is is being challenged is being defied.
It seems like with people attempting to converse with one another, okay, where they literally look at the same thing.
And we now have the observation being more important than the reality of the thing.
And this keeps happening over and over again. And this is why people, it's like there is no point in that debate even even if you want it to be victorious and debates and things like that.
At this point in time, what I observe, understand is that they, we are in a time when the censorship is changing because now there is even less of an ability to have a common, you know, what they, what they call again, we'll go to the legal system per second.
Were you stipulate to something, okay?
Sure. No, but it's all controlled. Well, the censorship was controlled. I think I warned of it because you're going to go into an ultra conservative return to lawfulness supposedly.
And it's all done by the same people. And this is going to be in the next few years or a 2025 is a benchmark time, especially if you see the geographic political changes in the Middle East that I've talked about.
But, but the time is all controlled. In other words, the censorship and lifting of the censorship look, information is like traveling.
So the purpose of 9/11 was to restrict travel. Right.
And the, and travel is also information. In other words, whether it's by post or digital or whatever, the only difference with digital is that it's, it's, it's, it can be instant meaning within 20 minutes something can go around the world several times of audio and video.
So that's a form of traveling. The freedom or the openness of the internet is by design and shutting it down is by design. Just like years ago, you were able to build a car or buy a car and drive around freely.
And now you have to have license, insurance, insurance, registration and all this other stuff, right? Right.
So this same thing is going to happen with the internet.
You know, but that's, yeah, there's already, I assure you by 2025, what I'm talking about is the restructuring of information flow will for sure will happen by then. Most likely it'll be in the fall of 2023, 2024 or by 2025 for sure.
Well, that's why I'm bringing it up now because I'm saying that we already see the indicators of what's coming because the ability to stipulate between two people about seemingly anything.
Well, hold on a second. Where are the people? There's only a few. I think on one of the sonic events we went through this less than 5% of the people, quote, quote, whatever billions they say exist are really people.
If you know what I mean. Oh, yeah. Well, I look the rest are just.
I can call them NPCs, call them shells, husks, space heaters, you know, because they take up space, give off heat. And I'm talking about this is on a spiritual level. They could be your family members. They could be your children. They could be your parents. They could be your coworkers. They could be your boss.
Right. But honestly, I fortunately have the ability to spot them very quickly. And I teach other people how to do it. And we will actually talk about how to spot them in the future when we get this thing started.
No, that's something that we're going to need to address. And I assure you it'll be nothing you've ever heard before.
Well, and that's the other thing. The last thing I want to hear is, oh, the Greeks just talking about what he talked about before. You're not going to get any of that. Do a quick rehash, but you're going to hear stuff you've never heard anywhere before. I assure you that.
Well, and it's also going to be done in a much, you know, excuse the terminology here, but a tighter format because we used to do the two hour show. That's how we started with the, you know, with the two hour presentation.
How am I going to worry about the show? Yeah, I'm sorry. I knew that way. I already called myself. I felt it on the telepathic highway. Yeah. My apologies.
But the two hour presentation, the two hour sonic event, I'm saying we shouldn't be two hours. No, I don't think so. I don't, I don't think you require it. And I don't think it's necessary. As a matter of fact, I think that we'll be able to do it in less than one hour according to the, and that's another thing.
People are even starting to argue about time, which was a common stipulation between people, right? Too long, you mean? No, well, I think I think it is too long. The two hours. I think it can be two hour format. I think we can do it in one. But you want to show and it could always be a part two.
Yeah, I think there was no harm in breaking it down because this is too, so they can digest it.
And that's what I'm thinking is that, you know what, it's wonderful to have, you know, time, but how old on how often you want to do it once a week, twice a week, I think twice a week is pretty good. So each week is part one part, too, maybe.
That was the thing I wanted to find out from you because really honestly, I mean, I'm busy at creating sonic elements constantly. So this is what I'm going to be doing anyway. It's more about what you have time to do. If you want to do it twice a week, I think I heard you.
You ready? We'll do one hour a week, like you said. And then the second hour, I'll just do it on my own and then send it over to you and it gets uploaded.
So we have one hour with a cell in the Greek and then an hour of the Greek.
Look, if you like the two hours, because I think two hours on a topic is not enough. So if you get four hours on a topic from the Greek, it's like getting a graduate master's degree on the subject.
Not because I'm, you know, whatever it's just like, look, I get emails, right? And I don't think anymore because I'm not getting the right messages.
Well, do you think that we would service better to do just like a singular three hour presentation?
No, no, no. Well, yeah, yeah, well, we could know that I think being conservative with your time is paramount at the moment until we get a response.
So if you, I think an hour with you and I and then an hour or two hours, I'll send you, I could record it on the, you know, on the whatever and send you the file and then you upload it.
Okay. Just just to be conservative on your time and also less wear and tear on you. I'm wearing a tear meaning, you know, oh, man, I've got, you know, what, 20 hours, 30 hours a week, you know, I'm talking, you know, eventually it's going to, you know, it's going to break you down, right?
Well, right. But I mean, this is well worth and here's the thing. It's about priority. This is well worth my time. So I'm not objecting to doing.
Well, see how it goes. I think, I think let's do, you know, whatever, whatever works. But I think we'll, we'll base it on, on, on the feedback that we get.
Look, I was going to say this. I read all the emails I get on the uncommon radio.
But I haven't been responding to them for about a year. And the reason why is because I see it doesn't go anywhere. This is 90% of the emails out of this, like, 3000 or 4000 emails that I've gotten 90% of them are broken down as two. They're all identical.
One of them is, hey, where can I get more information on your stuff? I can't find it anymore or are you doing anymore? Okay. Me, me, me, me, feed me, feed me like the little birds.
The other one is so it's like, okay, nothing, nothing about like, what can I do to help? I do this and that, right?
Okay, because they're used to that, you know, you lead, I follow. I don't know looking for that. Okay, the other emails that I get is, hey, Greek, your stuff is great.
It's the best stuff I've heard. I'm like, that's another garbage email because I know my stuff is great. Not because I'm saying from an ego point of view. If it wasn't great, I wouldn't have the urge or good. I wouldn't have the urge to be...
It's not because you're great. It's because the information is great. I would like to write it or coach, look, talking about debates, you know? Someone wanted an academic wanted to debate me and I said, no, but I'll get into the debate, the answer to that.
But basically, don't tell me my stuff is good. It's, first of all, it's not my stuff and it's not me. The only reason I'm saying is I'm embarrassed for humanity that no one else is.
You see, so those 90% of the emails I get are those two categories. Give me more, give me more, or your stuff is good, your stuff is good. I know, I know, I know. So, I'm not getting any quality feedback at all.
So, why should I be... Part of it, you know, why should I continue? But the other thing is, why don't we go a little... why don't we go to the next step?
Why don't we go to the stuff that I've been sitting on for two decades or a decade or five years? I'm coming up with new stuff all the time, not coming up as in terms of creation, but discovering and piecing things together. Why don't we just go to the next level? So, we gave 10%.
Let's go 11, 12, 13, 15, 20%, 25, 30, 40, 50% more and see what response is because we're at a different, you know, we're on a different part in reality right now, right?
So, that's it. So, yeah, by the way, if you do send emails, yeah, I read everything, but I don't respond because it's for the reason that I said.
The purpose of really being public initially, even back in the days of Venice, and before that, with Seth on Revolution Radio back in like 2010, and with some talk shoes and all that, was to find other like-minded people.
Right. So, we can work on these things and, you know, am I going crazy that the Pope's work schedule is piece of rubbish or, you know, am I going crazy that we're on legal time and we don't know what lawful time is anymore? Am I going insane? You know, I want to any to bounce this off with other people, right?
You know, am I going crazy because I look at the human body and it's completely sealed, nothing passes through the skin or the intestines or any of the organs and it's just like a steel belted tire, you know.
Am I going crazy that I see that this is by induction and not absorption? Is there anybody else out there work with me?
No, I understand much like I tried to explain and people think I'm nuts with the whole thing about the sun and, you know, how it does not actually provide light, it's not a giant light bulb in the sky.
And that's just observable to me, been through that many a time and, you know, I don't know, just ricochets off of people's ears, so to speak.
Yeah, I get it. Of course, you have a lot of information that you've been able to put together concisely and present.
You know, and I'm rattling around this idea as to whether we should start with two hours. I don't know, you know, we could just go for the two hours and do it twice a week.
I think the twice a week intervals are probably the best idea, but I'm trying to think about the amount of time should be in each one.
That's your overthinking. Wait till you see the subject matter. We haven't even discussed what we're going to be talking about.
Oh, that's the thing. I think we can frame it as we go. It is pretty easy. It's the same stuff we talked about before but further.
Because what else is there? If you look at all the subjects we covered, I mean, is there any other subject that we didn't cover? That's of any importance at all?
Not much. I mean, you explained.
Well, if we, let's say we want to talk politics and why people are unhappy, are we going to discuss it the way everyone else is? And should we?
Because if you take the red pill and the blue pill together, what the hell? Right? What's going to happen? It's neither. Right.
You've got to take the blue look like we said earlier, if you're going to go into any kind of a viable discussion, viable to them.
Because first of all, with the religion stuff, someone who has a particular faith in a conventional religion is not good in the head. Right? It's not sane. Right? This is a very well-known, but it's a fact. It's well-established.
If you're going to have a viable discussion, meaning what they think is viable. Right? You have to know their stuff. You can't go into a, even a basic conversation with someone and everything you're saying is completely new to them. We're different.
They're going to go and they're going to shut down. They're going to go into complete dissonance. Right.
So you have to resonate with them, but you have to show them with their own stuff. What's going, it's contradicting.
But look, the political stuff is not understood very simply because you've never been taught the situation of any national, let's say, status, any country.
And when you look at the status of any country, you'll notice that they don't exist anymore. We're living under a worldwide, what do you want to call it? Umbrella, hospice of control. Right?
So then you see how it became that way, and then the rest of it's irrelevant.
Oh, right. Well, if you're, see, but there's that other point of view about becoming a citizen of the world or of the planet, this kind of thing.
Where, you know, how about we face that? We are all indeed breathing, right? And oh, and by the way, that's another thing that came up in a recent question, which was one of the most relevant questions because a bunch of people sent me feedback about they were happy to hear that.
We would return to doing some sort of sonic presentation. But they, there was a question about spirit. Okay. So I want to address that actually because I did assure that individual that I would address it with you because we discussed this before. What is a spirit?
And what is spirit in general? And I know I started off that discussion, according to my memory, about talking about how there is, you know, look, you, you, what, what do you do when you conspire? Well, you breathe together. See how the word spirit starts to come up.
Okay, because you are cooperating. That is the, the con which makes you work together. Okay, and you're breathing together. That's, that's the root of the word conspiracy, right? So the thing is that when one does these things, you know, the spirit is the breath.
Okay, hold on Chuck. Yeah.
All right. That's how I had to get the analogy. You know what dendro chronology is? It's like, you know, they, it's that dendros tree chronologies time. These guys that study tree rings and all this other stuff. And I just have these academics come over here and talk to me. And I said, look, I'll listen to your dendro chronology thesis. If you can explain to me how a blade of grass grows.
Okay. And they can't. So how the hell are you going to deal with trees, which are far more complex and substantial than a blade of grass? If you know nothing about a blade of grass? So the spirit is very simple. Let's, let's use the botanical purpose analogy.
So someone's got an ailment and, and the quote unquote establishment can't figure out a remedy for it or cure. So they discover someone discovers whether it's through tradition rediscovered, it was lost or by experimentation, a particular plant leaf.
If you take that extract or eat the plant, it cures or relieves the the ailment with me. Yes. Okay. Now someone who spiritual is going to study where the plant grows.
And what the plant looks like the seasonality of the plant and all this. But a materialist, the first thing that they want to do is they want to take the plant and find out what chemical in the plant is is in there that that cured and make a pill.
You see the difference? Well, yes, because one would want to use the energy, the plant, the actual thing itself, which collected the energy.
And actually use it that someone else represents what the plant represents and you when it goes back to what the ailment that made what the what made the individual seek the remedy was the ailment and the ailment is an energetic problem that manifests physically.
When you see a house burned down in a fire, that's an energetic problem. Yeah, the fire you, but you know, fire is energy, right? Right. It's the heat. You could, you know, if you had, let's say, a big plasma ray, you could vaporize the house or whatever. Also, it's not the plasma. It's not the fire. The house is gone. It's the energies. Once it was there. Now it's not this. That's the realm of spirit. It's a non material thing.
So the, how do you break the brainwashing? Look, like recently, there's this little thing that you that went between people and made them sick, right? They were the virus, right? It doesn't exist. And, you know, the deeper you, it doesn't exist, right? It does what they're calling a virus is mitochondria in the blood from broken down tissue and liver dysfunction, just like anyway.
So the energy, like, for example, you know, a male and a female are different energies, right? Summer and winter. Different energies, right? The moon and the sun, different energies. Right? And then you go within each species, you know, a chihuahua has different energy than let's say a mastiff, full mastiff, right?
Absolutely. Right? So when you start looking at the energies, there's an ancient, Taoist way, I refer back to it, why reinvent it? If something's good enough, use it, right?
Like we're using, you know, the English language right now. Imagine we invented a new language and wanted to do a cell in the Greek. Well, they have to learn the language first. Otherwise, they would no one would understand what we're talking about.
So when you're going to discuss spirit, you have to use the language of spirit and sadly to say, if you start using that language, speaking English, by the way, no one will understand what you're talking about. Because it's a foreign language to them.
So it's very easy to see the difference between male and female physically. And it's, but what's interesting about it, the energy level is also the type of energy that one exudes is also easy to see. Right?
But, you know, I think we went into this before, you know, you were discussing the effects of the moon on the tides and, you know, if any good farmers, Almanac, you certain things if they're not planted during the full moon, they just don't come up, right? Right?
Well, you know, was it the light of the, no, it's the energy of them. And so you want, so teaching the language or learning the language or acquiring the language, I don't think it could be taught. I think it can only be acquired. You know, the difference of teaching and acquiring, right?
Teaching usually means you have a teacher in a student acquiring means you pick it up and find it on your own. Right, right.
But it's nice like if you're changing a tire on the side of the road, you know how to change it. It's fine. But if someone comes along and helps you, doesn't, you know, more hands make the work a lot lighter, right?
Of course, yeah.
So that's the purpose of you. I found you cannot teach anyone anything. It's best if they acquire it and you just help them along if you're able to do it.
Oh, in train, look, I told you I used to train people, you know, in business. That was one of my main jobs. And that's exactly what I used to do is, no, I'm going to have you do this. And I will assist you along the way.
And that was the best methodology for them to retain any of the routines or any of the things that they had to know in order to go on in their circumstances, whether it was a cashier or teaching somebody lottery or teaching them how to keep books or whatever.
That's what it was always. No, you're going to do it. And I'm going to guide you a bit.
They have to have in Spanish that call it ganas means the desire. If you don't have the desire, it's any Nate desire. Sometimes you might have a desire that you want to acquire knowledge or acquire something.
And you didn't know you had that desire until it was somehow introduced to you.
You know, how many times do you hear people took a career path? And it was very different from what they thought it would be because one day they walked in and heard about something and then their whole life change in that moment.
That desire, it's not that their whole life change and they suddenly developed that desire was latent.
It was sitting there. It was just was not sparked. It wasn't turned on. They just needed that one little spark.
Right. You see? Right. And there is the, we talked also about the inspiration. Here comes that that's spire, that word again.
That's right. Look up the word. It's very interesting word inspiration. It's divine. That's the thing we'll get into with the NPCs. Most people do not have the divine in them.
Right. Well, unfortunately, yeah, the, the, the, the, the, namaste if you will, you know, that, that is an interesting little phrase that means quite a bit more than people give a credit for.
But the idea of recognizing divine in another as you recognize it within yourself is, is a fair and lawful thing to do.
The ones that are locked up in the concerns of this world and get angry about the way things are going are not happy with the way things are going.
Or the ones that have diminished spark. And then there are those that are below that, which are the great masses.
By the way, when I talk about people being moronic and I educated, I'm not talking about the masses. I'm talking about the academics.
Of course. So can you imagine if the academics are viewed as being the elite intellectually elite, what the, what they are, not even worth talking about?
By the way, don't that when you hear Greek speak me, whoever you are is, I am not addressing the masses, the public, the collective, the space eater is the, the population at large.
I am not addressing them at all. So when I say moronic, I'm talking about your professionals. Right. I think, I think I've made a point of this already years ago.
Oh, no, you did, you did, but it's, it's well worth repeating.
Because, you know, it's not, yeah, it's not the masses. That's a given. That's, by the way, if people, you hear, times are changing, right? The times will, what, what, the masses have always been looked down upon and whatever, whatever.
Look, I've pulled out pieces of work from ancient Persia, from ancient Greece, from a thousand years ago, you know, which is, you know, half the time.
And I've read the paragraph for a few sentences to someone and they said, when do you think this was written? Oh, this sounds like the way we're going today. I said, this was written two thousand years ago.
Hmm, about the masses, right? Right. Right. But it's still a look, but, but that's the thing is that some things do not change.
When it comes to the, you know, the levels of control and the high control systems that exist, they exist because they work, first of all.
Secondly, there is always going to be a hierarchy. So therefore, this is what we have. But they, they are changing though. That's the thing. Look, it's, it, okay, time, you know, people say there's no such thing as time.
Time is just the measurement of change and the memorialization of history and things that change. That's all. If there's no change, there's no time.
You know, how many times have you heard in the literature, it's a literal mechanism where they say this is the place that time forgot because they're still living the way people were living three thousand years ago, right?
They still have change, but relative to the change that's done somewhere else, it seems like time hasn't, right?
Well, look, this is a rather fascinating sort of, hmm, almost like a scrapbook, to be honest with you, of many things that have been gone over. I think we still need to address the concept of spirit though a little more.
But in, in the moment that we're in currently during this sonic event, the Greek and I are going to take a little break here and we'll come back for another hour here on the Ocele effect.
Wall Street window dot dot dot gold, so the stock market. Wall Street window dot dot dot. Perhaps you're invested deeply perhaps you're not in deep enough. Maybe you're thinking about getting started.
Wall Street window dot dot condo dot com. Michael Swanson, the brilliant author of the war state, understood these trends professionally for many years and now he gives you the benefit of his knowledge.
Wall Street window dot dot.
I am here every Thursday, three o'clock to five o'clock, Pacific time right here on the Ocele radio network, which is really one of the most, uh, I think a sip gem in the landscape of media today.
Please donate by a coffee and some smokes for my man, my producer and owner of this network. Chuck today by donating at a Shelley dot com. Keep it alive. Keep it alive.
Oh, chili dot com. The war state by Michael Swanson explains the great national transformation that took place and put the Kennedy presidency in the context of the times and reveals never before published information about the Cuban missile crisis.
The American Kennedy would not have been assassinated if he had been president 200 years ago. His assassination took place in the context of the Cold War and the rise of the national security state before World War II.
The United States was a continental republic in the decade that followed it became an imperial superpower.
So it was not just Curtis LaMay not only wanted to invade Cuba, but knew that there were short range missiles on the island armed with nuclear warheads that they could not destroy because they were on mobile launchers. Their invasion could have led to a third world war and they wanted to go to war anyway.
The war state by Michael Swanson reveals why and will show you what president Kennedy was up against for more information the war state dot com.
This is James Corbin of CorbinReport dot com and you're tuned into the O'Chilly Effect. O'Chilly dot com.
Revelation through conversation.
The second segment of tonight's sonic event with the Greek now this is probably the last time you're going to hear this for a while because going behind a paywall at O'Chilly dot com for the time being will be a brand new.
Are we going to call it O'Chilly in the Greek again Greek or we're going to do something I mean I don't know it seemed to work.
I got a couple of ideas I want to buy you when we talk about the spirit to in this real world.
One idea is what if because everything I mean you don't really know but you might look you know enough that if you see the people around you faltering because they don't know what you found out about something right.
You get it so so what about calling it what if right what if right that's a good way to start into it but it's still a cell in the Greek that's that won't go away right because if we go away then there's no a cell in the Greek.
The other thing I wanted is calling it was rated why because you know why you know why are the things like this right and then you know you have xyz so x rated x and then I rate this is rated y.
And but you could just spell it with the letter y or w h I like I like the letter y that that's a good you know rated y the first the first network I was ever on I thought it was very clever it was called ucy dot tv.
So you know beautiful vowel yeah say it you know say five times it's soothing it can be actually yeah but you I thought that was really clever Greek I mean you got to give it to them there ucy you get it so it's the letter u the letter y.
The letter u the letter y and ucy yeah I remember you on that billing I was those back in the day that's when I first when you filled in for for Vinnie for Danny.
I had American free radio and I checked in and I saw you there I said this guy sounds like Alex Jones but he's not like Alex Jones let me let him know remember I said hey I was supposed to be doing what you're doing right well he had he had invited you to fill in for Vinnie when he was out yeah before me and then I don't know for oh I was a guest on somebody show or something
you know you want to you want to try this I said yeah sure sure yeah it's all about trying that I want to get in something too quick on the last song that you said there is there nobody died from smoke and weed but you know that the what real quick the the whole thing now they there's this tempted down a little bit that cigarette smoking causes cancer is it doesn't right.
The real statistics on that are by the way the censorship is so high right now that you can research anything medical very difficult to find if you're using any of the internet you have to know be very savvy but the statistics on lung cancer is 85% of the people who have lung cancer have never smoked or second hand smoke.
And 85% of those 85% are either black or Jewish women over 50 years old because when you go into the Taoist perspective like we're going to be talking about the spirit the non physical the lungs are susceptible to grief.
So someone who experiences a lot of grief is more susceptible to get lung cancer dysfunction of the lung where it's not reputable.
So do you think black women over 50 and Jewish women over 50 have a reason to have grief in the society heck yeah okay so why was there a rash of cancers in the early 70s in the late 60s that made this popular now if you if you statistically map out where all the cancers were because everyone smoked before that.
I mean you see it on TV whatever and even you know the day anyway you look this up doctors recommended you know smoking certain brands but anyway.
Oh yeah look I watch a footage from the Kennedy the day that john up Kennedy was assassinated all the time everybody broadcasting the news there was an ass tray on the news desk sure they're smoking yeah.
Moro and all these guys but anyway if you did a thumb you know the map on the wall with the thumb tax to locate you know okay like the old detective shows if you did where the most amount of cancer is where it was all downstream of Nevada meaning to the east because the wind goes from the west to the east hardly anyone in California.
Or you know west of Nevada had there was no lung cancer almost it was all downstream on the upper half of the of the country the reason why is with all the nuclear testing they were blowing this ionized particles into the air and people were breathing it and it was going in the ionizing you know radioactive particles in their lungs radiate irradiating them night and day night and day creating cancer is tissue when they went underground only and they made sure that the detonations were more than a thousand feet so the soul.
It would filter out the material the lung cancer went away so if you look at when the new tests were done and downwind is where all the lung cancer was period just like polio polio was is would they were spring almost from a biblical point of view in the 1930s 40s and 50s there were swarms of flies in the day in cities and suburbs in Main Street all over the U.S.
People go out shopping and suddenly it would get dark I mean a cloud a black cloud would come over the city or the suburb or Main Street and what the hell is that and the flies and bugs would descend on all the pass or buys and they asked you know that the municipalities do something about it.
So what they did was they went around with trucks and they were fumigating with DDT and it found out that DDT we know is banned but it was a neurotoxin so you couldn't walk turned in basically form of.
We could just for you are the muscle tissue in the nerves don't work together anymore so you couldn't walk but when they stopped the DDT spring and the polio went away the doctor said oh we have a polio vaccine it was a virus is what they stepped in.
Right.
Just like with assassinations and the more over place here they have the team that does it right and then they have another team ready that if it goes south that comes in and arrests those guys that does it gets rid of them and brings in the scapegoat that's always there ready to go because nothing is perfect.
If the assassination team doesn't work out they're promptly arrested right and the pat sea is produced right and everything is okay.
Have you ever actually looked up the thing that is commonly referred to as the assassination guide.
I've heard is that like the devil's cookbook kind of so similar ilk of stuff?
No no no it's even weirder than that the CIA actually memorialized all of its you know techniques or how it is that you do this and literally bringing in the path.
And the team is not really bringing in the pat sea and the teams and what you just described is in part of it.
It sounds familiar in that.
Yeah and the thing is.
People refer to it as the assassination guide it's literally they were explaining what they had done is a particular South American country.
Oh particularly I could tell you about a North American country.
Oh yes so can I.
But the thing is I'm just telling you about this particular document and if you were to look it up it literally is there and tells you you know there's different types of assassinations.
There is the terrorist type there is the you know where we have a sacrificial lamp all of it all the different options on the menu of you.
But it's just funny because what you just described is in part of it.
So let's say the shooters did get caught they would be arrested by their own people and the produce the pat sea immediately but if they don't get caught the other group doesn't have to reveal itself.
Then the other group reveal another group reveals itself as the quote unquote investigators days and weeks later.
Right.
That's another group.
Right exactly.
So it's just very funny to me if anybody wants to do a little digging on the road I advise you go go ahead and find that because it's a kind of ultimately you know who assassinates ultimately on a spiritual level.
Any any leader that's been assassinates been it's been done by his own people.
Their complacency right the complacency who really killed JFK is the American people.
No that's a guarantee regardless because American people killed because of their complacency.
If it was a if the American people had any worth at all they would have just over especially after the war in commission they would have just stormed the capital.
Stormed all the municipalities stormed the Congress just physically just millions of people who just walked right through and leveled the place.
This has been done before by the way in ancient times when you don't hear about that that's all been taken out.
Well it's it's you know it's it's Romans with the knives there with Caesar yes I mean you know let's even that was a setup but yeah you've been set up for 6000 years so.
You want to talk about spirit yes absolutely because again as I said I got this this interesting message somebody who had gone back and listened for a bit and they felt as though there was it was a little confusing.
What was presented there regardless you know and they said well to me spirit is breath and I said yes it is but you got to listen to the rest of the conversation that's not well that's that's what's put out there because what they what's been done is a very narrow.
Okay let's just use the biblical parlance for example the Christianity is a historical fact historians right we are in the Christian era and they're atheists they don't care about the religion they just saying this is.
What dominates so they'll talk everyone pro or con Christian will talk about anything except what's been documented the same one nine eleven the same with J. K. they'll talk about anything well you could find in the document itself.
So very simply some Christians say yes he was crucified and if you deny your faithless and others say no he was put on a stake others said this that well if you read the document very clearly.
He was subjected to the Roman authorities ultimately after going through the other today authorities and that authority very clearly states that he will he will allow the Giants to use their law and they protest saying well how can we do it under Caesar is use your law I know you have a law because.
Punches pilot had the area book you they don't send you as a perfect governor over a subjugated people unless you know their laws he knew their laws and he knew that capital punishment was done by stoning but we're not that stupid if we go back to where they get that mosaic law the high crime you're nailed you're nailed to a tree.
And stone while you're hanging from a tree right and we know that right and then everything is burned and we know that because they cast lots for his clothes before the event started because the everything would be burned and you don't want her it's robin burns so there was all this quickness and stuff so no one addresses that they'll address everything else but it but you know it's kind of like a teenager you know with his first you know what in the back seat he'll do everything but.
But he's in the whole kind of thing right so.
To make a long story short the same thing is going on with spirit and soul they confuse it if you look up spirit they'll say it's the soul blah blah blah blah blah blah and if you look at the soul they say it's the spirit spirit wait a second you can't do that circular logic here because it's very important to not let people know.
Defint not definitively but enough about something because then they can do something about it right you see what I mean it's kind of like might as well keep it I believe it's this like this person said and you believe it's that but ultimately it's just this ritual what I mean by a ritual it's like the wealthy woman with a fur coat she gets into her BMW SUV and she doesn't know anything about cars all she knows is that she performs this ritual lastly.
The one foot makes the car go the other foot makes the car stop and this wheel if I turn it to the right the car goes to the right in this wheel if I turn it to the left it goes to the left and that's her is a ritual because if anything happens she doesn't have a clue what's wrong with the car you cannot discuss with her.
Oh you know the hydraulic your low and hydraulic fluid on your power steering pump huh what does that have to do with the ritual that I've been embarking on for the past five years since I've had this car so when you start speaking about soul spirit and body to people who are part of that ritual like the woman who uses the car as a ritual she knows nothing about the mechanics of it.
How do you bridge that the first thing is leave it alone leave it alone there are other people out there that like nice as a matter of fact people who have the ones that have car collections is it like a J Leno type guy they also know about the car and know how to work on it like if you know anyone who has a Ferrari Lamborghini Maserati they do maintenance themselves as much as they can.
They don't always take it but then again the great majority of those cars are driven by people that don't they get the car picked up and cleaned detailed on a regular basis they get right they Ferrari sends out someone to pick up your car.
They don't know anything they're part of the ritual so the first thing what's difficult about this if you believe cognitively and emotionally that you are the concept and the discussion of soul spirit and body is a ritualistic sense you will never understand anything.
As a matter of fact I assure you will never understand the differences or what it is I assure you that but if you see it from a creator's point of view a creative because remember the creator relies on us to teach to our part right.
Like the guy praying to win the lottery you praise to win the lottery for a year and a year every year every year and then suddenly he gets down you know one day he gets down on his knees and prays and he hears a voice come through the wall and says listen I've been hearing your prayers but you got to do something to help us out by a ticket.
Right right so so in other words if you know that we are created and put here right that the creator demands your part also right right he tells you what it is.
In many you know what if you don't not the religions but what's been if you took all the religious texts of the world and and put them on sepia and held them up to the light they all say the same thing all of them but the different groups you see.
So just like assassinations right if you took all the assassinations and held them up on a slide and they're all the same pretty much within couple of wood but they're all different right now how can they be you know.
So the same thing so if the people view this as something that has to do with quote unquote spirituality religiosity or it's referring what they think they know have been taught through whatever system of education or religiosity they have I assure you you might as well just do something else put on Netflix don't listen to this you will not get it but if you believe that you have a Ferrari.
And it's pleasurable to you to even though you may not know how to work on it to learn how to work on it and then work on it and reap the benefits then absolutely.
Well and if you're if you're the lady in the fur coat that thinks it's purely ritual you just do there's better things to do with your time.
Right you might as well just make sure you have the you know ready to send it to the mechanic or the detail or whatever because that's the person is actually going to know how to take care of it because you're not actually.
Yeah and if it's not the car it's cooking you know this plenty of rituals you look you don't you don't want to learn how to cook and enjoy delicious food there's plenty of pre cook meals there's plenty of fast food right right.
Right true.
So what what is the you know the sense of learning and defining spirit as much as we can is to do something about it though the reason of learning I keep harping you ever notice I harp on the body the container and the spirit the soul right what the differences are in these things right.
By the way the soul is part of the body right the soul is the living body and the spirit is the mind and we can quickly from a material is point of view like I said earlier the energy if you find a plant that is a remedy for a certain ailment and it works when you give it to your common educated whatever they're going to take the plant there they don't say give it give me a sample and they're going to burn it take it apart and find out what chemicals are in it.
You see it has nothing to do with that it has to do with the energy of it so the spirit is the information if you give a vinyl album or a CD or even a thumb drive of the Beatles wide album to a material scientist tell me what's on this he'll come back with two pages he'll tell you all the materials the metals the size and everything but he doesn't see the music.
You need an appropriate device whether it's a turntable CD player to plug it into the USB port that has an audio file to play it or the record in the needle in the amplifier or the CD in the laser in the amplifier to hear really what the spirit of the thing is information if you have a CD collection.
I actually this happened to me once you know when you years ago you do more CDs than digital downloads and you forgot to label something you have to play it to see what's on the desk.
So if you have all you took all the labels off and you put them in a big pile and tell me what music is one has how the hell do you know you have to run it so that's why we're here.
It's to run the spirit through this analysis to find out what the spirit is this is what we're going to talk about and practical and I'm going to stop right here and be reserved.
I'm long winded I can I can keep going and but it's not going to be what the Greek says or what the Greek things it's what you're going to hear that you could put into use.
So I'm going to stop right there and and the the person who is stuck on ritual which is an algorithm by the way for spirit right like for example doing calisthenics and exercise are going to the gym is the algorithm for a stronger body.
You okay you see oh I'm doing what do you mean it's an algorithm I'm actually physically doing work that's making building muscle yes that's right that's the material side but the energetic side.
Is it's a set up you know what I mean by algorithm look it up but yeah but that's the thing the power stronger body forget about the lifting the weight since the sweat and all that so the spirit is the same way.
But this is why ritual is important and this is why you know when you do something actually religiously and not based on what they say religion is when you do something religiously it is important but it's not because it is important but it's not the ritual is what is what it's the collective system that is here.
It's a very it's negative it's anti human is is banking on and relying on most of the people if not actually would desire all of the people to be just in ritual.
But different things done religiously create different results it's that simple you and I talked about this before was like oh I religiously tie my shoes yeah good idea.
Yeah okay because you're not going to trip.
I think what have we got crossed over here if you're just stuck on the ritual in other words if you ask people why are you doing this I don't know why I'm doing it this is the way my mom did it or my dad did it or this is the way it's done I think we talked about less I'm as seen on TV people they're very easy to spot the 90%
and what comes out of their mouth is what they saw on TV and if you ask them the clean or cook where it's the way that they've sought on TV because there's nothing wrong with that because that's just the age we're living it actually there's nothing wrong with it but there's nothing right either just like years ago if you went to a village it's say 500 years ago
anywhere in Europe the way that the women cooked or anyone cooked was the way that they saw other people in the village cook you see what I mean prepare their food right that's why let's say for example Northern Napoli Tonto food is very different from the sudden Sicilian food because this is the way they're just carrying on tradition it's a ritual this is how they do it why it's Italy
what's why is it so different in the north and the south because they separated themselves geographically and they isolated themselves with these things and they say I'm from here I'm going to do it this way so a Napoli ton living in Sicily is he going to cook Sicilian no he's going to cook Napoli ton a Sicilian living in Napoli is he going to cook like Napoli no so the the thing here about the ritual is when you have a certain ritual and you go to a place where it's different you're going to experience resistance
and you have the option to hold on to it or to change or to integrate and do the cross-pollination thing you mentioned earlier right so when I'm talking about it's got nothing to do with any of that this is the most basic premise and why going back to the definition why when you look up solar spirit they interchange them when they're not this they do the same thing with legal and lawful most attorneys by the way don't know the difference between legal and lawful most attorneys don't know the difference between an attorney and a lawyer they're not the same at all
they interchange them right pleasant and nice are not the same but they're interchangeable why how can you take something as hard of a definition as nice that's a hard definition hard meaning such foolish
students and it's your change it with something that's pleasant and good how can you make that interchangeable well how can you make a lawyer an attorney legal and lawful and
spiritual and lawful and spiritual interchangeable at the these things are not hard on their own but when you make them interchangeable yes they're hard you see well it's just like the confusion between a psychology and what is actually psychic or see here we go
side this is this is the spirit that's right size spirit has to do with information and mental psychopath psychic so all the brain right so if you ask a psychologist psychiatrist to find
side they don't know right there's a spiritualist if you if you've got away from the Greek prefix this they would be actually if it's instead of being psychiatrist take away the Greek well it would be a spiritualist
there's spiritualist and they don't even know that's almost bizarre anyway you know I've had many private discussions with people in the
medical field and doctors that teach other doctors and I showed them there's no blood pressure there's no nothing goes through nothing is absorbed all these other things that says yeah I yeah it's
amazing Greek that you see that I've been working in this for 30 years but this is what they tell us to do so I do it yeah that's a moron that's an idiot
well that's the thing is why are you doing the thing that you know is you know flies in the face of the reality why do you do that
look there's a lot of stuff look then one thing we've get into the eschatology sometimes I talk tell people what's coming in this society's got to go can't be fixed you know there's you get to certain things whether it's a bed frame a car a pair of shoes where you can't you shouldn't fix it's got to go we can't be fixed really
right it's got to just got to start all over we got to recycle it right when I tell us to certain people and they say there's anything we could do to stop it that right there that individual man woman child whatever they are
they are part of this collective this they don't see the world for what it is someone who sees the world for what it is and is a spiritually
more spiritually developed say and more connected to divine wants to see this go has to go it has to you have to restart reset it's just right so
that's a long time to get to you know it took me a long time to get to that personally because for quite a while I wanted to believe that there was a redemptive track here you know
because you you kind of want to believe that well no this can be reappealed you know you always want to believe that things can be fixed you know what I'm saying I think that's a general default for most people
that they feel as though it's a one that should be no hold on that should be the first plate like if you don't contemplate the subject or no much about it we're on the on the fly that is the correct answer I believe that's the glasses half full right
the glasses half full list I do that off there's still we fix it yeah but upon further examination it's very evident very well established you can't be fixed it's unreal table I that's a term that I used a lot on the Greek speako
in the Greek right well I mean but that's the thing that it comes down to is that look if if after you seek out a way to rehabilitate to reuse to repurpose to redirect if you find that it's irredeemable if you find that it's a you know as you said
you you're at a place where this you cannot be rehabilitated but it is redeemable it can be redeemed but it cannot be improved or changed for the better as it is
because for example let's say you got a car that's completely you can't be fixed it's still redeemable for a certain amount as scrap right yeah I've got just about that situation with a with a 2000 Saturn actually
yeah so you know like they say the human body's twenty eight dollars worth of raw material or the car I know that the going rates about four five hundred bucks no questions asked right and but then they subtract another 200 for disposal for the tires right so you get 200 anyway yeah
they advertise you know just to get you there so so what I mean is it is redeemable in other words the remnant of what pass through here what people are and that's what I'm going to stay reserved on this
you've downloaded all these all this music on thousands and thousands and millions of CDs and they're not labeled and they're in the big pile and I want you to chuck go grab the one with the classical music
and you're looking at this huge pile of on mark discs right and you're like oh shit I'll find it someday right right how are you going to how are you going to sort the how do you know which one has the classical music on it
there's no way to tell other than playing it I'm going to have to start playing them one at a time fine right that's exactly what's going on with the spirit here we're born into this world only you know you're born naked you died right right rich man can't take it with him you see the analogy
okay I'm I'm getting there now this we don't know we are until we play the music right you don't know what's going to happen in the next hour and next day in the next month definitively yes
there are certain plans and guidelines like the cruise ship right everybody's going from London to New York in a cruise ship but while you're on the cruise ship you could you know do different things some of these cruise ships are like cities
oh you can do in a city you can do on a cruise ship but I could tell you for sure that everyone is going to New York right you see in a bulk fashion yeah we know what's going to happen in a bulk fashion in a bulk way
but in a personal very minute way we don't know but so you're playing the CD to find out what kind of music you can make being here and there are many ways to play better music and yes you have to practice but if you don't know why you're playing and why you're practicing and you see
if you think that you absorb calories and you some quack told you that you got high blood pressure when there's no blood pressure or you're going to catch a virus when your body is 90% virus already I mean you're pretty much
you're ready for the scrap peak doesn't mean you're not redeemable but you're doing nothing now I understand okay so still the unlabeled pile sits there but as you work through it you might see how much of that music do you have to listen to
to put the label on it should you listen to the first chord the first minute the first or should you listen to it all the way through to be sure well depends on the quality of the label you want to put on it now if you want to just give it a general sort of category and move on that's one thing but if you want to actually lay out each track and know what's on there
there you go you just answered your own question what spirit is thank you or the whoever else we've just presented an example there's much more to it because one of the the keys to listening to the Greek speak stuff is if you ever listen to anything the Greek talks about you've got to put it down whether it's the first 15 minutes hour or two hours or whatever and you have something that you can do within five feet around something usable
either something to look up that's readily accessible or something you can physically do or think about that's readily accessible
well that's what they call practical no that's right so very habit and in the very near future we're going to start presenting these and put them behind a paywall here at Ocelli.com
at least that's a way to start out that's all your friends and whatever you actually be careful if you got friends but tell people you know that's you know there's a subject you and I never touched on actually I don't think where where you know the interpersonal relationship right as a simple way to talk about it there's people that you consider friends some you like and you don't trust and there's other friends that you trust but you don't like
you know what I mean like the guy goes you love hanging out having drinks or shoot in the shit or whatever but you wouldn't give him your car keys or your house keys is other people that you wouldn't want to be seen in the bar way that you don't enjoy drinking with them but you would definitely trust them with your house keys or car keys.
There you go right there you go well look there there's always a different levels of quality that one can discern or contained within and there you go we're going to talk about these NPCs as well
and how to recognize them I don't think we went over that you know you know I don't I only do that's a very close circle I don't do it in public but I will do it on this well yeah that's the thing is that this won't be exactly in public but you'll be able to sign up for it not you Greek obviously but I mean I already signed up for it trust me I put my yeah so anyway.
Well that's the thing you've already you've already agreed to do this I've already signed up yes we we shall see we shall see exactly who else does that I know others said they would but you know you know how it is when people say they will do something and then you wait and see exactly how many will do it.
Well I assure what I assure people is they'll walk away with a lot more that they thought about anything anything when I say anything literally any subject we bring up and and how simple it is and how it's been there the whole time and you haven't noticed it it's kind of like the spaghetti on your shirt you know you you you like the spaghetti so much you didn't realize you splashed some you know never wear white you know when you're going to right eat a lot of sauce and someone says to you you got spaghetti on your shirt but it's not the same thing.
But you know you've got spaghetti on your shirt but it all makes sense you got you got red tomato sauce in your shirt and he doesn't know that you had spaghetti or whatever or you know but it makes total sense to you when it's pointed out because you just recall eating right you see hey you got some red stuff on your shirt I don't know where it's from but you know the minute it's brought up the one with the red stuff on their shirts is of course you see.
Now look if you were eating it makes perfect sense. Yeah the guy the person wasn't there didn't know what it was but with the moment it's that small thing is brought up it makes total sense.
Years ago I don't remember in the 80s it was very these polo shirts everybody was doing these logos on the on the shirt on the rest area.
And it was popular and it wasn't a really good shirt unless it had that when people used to walk in you know I said hey you got some bird shit on your shirt and that's a really I said yeah I pointed the logo.
And so that's not a purchase but you know from a distance it looked like bird shit and it makes them think you know it's like what are you doing you know.
Yeah well.
You know a regular polo shirt was like 15 20 bucks and this thing was like 70 because it had the bird shit on it right so I'm trying to make them conscious like hey you know.
Yeah well and there's there's the thing now now that might be an easy way to discern that there was a little bit more quality to it than the one that you got it came out without it but the thing is.
Yeah but the point is is it worth for the extra little isod things sewn on there is it worth double the price right now of course not.
And the bottom line is look a shirt is a shirt I mean what are you doing but that's the point that's that's the message the message is are you aware are you fully aware doesn't take much more time just like sometimes when you say something you add one little extra word to it right and the value goes up like I'm not like earlier saying I'm not at all depressed angry sat or want to challenge any of the history books whether whether in library or university because when I look at the binder or the cover it says history of whatever.
But it never says true history does it so they're telling so the moment you start arguing that this is false most people want to argue but said look there's nothing that debate here because it doesn't say true history does it.
Well that's that one thing well because if they were making such a claim then you might have something to complain about right because you have substance then it's substance.
Yeah substance that word substantive substance then it's thank you it's okay I get addiction area for my pronunciation every once in a while yeah no addiction area does serve a purpose but it's not the purpose that most people try to use it for very strange to me that a lot of things are actually designed that that's another thing that we might have to discuss during these two is you know there are many things that have a design.
There in there for an intended purpose and nobody bothers with it there's a whole trend of that on like you know on the I don't know if you're familiar with tick tock and all this but.
There's a short little they do short little videos and it's the strangest thing some of the most popular people show you things like do you know that this you know the reason why there's a dent in the plastic milk carton and things like this like stuff that nobody even gets it.
Why is there don't make me go look it up tell me well because what happens is when the milk goes bad that'll dent out.
Oh it's a pressure it's like a pressure sensor.
Yeah it's like a pressure sensor indicator to show you that the milk is no bloated bottle.
Yeah I've seen that.
So and you've seen it before but nobody ever pays it any mind or thinks it's just a dent on the side of the bottle so what.
Yeah it's very crude it's a crude sensor.
Yeah but the thing is there's a practical purpose or even for the way that they've just you know when they redesigned the pop top on a can.
Right it actually you fold it over it holds a straw.
Look up if you take anyone's listening this may Abraham with an eye you've been a ham Karim he is a science or a body of work he calls bio geometry.
Right on how certain geometric forms affect the environment for positive or negative a simple way to do it is you know they paint the gaudy colors in fast food restaurants so you don't want to sit there.
Right right that's a very simple application of but it gets more complex it gets complex to the point where form follows function where you should always keep water in containers that don't have 90 degrees you know in an egg shape around.
Right yep eventually those forms in geometric forms actually increase the quality of the environment right which we talked about on a private discussion right and we'll get into it a little bit more we're going to get into the treatment of water that will blow you away and you'll be able to do it as you're listening.
Well yeah I've actually only been partially privy to that and you know just the changing of the shape of the container you put it in and also it's exposure to light or lack there of and things like this absolutely cool yeah keeping it cool but we're going to go we're going to talk about things you can do with your own you know your body mitts of magnetic field a thermal field light field.
Right infrared the call it thermal but it's really light.
A magnetic field electrical field and how to use that with water that's going to be and you can do it right away and notice the difference well that we're going to talk about the emotional component a little bit more also well that'll be interesting because I know during that discussion I talked to you about the different you know like vibrations that you could kind of put out at the water and then they froze it.
Now by the way when he says keep it cool it's not keep it cold it's keep it cool there's a specific.
Yeah it not froze yeah because that is below that temperature the water expands above that temperature the water expands but when you when you expose water to like say angry vibes so to speak you know in a very crude way it will put it that way like angry vibes and you freeze it and then also you freeze like you know positively.
Conley dealt with water and you freeze it next to each other the ice crystals form different.
Oh yeah we'll go beyond that because the when you expose those vibes those vibes are merely the carrier in other words it's the line of sight and once you have that established then you send the message we've never talked about how to send the message.
Well I have privately again I kept it for private but I think it's time to speak it and in a more private group again.
Yeah well these are going to be a lot of fun all this stuff you'll be able to use right away.
Well and these are just some of the things I'm just bringing up to give people an idea about what it is that what will be developing over time there because a couple of week I guess we'll start with and see see how that goes.
And so you guys will see a new tab come up at the top of the celly dot com which you think rated why is the is the label.
So I think o and g rated why yeah maybe you got it maybe or what if I think you could do a series rated why and what if or just o and g on the future we can expand to another series and call that you know.
Yeah the the o and g I like because it's they use the you know they use a we live in an accurate acronym mystic language infuse in the regular parlance right like when you say WTF they actually use that when people speak or AF right.
O.G. when you have heard you a lot of young people so that's real O.G. That means like original gangster or something right.
No yeah it's funny O and g as opposed to O.G. which is little you know you get that you get that bit of a it's there everything everything we need to show that we.
At least look like we know what we're talking about is already there right fair enough so separate from the regular you know subscriptions that I have at O.G. com will be this right and yeah so just it'll be it'll show up as a new membership level entirely different and.
I'm gonna talk to the Greek a little bit privately although we've been doing it publicly tonight we're gonna talk a little more privately about the particulars but i'm thinking of will be a little more.
We're always having private conversations it just happened to be broadcast and recorded in some way or another story of my life fair enough.
But you know again it's it's always worthy of the effort to memorialize something that contains information that's worth sharing right.
Well to an acceptable vessel that to receive it you don't want to put fine wine in a paper cup oh understood but i mean i'm just going back to the pile of CDs you were talking about you know yeah some of those CDs might contain you know what's alleged to be music that's not even worthy of keeping you might want to throw it away without labeling it because.
I think there's enough fate and things that we don't know that are preset that doing this will bring more people that i've never heard.
X perhaps or have heard and want to revisit and go to the next level with it or whatever you know.
I think it needs it needs to be done it's kind of I mean it's really pathetic out there but by the way what's pathetic is communication people's personal ability communicate the communications that are broadcast out there all this now.
I said earlier the internet was going to be compromised just because it's part of travel right restricting travel right and you see the lockdown was about restricting travel right well until it was plausible to do so.
Here are your signs one of them is that there's a lot of pushback on people trying to revive ham radio they look they made it illegal in certain counties in California right.
The other thing is YouTube is promoting shorts well the promino someone who has YouTube and they're like oh they're promoting shorts like why.
Because when it goes down if you've got you know a piles and piles of hour half our videos and you lose it you're going to be upset but if you got ucals and piles and of these little shorts and shorts see so they're telling you start trivializing in other words stop focusing.
On the you see right the other thing is there's going to be also limitations on the post office.
So what I'm trying to say here is people with an engineering and intuitive mindset need to get together and develop a new form of communication it could be a mixture of digital.
But I'll tell you what it has to be a mixture of sorry but let me rephrase the outline of a new engineered communication system will be a snail mail type combined with a radio type ham radio which you know is very long wave combined with digital.
But not just the internet right like if you don't have a Wi-Fi or plug-in connection you're not going to get stuff on the internet you know they have the satellite thing too but those will shut down see because they're going to work it on the Google itself right or whatever the systems that carry all the servers and things.
So you still should be digital even though digital takes more energy than analog when you're doing a phone call by the way it still should be parcel and post of some sort but not the postal system that everyone's used to.
And it's still and it has to be still radio but not the ham radio that they but it's a fusion of all three the pony express right with the radio with the internet put together.
And for those of like mine because those of you know the masses in the collective there they just gonna panic or be unhappy.
Well let me let me throw something at you because I started discussing this a few months ago with somebody and I was talking about how I think we're all going to if we want to continue to do broadcast.
And things like this that we're going to need to find a new way.
So I definitely see that this is all going to be very suppressed controlled and only going to be available to those that are allowed to have it available to them.
And what I was saying is I found it interesting that they have these AM signals that you are perfectly allowed to use right now because of all the changes they've switched over a lot of things the digital but like literally you or I could easily purchase the equipment to have our own little AM signal.
Right. You want to take it you want to tweak that okay you ready you want to tweak that where you don't put it out through the air because AM need a ground antenna very large ground antenna basically if you ever see the old AM radio stations being built they would dig a trench around the place.
Yeah these are low power but these are low power AM stations that are outside like in other words the FCC doesn't have you.
I know because they're more liberal about that but what I'm saying is you don't put your antenna in the air you put your antenna in the ground.
Okay. Right and you have to have the sensitivity and the what's called the separation right from all the other stuff that's going through the ground so you're not pumping it you don't have to you not because look I was going to say earlier to do AM radio.
The old stations if you saw one being built or or plans on one they dig a trench around the building very large trench not very deep six feet deeper so when they put what looks like a chain link fence and they bury it right that's your ground you need a mean ask ground that's why they used to have a lot of the radio stations near the near the shore.
Because the wet sand and the wet right better lower resistance Tesla talked about that but again just like with Tesla it's very hard to talk about Tesla because he didn't he was not an engineer he didn't use engineering terms but the thing is to have a radio system.
Like there are videos with Eric P dollar where he goes to a fire hydrant he has this little tweak crystal radio he attaches a wire this is from a 30 40 year old video if it's still online and he attaches a very small wire to a fire hydrant which got pipes underground and he's picking up radio in China.
Yeah I remember those actually I thought that was really fascinating sort of turning the the underground infrastructure into the antenna basically so that you can pick up stuff from all over the place yeah you you find something like well you have your water means that's why they're switching everything the plastic right so but like what's really also good is a defunct gas station that still has the tanks in there they want they don't they pull the tanks out now but something like that.
And you do your Skype or your zoom or your whatever on that now what I'm talking about can be done now with all the existing technology you just need someone to be able to put it together and I know how to do it by the way I'm not I haven't perfected it I do have the but it would be very good if other people that are willing to work on this type of system would come forward.
Yeah see now I I would love to figure out how it's done and participate in it I am not the engineering guy though you know but I have a feeling there's something I could do to assist with it I just don't know I don't know all about it but I do know we're all in that we're all in in in the same position that we might know a lot more than someone else does but we don't know everything about it but when you get enough people together then we'll have a special
especially people that don't know anything about it that have an engineering mindset they'll say you ever try this we never thought of it because you know so right and in this case sometimes you have somebody who has just a a set of tools as opposed to the knowledge of how to build it you know what I mean and there you go somebody who knows somebody who understands engineering you know in the concept of you know exactly how the magneto you know like the magnetic interaction and all that which is which is an absolute.
Which is which is an element to that which I know very little about and I dare say a lot of people don't know but it's all the same magnetism electricity heat light they're all just just like water ice and steam.
Oh yeah but the thing is that if you don't understand how these things interact with one another it's difficult to create the circumstances to generate the kind of thing that you could create a broad can like reception is one thing but broadcast is another right.
So this is the this is what I want to drill drill home is this system that I'm talking about is is equal in other words it's equal it's almost on a scalar capacity.
Okay in other words it's kind of like we're not concerned about reception when we're on zoom or sky would you you're on and you're on there's no better on you know there might be bars of Wi-Fi whatever that's why I think it's going to be a hybrid of the digital the AM.
The underground AM and the post because the reason you need a post in parcel is because if someone doesn't have the physical stuff you have to get it to them right somehow of course well you know transportation listen transportation of goods and services and people this is exactly what creates the circumstances whether they are for better or for worse for anything to evolve or to devolve.
Right so I mean it's just a real world situation you have to be able to move people things and knowledge from one place to another otherwise it just stays in one place and does nothing.
So right but that's that's okay if you don't make too much and you're just making it for your local community which is what you're going to be seeing that they tried that in the eighties they would remember in the in the eighties and nineties in the urban cities started doing these urban gardens right we're buildings were right okay they gave a little attempt those.
They gave a little attempt those still exist but there's no talk about it so more of a less centralized more scattered is where it's going to be but look you're you're from a spiritual again and moral and ethical perspective the worst things are getting when the things really get bad people are going to think they're fine when people think let's say now things got bad or whatever that's just a show that's not real in other words.
Like for example I tell you know this thing about inflation which I've been talking about a long time already always if what they're trying to do is double the seat during the depression I don't want to make the talk about my real quick the depression was fully orchestrated this stuff written about it even from the federal reserve itself people didn't use checks and credit cards and everything was cash that's why when you look at a movie
the black and white and it's a corporate office the president of the company what was always in the back of the office a big safe. Why because everybody got paid in cash so what they did decided to stop create a cash shortage so at the end of the week
they couldn't pay there was plenty of goods in this plenty of money just prevent the people from getting cash so if you worked at a factory that made electric fans the president of the company says look I went to the bank that's all me no cash is available pay so be could take as many fans as you want for payment.
So the people the employees did that they go to get milk and says I don't want you know they produce the fan to the store owner and he says I don't need any more fans is look look down here I got ten fans already what am I going to do with them.
So everything stopped it took a couple of months. Okay so now what they they can't take the cash away because there's every 90% of population relies on you know everything else checks and whatever so digital digital so what they're going to do now is just if you raise the prices so much and the people raising the prices of the ones that
they get all the profit and but you keep the salaries and the wages low right it's the same thing right basically as if you have not right they're doing that in New York right now with a rents of tripled in two years so so so in other words if you're working a salary or a wage in your salary you there's no plans on your salary doubling within a year or at least 50% more you're going to have hard times right period that's and this is I talked about a long time ago you cannot depress you can
not depress you cannot create a depression anymore because there's no money it's all credit comes out of your signature right so the reason they're doing this is twofold I do understand why they're doing is because they've very publicly announced that they took all your money away and have you running on credit for 90 years and no one's making a big deal about it so they're like you know let's go out it's the same thing like the little spoiled boy who has all the toys and he's tired of playing with all the toys so now the next thing to do is to go out with a magnifying glass
and burn some insects or tie the dog up when no one's around and torture them right you see sick so this is the level that the the administrators in the elite you know are being telling people look these people are let's just start screwin with them
because we're tired of shooting fish in a barrel right so it's all it's all going to be and it's the people's fault you know well and there is no dead I tell people look
dead I tell people look credit there's no debt they got it from your signature they send you a bill at the end of the month to make it seem like there's a debt
but there's laws ftcpa that says look you just deny it and they have to prove it every time if they can't prove it every time they send you a letter it's 500 bucks
you know that you can find them with so you just you know tell a credit card company hey go pack sand I don't know you anything they're going to keep sending letters just keep collecting those letters you get 10 letters it's five grand and you just do a federal case against them they're going to say okay we got to pay
you can actually make a living doing this you know this is the law is the ftcpa regulations but they've there's enough people thousands of people that figured it out that they're starting to change the verbiage a little
verify is not it has to be validated because they we verified it but verif i validated means us to be a sworn statement that you owe and nobody does anything doesn't matter what it is now obviously there's a bunch of people out there
an entire groups that if you have a car or how's they try to repossess it's called a secured loan they take it from you right even then they don't have the right but that's the the way it's done you know
so but not enough people care so actually they get what they deserve that's what I'm saying you cannot fix what's what's here there you can quietly in live off of credit cards and make a pretty good living just by using them and denying and having them send you letters
yeah and it doesn't go on the credit report either if they put on the credit report it's another thousand dollar fine I haven't had it it's amazing I haven't had a credit card in in I don't know how many years I've never had one that one
when I got divorced my access to all that went away well there's no reason for that either right now because they just see they have to create plausibility the reason why you pay utility bills that's all paid for
the reason you pay for is to make you feel like the paycheck you're getting is worth something so imagine all utilities were they're paid so you would call them free but they're not they're already paid
everything is paid for even the food in the whatever we talked about this last time no word is any big story say you must pay here before you leave nowhere they can't do that legally or lawfully because all paid for but they do call it shoplifting right don't they don't call it stealing through notice very careful with the words shoplifting
okay so if you're shopping and you're lifting something a bag of flowers that shoplifting anyway so so this is the thing all of this stuff imagine that
imagine that you walk into a store you get all the groceries it's already paid for you chose to rate pay for you get this paycheck right it's end of the week you're like screw the boss I don't need this paycheck you see you get it so what happens if enough people say screw the boss
I don't need this paycheck and they leave the water running all day or the the heat on max burning all this fuel and the doors open and you tell them hey why don't you consider screw you it's already paid for you see
that's why the people that are here cannot partake in the next society that's coming there even if one person let's say you let's say you believe the numbers and there's 300 million people in the u.s. right if one person did that screw the boss I'm not doing it I'm gonna let the water run let the electricity run it's already paid one person at a 300 million people has that attitude that's enough for the spiritual police to shut it all down just one that a 300 million
and I'm telling you that almost 299 million 99 thousand are that way not just what you see so the chances of you getting what is actually reaping the benefits of what is really happening in other words what is really happening there is no money you're living on credit your credit
everything is paid for and you will not read that benefit you not you chucked maybe you I don't know you personally know well enough to say definitely not you but that that because there is someone in your society that will take advantage of that and be reckless with it that's why you're not reaping the benefit and the chances of it turning around is like zero point zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero like pie the chances are finding a thousand people in this whole country that would be concerned is slim the number of people
and the answer is slim the none so that's why it has to go in the people that know this know the the way that the people have been raised are know that the this has to go this society has to be white clean and you know in other words a mop up crew and physically remove them physically remove their structures the infrastructure homes them their children everything has to be swept away physically the spirit
part remains the information remains the residents and that's why I like those sci-fi movies where you know they're the aliens or whatever visiting earth and they they're chasing someone down and they go into the room all they left an hour ago but doesn't matter because they spray the stuff on the glass and they could hear what they said an hour ago because the glass is still resonating right just like they could shoot a when you say laser it's people think sci-fi you know you see the beam most lasers are invisible to the eye
you can have an intelligence officer sitting as long as it's a line of sight to the window that you're in he could record your conversation because the laser will sense the sound on the right on the window as long as they have line of sight and by the way I can be done by satellite
yeah that's that's something that I actually learned a couple of years ago is that this whole thing with being able to turn the the windows of a house with regardless of whether the shades or the curtains are drawn or anything else you can literally be aware of every single thing going on every single word being spoken every sound right just for the residents yeah
as a matter of fact they're even replacing radar with later which is laser right so these little it's which is coherent you know so so what I'm trying to say here is that the people that are here now will not be able to reap the benefits and privileges and rewards and rights of all of the things they already have access to because of that spiritual problem of of putting negligence in the right place putting what doing what's right in the right place right you see
so because right now like I said I'm just going to repeat myself again everything is paid for there is no reason for want or need or everything is paid for completely it's provable legally it's provable lawfully the worst thing about it is that it's proven even legally within her own system no one has any debt everything you ever bought is already been paid for before you did it the reason it's done is because once you're aware of it you will misuse it and that's big the potential of the misuse and the negligence is why you will be able to do that.
And the difference is why you will not reap the benefit of what is I'm not talking about some society to come you are living in it where everything is already paid but you are not going to get it because it's the behavioral control to make people subjected to this to this tyranny of of what is it called being motivated by penalty right
until that you see it's and it only takes a little bit you don't have to change much a little bit of self awareness you know if five or ten percent of the people started speaking on just what I'm saying right now that would that could change well what would have to happen it would change maybe another five or ten percent and then the thirty to fifty percent that will not change that's where you get into the scenario where you go to a future earth and there's a certain planet or a country that's all the savages
right and then the other is not about the lot of stories written about that and the other island is there very civilized and they have to defend themselves from those savages right right
so you can have to separate you cannot do this to everyone it's already established half the people thirty people have to be separated into their own wall confinement something where they cannot come out into the rest of the world where we know everything we already can take all the benefits and rights and privileges
and all of it all of the work that's been done to get us to this point where everything's already paid for right the other savages will not there you go and you're going to hear a lot more of this again in the very near future as we go to this behind the paywall on ocelli.com I guess we're going to call it o and g rated why
so we'll go forward with that in the very near future and we're done with this public discussion for tonight but we'll be talking to you soon if you subscribe that's the way to go
I am here every Thursday three o'clock to five o'clock Pacific time right here on the
ocelli radio network which is really one of the most I think it's a gem in the landscape of media today please donate by a coffee and some smokes for my man my producer and owner of this network
chuck today by donating at a jelly dot com keep it alive keep it alive o chili dot com revelation through conversation
I
And I see if I still
You are the only one I hope that you are One pain
But the only thing that's deep
And the one that's deep
So make your sense of hope
The only thing I hope that you still
You are living all the way
And I remember everything
But the only thing that's deep
I remember everything
Every moment I remember
You're the one in the aviation field
And you can have it
Oh, yes, I'm perfect
I will question you now
I will have it
Because you are
You're just a little bit
So long
I will have it
You're the one in the aviation field
And you can have it
I'll wait, the end
stop my love again
I'm in a mirrored town of grey
I'll keep myself
I'll follow you