[Music]
Beaming out across the galaxy.
This is where conspiracy on the wall side
means the perspective of a lifetime.
This is the freeze-on-the-roost, free man.
[Music]
Well, the Francis Crick Institute just announced
that they are going to begin DNA altering.
That's right, this is going to make the UK the very first country
to start producing GMO children.
Now, it is currently illegal to implant these genetically modified embryos
into women creating designer babies.
But as it is now, legislation has been passed, DNA altering
is going to begin occurring in the UK at the Francis Crick Institute.
Now, when you start to tell people things like this,
they tell you, well, I think you're watching too many episodes
of the X-Files, and people only hear what their own bias
will allow them to hear.
And they will throw this off into the fringe zone
and never accept it into their real world concerns.
Well, today we're going to talk to the Greek,
and we're going to offer some practical information,
not opinions.
We're going to look into all levels of our being and our media.
We're going to analyze the flip side coins of Alex Jones versus Fox News.
And the most important part that I want you to take from this,
tonight we're talking with the Greek.
And the reason he is coming to speak to you now is because
if you know something and you say nothing,
you are just as guilty.
So please welcome to the show, the Greek, as we lay out for you
some of this amazing research that he has been working on.
Welcome to the show.
Oh, well, thank you very much for having me, Freeman.
It's great to be here with you.
Well, we're going to focus some on how do we change our world today?
And we're going to just get into this idea right now.
Okay, there's so much information coming out at people.
And we're starting their senses.
Nobody knows what to think about.
And we have what now is known as the alternative media.
But I saw that immediately as a flip side of the same coin.
Everybody's still focusing on the same issues and the same false reality.
And yet they want to say what we have the supposing opinion.
So therefore it's change.
Well, you see people naturally have a desire to learn.
That's what separates us from the animals.
We require training where we have to dedicate a certain amount of energy
to learn and get input about the environment around us.
And especially how we should think and speak and behave.
And this energy is being dumped or damped out by what I call the dummy load.
That's what most of the media is.
And notice it's just done on a weekly basis.
There's a weekly story.
It's like what happened about, you know, we were supposed to end society three times already last year, you know, with comments and financial collapses.
And none of that seems to happen, but people seem to ignore it and go on to the next dummy load.
So we need to get more practical when I say we meaning because we're all here together.
And start really paying attention.
I think mentioned before the most occulted and the most secret knowledge is actually discovering the obvious.
So we need to start looking there perhaps.
Isn't that the truth?
I mean, everything I have ever said to anyone is straight data of resource backed up for you to find.
And yet I'm constantly bombarded with, oh my god, I can't believe you think this.
And I'm like, it's in the news. It is real.
You know, I explained how we sent a Doritos commercial to Earth's a major using the icecat antenna array.
And I'm getting messages, well, you had me with your information until you brought up that we sent a Doritos commercial to Earth's a major.
Obviously, you're just, you know, full of it.
And I find that people won't even hear things that don't relate to their own personal bias.
And then they come back and say, well, you said this.
And I'm always like, I never said that. You heard that.
Yeah. And also, I don't think anyone on Earth's a major will really get that commercial because the type of wave provocation they're doing will not make it there.
It's another thing about how people consider the state of technology that they're in as another form of deception or delusion because the quality of what's been given or portrayed as high technology or even like you said, the news is qualitatively very low.
And people just accept it.
Yeah. Well, okay. So for 20 years, we've had alternative media host that let's use Alex Jones as an example since I'm friends with it. Well, I know him and I feel like I can talk about him.
As simply being the flip side of the same coin, when 9/11 occurred, I said, don't freak out. This is all for your reaction.
And in a way, I was predicting the Alex Jones type movement in saying that fanatics are going to rise at this time. And I mean, for 20 years, this guy's been the alarm bell saying it's the end of the world and people are all taking this into their soul and acting on this planet in a very skit-soid manner because of all of this information that's being bombarded on him.
Yeah, and that has to do with things that I discuss, like for example, what's fit and proper, what's lawful and unlawful. And if anyone hasn't noticed, the planet right now is under an unlawful society.
And this is just to go back to Alex Jones. If it were a lawful society, people take what others say very seriously. And if someone is going to preach doom and gloom, especially and give a time period when these things should happen and they do not.
Those people won't be walking around too much longer. They're held accountable in life and these life and death matters. And what's going on is because it's an unlawful society, people allow this to go on.
Well, let's talk about that then. Let's understand our laws, legal advice and contracts and try to figure out where it went wrong because, you know, if we want to go back to the birth of America, Freemasons coming over with their goddess Columbia and establishing justice on planet Earth.
You know, let's start there because I mean, people don't even know, first of all, that their nation was founded by the secret society. And they don't know that so much of what they're coming comes through this also religious programming.
I mean, I don't want to jump topics too quick, but we're looking at laws legal and advice. We might as well also throw in there the clock because I mean, it was a regulation in the small towns in the back in the day in the 16, 1300s, 1100s where the church bell had to be able to be heard by the next town.
And the towns would be determined the spacing by being able to hear this chime that sets you to the clock and folks. If you go around and look right now, you will see on every one of your cathedrals, that's where you get the town clock.
This is where time comes from. So if we want to go legal and time, uh, agree with, let's, let's look at that world.
Yeah, and there's many levels to that as well. Maybe we could squeeze that in enthusiastically, the other levels as well. Like real quick, the church bell ringing.
If you look at the etymology of the word church, it came from Sirc, which meant the ancient circus. And it was borrowed and synchronized from various religions.
The reason they're wearing these bells in public is because of the human sacrifices that were being done in public. So that wow, it's like, what did he just say? Yes, we could tie that back together again.
But regarding law and timekeeping and all that, when we say law, I'm not talking about traffic law, attacks law or these things like that. I'm speaking about your basis for operating in the world.
You know, what do you eat? What's fit and proper to eat or lawful to eat? What's fit and proper to wear or lawful to wear? How do you raise a family? How do you do business?
You know, all of these things are your laws, like laws of physics describe the natural world when we say laws for mankind is that it affects or it's the impetus to how he will behave. All of that law comes from your deity.
And I know it sounds kind of strange and many people wanted to bait me on this and when they do, for example, someone says, well, I'm an atheist.
I don't have a God. So how do you deal with that? And I said, that's easy. Do you believe in the laws of the state? And they usually say, yes, I said, well, then the state is your God and April 1 is your holiday. Next, it's very simple. It's part of the operating system.
Now, the legal aspect that we sense in the Western world today, when I say sense because it's very convoluted, you can only get a sense of it. If you actually put your handle and study the legal system, you'll see it's what they call legal based on legal fictions, representations.
So when you look at the Western world, especially, if you look at the American Constitution and the preamble within the first preamble, it states that the people are to establish something called justice.
It's like, wow, what is justice?
It seems to be a statue of a woman blindfolded carrying scales. And if we do some research on that, we will find that is the revival of the ancient goddess religion has nothing to do with law, never did, never will.
And essentially, the people from Europe were coming west to escape justice because it was destroying them.
So if you want to know something bad is going to happen, it's very easy to determine that when you see this term called justice arising in society.
Well, let's talk about her for a minute because I was really the first expert on the goddess Columbia.
Yes. And it was my second film and I laid it out there and I explained her connections to the pentagram, her connections throughout the different goddesses of Diana, Minerva, and Anna.
And what I found also the connection with this pentagram, then it was a year later that Dan Brown came forward with the Da Vinci code and kind of bonded the idea of the pentagram with the goddess but never gave any explanation, which I had done.
And so, yeah, let's talk about Columbia and this goddess justice and because I've asked Freemasons and people at the nation's capital, who is that standing on top of the capital dome and no one knows?
Yeah, the thing is also we have to throw in here believe it or not, there is a parallel society to this materialistic human animal type, you know, materialistic world that we look at sentient beings.
And this is the spiritual realm and it is a multitude. And here's the thing, you know, if we're going to say that everyone that came before us that memorialized information, what they call the holy rites of the world, even in the mythological texts, if they're all just a bunch of ignorant savages, and because we have iPhones and we can, you know, spin a prop and fly in an airplane, where more advanced and we should ignore everything that came before us is quite foolish.
If we look at all the information that's been memorialized by what we might call from the ancients far reaching back even to the local, let's say, thousand years ago, what's been memorialized about the spiritual realm seemingly has been ignored and that there is a mass plurality.
And yes, there are many gods, there is a hierarchy of gods just like in the military, there is a hierarchy from the private, you know, boots on the ground and listed guy all the way up to the colonels, generals and the emperor.
This is how the spiritual world is set up in other words, the military ranking system on the earth is not unique. It was actually conveyed from the spiritual realm.
That's why you'll see almost every country in the world has a very similar ranking system.
Now, within the ranking system of the spiritual realm, especially if we take heed to what's been memorialized, it seems like these lower level what we call ranking spiritual entities are interacting with mankind and have been for a very long time.
And it just so happens that one of the predominant, inspirational spiritual entities on the earth happens to be female.
It's not that it's because someone might say, well, Greek, that's an anti-female feminine sentiment. It's not. It says if you were, let's say robbed by someone wearing a ski mask, then you caught the assailant an hour later, you pulled the mask off.
It's a woman. If you say I was robbed by a woman, does that make you anti-feminine? No, it just so happens to be a female in this case, you see.
And this is also memorialized in the ancient texts. Her priesthood is male and a lot of people have misunderstood as being a patriarchal system because of the male priesthood that she has.
And when I say she, there's actually more than one goddess as well in name and in attribute.
But this is a long-winded preface before getting into the goddess religion because you'll see there's the concept of ISIS, Colombia, DK, in ancient Greece.
There's the Statue of Liberty, there's justice, Lady Liberty, all these things. They harken back to this very similar type of system.
Yeah, and it's being carried forth in near secret, but yet at the same time our capital is the district of Colombia.
Yes. You know, there's not a single person I know out there that ever asked the question, well, who is Colombia? I think I was the first.
Yeah, probably. And even though it's pretty obvious though wherever you go, you do see it, but no one wants to discuss it as you would have been probably the first to do it, as you say.
But what needs to be looked at is very simply when you're brought into, let's say, the paradigm in the law or legal system is justice, for example.
And you ever noticed, it's in the language, if you listen to what's being said, you are brought to justice, you serve justice.
There's a miscarriage of justice. And where is the law in that, you see? Because when we study the history of it, these goddess religions impart great cruelty to the societies that adopt them.
Now, it sounds kind of harsh, but not making this stuff up. You know, this is a fact. Typically, the societies that have adopted these, again, I'll repeat myself, adopted these goddess religions, end up falling into situations of great cruelty and apathy, and a level where humans intuitively sense things shouldn't really be this way.
But yet, your common citizen or plebeian or person will say, or man or woman will say, I want justice. We need to bring him to justice. Well, if you keep asking for it, you're going to get what you're asking for.
And henceforth, a lot of the complaining and bickering and whining about the justice system. There is nothing wrong with the justice system when they speak about corruption and cruelty and privatization and monetization.
And all this stuff going on, that is inherent in that goddess religion or the revival of it.
Well, so we've made these social contracts with these people. And really, as you're saying in our more, more atheistic mindset, I mean, we are controlled by daest, the free Masonic order, the orders in charge, you know, you have to accept that you have to state that you believe in a higher power, a deity.
But yet, when we're looking at a Masonic lodge, you will see the Quran, the Torah, or the Bible all on their altar. Yet free Masonry has all the trappings of religion.
So this obviously is a king underpinning of why we have a goddess, Columbia, in their religious belief system. But also just the idea that this religious programming, this tradition is,
is idolized and, you know, we're like, we're not going to allow somebody in that isn't in the club that believes in religious programming.
And, you know, so let's look at where their mindset comes from in this religious programming. We already got into the idea of the time and we'll get deeper into that as well as that.
Sure, but in terms of the religious programming, it's beyond programming, it's more of the operating system and use the computer model, you know, the actual machine we call computers these days.
When you first start one up, you don't install a program, you install an operating system. And then the program and then the files.
The operating system of let's say nation building or nations or groups of people is that their government has a patron deity and you will find this throughout the entire history of mankind.
What's going, what's unique and what's going on today is that that concept has been brushed not only under the rug, but out of the room and into oblivion.
No one is discussing what patron deity this nation has and this is the actual part of the operating system that you mentioned the Freemasons.
They tend to be, you know, like we like it said, a secret society and that they hold certain things in knowledge.
They do have this in their structure, the concept that each nation has a patron deity, but they don't discuss it and they can't cognitively recall it, but they do sense it.
And part of speaking out publicly is that people go to a lot of these secret societies thinking that they actually have some deep knowledge and they don't anymore.
And I know this might be like kicking them in the in the in between their legs, but what I mean by that is, you know, someone like Henry Ford, who started a car company on his own, do you think you can take his great grandson and give him all the resources and he can start a car company?
Probably not. The people that originally formed a lot of these secret societies were very unique and very talented in that field.
And the people that come after them are just simply going through the motions. If that makes any sense.
Oh, absolutely. You know, I don't for a second believe that George W. Bush or even Jeb Bush is a devout Christian.
And you know, what does that even mean? Can you can you get it?
Sure. Well, this is a general thing like you mentioned in the Freemasonic lodge. They have the various holy rites of the corresponding religions. Let's say and I have made this statement and have been making it and have not been proven wrong for years now that there is not a religion on the planet bar none.
That does what is allegedly in the text that they subscribe to.
And this is the truth and it sounds shocking on its face. But it's true if you look at it now religion just means something you do regularly like if you you could be if you brush your teeth and tie your shoes every day that is a religious act that just means something you do regularly.
And because religion tends to tie in with a spiritual side of humanity or the gods, let's say that ties in back where you get your law and what you do based from your God, but people are not acknowledging this.
And this this type of discussion is typically not popular because again using the computer model.
If you're going to discuss computers, you might discuss like this program, how you like the how you interface with it or the color of the web page, but no one wants to discuss the machine code, the C++.
You see, and this is what we're discussing is the machine code or the code behind what we call not just modern, but civilization at large.
And this is also very, probably a good point or very opportune to go into what's called timekeeping because it is very important.
So with that, maybe we should mention that there is anomalies in people believing that the calendar is a timepiece.
Right, how many times have you heard, you know, ask someone what day it is and they emphatically tell you something between January and December and something between Monday and Friday with a number thrown in as if that is actually a timepiece.
It is not what the people on the planet today are using as a calendar is not a timepiece.
You cannot reckon time with that calendar.
What I mean by that is if let's say you celebrate a birthday, you'll notice that it's on a different day of the week every year.
What that calendar simply is, it is a work schedule for papal subjects.
I'll just say one more time. It is simply a work schedule.
That's why it's called the work week and the weekend. You cannot keep time with it.
But just like a multiple choice question and answer test, they give you four months out of the year that similarly to note the correct correspondence of timekeeping.
For example, September means seven. Octo, like octopus means eight. Nova means nine and decenn means ten.
But everyone is writing December is 12 November as 11 and so on and so forth.
So the way the time is being kept is part of the operating system as well.
And this is a recent phenomenon that the entire world is under this papal work schedule, which is pretty fascinating to see in itself. How they've pulled that off.
Yeah, definitely. Do you have any thoughts on the fact that we now have a Jesuit Pope?
Not much because here's the thing. What's interesting is if you look at Christianity as you brought up and with the modern Catholic system and just to make a quick slice of what that really is, first of all, you will not find Christianity in the biblical text whatsoever.
And second of all, the biblical text, which was, which is delivered to the world today based on what's called the King James version is not a translation of what is known as the scriptures that are preserved in Hebrew and Greek, correspondingly meaning old and New Testament.
What is called the old and New Testament, which will not find that in the text either. That is subtitles that have been put in after have yet to be translated to this date.
So what they have is a version that has been custom tailored and basically the world still does not know what is held in those scriptures unless you have done private research on your own.
Now back to the Christianity and the Jesuit Pope, what is called Christianity is actually started by someone called Simon Magus around the first century AD because there were things going on in the world that no one can explain things that were done in secret.
Because the reason I'm saying they were done in secret is because they were actually public events. So go figure. And they try to syncretize through syncretism. They try to explain modern day events in their time by putting together all of these, let's call them pagan religions from all over the world in concepts and traditions.
And they formed early Christianity like for example if anyone does any referencing to texts that are preserved these are secular texts about the Christians being thrown to the lions in the Colosseum.
Okay. If you go look at the texts that are preserved and what they were actually doing because they would actually announce a decree before the game start just like they sing the national anthem before baseball game.
And in those decrees before they allegedly threw the quote unquote Christians into the lions in the Roman Colosseums you will see that in the decree it states that the reason they are thrown into the lions is because they are atheists.
In other words they have an unidentifiable God this is really bizarre but you know this is I'm not making this up you can anyone wants to really do the legwork and discover this.
Now what's interesting is that the syncretization of all of the religions then solidified around with the time of Constantine and up until the first century AD and you have what's called the Catholic church which means universal it's like we swept everything that we can and brought it up into one big pile.
And we've mixed it all together and we syncretized it and this is what it is it has no bearing on the biblical text whatsoever.
Yeah I don't think many people are reading in Greek or Hebrew in these days.
Well yeah and even the thing you know what's interesting when you do read in Hebrew or Greek or even in English to understand the text it doesn't say that you need to learn any particular language it states that you have to have the ability to perceive with eyes and ears.
Okay so on that thought and to take this to kind of back to the beginning and on to another level when talking about the 9/11 programming and the idea of the alternative media then saying it's an inside job it's an inside job.
You know I was I was quickly one of the people saying no you're you're throwing yourself into the fire they are going to use your own homework to bring America to a war crimes tribunal.
And so with everyone that is out shouting the government did a 9/11 they are therefore throwing their own nation under the bus without looking at the whole picture.
And I feel that you know it began in the Middle East it's going to come to the Middle East it's in the Middle East right now and with America coming down and this potential of being called forward for universal war crimes.
What do you see going on in the Middle East why is this such an important time in place right now.
Oh from a geopolitical and from a large let's say looking at the forest through the trees where you know we're going above the forest looking at the entire forest you'll see through history and I don't mean history like we started off alternative media just focusing every week on what happened.
But looking at history in thousand year chunks let's say or millennial or ages even in secular history you will see that is stated that civilization started in the Middle East.
And there's a lot of preaching and teaching and all this stuff about where in the end times well we're really not but we are because it's not really it hasn't been defined properly.
What's interesting about everything starting like grandma said what goes around comes around it is established through history that everything started in the Middle East and things are going to sort of wrap up in the Middle East and what you're seeing right now is the precursor to the formation of a Middle East union.
Unlike the EU see the EU is also a union of nations it's going to be very different than how the EU is operating today but just to give the EU meaning European European Union as an example.
Like I said anytime you preach doom and gloom you'll be popular and when they were preaching doom and gloom during World War Two with all of the bombing and terror raids that were being done in Europe it was very convincing to say it's the end of the world and obviously it's not when I say world meaning man's rule on earth right.
So what had happened during World War Two was like the pulling out of teeth out of very nationalistic governments because you can't have let's say ten nations forming a union if they're very if they're independent and nationalistic and don't want to work with each other so what people are witnessing is is that going on in the Middle East at the moment.
So Middle East union in the future yes and there are many many many details regarding that and it's not very difficult to see just as if for example if someone is trained in chemistry and you're not and you walk in and speak with this individual he might say well don't touch that or don't mix this with that you're like why they're just too perfectly clear liquids what could go wrong right.
So if you're studied in a certain field you then you then you can impart that information you see but most people seem to have wanting to get stuck in this myopic narrow or modern we can't we don't need to look at what was written before us and by the way when you look at history and other languages you know that every civilization before its fall or when it's when it was in the period of its downfall which could have taken decades or century.
Always called themselves modern the Babylonians called themselves modern in their texts at one point before their fall so did the Egyptians so did the Greeks so did the Romans interesting parallel absolutely well in this modern age we are taking in tons and tons of data and you were talking about this info dump that you know this is one of the biggest problems I see in our current trying to change the world is the world.
Is that we just don't even know what to focus on anymore and we get data data data and every day there's another thing that you can sweat and Skype and you know track and Facebook about social media all over the place and it's just going hey wire Greek and so yeah.
So I think we can talk about that sure a real simple way to do that is just a sidetrack here for a minute go right back to it let's say we got a job working in the sewer right so the only job you get it pays real well do you skinny dip and drink the water or do you put on a full hazmat suit with breathing tanks.
Probably the second part okay so anyone that does any research in society will see that it's basically a sewer every aspect whether it's science you know within that system.
Medical legal religious it's all really bad it couldn't be any worse you know like the frog being boiled kind of thing and everything is a little bit worse today than it was yesterday but not as bad as it's going to be tomorrow it's a very gradual.
Downslide that plateaus okay so it so are you going to drink the water not really or the cool later whatever you want to call it so the what that means then if you're going into the sewer wearing protection.
You're actually setting yourself in part apart from the medium you're not you creating a buffer zone or a boundary layer and you walk away from it and an example for this just to fast track this thought is for example during an election season people are always bickering about following political leaders and whatever and how the government is bad and we can change it or whatever you notice there is no change when people get involved.
But this is an assurance that when they do have let's say an election and by the way voters don't elect electors elect the word vote means that you are vowing that whatever the electors do you'll stand behind it okay that's another that's like a bombshell right there but.
But if people want to change let's say the way their government operates if no one at all this has to be an all or nothing if no one showed up to vote now to one person at all not even the crickets okay within 72 hours all of the government buildings local state city and federal will be empty why and then anyone could walk in and take the position why because they're going to say okay the gig is up the next thing is we're in deep trouble so we better leave now well we're still alive.
You see not violent revolution not protesting not all the stuff you hear you know just shut up and withdraw and then it goes away and now you can rebuild it that is the ultimate peaceful side of the perception of what is going on.
I definitely see that and I was introduced to the sylistine prophecies by James redfield and it really described what was going on in my own personal view as life had swept me up and presented me an experience that I could have never imagined or thought up on my own.
And at this moment I realized oh my god the world is alive and working in my favor but I have to be open to the opportunities and the possibilities that are being given to me and I have to be in a happy mindset friendly and and agreeable for miracles and angels to enter into my life.
And I found that if the world followed these simple insights of connecting with beauty therefore finding your inner peace and then projecting this out as an energetic form of your soul that that will attract the right energies coming back and you will find miracles going on in your life where you're like wow I would have never thought to do this this is perfect.
Wow how did this even happen?
Well what's interesting about that it sounds wonderful but in order to get to the manifestation point we need specifics and there are certain generalities that work like most people that operate what they call it automobile don't know how to rebuild the engine but they know if they put the key here and push this pedal and turn that they are going to get the job done.
And when we're discussing help from the spiritual side most people have completely devoid of it like for example when people say angels and gods they are under the misconception that all of that is benevolent.
And if you are not benevolent you are always going to show as being benevolent you see it's kind of like if you're someone is going to counterfeit a note do you use a crayon and draw a quick doodle of Ben Franklin and write 100 in the corner with a crayon or do you try to make it look like the original note as close as possible you see.
So mankind has fallen for a lot of this and we do need specifics and these specifics are part of what's going to be coming in the future regarding the spiritual realm.
Well using the concept of the idea counter-fitting you know I would say at this time in space that money is the deity of most people right now.
Sure and you know most people refuse to research things that they established as things to be worshiped like for example like we mentioned earlier you will not find anyone that categorizes themselves as having a particular religious faith is ever researching what that faith is supposed to be based on because if they do they retract and say I can't call myself a Christian or a Muslim or a Jew or Buddhist or a Hindu or whatever because I've researched what this is based on and I just can't do it see people.
I don't want to idolize and worship things and once you they get into that realm of worship and idolization they no longer want to look at anything about it and then it's very easy to have it that system debased like for example all of the religions are debased currently all of the money is debased you know if you if you tell anyone this is fiat currency they say well I don't care as long as I go to the store and get something for it.
You see so there's this worship of things that makes mankind retract from using is cognitive rational ability and then falls into these debased things if you ask people why do they go to particular temple or religion they say I don't care I just like there because I have a good time I feel loved or whatever you know so the worship of money is an interesting concept because what is actually being used as money today is clearly not money.
It is just a means of exchange unlawful means of exchange right because if you're going to do barter or exchange it should be of equal value and no one seems to care simply because they worship it and anything people worship for example even people that go to these better universities they don't care what the professor says they just want to say I went to an Ivy League so they can be worshiped right if someone walks into the room and says I have an Ivy.
I have an Ivy League education how dare you question me about anything you see so there's many things that are worshiped in society and money being the base of it and money is not the root of all evil it's the love of money and it's sort of like a joke that the spiritual wrong because they do have a sense of humor apparently is playing on humanity they probably said let's take money away from them and watch how much they still want it just to show that it's the love of money you see.
So these things are pretty much the money the religion all these aspects are debased there is nothing backing them up anymore and almost everything that mankind is dealing with right now is debased it has no basis whether it's scientific medical and so on and the money being the root of it because it's very hard to operate in society without it and by the way I've also said in the past
you hear a lot of these economic people making comments on the economy and money not a one of them ever says there's a difference between lawful and unlawful money and what the money is actually based on if it's not based on anything it is based on something because you see numbers and things flying around
again escapes pretty much everyone but what I've said is that money just is portable land that's all it is because in a perfect society you'll be able to gardener everything you need from what's under your feet but when you travel and go to someone else's land you can't bring your land with you so you bring precious metals and or something that is based on representation of the land.
So these things are very simple concepts but again once they're thrown into the realm of worship no one wants to look at it.
Well this also has brought us to the level of waste and planned obsolescence and the way that we are trying to make more money than we are you know things we're making more things than we need so that there's more empty houses than there are homeless
and we have this built in planned obsolescence which is only due to money you I mean what kind of idiot world would create such a thing.
Sure well the thing about the homes is interesting is let's look at the western world remember we said what goes around comes around most of the western world meaning this hemisphere let's call America.
How did it start it started with slave labor and stolen land guess how it's going to kind of wrap up slave labor and stolen land.
So it's just these things are very simple you know like what I mean by slave labor is back in the 80s Ford was a motor company was hiring line workers for 20 to $28 per hour in the 80s right now they're hiring them for 10 or 12 an hour.
Okay yeah so minimum wage according to lawful perspective should be around 23 bucks an hour about 2250 right now.
Okay so and stolen land what I mean by that is there hasn't been a legal or lawful foreclosure in the US in the past 80 years it's all presumptive and people go for it.
So boy these are these are topics that people just don't want to look at simple to understand you know simple doesn't mean easy does it.
Not usually no usually as you're saying the obvious is some of the hardest stuff to take in.
Oh yeah you know here's an example throw this in maybe about the obvious you ever notice when you heat or cooler room the heat goes to the ceiling and the cold goes to the floor all year round.
So you have a hot head and cold feet but if you go out in nature it's hot in the valley you go up to the mountain it gets colder and if you go in an airplane towards the sun which is supposed to be a heat source it gets colder and colder and colder.
Because could it be that in all natural biological systems cold rises and heat descends but in all artificial type situations you have the opposite so where are the people asking their air conditioning and heating engineers why don't you design systems that have an ascending cold and a descending heat like in nature.
Because right now we're getting hot heads and cold feet I have never thought of that and how obvious is that I'm sitting here exactly in that condition I've got my slippers on trying to keep my cold feet warm and yeah I got a hot head.
Doesn't make any sense so why would it be that way even.
Well if you want to just give a quick slice for those that tend to be technically or scientifically inclined let's say whenever you have chemical decomposition or things being destroyed or exploded you have the heat that rises in the cold at descends but whenever you have a chemical agglomeration where things come together and build like natural growth you have a cold that rises in a heat that descends like for example if you called a medical person and said I'm not feeling well and they say well how do you know.
Well my head is hot my feet are cold you're not feeling well but wait a second I thought heat supposed to rise and cold supposed to descend but you see an all natural biological systems whether it's the earth the planets a dog a cat a plant or you the heat becomes dense and descends and the cold becomes verified and lighter and it rises and no one is paying attention no one is going to follow that.
Yeah but why because it's right in front of us the same what the time keeping schedule you know here's the thing you know the for for thousands of year the ancient.
kept time using the sun the moon in the stars be and we're very precise and very accurate like even today if you want to convey an accurate time event well by the way time is just the recordation of events so whenever you hear about time travel or this or time being a dimension that's all bunk if there is time travel it's traveling to a past event it's not time travel now Greek that's semantics but think about it all right so for thousands of years people settled the
debts with the full moon which is the new moon today don't you get a moonfully built yeah and the day starts at high noon like before the electronic banking conventions the banks if you made a deposit
after noon it was counted as the next day yes some people say after two o'clock or whatever but typically that's how it works and even this if you go to your time keeping
authorities in Greenwich or in the observatory in Colorado Springs I believe in their website they used to have a since I've started speaking about this I think they've taken it down but you can still find it under Julian calendar date that define the calendar and they tell you in their time keeping
the for is it tell you that for astronomical and scientific purposes the day starts at solar noon but for the people it's civil midnight now wait a second that is such a put down what I mean by that is when dictionaries in the
19th century were becoming coalesced to be put out into the public they didn't quite know how to define words because you see a dictionary doesn't give you the meaning of the word it gives you the
definition of the word how you should pronounce it so you seems like you know what you're talking about that's why when you look up a word in a dictionary it always shows you the phonetic spelling first you know like the upside down e means an a and all this other stuff but if you want to know what words really mean you
need to look up at a mology but back to the dictionary when they first started writing dictionaries they didn't know how to define words so like for example when you looked up in an old
word oats it's what they feed horses in England but it's the staple of the people in Scotland what a put down right so the scientific community and what you want to call them
illuminati or secret societies or the people that are in the know know that the the papal works schedule is not a timepiece
yeah webster was a free nason and he actually encoded many things into the dictionary like the bible that would one thing should lead you to another you know see this reference that it would lead you into this code so
you know even the dictionary was written by secret society
oh yeah and all the time you know how you know it's very important inside of free masonry as well yeah oh sure sure and that that's how you know your concept of equinoxes you know equal day equal night that's the same johns inside of free masonry
yeah and that is also erroneous because the term equinox equine meaning equal knocks meaning night means that there's an equal measurement that needs to be taken at night
we can discuss that later the real equinoxes and really freak people out it's very subtle so the equinoxes erroneous and even what they're calling solstices are erroneous because if you even look in their own
documentations like weather websites what they're calling the solstice you'll find like this year the day was still what they were calling solstice was about two minutes shorter than the then the then the day that would come after that so they're not acting but no one's checking right no no one wants to look at these things
so because it's part of tradition but you know the time keeping the secrets and the secret societies all of these things are linked together and these secret societies all they all they do it's it's kind of like the sewer analogy they kind of look at the behavior of the masses
and they say do we really want to share this information and they say no so they keep it to themselves to a certain degree but here's the thing well then what they've done is they've removed the eyes of the people and then blame them for being blind so it's a catch 22 you see so you know the information should go to mankind and it will not now because there's a right time in a place for everything right
and but in the near future there will be a time where people will start to look at what things are based on and referencing them more properly absolutely etymology is an amazing study you know when you start to realize where things come from what they mean your whole language changes you start to understand the legal system in a whole new light you know why human being is classified as monster or things you know
or nice you know you're a nice guy this is a nice show people are nice you know if you look up that word and I don't like to give the meaning of it because for some reason when people look it up on their own it has to have like 70% more punch to it and like they don't want to believe you when you tell them but the word nice if you look it up in an etymological dictionary it means foolish senseless stupid huh so yes that's just it we are we are really ignorant and and words are power and we know this
well what they are is the action to it's the pre action to action just like for example in the military and in an analogy you can have a commander sitting in one continent giving a word to someone on the ground in another continent and then the action is conducted so they are very powerful in that way it's communication and just like the military before you attack you make sure that the opposition cannot communicate amongst themselves now if you actually look at how society is on earth
if you think people are communicating you're not paying attention because they're not one of the first things that has been taken away is people's ability to communicate effectively
Amen, Amen. Well we open this show with the idea that the Francis Crick Institute is now legally altering DNA in embryos and opening the door to designer babies
and so I would like to close out this hour with you with the idea of the satanic view if you will the idea of stark materialism sure how we've gotten there and what that's going to lead to.
Well there's two aspects to that when we say something let's say the mark of the beast or the end times or Satan or the Antichrist we in order to prevent those topics or notions from being debased we have to go back to where those things came from
and obviously they came from what's called the biblical text so we have to go adhere to what is memorializing the biblical text first before we start making up porky pies and things like that because then we are just drifting off into law, law land.
If we go back to the text where we get the concept of Satan we will find that the word Satan just means adversary like if I say black you say white if I say ugly you say pretty that means you're an adversary to me.
This is a cosmic thing now what's interesting is when we look at the ancient text and this has nothing to do with opinion of what you believe in that the entire world is run by a cosmic adversary and for example Satan just means adversary for example court TV if you turned on court TV in Jerusalem in the modern he break tongue the prosecutor is introduced as ha satan.
So it just means the adversary.
So what is interesting when we look at the ancient texts regarding Satanism, this cosmic
deity or entity known as the adversary, and he does have a name by the way, which is
memorialized in many texts is in control, you're ready for this, of every government, every
major institution that man is involved in.
So all of your religions, all of your sciences, all of your philosophies, all of your governments,
all of your laws are controlled by this satanic cosmic deity.
Wow!
Now what I want to say about that is when you have these groups calling themselves Satanists
that is erroneous, because if you look at, for example, these Satanists, that is not
Satan, they, like, for example, the temple of set.
Set is not Satan set is like the Lord of darkness from Egypt, and you'll have various
sects, the columns of Satanists erroneously, they are reviving these ancient balls or
lords or demons of particular geographic locations of the world.
So again, we are not communicating.
But what I mean about the darkness, the second part to this is that when you read in the
ancient texts, beware the workers of darkness, for example, that is not necessarily visible
light and dark, but that as well.
And what I mean by this is, for example, in ancient days, society garnered most of their
behavior and materials from the light.
The day started at high noon, the full moon was the full month, and they used the stars
and the luminaries to keep time.
All of their materials to make furniture, clothing, food stuff, buildings were garnered
from the light, surface minerals, trees, plant fibers, plant inks.
See now, this is the time of great darkness, because your day is reckoned in the middle of
the night.
Your new year is reckoned in the darkest season, in the darkest day, the darkest month.
Your materials are all garnered from petrochemical products.
And anyone really say that there is nothing that is petrochemically derived within five
feet of their reach.
All of your food is wrapped in it.
All of your materials are affected by it.
Petrochemicals come from the dark.
It's black crude oil.
And also the light destroys the dark.
If you leave petrochemicals in the light, they're destroyed.
So this is the light and dark and the satanic and satanic.
There's contrast within each one and people fail to understand them still.
Amazing stuff.
Folks, his name is The Greek.
And this is where he's going by.
Getting us out this information that no one else is sharing.
And so I can't give you a website or anything to share.
But you are now currently on AFR doing a bit of a block there and sneaking your way in
sometimes in the late night shows.
I love Danny.
That's American Freedom Radio folks.
Definitely check out their shows.
And you've got a slot right now you're doing, right?
Sure.
And the site that we set up around that slot is called Ocele and The Greek.com.
Because I need adult supervision, Chuck Ocele, I feel very much indebted to him showing
up two hours a week to be the sonic counterpart to The Greek.
Because I just can't do it alone.
And it's called Ocele and The Greek.
And it is on AFR, yes.
And I do appreciate being here as well for these small bit of time.
Well I knew we were going to have a good talk.
And folks, I hope you gained some from this to really just to start to look at the obvious
again and take things in deeper.
And members, you know, it always gets stranger on the other side.
So when we get back, we're going to take this thing off this out of the world.
And get into advanced energy ideas, our future radio activity, end of the world, prophecies,
predictions and everything coming for you in the members section right now.
The rest of you, thank you so much for tuning in every week.
And I love seeing you all there at freemantv.com.
And please give us thumbs up, shares, rates and all that good stuff whenever you're listening
to the show, especially on Stitcher.
I don't know of me bringing this up will make it go down even worse, but it seems that
on Stitcher, when you're listening on your phone, you can give a thumbs up and it seems
like only the haters give the thumbs down.
So I would love to rise up in those top 100 ranks so that this show goes out to more and
more and more people because, you know, we're doing this because if you know, you better
share.
And that's the last message I want to leave with you all is share this information
with everyone that you can because you want to feel like you had a part in making the
change and you don't want to live with the guilt of having done nothing.
So if there's no more else you can do, at least share the information and that is at
least, you know, the least you could do.
We all have a big job in front of us as we're learning to learn, to get this true information
understood and to know what to focus on and what not to focus on.
So I'm so happy we have people like the Greek coming around to hone in our focus a bit more.
So stay tuned members, we're coming right back with some really good weirdness, you're
going to really enjoy this show.
And the rest of you, we will see you next week and, you know, a Freeman TV completely under
construction.
So don't worry, it's going to be awesome.
So if it's down, just don't worry, it's going to be great when it comes back.
It'll only be days.
So don't worry.
The website is down.
All right, so thank you all so much for tuning in.
We will see you next week.
And welcome back, members.
So wonderful to have you all here in York growing.
I hope you guys are all using the friendship agenda to get to know one another.
It's there for you if you're in the members section, scroll down to the bottom of the page
and it'll be there.
I'll have it better linked up for you on the new website.
But there is a social forum and social media platform for just you to go and share your
information, thoughts and wonderful feelings with everybody there.
Check out friendshipagenda.com because it's yours.
Academic understanding of the word Satan brings you up to this interesting concept of a stumbling
block.
An idea that there is a divine force sent by God, deity, whatever you need to stand in
your way so that you will make proper choices.
So from academic standpoint, the idea of a Satan in the original Hebrew form was an
emissary of God that came down and stopped you from doing something stupid.
And one of the examples in the Bible of this moment is Belom and his talking donkey.
And the idea that the donkey could see the mastima or Satan and the donkey driver was
just whipping him, telling him to get going.
So this is the idea when we start looking at our world, we are controlled by our biases
and the words that we use.
And so when I say the word Satan or Satanist, I mean something completely different than
what you mean when you hear the word.
So this is a very critical moment in our understanding and we have the Greek here with us today to
help lay some of this out.
Now we're gonna...
We're gonna look at catastrophes, we're gonna look at stumbling blocks that are coming our
way and we're gonna analyze, you know, what is academic.
So let's get into this Greek and just start looking at our world with a whole new light.
Sure, let's go alphabetically real quick.
Academic, look it up in an etymological dictionary.
Just put an etymology, the first site that comes up put in the word academic in the search
box.
What you will find is the word academic means impractical, theoretical and never coming
to a conclusion.
Hmm, great stuff, huh?
Okay.
Sounds about right, yeah.
Yep, and this is not my opinion, this is not my belief, this is anything that anyone can
access.
But you know regarding the adversary, what is called Satan.
Again, go back to the multitude of spiritual beings.
This is, I'm gonna make a strong statement here and people will find this to be true in
the future.
Men does not interact with man, just as if directly, it does it by proxy, just as if a military
general or a high official does not interact with the public.
Like people might say, well, for example, in America, Obama bombed this country.
No, he didn't in reality.
He gave the word, but you'll notice there is a whole proxy of troops and administrative
things and boots on the ground that executed.
What mankind has always been interacting with our messengers or lesser ranking deities
or beings in the spiritual realm that approach him.
Like for example, do you know that what the chief adversary, which is known as Satan, has
never possessed anyone, ever, but he will in the future.
That is what makes the antichrist so unique, by the way.
He's the only man that has ever been possessed by Satan himself.
For example, and this is not my belief.
Now this is coming again from a level of study that anyone can approach.
And what I mean by a level of study is, let's say, Freeman, I said, you're going to get
a free airplane ticket to go international.
It's free, okay?
Do you want to sit business, coach, or first class?
Well, you're probably going to say first class.
It costs the same.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So when you look at ancient texts, there is nothing to do again with what you believe in.
The biblical texts, not the King James.
Well let's say the King James for now, even though it's just a horrible document.
And I know this really sounds like I'm insulting people's religion, but I'm not.
The thing is, if you believe in something, you need to find what it's based on.
And furthermore, if you look at the biblical texts, you will find that it is first class
in terms of science, astronomy, health, history, all of these things.
There are many articles written by secular atheists historians that state that the biblical
text is by far the most precise and accurate historical document we have to date.
Okay.
But let me, hopefully not throw you off.
Hold that thought, but I want to throw these things in.
That one, folks, is the idea that this Bible in these ancient texts that have been around
for millennia.
And there is a reason for that.
We can't just toss these things out of a baby with the bathwater.
Correct.
You know, there is a purpose.
There is a reason.
We can't just be the ones that go, "I don't believe in that anymore."
We got to understand why it has controlled civilization for millennia.
Second, the King James Version, just as an example of mis-translations or misunderstandings
of what they were translating, if you go to the story of King David numbers, the fighting
men of Israel.
Now this story is told twice.
It's told in chronicles, second chronicles, and it's told in, I believe, second kings.
And it's the exact same story, but one was written 500 years later, which was the kings.
Right.
So when you start to look at this, when they open this puzzle in the Bible, in the King James
Version, especially, it will say, "And the Lord incited David to number the fighting men
of Israel."
And he paid such and such a mount.
And then the second one, the second telling, which was written 500 years later, says, "And
Satan incited David to number the fighting men of Israel, and this time he paid a whole lot
more."
But it's the exact same story.
So in the King James Version Bible, you go to chronicles, second chronicles, second kings,
and you will find the same story.
But in one, it says, "The Lord."
Now the Lord, that's a very obscure term too.
Are we talking about Jesus?
Are we talking about God?
What are we talking about when we say the Lord?
And it probably had some completely different word in Hebrew that meant something.
Correct.
And then you have, and Satan, in the second telling of the exact same story.
So is the Lord Satan in the King James Bible, you know?
Yeah.
Well, they don't translate the same word throughout.
Like, for example, they interchange soul and spirit, which mean totally different things.
It's gotten to the point with the King James, for example.
If you read the first verse of the first book in the first chapter, you're already thrown
into the meat grinder and you're done.
You know, in the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth.
If you get past that without inquiring what is written in the original, you are just going
to be in the meat grinder for their entire rest of it.
That's why you'll never hear me recommend anyone go and read or study it because you're
not going to understand anything in any way.
So why waste your time?
But, you know, and not to discourage people, if you want to go, and for example, examine
the first verse of the first chapter of the first book in the beginning, God created
the heavens and the earth.
That's ten words.
But if you look in the Hebrew, there are sevens.
You might say, well, they added three to make it make more sense in English.
No, actually, they added four words because they're not even translating one of the words
there.
They're not translating the fourth word in the first verse.
And if you want, I could give it in Hebrew real quick.
In the first verse of Genesis in Hebrew, it goes like this, it goes, "Bet a sheath,
"Bad a' al-Alam, et ta'asham, a yeem, behet a' adhats."
And if I could give you a directly translation of what that means, is beginnings of the
aloheem, which are the gods and plural, and the aloheem mean the emanators, okay, the
L, to be an L or an aloheem is to emanate.
And that just means very simply, if you're standing in an empty parking lot with an emanator
or an aloheem, and he says, "Farrari," a Ferrari magically appears in front of you.
That's all it is.
And that's been played upon by genies and things like that in popular, whatever.
Okay.
So beginnings, the aloheem, created, now this is the word that they're leaving out is the
aliph in the ta'av, and then the heavens and the earth.
What is the aliph in the ta'av?
The aliph in the ta'av is the first and the last letter of the Hebrew alphabet, or the Greek
alphabet, it would be known as the aliph in the omega, and the English would be known
the a in the z.
Now, if we look in Scripture very carefully, there's someone that identifies themselves as
the aliph in the omega.
So a very quick read of what it should say in Genesis 1 verse 1, "In the beginning, the
gods created the first and the last, or the Christ, and then the heavens and the earth."
Now, how does that make sense?
It doesn't really tie in very well.
I want to give another quick example regarding something that's in memorialized in art by
Michael Angelo.
If you go to Exodus 34, Moses comes down off the mountain and the people were afraid
to look at him because his face was shining.
That's not what it says.
If you look at that word that they're using for shining, now first of all, why would people
be afraid of his face is shining?
Because we actually compliment people.
You're glowing.
You look great.
Why were they afraid?
Because if we look at that word, "shining" in Exodus 34, you will find that the Hebrew word
is Karen, and Karen is where you get the scientific word for "carotain," which is what
bones are made of.
And horns.
So if you actually read the text and it says Moses came down off the mountain, he had horns
and the people were scared, well, that makes more sense.
And this was memorialized by Michael Angelo.
If you go do a cursory research on Google, sculpture of Moses by Michael Angelo, you will see
a seated person with little horns on his forehead.
With that?
Michael Angelo, because that's what was in the original text.
Here's, I'll throw in another example, the main fixture in Christianity is a guy nailed
to a cross wearing a loincloth, and without being disrespectful, I sometimes call it other
things.
But if you read the text, even if you watch the Hollywood movies, when he was brought
to Pontius Pilate prior to execution, Pontius Pilate did a public hand washing, and in
various books, harmonized, book of Mark, book of John, for example, which are very nice
Hebrew names, by the way.
No, you're not.
Pontius Pilate says, "I see no guilt in this man.
You have a law.
Use your law on this man."
So how could, if he's addressing the Judean authorities, how could there be a Roman crucifixion?
Now here's, there was no Roman crucifixion, and this is easy to back it up.
There's a lot of people discussing, there is no historic reference to Jesus.
And that is true.
There are many people discussing this.
But if you look at the biblical Christ and the biblical story, you will find that the Christian
Jesus is not in there at all.
What is being depicted in the religion of Christianity is not in the biblical text.
But if you look at the biblical text and you look at history, you will find that they
are perfectly aligned.
Now what this means, when Pontius Pilate said, "I'm returning this man to use your law,"
they used the Judean authorities, used the law of Moses.
The Bible punishment under the law of Moses was death by stoning.
But if you look at Deuteronomy 21, it makes an exception that a high crime, you are to be
nailed to a tree and taken down before the next day or noon.
And if you look at the book of numbers, it says anything that's been hanging on a tree
is a curse and to be burned.
So if we actually look at the event that the Christ was actually nailed to an almond tree
with two others on the same tree, we know it's an almond tree because there are over
30 references to something a specific event happening on an almond tree.
And it says that the people pass between the third and the ninth hour doing what?
Paddy cakes, hopscotch, watching someone nailed on a Roman crucifix or are they throwing stones.
Now remember that the Romans cast lots for his clothes because they knew everything would
be burned and he had herds robe.
And also when the Christ was being executed, he said, "Take care of my mother."
Why?
Because when you were killed in such a fashion, if you had any belongings in the world and
people went to, let's say, sell it or take it and said, "Do you really want that television?"
That was the guy that was, you know, a stone because he was blaspheming.
No, I don't want that.
So all of the personal belongings of the individuals were also piled up underneath the tree
and burned.
Now what's interesting about this is that when the body was put in the tomb, it had to be
guarded because of today's authorities wanted to take it to finish off the ceremony.
But here's the interesting part about the historical reference to this.
At the time of Pontius Pilate, anyone can do some research on letters of Pontius Pilate.
There are in the Internet better ones are found in books.
And what you will find in letters of Pontius Pilate during that time when he was sent as
the governor of Prefect to Judea, he was writing frequently to Claudius Tiberius Caesar for
backup because he only had a few hundred troops and he even told his men to walk around
in disguise to look like the people that lived there because if they found out how few
numbered they were, they would be endangered.
And Pontius Pilate had written in his notes of Tiberius Claudius Caesar that there's this
one Yahshua that should be looked at because he speaks against authority and he had gone
and heard him speak and he had said in his notes that he did not speak against the Romans.
He spoke against the Judean religious authorities.
And if you keep studying what he had written to Tiberius Claudius Caesar in secular documents,
he said that at one point they had brought this Yahshua to him for execution but then the
the mob of Judeans took him away to be stoned.
And this is in history records, not so if you look at the biblical text what actually
happened in the biblical text and in history, it's in perfect coincidance or coincidence
where in the religious side you will not find any evidence of any of that.
Very interesting.
I've always wanted to know more and more about that.
That's great places to start to understand and to look.
As we move this towards the idea of past catastrophes and coming global catastrophes, can
we focus a little bit in on another character that is often referenced and rarely understood
the rebel we know as Lucifer?
What's interesting about that, and this is a shocker to most, we have to adhere to what
the source is, you know how we say everything is debased, like the money is based on nothing
but we use it anyway.
The concept of Lucifer is being used very much so in all forms of media but it's debased.
What I mean by that is again we need to go back to where it came from.
If we look at the biblical text very carefully in the book of Isaiah, Lucifer is not a spiritual
being, it is a man, it is a Babylonian king of no name, for example, just like for example
you will find certain pharaohs are not named but their title is mentioned.
Now I just want to back you up there, that is completely correct folks.
When you read the passages, the single passage in the Bible that mentions the word Lucifer,
they are referencing a king.
Correct.
You know if you read it then you know this and then if I just ramble a little more, the
idea that people then toss in because this one says he fell and this one says he fell
like lightning therefore Satan is Lucifer.
I'm like how does this match?
How does this track?
There's no math here.
You can just grab these two partial sentences but when you read the passage about Oh Lucifer,
how thou has fallen that is in reference to what I thought was perhaps Nebuchadnezzar but
absolutely a man, a king.
Yes, it is a man and it is a king and one of the other giveaways is when you look at the
original language he is brought down to Shiel which is the grave, an earthly grave.
If he were a spiritual being, you cannot hold a spiritual being in an earthly grave meaning
six feet under when I say earthly grave.
I mean physically being put into the earth after you are killed or died.
The place where spiritual beings are contained is a place called Gehenna which is the pit let's
say where it's a sensory deprivation chamber because that's how you punish a spiritual
entity by the way, another whole other concept there.
But yeah, the thoughts that you read about in the description of Lucifer are the thoughts
that this man had.
Just like for example in the book of Exodus there is the thoughts that Pharaoh had if you
read where he says Pharaoh says, "I created you, I made the river, I made this."
You see and we know this is the thoughts of an individual, a very arrogant one for example
but Lucifer is dead.
Let's just say it that way.
If we're going to be factual, Lucifer died, I would say roughly three thousand years ago.
So all this stuff around, that's being discussed goes in the realm of the Easter Bunny and the
Santa Claus.
Well, I guess in that idea that I want to go ahead and lead you to a little more Easter
Bunny stuff.
We've been hearing a bit of a hum in your background and I know that you are into some
advanced technologies and so let's talk about another mastima or stumbling block in our
world and that is what is commonly referred to as free energy.
Oh, yeah, this is really the toppling of the psyche, I call it.
There is no such thing as free energy and what do you mean by that?
Well what you're looking, what people are actually, and that's put words in their mouth
with thoughts, what they're looking for is free power.
Energy is akin to let's say what people consider energy and matter and things like that.
Energy in its natural form is truly static unless there is movement.
What people are really looking for is free power so they can light their houses with lights
and machines and things like that.
Energy in a sense, let's just give an example.
For example, someone says this is an electrical generator.
No, it's not.
No one has ever generated electricity.
Any more than anyone has generated water with a water pump.
Someone going out and buying a water pump, even in the box, plug it in and all of a sudden
do you expect water to come out of it?
No, because the water pump is designed with certain features.
Let's say to give a certain volume or pressure for taking a static body of water and putting
it through the other side into a pressurized form.
Now when you have what's called an electrical generator, which is a rotating coil and magnet,
in essence, what it's doing, like a water pump based on its design is taking the static
form of energy in the environment and turning it into power.
So how do you do that autonomously?
Now how do that's done is you have to have a very good comprehension of objectively what
is going on and seemingly everything that's being discussed regarding the subject is erroneous.
And I know that's a tall statement, like for example Tesla is completely misunderstood.
What is known as light is misunderstood.
Electricity is misunderstood.
Electricity is not a conductor, it's an obstructor.
So once all of these things are put together, then we can have actually a field of science
where we can get the people that have more than two sharpened pencils in their pocket to
start building things.
But what is being put out by academia and the alternative media regarding energy right
now is false and that's why I can infatically tell people you will never get that free energy
because you're looking for something that doesn't exist.
What they should be looking for is for what was announced let's say in 1918 I believe
by the American electrical engineers that within six months because of the work of Charles
Proto-A Steinmetz and Tesla and others like that that they would have an autonomously
rotating electrical device to produce power.
And this has been almost a...don't have it because there was a mass diversion with Einsteinian
relativism.
Now I know this is a lot for the listeners but let me just throw one more thing in.
There's a fellow named J.J. Thompson who's kind of credited with the founding of what's
called the electron and the way that it's shown now is by the way that Walt Disney wants
us to see it but that's not what it is.
And he's the one that propagated it.
It was pretty much buried before Walt Disney.
Walt Disney spent millions of his own money and today's money let's say to promote the
concept of the atom as we have it.
But the most fundamental work of J.J. Thompson that's been buried is such is that weight is
not has nothing to do with matter or mass.
Now wait a second that sounds ridiculous.
You know if I pick up a brick it's heavy or it's the effect of gravity.
He had shown that mass has no weight.
What is happening is when you move mass electrical lines of force attached to it and the more
you move it or the more it's moved more electrical lines of force attached to it creating
what we call momentum.
If you know how to disconnect these imaginary or let's say almost intangible electrical lines
of force and send them to ground now you have what's called weightlessness.
And an example of that would be if you put a brick on a scale you'll notice it's about
six pounds but if you drop it from 20 feet the scale will register 150 for a moment.
That's because more electrical lines of force attached to it.
Stop thinking about the gravity acceleration stuff.
Yes that's fine.
The physics with that is nothing wrong with the acceleration of gravity but what we're
actually talking about is how it actually works.
Now when they had discovered this and actually had bench top working models of being able
to disconnect electrical lines of force and make things weightless back in around 1905
they started promoting this and developing it and when they figure out that weight no
longer mattered.
They said if we're going to put some people in something where weight doesn't matter the
pressure up there is not very it's very low and we need to have it pressurized.
So they had the early submarines like the World War One version of submarine.
So what they did is they took the rudders and propellers off and they elevated these things
and flew them around and they still are up until maybe 10 years ago it was quite popular
to see what's called a flying cigar shape.
Have you ever heard of that?
That is enough if you have a really good set of binoculars or a telescope and you actually
got a look at it you will see that the thing had rivets on it and it was really a submarine.
I have read this description in many of the UFO research I never never knew that.
Yes.
It's a complete sense to me.
Yeah and all of these things you see the thing is you don't want to demystify too much
because people have nothing to grab onto because if you're grabbing onto fantasy and
the Easter bunny and things like that then it will suddenly get taken away no more security
blanket you see.
The scary part here is that the people that realize this is starting from J.J. Thompson's
work and also Faraday's work and all these you know we're talking 19th century they're
not sharing right and they're not sharing the same way as if let's say that's put down
the people that live in Chad.
If you take the continent of Africa right in the middle is a country called Chad.
It's a very difficult place to live they even have human road kill on the roads that they
don't clean up there.
If you went to a place let's say like that where people were living very differently with
your iPhone or whatever and they said give it to me give it to me give it to you're like
oh we better hide our iPhone from these guys because they just want to take it from us right.
So there is a group of people on this planet that had their pulse on what was going on
quite scientifically let's say and these people were not known as scientists back in the
day they were known as natural philosophers so the term scientists is fairly new by the
way and when you are a natural philosopher you either a naturalist or a materialist you
know and this work of J.J. Thompson Nikola Tesla is not being shared and the key to figuring
out how to disconnect these electrical lines of force to get things moving is finding
what's called a virtual ground.
What do you ground to to disconnect these things from matter?
And that should be the basis of anyone in everyone's research on what's called free energy
or free power or the autonomous movement of objects or anti-gravity.
Wow you have some technology that you're working on that you're not ready to divulge yet
right?
No and a thing is because it's always changing just like in nature if you are growing let's
say crops on a farm it's always at different stages and then you have to harvest it and
start all over right?
But each harvest brings a yield which you can benefit from okay?
So yeah so this is how it all is just like look at technology how cars were and airplanes
back it's just a progression right?
Now the interesting thing about for anyone who is interested in experimentation is that all
natural energy goes from a low potential to a high potential.
We are taught that all potentials go from high to low.
So once you comprehend that now you will understand how the weather works now you will understand
how to begin working on disconnecting these lines of force from objects and getting things
to move on their own.
You will also get a much deeper understanding on what chemical reactions really are and
you will get an understanding on what matter is and I just want to throw this one thing
and you hear a lot about this Fukushima and radiation and all this other stuff is being
whatever it is that is completely misunderstood.
It was proved over a hundred years ago that there is no energy in matter.
E=mc2 just means Einstein equals a moron times a speed of light squared.
It was just a big diversion to get people away into Lala land or relativism.
You really don't think there is any danger from Fukushima?
Well here is the thing yes there is depending on how you approach it.
If you can take a block radioactive material and if you research it enough there is no
radioactivity in the material itself.
This goes against a lot of there is a particular guy called a polymath.
I am not going to mention his name around the turn of the century.
A lot of people follow him.
His first name starts with a W as last one is with an R. He has done a lot of really good
work on harmonics but one of his biggest misunderstandings is that there is energy in matter
and there is no energy in matter.
Radioactive material what they call radioactivity material what it essence is they are called
heavy metals correct?
They end up being dense in a certain way.
All they are is reflectors of this cosmic energy and it reflect this cosmic energy into
the environment very intensely and when I say very I mean that is what the capital are.
They are intense reflectors.
Now an intense reflector anyone knows that if you stand in front of a concave highly polished
mirror in the sun that is very intense sunlight so much you can melt a penny on it right?
Does that mean that all of that energy is coming out of that reflector or is it a matter
of just reflecting the ambient you see?
And this was proven by Tesla and Wilhelm Reich.
Tesla proved you can take material that is not radioactive and make it radioactive and Wilhelm
Reich proved that you could take radioactive material and render it un radioactive and
many people doing research with hydrolysis which is the degeneration of water into hydrogen
and oxygen also found the able to render radioactive material neutral with that process as well.
So yeah.
Ed Lee Scalnan of Coral Castle fame said that he could do this with magnet magnetism.
Correct now what is interesting about magnetism is there is two components to it there is also
the dielectric component to it which is what is called a capacitor or magnetism would
follow an obstructive medium known as a metal and a dielectric side of this energy is our
things that are organic like wood, rubber, plastics things that we call insulators are actually
dielectrics.
They also store material like for example if you're in socks in an apartment that has carpeting
and you're walking across the room and touch the door knob you get a zap.
The ancient Greeks found if you rub wool on volcanic glass you get a spark.
You see that is the dielectric component and everyone is talking about electromagnetics
but no one is talking about the dielectrics which is the storage of this energy.
Sure yes.
Now a lot of these guys getting into this also get into the human body and I think the orgasm
has come up in this research as well.
Why is this?
Yeah.
So yeah let's take it there.
We were talking about having to build pressurized UFOs out of submarines.
And the human body I understand that you have a different perspective on some of the inner
workings of this and maybe this inner body.
What I really wanted to work with you through is the body, the understanding of some of
the misconcepts and then also the soul and the spirit and then we'll take this into some
future predictions of coming mastamas and stumbling blocks and catastrophes but let's
understand ourselves first.
Oh absolutely very simply I love giving the analogy of what's considered to be blood pressure.
Let's just look at this, let's just look at ourselves right where people, let's get up
on our hind legs you know, not a metaphor that we were dogs but you know a very often say
let's get up on our hind legs and pay attention.
When you put your hands in water and your feet water do they shrivel up or do they puff
up like a frog and the answer is they shrivel up.
So guess why? because it's a negative pressure like if you're going to vacuum seal a piece
of meat in a bag when you pull the vacuum on it does it shrivel up or does it expand?
It shrivels up.
The body is a sealed, it's we're not filter bags or everything is completely sealed.
The intestines the lungs the skin and it's under a slight negative pressure, slight vacuum,
not intense vacuum but very slight under the ambient.
What they're doing is they're strapping a cuff around people's limbs and inflating it
to block the flow of the fluids that are moving under a vacuum and telling you you have
blood pressure.
Now if you actually study what they're calling blood pressure it's not really pressure
in the entire body they're looking for.
It's a particular function in the heart but most people walk away thinking that the body
is under pressure.
It's not.
The biological things are under what's called what Victor Schauburger called a biological
vacuum which is a very subtle vacuum.
That's why when you cut yourself you need a few seconds if not longer for the vacuum to
be broken and the blood to reverse its flow and come out.
Even the femoral artery where if you see in the movies when it's cut the blood shoots out
three, four feet into the air once it's cut the vacuum is broken and then after a certain
amount of time then it starts shooting out from the artery.
And what's interesting about how the body works were taught that were these porous filter
bags.
If you look at the how the intestines are structured in medical books you will see there
are three major layers and they're all hydrophobic.
They're not porous.
For example in many countries they use bladders of animals to hold water.
You see.
And intestines.
The body is a unique thing tying back to many of the sciences that were beginning to
give.
Initial research had shown this.
But somehow there was a fork in the road where we bring the stumbling block where we
know just enough about the body based on three thousand years of accumulated battlefield
medicine.
If you look at what's being applied today in the medical community the entire medical
establishment it is nothing more than derivations or expanding battlefield medicine that's
been gathered for thousands of years.
The actual true nature of the body needs to be understood as we'll evoke the name of Victor
Schauburger.
Anyone can look him up with its V.I.K.T.O.R.
Last name would be Schauburger S.C.H.A.U.R.G.E.R.
Talked about a biological vacuum in all things.
So once we start understanding how the human body works and when we eat food we don't absorb
anything.
It passes through the body and becomes de-energized very much like Jean Roddenberry's
food replicator.
These things are in the realm of science fiction almost when you discuss the reality of it.
That's why I was jokingly once someone said you have an organ donor card I said for what?
He says well you know donate your organs to science.
If something happened to you I said are you kidding I'm already donating these organs to science
fiction?
But anyway.
So the reason why it's important to understand the body is because if you're deceived about
how your body works which is your headquarters you're going to accept if headquarters is
deceived anything that comes out of headquarters is going to be laced with this deception.
So if people start looking at how the body actually works like for example here's another thing
let's talk practical stuff right now.
You know how they tell us that we get the common cold because of bacteria and people believe
it?
Well guess what?
If you believe that the common cold and these things are caused by bacteria and pathogens
what you just did is rendered the need for refrigeration useless because the reason we
have refrigerators is to retard the growth of bacteria.
So how can it be getting sick?
How do why do most people get the common cold in the winter?
Very simply because of their diet.
And what I mean by that is that if you are living in a cold place and you eat food that is
grown in a tropical place when you pass that food through the body that will adjust the
body to a tropical climate.
Thinner blood, different type of metabolism.
The body tries to make balance with that by developing mucus because you're losing vacuum.
You see like whenever mucus is developed in the body it's because the body is losing vacuum
or it's trying to plug.
Like here's an example, anyone can look this up when a woman is holding a baby in the womb.
If you go look at it anatomically there's a plug in the uterus to keep the baby from falling
out.
What is that called?
That is called a mucus plug.
So in the opposite let's go back to why people get sick in the winter or the summer.
If you're living in the tropics and you eat a piece of salmon what does salmon come from?
It's a cold water fish let's say.
If you eat that that will adjust your body temperature or your body metabolism and blood
quality to be in the Arctic or cold place.
And you will be in the tropics and you will turn the air conditioning down to near freezing
and you will still be warm in ill.
Now what's interesting about that the opposite occur when you're in a cold place and you
have a fever it's hot.
When you're in a hot place and have a fever it's cold.
So we have to understand the various things.
Now the reason I'm saying this to be practical is because we can get more into the science behind
it, the real science behind it.
But I hear so much of alternative media.
How many alternative medical people, nutritional people are out there, thousands of them.
They have websites, shows and all that.
And how many are saying these basic practical things?
None.
As a matter of fact they're still using terms like viruses.
And viruses don't even exist.
No one has ever seen a virus.
All you're going to see is a computer graphic or drawing or a description.
But if you actually look up what a virus is even in Wikipedia they tell you the whole concept
of virology is based on toxicology.
And what they call viruses are all come out of the liver.
So this is just, we're talking about fantasy land here but the best practical information
anyone can give is remember the body has to maintain a vacuum.
Like for example, if you receive a bruise you notice how the material swells up on the
body.
That's because the interstitial spaces are rearranged in a way that the vacuum is broken.
So one of the ways to heal a wound or something very quickly is to wrap it very tightly.
And if the room for a good amount of time let's say a day or so.
And you have to release that wrapping when you start to get let's say a blue or purple
finger every few minutes and then re-wrap it very tightly.
What you're doing is you're decreasing the volume of the body which does what?
Increase vacuum.
So understanding vacuum and also understanding what is causing most of the common illnesses
in people.
I've actually experimented on myself when it's winter time.
I eat seasonally or cross latitudes.
So when it's cold out make sure that you eat food cross lateral.
You know take the earth and look across the line.
And this way you have some variety.
So let's say you live in middle America you go across the line and you'll see places in
Germany, middle China, places like that.
So you have variety in your food.
Eat cross latitude.
Now it's interesting you ever notice the pagan holidays, Christmas, New Year's all those
people get their colds.
Why?
Because they have their festivals and guess what they're eating?
Sugar, snacks, desserts, exotic foods.
Where do most of these come from?
Tropical places.
You see?
Amazing.
Yeah, I've done experiments where I've totally acclimated eating seasonally and I say okay, it's
a middle of winter.
I'm going to go buy a banana.
I eat the banana.
I feel like crap.
It's about three days to get out of your system.
And the other ridiculous thing is like, oh, I'm a school teacher and I caught a cold from
the children.
Total rubbish.
Because I saw you in the supermarket buying bananas and tomatoes in the middle of the
winter just like the school children are eating them.
You didn't catch a cold.
What happened, the reason why they say there's bacteria is because there's something called
an emergence, things emerge.
If I take a blood sample from you or a mucus sample and remove it from the host, a living
tissue, blood, whatever it is, now it is going into decomposition mode, put it in a slide,
it's decaying and there's going to be an emergence of bacteria and things like that.
So this is what they're saying.
That's why most of medicine, modern medicine based on their chemistry is detrimental because
whenever they remove anything for examination from the host, whether it's a plant, animal
or human, it goes into immediate state of decomposition.
So now they're designing drugs around decomposing things that would not exist in the natural
host.
So the simplest advice to give anyone, and it's not a matter of giving medical advice, it's
a matter of giving good, common sense.
If you eat seasonally, you will notice that you are a lot of things called allergies and
colds and even a lot of things that are quote unquote contagious will not occur to you.
I'm totally going to try that Greek.
Oh, you'll like, it's kind of difficult in the beginning because if you like coffee and
it's real, and you're in two feet of snow, well guess where coffee grows, you know?
Yeah.
But hold on, you know during World War II when the shipping lanes were caught off, they
did a lot of great coffee substitutes in Europe.
You could look them up, they're made with chickery and hazelnut and things like that because
you know, there was more important to ship rifles and guns and bombs and coffee during World
War II and the people in Europe love their coffee.
So there's a lot of good coffee substitutes and sugar substitutes.
Maple syrup for example is a good one because where does that come from?
Pretty temperate, cool place.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so think about it.
It requires a little thought.
Don't take anything for granted.
And the reason I'm giving this and emphasizing this part of a bit of information is because
it, almost everyone who takes this information and uses it is spared the misery of what's
known as the cold or feeling under the weather, you know?
I hate it.
And you won't and it takes about, and here's the other thing specifically, unless your
under, you know, unless your body is so beaten up and you're, let's say you're even moderately
healthy, it takes about two or three days for your body to turn around and I recently
did one where a woman said she was cold and I'm in the southwest, it doesn't get very rarely
near freezing.
And I walked into her house and she had one of these little banana trees and I said, what's
that?
She goes, bananas, why do you eat them?
Because of potassium, I forget about that.
Get rid of that.
We went out and bought a piece of salmon and poached the fish and she ate it two days later.
She was out in just a long sleeve shirt instead of like a parcher coat in 40 degree weather.
She said, I can't believe it works.
I'm like, I'm not asking you to believe anything.
I'm just asking you to try it.
There you go.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Yes.
And I must eat pretty well because I am rarely ill and if I am it's minor.
So I do eat salmon in the winter.
I do love to cook and I think that's also critical.
I was once asked to train pizza hooks all around the United States because I made the best
pizza in the world.
And I literally told those men in suits, you know, the regional managers had come to
me to ask me to go train everybody in the region and I said, well, you know, love is an ingredient
and I can't treat that.
What am I supposed to do?
I just love to give people good food.
All right.
Let's move to the realms of science fiction and science faction because we're wrapping up
the end of the show and I don't want to go out without getting some of your predictions.
Just last month, bizarre news coming up all over social media and even making its way
to my local news in South Carolina and I believe in news around the United States.
Two major sonic boom events just occurred.
One happened in Charleston, earth shook, building shook, sonic boom, people thought it was the
end of the world, military government, everyone involved, don't know what it is.
Have no idea.
There was no subsonic, no sonic flights.
There were no rockets.
There was no nothing going on.
There was no media just followed shortly two days later.
Boom, sonic boom's over new Jersey, earthquake, lightning shakes, not lightning, sorry, but
earthquakes.
Uh, same thing, military knows nothing, government can explain.
We are entering into a bizarre time right now, folks.
And with all the things that we've discussed in these last two hours, the religious beliefs,
the ideals of the secret societies, the reason things are being done is all occulted to us.
And when you start to dig in and find out what's really known, then you can even take this
and apply it, make projections and even get proper predictions.
So I know Greek, you've worked on this very deep.
Maybe you want to outline how you've come to your conclusions, but let's just get it out
there because we're running out of time.
Okay, real quick, you know, understanding the society on this planet, the gestures that
humanity has been making through their traditions and customs is quite offensive to the spiritual
realm.
And it's like, "Woo, wow.
Why is he saying that?
Who is he to say that?"
Well, unless you understand what cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common, you won't
understand human society.
What does that mean?
Well, back in the ancient days, where they spoke the Babylonian Caldien Hebrew tongue,
like, let's say, the Latin tongue would encompass many others, the people that was called the
Caldien Hebrew back then, the people then were told to worship these balls or lords.
And the way you worship the Lord is by having a child sacrificed and at the sacrifice, some
of the flesh and the blood of the child was consumed.
And this was done by the priests, known as the cahons, to worship the balls.
So that's where you get the term cannibalism, it's cahon ballism.
So literally cannibalism means priest of the Lord.
And what's interesting about that, it sounds like an abominable act to most people to speak
about it overtly, but I assure you, you will find this as being very common in ancient times.
That's why there's thousands of archaeological sites going on right now, but very little
is reported and the crews are rotated because all they find when they dig down is evidence
of human sacrifice.
The disciples cast in the shape of children with boiled bones, with scraping marks and this
is everywhere and it's so prevalent, that's why you don't hear anything about archaeology
anymore.
The second part, what do dolls have to do about it?
Well once the child was sacrificed, the parents went back to the family and the other children
asked, "Where is my brother?
Where is my sister?"
So the altar boys of these priests of the Lord are cahon balls, made an effigy of the
child and told the parents to give the doll or the effigy of the child to the other
children to play with.
So now you know what the history of dolls are, why children are given dolls.
Now the birthday is interesting because of the 19th century, a small little book in a
university archive, it was called Ancient Rites and Rituals of the Caldean Hebrews and
Rites was spelled R-I-T-E-S, stated that they started going away from human sacrifice
and baking loaves of sweet bread and putting lights in it and having children and adults
make a wish of prosperity to blow the lights out.
And anyone attending the ceremony was to bring a present to show that the ceremony was effective.
Now if that is not a parody of the birthday cake or parody of human sacrifice, I don't
know what is.
That is so creepy.
It is very creepy.
So now you wouldn't believe how many people I explain this to and they say it's horrible
and then invite me to a birthday party a week later.
I'm like, are you guys listening?
But anyway.
Did you bring a doll?
Yeah.
So what are the chances of these things going away?
Now this is a gesture being given to the spiritual realm because what people don't understand
is that the spiritual side or the gods, especially the chief deity, take the dealing of young
children as being un, as you might have read, they're uncorrupted, corrupting them is not
good, right?
They actually, the spiritual realm, the benevolent side actually loves children more than
parents do.
This is a hard thing to say because a parent's love is something that's very strong and dynamic.
But could you imagine a spiritual being that would love your children more than you love
theirs?
And now you're putting them through dolls and birthday cakes and, boy, you're going to
have problems on the spiritual side.
This is just this is not something I believe in.
This is something I am reporting and imparting accurately.
What I mean, believing in, meaning there is no wiggle room.
You cannot wiggle out of this once you hear it is what I mean by that.
So what is coming upon when you read about all the doom and gloom and the end of the world?
It's not the end of the world, but it's the end or stopping of these types of traditions.
The earth is going to be just fine, you see.
Right, absolutely.
The world meaning that society.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, humanity that's on the chopping block here and we're definitely looking into, I
mean, the amount of reports that we get of coming solar EMPs, they're saying not if when,
you know, and this of course would shut down global power networks and pretty much just
turn off the world or for us, we have the ideas that they're warning us of asteroids.
We had a poffis, which of course is the Egyptian serpent deity of destruction that's supposed
to come back around in 2029 and destroy all life.
So yeah, let's get into that.
And how does that relate to, yeah, this, yeah, you know, in many of the texts, you'll see
that there are cosmic events that are going to be, I call them cosmic kill shots on the
earth because the earth isn't very happy either on what we're doing.
So we meaning the collective human race.
I try to set myself apart by, by, by behavior and other things and try to give information
to others.
And we can't deny the guilt of the golems that are known as corporations.
Right.
Now, a corporation could just be a group of people forming a fictional entity to make the
innocent pay for the guilty.
That's all it is because you're fixing to do something wrong, start a corporation and then
just collapse and then no one can go after anything.
But not all corporations are like that, but that's essentially what they're doing.
Yeah, I guess I had to throw that in there because I've found humans to be such wonderful
beings just completely misguided.
So yeah, we are misguided all the way to birthday cakes and dolls.
So let's, yeah, sure.
Now, the final, I just want to just because we don't have a lot of time.
What you call the early 2030s, and this has been also interesting.
I don't like saying NASA and all that, but in scientists, but they do put out information
quite accurately and then retract it or they cover it up or change it.
But unmistakably with even the basic mathematics and observations that the mainstream scientists
are looking at.
And then some major asteroids are going to be coming into the late 2020s, early 2030s.
I think they have one pinned around what they call October 2028, something like that, a
poffis.
Okay, that's pretty good actually because what we find in the ancient texts is that there
are going to be three kill shots.
Two of them are going to be asteroid types and the third one is going to be solar.
Now the two asteroid types, so we'll go through the first one is pretty common.
You'll probably be shown what it looks like, you know, that potato shape or cratered
rock kind of thing.
And that will hit a particular part of the earth.
And the second one, and it will kill many people, many casualties will be in the billions,
but with a B, not an M.
Let me just ask if you have any projections as to where that would hit.
Yes.
What's interesting when we look, for example, at the biblical text, it says one third of
the sea, one third of the fish, one third of the ships, three times it gives you, so
you got to look at something.
When you, we have to define when the biblical text states the sea, it's specific about the
Mediterranean, unless it speaks about all the seas, right, in plural.
This one is singular.
So if you look at a map of the Mediterranean, you'll see it's divided in three parts.
Greece and Italy comes down as a peninsula, if you will, and divides it into three different
parts.
So one of those sections is going to be where the epicenter of this drop is going to be.
And you can guess which one, it's probably going to be the one closest between Greece and
the Levant, because that would be more towards where more people are inhabited, for example.
Okay?
Now the second asteroid, if it's all right, will go on with that one.
Please do.
You will not be shown any imagery of that.
Well, wait a second.
Why not?
Well, because too many questions will be asked if you're shown that one.
And the reason why you will not be shown is because it has an extremely high degree
of manufacture.
It will appear as a flat disc with an aspect ratio of about seven to one, meaning it'll
be seven times wider than it is thick.
And I'll have a hole in the middle of it.
Very highly polished stone surface.
Now the last thing you want to do is now put out a photograph, say we have this two mile
wide near-earth object that might collide, and they show you a picture of something of
high degree of manufacture like that.
People will freak out too many questions.
You will not be shown that one.
Quite interesting.
This is in the ancient text.
You don't have to believe in it.
I'm just reporting on it, right?
If you want to bring an umbrella or do what you, if it's going to rain tomorrow, you don't
have to believe it, but when it does, it's up to you if you were or encoder not.
This is how I like to give the information.
Almost in a cold fashion, because I have to disconnect myself from this from things, whether
they're positive or negative, you see.
Right.
Now the third thing is a solar event.
Most people are aware of solar flaring and types of things like that.
This third event is going to be a solar event that has never happened in known history.
It's not going to be a solar flare.
It'll be the sun.
Imagine the sun has a dimmer knob on it, and right now it's been at one-seventh.
Around that time period, after people recover or sort of recover from these two hits, the
sun will be turned up at full volume, and put that in perspective, what it will look
like, is the full moon will be as bright as the new-day sun.
We're talking an ambient daytime temperature of well above 150 to 180 degrees Fahrenheit
for about a week or so.
We know that it will be around the lawful timekeeping of the moon, because the reference
is given that the full moon will appear as the new-day sun.
The actual sun itself will be extremely hot.
You will no longer be able to see its disc.
It will be like the entire horizon will be lit almost as bright as the sun is.
It will also cause probably damage or destruction of all vegetation.
Now, most people hear this.
They think it's complete catastrophe, but it's not because if you look at a forest that's
been burned almost days later, you have an emergency of minor vegetation coming back, and
within a few months the shrubs and other things come back.
So it doesn't mean that there will never be plants on the earth again.
So all of these clustered events are things that might people might want to, I never
want to send people to read and study the Bible.
Why?
And I'm not being sarcastic.
You're not going to understand anything in it, so leave it alone.
But if those that hear me say something like that are feel antagonized enough and want
to prove me wrong, by all means, please study these ancient texts.
If you could even look at what they call the Mahabharata, the Rig Vita's, you could look
at the Biblical texts, the Quran.
You will find that they are all in agreement in many of their points.
And how do you think they knew this?
Oh, what's interesting is, you know how people discuss source or creator?
They actually make the source and the creator as being a dummy, or illiterate, or mute, or
dumb.
Because if there is a source or creator, are they intelligent enough to communicate with
us?
That's a sounds like a stupid question, of course they are.
And would they communicate with us in a certain way that would allow us for still going
through the curing period of 7,000 years that mankind requires, with that being heavily
disturbed?
Because if we look in history, the mankind accelerated his, let's say, evolution and he had
to be stopped.
And you know, Tower of Babel, things like that, right?
There was also another cosmic censorship that was put on the planet around 2500 BC, 2500
years ago, and that's where all the world's religions emerged pretty much from except
for Islam later on.
So we are being censored and held in a curing period.
What I mean by a curing period is like when you bake a cake, it's 45 minutes in the oven.
If you take it out half way, it doesn't work.
So there's a curing period of 6,000 years which already ended in roughly 1998.
And we're in the credits part right now.
And all of these communications were given through man in very, let's say, inspiration.
For example, let me just give, and some of it was direct communication.
For example, if you read in the book of Jeremiah, in one of the passages, it says all the towns
paraphrasing here, all the people come and knock on his door and they ask Jeremiah, what
were you told?
Well, how would everyone in town know that a message was being transmitted to this one
particular person?
Well, maybe because it was like a hovering UFO over the house for three days and no one
could approach because of the force field?
Well, you know, this is very much like the stories of the angels that visit and, and
what, everybody wants to have sex with them?
Yeah, which is also, you know, there's three, by the way, I'll throw this in real quick.
There's three human type-looking forms.
No one has discussed and I'll throw this in.
It could be another show.
You have the sons of gods, the sons of Adam, and then the, the Nephilim, which are the
hybrids.
And the King James Bible says the sons of gods took the daughters of men and had the Nephilim,
right?
That's not what it says.
It says they took the sons of Adam.
There's a big difference.
I mean, it's denoting a bloodline.
So you have a line of Adam, the, the sons of gods.
Let me just throw this in.
This is the members area only are the progen, or the, the offspring of the subcontractors
in the spiritual realm that help redo the earth because the earth is a redo, if you read
in Genesis, by the way.
Yeah.
There's two Genesis accounts.
There are two births of man and as you say, there's the line of Adam in the second.
Well, there actually isn't.
Let me just throw this in.
Okay.
This is a misunderstanding.
When you read Genesis chapter one, it shouldn't end there.
It should end around verse three of chapter two.
The reason why is if you ended at the round, verse three, chapter two, it has all the elements
of an affidavit for putting evidence into a court case.
All chapter one is, is if you were going to court and you were witness to something, you
were going to, or make a claim to something, you're right.
What's called a legal affidavit and then sign it.
So that's all it is.
It starts off with the legal precedent or lawful precedent.
Chapter two is where it gets into the story.
Now you also have to realize that the first five books of the Bible were delivered by Moses,
roughly 2,500 years after the fact to be given to the people of Israel, let's say, as one
would give a constitution to form a nation.
So they put the first authoritative document known as the, what I call the affidavit, because
if you want to know more about creation, you don't necessarily go to chapter two of Genesis,
you go to the book of Psalms between chapters 102 to 108 if you want extreme detail on how
a lot of it was done.
Okay.
All right.
Good.
I mean, we all need to understand this stuff because it does rule our world.
And I think everybody would be quite a mess with me if I didn't ask you, do you have an idea
of when these kill shots might occur?
The early 2030s with about a 95% right now, I would say, but as we get closer, we can give
more accurate time.
The reason why is this.
Let's say I'm going to drive a 2,000 mile road trip.
If you ask me how long it's going to take, I might say, well, it should take three days.
But half way down, there's a little glitch.
I need to stop for an extra time.
Then the time spreads out a little bit.
But if certain events happen and I'm saying one exit away, then you know no matter what
happens, I'm no more than 20 minutes away.
You see?
So all of these prophetic texts never give dates or days.
They give events when you see this, then the next thing will come.
You see?
Gotcha.
Got it.
All right.
So yeah, it's definitely keying up with the mainstream media's projection of catastrophes
on the rise.
Yes, it is.
As you can see, this is, it's happening already with these sonic booms going on over South
Carolina and New Jersey, things are happening and no one knows what the heck's going on.
So I'm so glad there are people like the Greek out there to start to lay this down and
give us more insight to know what to learn.
You know, this is more critical to learning is to know what to learn.
And I find this all just really amazing, Greek.
I think this has been a wonderful show.
Well, thank you.
Yeah, I do my best.
And thanks for having me.
I had a problem.
Let's see.
I had one thing I was going to go out with and I lost it in my notes and I asked it, they're
going, oh, what was that last thing?
But questions are being asked and answers are not always forthcoming and it's hard to know
where to trust your information.
And I just want you to go, folks, that we really vet our information and we also want to give
you all the resources necessary to go and learn this for yourself because everything
we say is not opinion.
It really isn't.
It's based off of all the science and we're still out here going, well, what does it all
mean?
There's much more to our soul and our spirit, something that we didn't quite get into
in this show, but we'll have a Greek back on to get deeper into that because that is
one of the critical factors for us to focus on.
And I hope that we all can do that, come out there, become friends, share this information,
share ourselves with each other and most especially share the proper food for everyone so
that we don't get sick and we can have the strength to do everything we need to do, right?
There's a Greek.
Oh, you bet.
Yeah, food is, yeah, it's that's food clothing and shelter and no matter how broke you
are or how rich you are, those are the three most important things we can do right now.
Physically.
Yeah.
Well, I don't think that thoughts ever going to come back to my mind.
I'll think of it after I sign off of the show.
But yeah, amazing, amazing.
Oh, I remember now.
Just one last thing I wanted to say was that I will be blown away if this discus thing
comes through.
I've seen something similar to that that's equated to the Syrians and it was something
to do with the Dogon tribe but it was actually a disc found in China that described a race
from Syrias.
It was, you know, and we're saying it.
You could play it, you looked like you could play it with a record, like a record.
Yeah.
Wow.
Yeah, very much so.
Yeah, you'll find these commonalities.
Again, most of the time I advise to anyone is take the information, ruminate, meditate
on it, file it away for later.
It's not going to do much for you right now but at least you'll be able to add it to
a collection of things that when they do start coming, you can piece it together and
say, wow, we were told.
Yes.
The information will find a way and if you open that door it will find its way in.
I will forever say I never went looking for any of this.
It came and found me.
So take that to heart because it will come and I love you all.
Thank you all so much for participating in this wonderful experiment.
We call it the free zone and I will see you all next week.
All right.
Have a good night.
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]