[Music]
Beaming out across the galaxy.
This is where conspiracy on the wall side
means the perspective of a lifetime.
This is the free zone, ghost, free men.
[Music]
You wanted to Greek and you got the Greek.
Welcome to the free zone.
We have gotten more requests to have the Greek back on so much that
we pulled them out of retirement.
Bring them out here for an exclusive talk here on the free zone.
And I am so excited to dig into this mind
because there's none other like it.
And I know this is going to be an intriguing show
as we try to discover really what is freedom, what is sovereignty,
and who are you?
What world do you live in?
So let's jump right in because I don't want to waste any time.
Greek, welcome to the free zone.
Well thanks for having me, Freeman, and welcome to everyone listening.
There's lots of them out there.
I'll tell you, tens of thousands of people tune into this show every week.
I am so impressed and so thankful of all of you guys.
And I hope that you will go and give us a thumbs up on whatever player
you listen to this show on.
If you don't know, this show is on every player out there from iTunes, Android,
Google, tune in, Spotify, Stitcher, you name it, the free zone is on it.
All you need to do is type in the free zone with Freeman and it will come up on any podcast player out there.
And there are tens of thousands of you out there listening right now.
You know, Greek, we, you know, I pulled the show from YouTube right now just because YouTube is like
canceling everybody's channels for saying things.
And since this is on our own private server, and I don't have to worry about saying what I want to say,
I've pulled it from YouTube because I didn't want to lose all that 15 years of YouTube content just to put the podcast on there.
So we are free here to say whatever we want.
There is no censorship. There's no worries.
This is my own private server, nothing they can do about it. So welcome.
All right. Yeah. Well, you know, YouTube, but the form of censorship that's been exercised and complained about by many is actually being done by YouTube itself as a private entity.
And of course, it's a wholly unsubsiderated subsidiary of Google. So which is Stanford, E.D.U., which is, you know, federal roots.
So, but nonetheless, it's all private and we'll get into what that misconception of government and how the planet is being run.
Let's say, perhaps in the next hour or so. Yeah, welcome to the technocracy, folks. This is it.
I'm just dying to know where you're at in 2020, Greek. This every conspiracy theory that has ever been put forward almost as manifested in 2020.
I would suggest that people heed what the ancients were talking about, but the problem is that the two minds can't come together, meaning the comprehension of the people today.
Let's just call them people and giving a lot of leeway because if most people have realized they're just considered livestock these days, right?
Meaning the past 150 years or so. And I mean that literally.
You're living in your and you're a stock. Yeah. So in essence, the ancient rites pretty much have it all because it's a series of cycles that repeat themselves, but they're slightly different every time.
So where can we start? I mean, do you want to start with the geopolitical, which is actually a very low level of addressing things, but it's a, you know, we have to start at the bottom, maybe, or do you want to start on the cognitive level and people's lack of perception?
Which one do you think we should start out? Oh, God. Is there a difference?
Let's just start on the lack of perception. It's kind of like warming up before you go for a two mile run. Is that okay? You don't want to pull a muscle?
Because if you lay on them, what's going on on the bigger, which is actually still the smaller and the smaller, which might be the perception is actually the bigger.
So let's start on that. You know what's interesting is I usually call the university physics department. I used to on a daily basis or weekly basis years ago, and I would call the HVAC people HVC is heating ventilator ventilation air conditioning people, right?
And I would ask the physics department and the heating ventilation air conditioning engineers, how many calls did you get yesterday about the public at large, calling you and requesting that you design machines that make for their cars, homes, planes, whatever to cool and heat, where the cool is, the cold is verified and it cold rises and the heat is densified and it descends just like the human body.
You want a cool head and warm feet or when you look at nature, it's hot in the valley and cool at the mountain top. And if you go closer to the sun, it gets colder and colder, not warmer and warmer.
So how many people in the public at large are requesting their engineers and physicists to design equipment for to cool and heat their homes, where the cold rises and the heat descends instead of the heat rising and the cold going down because if you, if you do the ladder or the way that it is, you have a hot head and cold feet.
And they always answer, I don't know what you're talking about, no one's asking about that. So I hang up and say a planet full of morons.
How can you not notice that you should have a cool head and warm feet and not demand that the cooling and heating equipment that you employ is in accordance with that.
No one is noticing that, right?
Well, there's a bigger thing, you know, when you chemically degrade something like if you have a campfire, you'll say, well, Greek, you know, the heat rises on a campfire.
But if you look at the wood that you're burning in the campfire, is it being degraded or is it building up? Well, it's burning it down, it's being degraded.
You have a ratified rising heat and a densifying, a lowering cold, but when you're building something like in other words, life is being employed to create chemical, let's say agglomeration where things come together and they grow into a higher order, the heat always descends and the cold always rises.
It's true in the atmosphere, this is true in the human body. If you called a medical technician in a lab coat and said, I have a hot head and cold feet, you'll say, son, you're not feeling good.
But I thought he's supposed to rise and cold is supposed to go down, but it's the opposite, right?
This ties in, you know, when you go to supermarkets or grocery stores, they have nutritional information on packages, right?
And one of the major ones is calories, you know, I don't want that's too high in calories, I'm burning calories. Well, let's just take a moment, you know, the calorie is defined as a thermal unit, you know, how much heat material gives off when you burn it.
And if you ever seen the calurometer, one of the ways they do it is they put, let's say, the food of banana, let's say, a 60 calories, they put it in a glass tube and they put pure oxygen in it with something that looks like a spark plug, it goes boom and it burns into complete ash or charcoal.
And the heat that it gives off in a water bath is measured as how many calories it has, right?
But let me say this, that's a valid scientific process, but it only applies to anyone who's pooping charcoal briquettes, right?
Because if you read a banana at 60 calories and poop it, you could still burn that poop. So how many calories did you get out of it?
You could burn a piece of wood and plastics got a lot of calories in it, but if you eat it, right?
So calories have nothing to do with food. It's like if I ask you how much does that weigh and you say it's 19 inches, you're using the wrong unit and no one is paying attention to this.
And they all start saying I'm burning calories, right? This just goes on and on and on. How about your calendar? It's really funny.
You know, september means seven, october means eight, nova means nine, indecent means 10. So how are you getting off writing September as the ninth month, october as the tenth, november as the eleventh and december?
So on and so forth as 12 when it actually means 10.
Because four times out of the year they actually give you something similar to what the true month count should be.
You know, you ever wonder they only selected four months out of the year to actually have the nomenclature correct where september means seven, october means eight, nova means nine, indecent means 10.
You know how that also follows suit when you take a multiple choice question and answer test is always four possible answers. You ever see how things coincide to show how no one is paying attention?
It's kind of funny that way, don't you think? You know, but anyway, since we're on time anyone that takes astrophysics or astronomy in university, I think it's a one oh one course.
They tell you the day starts at solar noon, but for the people it's it's a civil midnight.
That's kind of like when they didn't know how to define things in the early dictionaries. If you look at some of the old dictionaries that were printed in england or published in england, they said oats.
Oh, okay, oats. It's a grain that people feed to horses in england, but it's the staple of the people of Scotland.
Meaning it's such a put down, right? Now if you understand how to keep time lawfully, for example, you know, the all put down the side solar noon is when your day starts.
And if you understand that high noon, if anyone remembers the old banking conventions, if you're old enough, when you deposited a check afternoon, it was counted as the next day.
Does anyone old enough to still to remember that? So maybe you are free, no?
But the the essence of it is that's what I call lawful timekeeping and for thousands of years, people settled their debts with the full moon. That's why today you get a monthly bill in astronomy 101.
They will tell you that the moon rules the month.
So again, we have so many anomalies that go on and on and on and on and on that we don't know where to start with perception.
So we just relax into what we've been told should be our perception.
Yeah, that's never been sure then right now. That's for sure. You can believe whatever you want at this moment, which is kind of a positive and kind of a negative.
And I'm in the same way. Sure, well, we yeah, well, the thing is also you said 2020, you know, the year count, you know, it's funny you watch prehistoric stuff, the dinosaurs 60 million years ago, they're constantly, whenever the dinosaur meme is brought up, it's always six, they have to say 60 million years ago.
But how come it's not 60 million 2020? Where does timekeeping start? You know, it's interesting is if you study university or let's say not university university, but study what the academic convention is, in other words, that the academic convention is what transfer is what's transferred over to the standard social convention.
Right. In other words, when you start to look at the conventions and why what we're doing, not why we're having forbid why would never ask why you're doing it. Just do it, right.
But if you look at everything that's being done, it has some academic route to it. Always it's stemmed. You could always go into university library or library, per se, and look up some kind of source material that'll tell you.
You know, how this came about very rarely accurately why that that's where you're going to have to figure out why.
But if you start to look at reference points and what things mean like what words mean, you know, I'm not a Scientologist, I'm not into the all around harbored or whatever, but one thing that he stressed, which is actually correct is learn what words mean.
Because it's a form of communication. Think about operating a computer. If you don't understand what those all those little cursors or things that you click on mean, you can get yourself into a lot of trouble or not be able to use it.
And that essentially seems to be the problem. So learn what what words mean, how things are communicated and how they should be communicated.
And then go back to your resource source information, which is unfortunately tainted in many ways because of academia as a business.
And part of the social engineering, let's just say.
But if you do go back and look, you'll see a very different world that could have been or another world that is still operating parallel to this one.
And learn what words mean like anyone could do a cursory look up on etymology, which is the root meaning of words of the word nice like Freeman, you're a nice guy.
Haven't you ever heard anyone say have a nice day.
Right. If you ever look up the word nice, it actually means foolish, stupid and senseless. Now, how could it be twisted into something as a positive greeting.
Right. That would be that would be an interesting question. How did it go from its true meaning to how it's being used today.
And you know what my suggestion, my advice is to people don't even bother finding out how it got twisted.
Just look at it's, you know, how it changed.
Just look at the where the point of where you discovered this and where you are now and what you're going to do about it now in a way that you separate yourself from any malady that might come from that twisting.
It's very benign meaning using the word nice as it's being used isn't going to hurt anyone is it.
But if you start moving forward to other terms, it and then you might say well then it could become quite hurtful like if you study what's called the legal society.
When you hear words like person or presumption or fact, those words do not mean anything as used normally is another language, right.
If you look at for example of what's put out in the media and what's put out to the public that is all coded language, right.
You constantly see it's a lot of loose terms and but yet they're specific but don't make complete sense but make enough sense to get some point across when you sense that.
That's because there's some kind of a code there and one way to break any code is you have to go back to the Primer and if there if you words that are being used in your in the language that you understand.
You must know what they mean intrinsically like from an etymological point of view and not how they're being used because that's in in fact where the code lies.
Like the ideas of democracy being mob rule and government being mind control.
One way will think of democracy.
Crossy is the suffix Greek which means to rule or governing body and demos is usually used as the people but demos is also one of the moons of Mars which means terror or fear or dread.
So democracy can actually be taken to to mean to rule by fear and dread or terror.
That's why years ago I'm not political in a political Hillary Clinton said we're going to bring democracy to Libya.
Or we're going to bring democracy to Iraq right and she even threatened South Africa with democracy and he says okay I'll do what you want.
Meaning the government there so this is just an idea I'm not she's she's just an officer of an organization she has no power that's another thing I wanted to suggest we're kind of semi linear here and because we're taking parallel you know this is a parallel conversation every time I say something we could go into another direction.
What what people don't understand is if you've ever heard of anyone in history or currently or seen them they have no power they're merely there in an administrative capacity and yes Julius Caesar was in an administrative capacity.
He was his official role was what emperor Rome Rome and later on the Senate actually voted on decreeing that the Emperor's were gods didn't they so not only was he an official of the administration of Rome he was also a god so now we're stepping into a whole other category but if you've ever heard of them or seen them they have no power meaning the world as you know it has been ruled from behind the scenes.
By a conspiracy not a theory if you if you understand that it is is not in a lawful manner or a positive manner you can call it a conspiracy or you can if you don't like the word conspiracy you can call it a power base or a power group that operates in secret.
And if you understand all of the if you do any history and understand any of the ancient texts it's the they always state there are secrets quote unquote mysteries constantly.
Freeman you've heard of the mystery schools and how many people have you heard of that have been to mystery schools and I like it wasn't what I thought it was it was really a lot of this stuff was quite obvious and in front of us the whole time we just they all they did was added definitions right yeah.
So the same people here here's an example the same people have been operating through genealogy on the planet for thousands of years you can say safely 4000 years let's give you an example you know with the academic historians and we're talking about atheists now this is considered the Christian era the past 2000 years it has nothing to do with religion it just dubbed the Christian era right.
If you study that well where do you get that the they're supposed to subscribe to the biblical text aren't they they're supposed to you know specifically the New Testament which is not a soul document there is no separation that was done much later but nonetheless even if we were not.
If the students of the bible there's a scene there where we have these characters a caravan that rolled into town called the magi into king herds palace right they came and visited king her it in his palace looking for a king they said and if you read the just the biblical account this has nothing to do with religion we're just talking about what's in the account.
Well these magi this caravan rolled in in visited king herds in his palace I've seen this several times because I just want to get in people's mind what the setting was like the continents or king herds were shaking in his bridges he was terrified of them in his own palace here we have a king now let's just stop from in it when you're king you're not like set up in a hilton or something you have a palace with guards pretty heavy ordinance heavily guarded.
Your word is can mean a matter of life and death you're the king so here come is this far in caravan from the east and they're speaking to you and you're shaking terrified of them think about that for a moment who are these people.
Do you see what I make some add yeah do you do you recall that story by the way maybe you don't recall exactly that he was terrified of them but how can you be how can you be a king in your own palace and be terrified of a guest I mean you're the king right.
What kind of power do you have to wield or be known to have for to have a king basically being in his bridges right that's a very very powerful who are these people well what are they part of conspiracy absolutely are they still.
Around today absolutely do they know about the motion of the heavens and the effect on the earth yes or no of course.
You see yeah okay so these magic are not magic per se that just means they're there there are astronomers they were people that knew of higher order things right
that just as is a term that's used in ancient times for many reasons it could be someone who is a master of any field basically and and exudes that we're gone as a universal respect.
The magic I want not just astronomers they were masters in a veconomics masters of medicine masters of the sciences masters of weaponry masters of political mind control and social control and engineering.
Do you see where I'm going with this.
Now they're not a monolithic group and I'm not saying it's just the magi but we have a biblical account which is an old account it's proven that it was written around that time.
And there are many other accounts and if you go back to the time when Julius Caesar was assassinated or any of these other assassinations or other political things in the ancient times.
Do you think that was just an ad hoc. Do you know for example to have a in the past few thousand years to have a high political figure officer of an administration assassinated that is an order that has to be mold over voted on and considered executed from much higher than that.
Because the plan has to be put into place now what do I mean by this well you know sounds like the Greek is just you know rambling.
You know many people talk about let's say the government and all this you know dominating force in their society you know we have to consider in light of a king herod shaking with the appearance of the of the madry is that is it possible that there is such a group today.
In that light. I would have to say yes. Right question. Now do we let our imaginations run wilder do we go back and start looking up with things mean and seeing what the academics have put out in their reference material that's loosely publicized when I mean loosely public publicize I'm talking about doing a search on a browser on the internet that's loosely publicized you know because there's information you can get within university libraries and government libraries that you must sign in or.
Actually walk into right that still exists but loosely would be the internet so if you understand how things are set up today and you wonder and you have to understand this coincidentally coinciding with what the age of Napoleon was you know the Napoleonic wars let's say about 200 years ago coincided with a lot of the revolutionary wars that you saw like the American revolution and the war of 1812 and all that was the Americans.
Joining with the Napoleonic wars if you understand that right as a world war per se well at that point roughly 150 to 200 years ago is when it was decided that we don't we've already sent out all of these contract discoverers you know you've heard of all the people the Columbus Magellan.
Vosko de Gama you know they discovered all these places those were contracts that were sent out to get those you know the world under contract let's say to be discovered which is a legal term right discovery means evidence.
Had already been done we have this Napoleonic world war situation and revolutionary atmosphere going on this is a real good time through this mild to extreme chaos to take control of everyone but not how we did in the past by region but the whole world at large.
And one of the few places that this was done in was the American Civil War which was not a civil war Abraham Lincoln was approached by let's just say the Freemasons and the southern states were approached by the Knights Templar let's just say and Lincoln was told you have all these resources here meaning what you call America can feed the entire world and provide all the
raw materials for industry for the entire world do you know what you're sitting on and obviously he's like no I don't I'm just the president right.
Well we're going to show you what to do so all of a sudden a fort magically explodes all of a sudden the south has extreme superiority militarily you know they've invented weaponry machine guns submarines arsenals that were far superior than anything.
Anyone else had but they still quote unquote lost didn't they how is that possible.
Didn't you see a repeat of that with quote unquote Nazi Germany.
You ever study even a cursory study of not sure Germany wasn't their weaponry far superior you ever heard of the B2 stealth bomber sure I've ever heard of the Thornton flying wing yeah right okay and rock it so why did they lose again they didn't it's just a display.
So make a long story short after the civil war which is not known as the civil war till 50 years later was the war of the states it was about centralizing the American continent as such and Abraham Lincoln being the simple ten attorney that he was didn't understand so they had to get out of the way didn't he.
And the way very simple now a few years later everything becomes a corporation.
Quote a sovereign state so let's go back to see back to the definitions that was a big interjection when you go look up on the internet or even you tubes what a sovereign state is the best is the you tubes they have these professors and they can't define it.
There could be this could be that if you look up what a sovereign state is ultimately you find out it's neither sovereign and it's not a state just like if you look up the federal reserve you find out it's not federal it doesn't have any reserves.
So when you look up what's called a sovereign state the general definition everywhere openly is it is a political juridical fiction.
But what else is a juridical fiction corporation you know it has private shareholders and let's just say you're a president of one of these sovereign states and one of the shareholders walk in you think you're going to be peeing in your pants like her did can her absolutely yeah who are these guys yeah who are these guys we don't know and we don't have to know you ever heard of a private trust.
Of course right who owns it we don't know that's how it's set up so but this is where you're set up and now you you either fall for it or you understand the calamity that you were born into thanks mom and dad right.
So if you're going to be kind of upset at the state of affairs at anyone it's not your government it's not your priest it's not your mayor's not your governor's mom and dad I'm not saying you should be angry at mom and dad but you know what they didn't they didn't even think once.
About it you know they didn't even have the information they just went at it right so anyway you see where the blame is right it's where the source is right and there's no blame there either because they just didn't know but the fact is ignorance is not an excuse so that's another story and I could show you how that could be understood as well someday maybe not on this one but if we understand these the the that every time you know you know you're not going to be in the state of the state of the state of the state.
The the that everything is basically incorporated and incorporate corporations work on stock and and inventory the rest I'm sure Freeman you've had many people discuss the birth certificate registrations the money system and all that I don't need to get into that.
The the aspect of the sovereign state for example can also be examined with Switzerland you've heard of those wonderful people that tend to be neutral right yeah sure.
You know when you're watching a sports game the referee he's what neutral isn't he right but being the referee what is he do doesn't he call the shots who wins and who doesn't he call if there was a foul and the
game needs to be redone or was in the play was invalid doesn't doesn't that what the referee does yeah doesn't the referee make or break the game yeah.
Big thanks what's going for that or one of the ways that's an overt way where the the controllers stick their head out now one did Switzerland become a sovereign state.
2002 is a rhetorical question September 10th one year after one year and less one day after September 11th they became a sovereign state why weren't they a sovereign state before that incorporated think about that.
You lived if you were if you live in Switzerland every each each individual man woman of adult you know was sovereign meaning they were people.
And after September 11th 2001 and 364 days later on the Pope's work schedule known as the calendar they decided okay well fall in and become like the rest of you guys.
Incorporation because you couldn't have Switzerland become a member of the UN which is an association or club of these corporations.
Because each you would have to have I don't know how many they're 14 million or 12 million people live in Switzerland each one of those people would have to send a representative to the UN.
So this is one of the last the other places where you don't have sovereign states as places like Somalia or they're bad parts of the Congo the Tureg people the nomadic tribes of southern Libya the postunes and Afghanistan.
Those are the last remnants of free people on the planet as such.
By the way you know when this latest a pandemic thing started they started bombing Somalia for because there was reports of one ISIS person there.
It is bomb the shit out of it you didn't hear anything about it in the news.
Right.
Right because of course they don't get viruses they get bombs.
So anyway.
It's a very interesting thing it's a very the earth is a very very dark place it doesn't mean you are dark or have to participate in the darkness is what I'm trying to say.
Forbearing with knowledge of the current conditions is what's taught to what's called special forces people and when I say special forces they don't only exist in the military they also exist in business you ever heard of corporate espionage.
If you're a retired spy don't you know you get a lot you get paid a lot better a quote unquote if you work for a corporation there's such a thing that's corporations spy on each other right.
Now when you hear special forces people doing extreme things why is it have what is everyone's mind always have to go to the military or paramilitary why can't you be a commando in a sense a piece or a special forces operative within your world yourself and operate on a higher level.
And why shouldn't you see I'm a little lost on that in other words if you have special information and understand how things really work.
Would you function like your everyday Joe Schmo.
Or would you or would you just appear to function like a Joe Schmo but internally be on a much higher level where you're more self sufficient more defensive.
And more beneficial to those around you quote unquote friends family.
When you have a special operative let's say a Delta Force guy or commando in society does he where all of his bars and stripes and say I'm a good or does he blend in with everyone else.
Or aspire whatever so basically when you're visiting a place and you don't want to stick out like a sore thumb and be noticed.
And you're not going to be able to see the things that you're not going to do.
And limited is you explore all the possible movements and freedoms that you do have.
And you dwell on that and you make the best of that.
That's why I always suggest that people say, "Quick, what do we do?"
I said, "Food clothing shelter."
"Food clothing shelter" in that order.
You know, you have to have food and then clothing in the shelter in order to survive, right?
And somebody once said to me, "Quick, that is so simple and oversimplified that's almost dehumanizing."
I said, "No, it's not because it's not just about food clothing and shelter."
When you're looking for food, you're looking for the highest quality food.
You can afford or want to afford or can obtain.
When you're looking for clothing, you want to get the best fitting highest quality clothing.
When you're looking for shelter, you want to get what you want to afford in the best and highest quality manner.
You see?
So pursuing those things and amongst pursuing the highest order of things in food clothing and shelter,
you will encounter many other aspects of what it means to be alive.
For example, if you're trying to acquire the best food quality you can,
let's just take that as an example.
What do you know about the day and life of a chef?
In a three-seat Michelin star restaurant.
Well, he gets up at four in the morning, goes to the market, gets the best possible produce, goes to the restaurant,
thinks of how he's going to prepare the meal and hopefully has something by lunch and serves dinner,
goes to bed after dinner at 11 or so and then gets up at four in the morning, starts the whole thing over again,
seeking the best quality out.
I'm not saying you should be a chef, but that would be an example.
You see?
And all of those things that the chef is doing to get this highest food quality and preparation,
he encounters many, many other aspects of being alive on this planet.
You can't just pursue the highest quality food and you're not going to run into other aspects of what it means to be high quality existence.
Currently returning to others to tell us what we should get, how we should do it,
and where the highest quality is.
Right now, looking to the experts to tell humanity what is good for humanity.
Yes, and unfortunately, if you believe that and you function that way, it is unfortunate.
It doesn't mean it'll compromise your survivability, but it is unfortunate.
You will not get the quality. One thing I say to people, especially the younger, the better, is that all fields of study are completely open right now.
What does that mean?
If you want to study, let's say for example, what's called medicine, the human body, healing, health, biological, you know, how things animals, people, all these things,
you know, what it means to be alive, biology, that field is completely open.
When you go to school to study that, whether all the way university, that is grunt level ditch digging work that they've done.
And then it gets very misleading.
You know, if you want to study astrophysics, that field is completely open.
I have not seen a real photograph of anything pointing towards the sky in over 10 years.
Have you? Unless someone's posted one.
It's all CG, computer graphics.
If you want to study for example mechanical engineering, that field is completely open.
I mean, cars that you have to put gasoline in, that pollute, I mean that is insane.
That is, that is not how we should be moving around, right? Electrical cars with lithium ion batteries. Come on.
You know, I mean all the fields are completely open.
So, you know, one of the most important things obviously is if you don't have understanding of how the human body works,
and you need to mitigate something because of disease or injury, you're basically shooting around with false information,
your chances of being successful in mitigating disease or injury drops, the more fiction you incorporate, right?
The more realism you incorporate, the higher your success rate will be in mitigating disease and injury, right?
One thing that people, very few people understand is that the human body is under a slight biological vacuum.
Like if you look at all of the fluid in a body, whether it's a plant, a dog cat bird or human, let's just use that term man or woman,
there is no way that the blood vessels and everything else is supporting all of the liquid when you're standing up going all the way from the top of your head and to your feet evenly.
It's not possible. The heart isn't pumping anything.
So, you have to have a slight vacuum because if you built an exact replica of the human body and filled it with liquid,
all of it because of the flexibility of the skin and the vessels would drop to the bottom no matter how much of a,
even if you had a 1200 horsepower pump for the heart, none of the liquid would be rising in equal equalizing as it is when you're alive.
It'll all go to the bottom lower half of the knee and explode, right? It doesn't matter how much you're pumping.
The body isn't a biological vacuum. That's why when you cut yourself, you have to count several seconds for any kind of fluid to come out.
So, once you understand the plants, animals, human bodies under a slight vacuum, well, now we're dealing with a whole different perspective, right?
Just like for example, if you look at a cross-section of the human intestine and the lumina, which is the opening,
look at the walls of the intestine, does it look like anything actually gets absorbed through there or are there three hydrophobic layers that look as durable as a firestone steel belted tire?
It's the latter. So, how does the food get into the body by induction?
I have a cordless toothbrush, has no metal contacts, I put it in its charger and it starts charging, it's plastic against plastic, how does that happen?
Right, there is something called an induction stove, it's a glass stop, I have a pot of boiling water. I move the pot to a side, put my hand right on the stove top through temperature.
I put the pot right over the induction heater immediately starts boiling again, how does that happen?
Why isn't that studied and applied to the human body? For example, when you speak to any gastrointestinologist or whatever people that study the digestive system,
doctors do, they always say, if you ask them, how does it work? They say it all works by electrical impulses. If you talk to, speak to a neurologist, tell me in 10 words or less how that works in the body. It all works by electrical impulses.
Let me ask you, Freeman, since those two categories which represent maybe 5 or 10 or 20% of the study of the human body, how much electrical medicine are they actually prescribing to people?
There is certainly given Donald Trump a lot of crap about talking about using infrared light on the body.
Okay, but you see none.
Yeah, exactly. It's like going to a car mechanic and my car needs to be fixed and given the keys, just come back in a few hours.
By the way, can you tell me where the steering wheel is? And it's fine. Right? This is exactly what they're putting in front of you.
So, yeah, well, the thing is, again, Donald Trump has no power. He's an official. It's just not point him out.
But your mayors, your governors, those are officials of the administration. Simply.
Wow, according to that.
Like, give you every little, here's a little, here's a little insight information and this might help and inside meaningless a cultural inside.
But when the mob, you ever heard of the mob, they no longer do just drugs and prostitution and stolen cars and things.
They stretch out into the corporate world. They shut, set up shell corporation, shell corporation, not the oil, shell corporation, do whatever they want to do.
And then they just collapse the corporation, right? So they're like, well, set up a corporation.
We need a president and a CEO. I say real simple. There's a homeless guy right there. He looks pretty good. Give him a thousand bucks. He'll go sign all the papers and act to CEO.
Do you see my point? He doesn't care.
How many officials, police chiefs, governors or whatever that were, Congress people that you don't hear about? What happens when they're finished? They leave the country.
Here, not all of them, but here's the thing.
Okay, George Washington, the apotheosis of George Washington, they show him in a throne like Zeus, right?
If you're familiar with that, look it up. And he's deified in a sense, almost like in one statue, he looks like a gust of Caesar where the Zarm up, right?
And all this. So that is American royalty. This is before Kennedy and Kamalot, right?
Not only George Washington, we have Adams, Jefferson and all that. Where are their descendants?
Where are they? Yeah. They had children. We know they had children. Where are they?
Look up on these national holidays. We don't have them up on a podium. This is fifth generation. Thomas Jefferson, junior, junior, junior. Where are they?
Where are they? We have that with kings and queens, sort of.
Actually, with the current monarchy in England, you can't go back to far before you find out whoops. But anyway, where are they?
Where they had children, right? Because they weren't names Washington, Jefferson.
It's often Afro-American. Right. Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
If you look in the phone book anywhere in the East Coast Southern states and you look under it, don't look under J, because if you measure it, it's about three quarters of the phone book under Jefferson, right? Or W. Washington, right? And they're African-American.
But where are their descendants? See, because they never were in the first place. You know, here's the interesting thing. No one's paying attention. And I say this and I have to say it.
George Washington was a normal kind of guy, but after a certain battle where he went missing for a few days and was found, all of a sudden, the biggest concern about George Washington was getting teeth in his mouth.
You heard of that. They had wooden teeth. They pulled teeth from slaves. Why? Because the guy that looked like George Washington so much that would pass for George Washington, because George Washington is no longer with us. We found his frozen corpse in Brooklyn.
But that would be too demoralizing. This guy looks just like him. Sounds just like him, but we got to get some teeth in his mouth.
Renahari. Not only that, when they brought this guy who finally got some teeth in his mouth to one of the free Masonic rituals, he says, what the F is going on here? Freaked out.
Where the regular George Washington was just fine with it. So I say, this guy is going to talk, so we need to bleed him to death. Do I need to say any more about that? I mean, how obvious is that?
Have you heard of the battle of Brooklyn? Don't say this too publicly because you're a nut job. How dare you say that?
If you go look at Abraham Lincoln, the pistol that shot him, it's in a museum.
What pistol is it? It's a ladies pistol. You know why it's a ladies pistol? Because it was made for ladies. And only ladies carried ladies pistols.
So do you know any of any lady that was near him? Abraham Lincoln when he was shot? What do we know about the closest lady that was to him that night?
Was she going through some morphine or opium withdrawal symptoms? And was she very upset that her husband had syphilis from all the prostitutes?
Do I need to continue any further on this? No. Right? You know what's like the, with the Kennedy, you know, when you go up to the book depository, you know, where Oswald, it was a comedian that made a good skit about this.
Forgot who it was. Some people actually think I sound like him.
You said I visited the memorial in the library, the book depository where Oswald supposedly shot Kennedy and everything's very accurate. They have the area cordoned off. They have the rifle. This that. And you know, that's very accurate because Oswald's not there.
Right. Right. I've been there. I've been on the grassy. No. Yeah. Yeah. So you know, it's the magic bullet goes through his head. It goes through the windshield. It's the other guy comes back. It's him again.
So look about what words mean ground zero. Now is a technical term. If you look it up, it's the location on or below the earth where a nuclear device is detonated.
Well, that makes sense. You know, there's been many packs through the years that no more atmospheric. If you go study about 1200 to 15,000 tests that were done depending on whose numbers of record keeping you look at.
They've only only 5% or 2% of all nuclear testing has been done above ground. The rest of it is underground. You ever notice that? You know, they only blew about four or five of them in Nevada. And then they blew above ground maybe 10 and the other 1200 were where nuclear testing underground because that's how they're used.
And downtown Manhattan, you had a surface temperature of 2500 degrees and about 150 feet below the surface was around 5,000 degrees enough to melt granite and steel. That's why when they cleared the floors of the World Trade Center, you saw this big molten conglomerate thing coming out of the slab and they told you that was stuff that was deposited from the glacier age and you'd say, well, wait a second. The guys who poured the concrete slab and smoothed it out actually went around this thing. They didn't notice it back then.
Anyway, this is all easily to establish and but you're crazy, right? It's insane, right?
Right. So if you just take an empirical view of reality and say, you know, like we opened with the idea of cold going up and heat going down empirically, that's just incorrect.
Well, it dole hold on. It's correct if you're chemically degrading something like burning wood, not growing wood, growing wood, the cold goes up and the heat goes down burning wood, the heat goes because you're breaking it down. But go ahead.
Right. Well, it's just empiricism is out the window. I mean, we're at a point where, you know, Donald Trump, not to get political, but, you know, he's being blamed for earthquakes, fires, hurricanes.
It says if, you know, there's no signs of based reality at all going on in our current state, you can just blame whatever villain you want for any natural disaster that's occurring and empiricism is out the door.
Well, there is no, there is no science anyway since the poppul bull, anyone could look this up, you know, the poppul bull of Pope Gregory, which gave us the Gregorian calendar, right? The revision of the Julian calendar.
There was a previous Pope that did another poppul bull in the, I think it was in the fifth late 1400s, early 1500s and his statement in that bull was anything that does not have a material component is domain of the Vatican.
So all of you natural philosophers and scientists, you can talk about anything you want as long as it has a material component. So what does that mean?
If you want to talk about light, it must have a particle. If you want to talk about electricity, it must have a particle.
If you see, it has to have a material component, but yet 99% of the world is immaterial. It's consciousness, it's energy. It's in a sense of, you know, not tangible physical stuff.
You know, it's so ridiculous, you know, photons, you know, for light, I spell them FAUX, TON.
And what the electrons, you know, I still have this experiment, you know, no matter how small or how large the equipment I use, always get the same result.
I have a wire and I pump a lot of voltage and current through it. So I know the electrons are really pumping, that thing is buzzing.
I quickly put on some rubber gloves and an insulated cheer and I cut the wire and I immediately have a dust pan underneath to catch all the electrons pouring out and I still haven't caught any electrons.
So inside, so you have particles inside of a light bulb, right, which is supposed to be a high vacuum because if it's not it burns up, right?
So the photons are particles inside of a vacuum that are moving at the speed of light. They go through the glass where they slow down about an order of 50 times or 20 times.
And then when they leave the glass bulb, they speed up to the speed of light again. Hey, how come we don't harness that for our automobiles, man? That's really cool because I want to be moving at the speed of light, come to a red light and then go back to the speed of light, like a photon does.
How come they don't, because it's all a crock of bull and you're still operating, that's a pun, you're operating on the pop-up bull, which is if it does not have a material component, you cannot speak of it.
That's why when they built Sir in the collider, which you can go many directions, is it really a scientific instrument?
Or is it something more, like in other words, a religious artifact that's being reconstructed, right? You can go either way and they're both accurate and not because I say so because they say they show it.
That's right.
So actually, what are they looking for? The God particle.
Technically, God damn particle, but yes.
Right, but they can't say they're trying to create an energy, quote, unquote, field that affects the rest of the energy fields in a way that where they have control of it, they have to make it a particle.
So even with the idea of dimensions.
Yes. Well, there's only one dimension, but it's so, think of it this way. What we see is, when I say there's only one dimension, meaning when you're dealing scientifically,
because, for example, you can easily understand and that what we see with the visible eye is everything we see around us is less than 1% of the actual light that can be seen.
Most of it is outside of our visible spectrum.
And we don't need high-falutin equipment to prove that because there are animals that see in that spectrum that we don't see and it's provable.
Okay. Animals that are not, quote, unquote, that can discern color, for example, can, can, can discern colors of things in pitch darkness.
This has been proven with animals from the forests that only go after a specific color because it's known as their food and they put them in complete, absolute, dark room.
And they still can go to that object. This has been, this is easily found by anyone. Right. This information.
So we see, so we can say, for example, if something exists outside of our visible spectrum and taps us on the shoulder, we can easily say colloquially, hey, Freeman, it was a creature from another dimension came in and tapped me on the shoulder.
That's acceptable, but it's not. It's just not within our visible spectrum.
You see, right.
So once we start working with that, we have to understand that most of the things are just not perceivable, like the perception.
So for example, you know, if you understand that nothing goes in and nothing comes out of the body, the human body, you have an open track, by the way.
You have several ducts, but the main track of the human body is from the mouth through the anus.
You could drive a little miniature choo choo train, put it in your mouth, it'll come out your anus. Right. You could take a long trip through there. Right. Okay.
That's the only opening through the body. But if you look at the mouth and if you look at the throat and the all the intestinal system all the way throughout it is completely sealed, you can go online, look at anatomical books, look at the profile cross section of the intestines. There is no absorption.
All of those cells are so tightly packed, they're hydrophobic actually. What I mean by that is if you go out to the garden right now and pull out a plant very carefully and look at its roots are nice and shiny or whatever.
Take a water bottle and spray it on there just does the water get absorbed into the root like a sponge or does the water beat up like your spring water on a freshly waxed car.
All the water beats up like a freshly waxed car. So how are the roots absorbing because plants are also under a vacuum. When you water plants you're not watering the plant, you're watering the soil.
You see. So everything is working through induction. Here's another example of how things work when you do have something physical. It's always in motion.
For example, take a tabletop fan or a bicycle wheel with spokes when it's still you can put your hand in between the spokes or you could put your hand in between the fan blades.
But once you get that in motion, you can no longer put your hand where you did before no matter where you approached the spinning bicycle wheel or the tabletop fan. It will appear a solid to you want it when it's in motion.
So it's not because it's another dimension. It's because you're beginning now to understand the fundamentals of what we perceive as being solid and so on and so forth.
But going back to the human body, if it's under a vacuum, right, which you know, I'm kind of dropping this on without giving more examples and more explanation because I think at this point, like you said, 2020, it's a little too late for schooling from the basics and that can be done.
But if you understand that the body is completely sealed and everything goes in and out by induction, right, immaterial, how does a contagion or a pathogen enter the body and appear in your blood?
Well, that's because the body has to recognize it as something it could reproduce internally.
Right, that's called formatting. If you remember back in the days, they asked, are you Apple or Windows?
You know, I have a disco, I'm Windows. This is Apple shoot, you know, can't use it, right? That's called formatting.
So, you know, this has always been said for a long time that people who are sick get sick. Right.
So, for example, if there is, quote, unquote, a pathogenic condition in the environment, either transmuted by people, animals are just in the environment.
If you breathe that in and it sits in the cul de sac, known as lungs, the cul de sac is a place where you go in and the only way you could come out is by turning around, going back out.
Or if it goes through your intestinal tract or on your skin, the only way that could appear inside the body is if the body recognizes it as something it could replicate.
So, if you change the format of the body where it does not recognize it as something it could replicate, it will not replicate inside the body.
Most diseases are classified as someone being diseased by the symptoms usually exhibited by the body internally, right?
Appearing externally, whether it's a fever, mucus, sores, what do I have you, right?
Thrombosis, blood clotting is actually a major thing. So, how do you change the formatting? Well, it's been known for thousands of years that, for example, silver does it.
I don't recommend colloidal silver, but I recommend something called an aqueous Argentum, where you have water just exposed to the material.
This comes from the idea of homeopathics. It's not how much of something you have, but how little of it you have is more effective, right?
So, the other thing is if you, there's a YouTube on there about the 1918 pandemic and they're interviewing survivors, quote-unquote,
and one of the women says, "Everyone on our neighborhood died and the reason why we didn't know one in our family did because every morning our mom would get up and take a teaspoon of soda, you know, baking soda and put it in water and have a soul drink from it."
Well, when you drink sodium bicarbonate or anything like that, or any type of bicarbonate, it changes your body chemistry and you no longer format than the people who weren't, you see?
So, you form that--
For the things you couldn't get when the pandemic hit and everybody was stockpiling that, baking soda was high up on the list. It was hard to get.
Yeah, I find that alco-- rubbing alcohol still is, and I use that as in--
In spray bottles.
Yeah, not for the body because I don't think it's-- if you're going to use alcohol on the body, get moonshine or grain that grain alcohol, right?
But nonetheless, it's all about formatting. Like, for example, anyone that knows anyone that works in virology or epidemiology or with pathogens,
even though they take the strongest measures to separate themselves and be sterile, about 20% of them usually come down with diseases anyway, just being exposed to in the environment, not physically, just being near it by proximity, you see?
So, this is an advanced aspect, by the way, I don't know how well-versed people are your audience or yourself on what's called the secret space program.
Now, I'm neither a believer in it or an ace-seer, but I've noticed there's a lot of that stuff going on for the past few years more now than ever.
Well, it's really fascinating that they just came out and announced China and Russia having these space weapons and directed energy weapons that it's now become an official statement is pretty intriguing, but that's even below what people consider the secret space program.
Yeah, but what about, let's say, the Germans through Maria Orsik or whatever in the 30s were able through Hannabukraft and other, like, the NIMZA, you know, the Prussians that came to the Sonora Desert in California in the 1800s developed, right?
Stuff, a Walter Bosley is a done good research on those guys.
Yeah, it's the Sonora group. Yeah, it's a Grandfather in there. Yeah, I think actually some of the artwork that we've survived that time period does say Trump on it.
So, you understand you've been exposed to this, but in other words, when I'm trying to say, "Okay, let's just say that's an interesting thing to look at to pick with discernment, what's being said."
But on the other hand, let's just say you've heard that the bottoms of the oceans are less explored than outer space, for example, in other words, looked at. Forget about going there at this point.
Right? So, if you were going to go set up a habitation at the bottom of the ocean or in outer space, you cannot bring nonsense like calories of your body is absorbing nutrients, viruses, a bacteria theory, and all this stuff.
Absolutely ridiculous, right? That's the stuff that's fed to the masses to keep them just going.
You cannot use any of that. What you have to understand is the body is under a vacuum. You have to understand that the heart is not a pump. It's actually a breaking mechanism.
And, you know, it's funny when I spoke to a cardiologist, he went silent. He says, "Yeah, what you're saying is true. I just can't acknowledge it. I've got too much invested in this."
And my children are in medical school, you know? This is the typical thing people say. But basically, he says, "And what pumps the blood? What gets the blood moving? It's the capillaries."
You have 2,000 miles of capillaries that when gases and fluids are exchanged within the body itself, it creates a pumping action.
And he's like, "Well, gases and fluids exchange don't make a pumping action. Sure they do."
Actually, there's a very simple pump where they just blow an air bubble underneath the straw and as the air bubble rises through the straw, it discharges the fluid.
And then you repeat the process. Are you familiar with that? It's a very simple pumping system. You could use it for aquariums.
Can you imagine that? And you have a small air pump underneath the tube and as the bubble comes up, it pushes the fluid over to the next tank.
Very simple. So, there's a guy called Frank Chester who's done a lot of work or he actually took material that resembled blood and thickness and temperature and tried to move it down a quarter of an inch to, he needed like 20 pounds of pressure to move it three feet.
And you don't have 20 pounds of pressure. Blood pressure is an interesting thing. It's what, you know, give me an example.
You know, they have a lot of pharmaceutical outlets set up in typical grocery stores. You know, you've seen them in the back usually and all these people eager to get their meds, right?
I usually walk by there and they have asked the people behind the counter. I point at the blood pressure machine that you put a quarter in or a dollar in to get your blood pressure while you're waiting.
And I usually ask them, where do I get one of these? And he says, I don't know, we rent them. And I said, the guy says, by the way, why do you want one? I said, well, I'm opening a museum on medical fakery and quackery and I want this to be one of my prime exhibits.
And they all kind of look at me like, what? Yeah, blood pressure is part of medical fakery and quackery.
Let's just do it this way. You go to a doctor and I want to diagnose you, sit down. We're going to do diagnosis, right? So he ties a string around your finger and you'll ask, you know, your four finger, first digit area, you know, what it bends.
And he can't be a regular string. It has to be a medical string that costs about 30 bucks, right? And then he has a medical timer because you can't use a regular timer, of course.
And after a certain amount of time, your finger turns a collar anywhere between dark flesh to blue to purple. And he has a medical chart that goes from dark flesh to blue to purple and he holds your finger up against and depending on what collar shade it is is what level, what type of stupiditis you have, right?
And you believe it. And because it actually, he had a medical timer and a medical string in the medical chart that proves it, it says it right on there.
And the collar matches perfectly. So you have stage 18 stupiditis and I'm going to give you a prescription of, you know, whatever, right? Fuck it all. Yeah, yeah, sorry. But anyway, I'm not so, but yeah.
So you walk, so in other words, what he's doing is implying that this unnatural condition is a condition that you should be concerned about and should be addressed with pharmaceuticals.
Now let's just come down to this world because this is in another world, right? Because that's maybe a world a little worse than this one in this world.
You walk in, he wants to diagnose you, he puts a cuff on your arm and starts inflating it that puts an artificial pressure on your arm that if you put on a shirt or a glove or anything that had that much pressure, you would take it off because it creates an unnatural condition on the body, like jamming your toe on the kitchen table at three in the morning.
That's an unnatural condition. So he puts the cuff on there anyway and you're sitting there because your mom and dad says, well, he's a doctor, you do what he says.
So he keeps inflating this. So he starts measuring and seeing the pulses between heartbeats and judging a ratio to tell you you have higher low blood pressure and you believe it.
And you believe it's so much that 20 to 30 million of you are taking dangerous toxins to lower that blood pressure.
Yes, yes, yeah, okay.
And they're taking your temperature. Do you know, by the way, that in temperate zones, you know, north and south of the equator, when you have a fever, it's hot, but when you're the equator, when you have a fever, it's cold, your actual body temperature drives you're probably seen it in films, people with malaria, they're shaking and they're sweating and they're freezing.
Why is that? You see it? I'm not going to get into the why, but that's a whole that's more advanced than just a two hour call.
Yeah, we're definitely, we're we're we're wrapping up this first hour now. Okay.
So, boy, my brain is just having to cycle through a lot of what you were saying here and what's going on in this in this current program and try to bring it to a conclusion for us to move on into the member section and get a bit deeper.
And basically what what we're pointing out here is the lack of empirical data that the world deals with.
And that mostly everyone is listening to authority and just not ever, ever doing any of their own science, doing any of their own understanding, trying to logically put together what's going on.
I'm playing it earth. I mean, just as one empirical statement for this conclusion is that there is nothing going wrong around me right now.
Nothing. My life hasn't changed. My people around me, children are playing in the streets.
Life is very normal around here. I don't get sick. I don't know anyone sick. I don't, there's nothing here in my empirical reality to determine that there is something bad happening in the world.
And I have to reach out. I have to look to the internet. I have to look to the world and and then say, Oh, I should be frightened right now because things are really.
You know, bad. Oh, everything's going wrong right now. But yet my my reality. There is absolutely nothing going on. There's nothing.
No, nothing to worry about. No fear. No scares. No, nothing. And yet the the world has me uptight without question. And yet there's literally nothing in my reality to cause it.
And many cultures where they would play a trick on someone, let's say walking to town or walking to market. They have three friends separated and the first friend greets the victim and says, Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm feeling fine. But you don't look so good. I'm just, OK, I'll see you later. Then they have the second friend spaced apart. And they see the victim again. He says, Hey, how are you doing today? Because I'm feeling OK. He says, No, you're not looking so good.
And then the person starts doubting it. And he's like, Well, I feel OK. And the other guy said it wasn't looking so good. Then he walks up to the finally at the end of the road or another stretch of road.
The other guy that's the three that are playing the trick on this guy says, Hey, how are you doing? This is, I'm OK. I think he says, Yeah, you know, you don't look good at all. And all of a sudden the guy says, you know, three people told me, I don't feel well. So I guess I don't feel well.
And he goes home saying I'm sick. See what's going on. Yeah. Yes. So you have the three, they have everyone telling you that you shouldn't be feeling well. Well, how can you feel well? You must be insane. Yeah.
Yeah, welcome to our works. Yeah. It's a power of suggestion. You see, we don't have direct downloads. I think we've talked about this in the past. We are creatures that require learning and adaptation.
For example, if you had a puppy dog that was raised by gorillas taken from its mom's litter and you adopted the dog two years after it was raised by gorillas, it would bark like a regular dog. It would chase squirrels and chase a stick like a regular dog.
It would say you wouldn't know was raised by gorillas, right? But if you gave a three month old baby to be raised by gorillas after two or three years and you brought them home, guess what that human's going to act like?
It's going to sit on your table and take a poop. Right. It's going to act just like a gorilla. Right.
Why? Because all the animals have downloads and how they should act. For example, I had a litter of cats and after kittens after a few weeks, after they'd eat, they would all stand around and lick each other.
They would wash themselves exactly the same way as if they were trained very, very methodically. No one ever showed them how to do that. Right. But humans.
We need downloads and we need schools. I mean, there's a school of fish, but that's different. So we are subject to external input and we were made this way.
And maybe on the second hour or so, we're going to talk about the difference between making or creating and forming.
And what we're experiencing right now is not a creation aspect of society, social engineering, but a reforming and what that means and go back to the history of that.
All right. That sounds really good. All right, guys. So we're going to tie this up right here and take it into the member section to get much deeper because, you know, the members, they support this unscensored broadcast.
And there's the ones that keep us on our own private server so that we don't have to be concerned about what information we share so that we can bring you whatever we want.
And that's a true beauty of having this self-sustaining system here. So I want to thank all the members for being there for us for so long.
You know, there's people that have been with me for 15 years and still going, I am so thankful for each and every one of you. And I hope more of you will come over and join in.
Check it out, get deeper into this knowledge and get so much out of here. This is a very original broadcast that you will find on the World Wide Web.
We don't follow anyone. We don't share the knowledge of the common knowledge you get deep here. You get real new information around here.
So thank you all so much and well, we will see you next week.
Welcome back members. Let me tell you about last week guys and I want you to know that you're my family now, right?
I really have no loved ones left. I don't have any close family left, no family lines. It's you guys. It's you. You are my family now.
But I have one member of my family, the longest running relationship that I've had, which is Diva, my little poodle, who has been with me for 13 years.
Last week she fell really ill and I really thought that was the end and I was pretty certain it was it was four hard days of getting through that and preparing myself.
But good news guys and that little tank of a poodle, she just keeps going, man. I don't know how she does it.
She's 16 years old, 100 in human years and somehow she just sticks by my side. She's been there thick and thin guys. She's been in my lap for 13 years. She was on the bus trip.
She's been everywhere I've gone. She's just seen and done so much in her lifetime as a little poodle. It's amazing.
But she has the longest relationship I've ever had 13 years with Diva and I really thought I was going to lose her last week and that is why I did not get a show done.
So I just wanted to let you guys know since you're my family what was going on and why that happened.
So let me just clear that up and Diva is doing fine. It seems you know I don't know how long I have but I'm loving her with every moment I have. So that's what happened last week guys.
And so let's let's let's put that happy thought because she's back to her old self. I don't know how she does it. And let's move back into our reality where everything screwed up where nothing is going right and no one knows where to turn.
And there are so many places that are offered for you to turn be it religion or the current social engineering that is guiding everyone to a path of destruction and it seems no matter where you turn.
It seems like it's going to fall apart but I think we're going to hit you with some good news by the end of this and understanding how this will all fall.
So let's get deeper into this great let's let's jump right in religion let's let's go.
We're in the member section. We can say whatever we want right right.
You know it's a curious thing to me and I just want to throw one thing out there that I have a personal belief in a higher power right I do I.
But I was not raised with a religion my family would not allow religion because the Nazis actually saved my mother from the Catholics.
And so my mom would not allow religion into our household so I wasn't raised with the religion at all but in my travels and in my life experience I found that there was a higher power there was something that was guiding me beyond my own conceptions and that.
But what I find disturbing is that when you use the word God people think of a book.
And that just blows me away it's like God doesn't exist in a book.
No but the the ability to communicate might and what's interesting is it's one thing to say I believe in what I believe in but we can spend the rest of our lives making things up as we go along or we can take heed to those that came before us.
And know at least what they said in discern whether it's for us or not or whether we believe it or not or whether it's true or not can be discerned.
And what I always say when I when you bring up religion that there's not one religion on the planet currently today that knows or does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
I want to just go through a quick historical with references and texts where we are from the beginning till today very quickly.
This is something that is important because it leads on to where we're going in a qualitative way in in the future and it all ties in together as such so when you're ready I'm just ready to I'm going to hit the button and go.
What's interesting as I said earlier and hopefully most people have have a have quote unquote been red piled enough now to take the rest of this more openly meaning with with comprehension of what I'm going to say.
As I said earlier even the most academics you know professors are quote unquote atheist right and they still acknowledge this is the Christian era so we have this overarching demise of what's called I call it a demise and you'll see why.
Of Christianity on the world today and I'm not anti Christian.
I'm just anti deception and anti lies and I'm going to show you and backup what anti religion is in reality meaning your pro truth and I'm going to the only truth that we have is by seeking what has been memorialized as a record right and is the record true and correct and what does the record say a quick example of that is if we go read.
9/11 Commission of the war in commission and take that as truth right if you look at it very carefully they're telling you within the document it's not true even though you see what I mean there's no magic bullets and there's no airplanes you see what I mean what happened to building seven you see so we see we see the deception in in what's been memorialized you know in in previous history right even if you look at for example the atomic bombs the Americans dropped on Japan.
They said they dropped a uranium bomb but they never had a uranium program so where did they get it from.
Right they dropped a uranium in a plutonium they admit they never had a uranium research program so and it's standard Nazi ordinance right so these things I'm saying.
Look at it and it's revealed within the text itself so back to the being anti religion which is anti propaganda when you go to the truth side being that it's a question of the.
Being that's a Christian era even today president swear on what the bible and court they have you swear on the bible so this bible is very important and i'm just going to go through some very salient points that anyone will enjoy not because it's from a perspective of my opinion they will enjoy it because they i'm actually giving them.
10 years of my life in a few minutes in other words they don't have to invest it right it's like you want to swimming pool in your backyard you go out there and on the sudden it's all dug and finished and you ready to jump in kind of thing right you don't have to build it for yourself so what i'm going to share is is a very very high value and i have approached people in higher levels of society meaning
the whole religious leaders they all admit to what i'm going to tell you is true but they would never acknowledge it publicly and you know whether you want to believe that statement or not this is my experience so here we go if you're ready.
The biblical text is being used is something important do we know it and we meaning the society at large especially christianity today is so on that uses it and the answer is no to the muslims know the caran no and i'm going to get into these things let's start off with the biblical text for example very quickly you know we have this thing called genesis where they had a mini you know the first man and woman they eat the apple in the serpent all that right put that all aside and let's just go through what the text.
It basically says in just a two minutes you ready this is how we do it let's just skip to the part where man is made on the sixth day okay and man is made on the sixth day if you actually have a comprehension in the Hebrew it actually states that on the sixth day man zakhar and make nukhaba woman were created but ah there were so you have the man zakhar which means the man of remembrance meaning this is something really even before you.
And the female nukhaba means female usually given towards a female in any species were created but ah at the same time they were given a blessing they were blessed and they were given a job and their job was to go out onto the earth and populate it and make it their domain in other words they're the top of the food chain okay and then that's pretty much the creation man being created man.
And when the man being created man and woman at the same time they're blessed and they're given a job to go out into the world and dominated then in the narrative we have on the seventh day he took the day the gods plural took a day off it was the Sabbath day of rest right you with me so far pretty easy to follow isn't it okay then remember the entire the genesis is in chronological order so when you read verse one genesis verse one chapter one or you read the entire chapter one or you read the whole world.
This is verse one chapter one or you read the last verse in the last chapter of genesis that is chronological what happens at the end of the book happened at the at further on in time so it's chronological here.
So okay man is made on the created on the sixth day with the woman blessed and given a job to dominate the earth I've been repeating this because this is important to remember.
Then we have the Sabbath the seventh day and then then we have a garden setting okay and Adam man is formed not the word is I saw not but I he's formed not created from the soil taken from the earth.
And just man right now just one man right and he's given a job and his job is to manage the garden trim the trees mold alone take out the garbage etc etc I'm saying this in plain terms because it says his job was to manage the garden animals are brought to him for names not all the animals but whatever is brought to him it could have been more than two animals right now.
There's no blessing so far it's not good that this man is alone so we put a deep sleep in him we take a part of his body and form a woman hava and their job is also to manage the garden they're told not to approach this one tree which they do.
And they were kicked out of the garden not because they approach the tree of of of you're not kicked out of the garden because they ate from the tree of knowledge of good and evil you're kicked out of the garden because since they ate from the tree of knowledge of good and evil that they not eat from the tree of life that's why they were kicked out you see.
Right and they were kicked out and did they get a blessing nope she will bear children in pain and he will have to toil with forms and right no blessing and they were not created they were formed the term used is I'll saw which means to form.
When you get Plato I can make an elephant you can make a house you can make a dog you're forming the same Plato where in Genesis in the sixth remember a days a thousand years.
So now when Adam is put out on the earth all these things start happening on the earth and.
There are already people there for two thousand years because remember the sixth day man was created with woman created put out on the earth with the blessing the seventh day is another thousand years the eighth day Adam is made formed with a woman and they're kicked out and all the sudden everything starts to go south on the planet because of these two people.
Now that's why when came killed his brother and he had to go to a city of refuge in the reason he wasn't put to death because in the law if you deliberately want to kill someone you have to be put to death blood for blood I for I right.
He didn't know what it took to kill someone he killed him you know in he didn't intend to kill me just intended to kick his ass right.
Kane asks I'm afraid what are those other people meaning the cities because he was going out to other cities 2000 years as plenty of time to build cities he had to have a mark on him of the law meaning he because he just has to tell others that he didn't intend to kill his brother even though he did you know the cities of refuge if you know the biblical text they even existed the Wild West in the US were cities of refuge by the way from people from the East Coast.
So this is an interesting story why well because it's never been told that way before you know why because it's in print if you want to hide something publish and put it in the library better yet if you haven't even bigger secret Freeman publish about two billion copies and distribute them through the world that's how you keep the secret.
Okay now did I say anything that didn't make any sense regarding the creation account of man well just that there were cities when these were supposedly the first people.
Well the first people were created man and woman together and given a job in a blessing on the sixth day a thousand years go by which is the seventh day of rest and then on the eighth day after that seven Sabbath is over because they didn't make Adam on the one in the garden on the Sabbath it was after the Sabbath right.
Right Genesis to not Genesis one right right so we're talking 2000 years is plenty of time for humans to procreate and develop a civilization right.
And here come these two sort of like a pariah everything started changing in the environment and death was invited into the world.
So we have two bloodlines you see the lot of the Christian narratives as well you know she had sex with Satan and there's a certain bloodline see there they're kind of like.
And then they're just skirting on it they know that there's some there's two types of humans on the planet but they just can't refer back to the text because it will destroy the Christian narrative and I'm going to get into why and I'll tell you why and the same with every religion the Hindus the the paranas are contrary to Hinduism Islam is contrary to the Quran I'll tell you that.
So we have civilization human mankind the created type man that it has a blessing and is to dominate the earth for 2000 years before this new kid on the block Adam and Eve come on.
So what happened to these two bloodlines I'm going to leave that as a question mark maybe for another discussion depending on the interest.
Do you see what's going on this is in the text itself right so we have two bloodlines and then we develop more bloodlines with hybrids.
With the E.T. the supernatural beings the extraterrestrials ultra terrestrials non-humans however you want to talk about them so the Nephilim were in the earth in those days and then after yes hybrids also the hybrids were made right so then we continue that story so who's a hybrid and when you're a human are you human descendant from the six day man or eighth day man which is Adam and Eve who were not created but formed in the garden.
By the way they were looking for the garden of Eden a garden is part of another structure no one ever just builds a garden a garden is part of a complex of a building of a situation a city or something there is there is a heavenly city in the biblical by biblical narrative and that is a garden in that city.
If you understand how water is created I think maybe we've discussed it or not if you look at a rainstorm you know there's no water in the cloud the water is created in situ comes from counter space right.
You know if he was any water in the cloud millions of tons of water the cloud would hit the ground right so you have to understand that water comes from counter space which is another discussion so it's very easy to have a.
A divine or heavenly or ultra terrestrial supernatural being his dwelling place a mothership that with a garden in it forming these other humans that water pours out of that forms rivers like a waterfall right so this is I'm filling in a little bit more of the narrative without going down that line because this is just an eight hour study on its own and I'm not this is not my opinion when I'm telling you is reading out of the text right not reading into it the most typical thing you hear.
Is that when you read about Adam in the garden that's just a recap of the genesis six where that man and woman were created and blessed and populate the earth no it's not you have another human being formed not created go look at the Hebrew right so I'm dropping this as a seed I'm not going to water this and I'm not going to elaborate I'm going to go on with some other things because I think this is cognitively acceptable for most people to understand what I'm going to do.
People to understand what I just said. Now what is this matter with what we are today well it's not as simple as you see the painting with Adam and Eve and a serpent she ate an apple which there is no and then we all came from that that is false right do you know which one you came from the answer is no for no rhetorically right if I asked you Freeman are you descendant of the Adam that was formed in the garden or descendant of the humans that were made 2000 years before in genesis the sixth day which one you came from.
Can you answer clearly no all those two things a distinct categories of human that need to be understood and classified answer to that is freaking yes it is and you better look in that direction and you will open your eyes to many other things.
Does that have something to do with the people that are running quote unquote albeit small minority could it be the people that are running the world behind the scenes.
Think about I've sworn that they are not human this whole time or there are different type of different yeah they are different species of human absolutely right created human versus a formed one so these are things to think about now let's just go back to the Christian meme.
And this will be corrected not by me by by others in the future when the time is right because there's something called cosmic censorship you know where you're blinded you know you can't see it can it's been proven technologically they can pull slow frequencies to aggravate you or make you feel sleepy right and there's also things they can do to make you forget doesn't have to be drug induced anymore this is being done cosmically to humans right it's like the Greeks you know the river sticks you drink the water of forgetfulness right.
So let's go to the other thing when you talk about Christianity the first thing they put in front of you is a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper always they're always showing you this symbol just like 9/11 remember the towers they kept you know showing the towers for months every day every time you turn on the TV what are they trying to put into your head right some cover up something not real here what's going on right let's go back to the biblical account and historical account.
Even if you've never studied the Bible and you've seen the movies we know that the Christ is an important character I'm not saying J.E.S. U.S. right now he was arrested by the religious authorities I'm going to keep this simple you know why because it is simple he was arrested by the religious authorities tried by them via confession accused by them and convicted he said you said you were the son of God is as you will see me coming down in the clouds as the sun.
Oh we don't need any of these witnesses he just confessed so he's guilty he's ready to die according to them right he's brought through the various today and authorities and then finally ends up with people don't know Israel was under Roman occupation at the time if you don't know now you do.
And I'm sure most people do he's brought to Pontius pilot what is Pontius pilot do he takes out a laver and he washes his hands he says I'm washing my hands of this matter I am I told you I found no guilt in this man and if you see that he I'm paraphrasing here it's in the book of Mark in the book of Luke if you see that this man be done as you say use your law.
What did you day and say well if you don't know I'll tell you paraphrasing we can't under Caesar basically we're under occupation we have to use Roman what is Pontius pilot say I am making this exception use your law.
Now stop right there you've heard of the concept of kindergarten through PhD right you have it's cumulative K through 12 high school and you have bachelor's degree masters when you're reading these accounts in the New Testament these are done by men this is like that are giving you.
That are giving the testimony of what happened and that is PhD college level when you go take let's say college level math do they say everybody let's start again two plus two is what no it's cumulative you don't get to the New Testament unless you've mastered everything that came before it this is with all any book right let's go back to the account.
Pontius pilot returns the Christ back to the day and authorities and says I am making exception use your law let me ask you for you and don't answer if you don't want to or I'll answer for you what law do the Gi day is use they lose a law of Moses don't they.
And in the law of Moses what is capital punishment and how is it done that by stoning now we're not that stupid because if we study the law of Moses if you haven't studied it can't be called stupid but if you studied it and do it on me twenty one.
And then you're going to be nailed to a tree when this is done now again we're given twenty one or thirty one roughly hints that the almond tree is important so he's nailed to an almond tree with one man on the left one man on the right and he's being stoned the people are passing from the third to the ninth hour doing what throwing dice patty cakes.
And then you see that actually later on it does but in the text when people are a survived stoning certain of the disciples they say look I bear the marks of the Messiah after they escaped the stoning think about that right so.
Now anything that's hanging on a tree is a cursed and to be burned that's why people are confounded at the Passover the Christ said take this bread is my body and this blood is my wine there were confused when you read the text why is he saying that because the or there's no last supper by the way it's the Passover they were doing because in the ordinance of the Passover when you have left over is thrown into the fire so he was the lamb of God he said I am not the I am not going to be thrown into the fire basically.
He was buried in a rich man's to see how it goes and goes so here we have a stoning on nail to a tree with two others.
And then he's resurrected raised from the dead where did they get the Roman crucifixion with three crucifixes and how do you die from that I tell you where they got that from even if you read in the biblical text after that was done the high priest said we must cover this up.
I don't know if you ever read that or heard of that even Stephen Dunn in the films and not only that they have to go after anyone who knew him meaning the Christ figure that they executed had executed.
So they covered it up by saying the Romans did it and over about.
Oh 40 50 70 years later the story morphed into the Romans did it themselves using a Roman crucifix and then about three or 400 years later iconography with crosses started appearing how easy is it to do that in social engineering over a period of 400 years very easy as we see right now social engineering could be done at a drop of the hat back then it might have taken 90 years 100 years 200 years.
Okay so yeah if we look at how many people they say died in the Holocaust of and Nazi Germany it jumps from one and a half million to four million to six million it just keeps getting bigger and bigger as it goes.
Well actually I'd stick with the six million because that was printed about 30 years in a newspaper before it ever happened.
Okay British newspaper you know taken yeah yeah you know like for example in the Malaysian in Australian newspapers 10 hours before Kennedy were shot they said Oswald shoots Kennedy that made a mistake and they gave the information because they got the you know the tomorrow date screwed up you know yeah just like the Solomon building building seven.
Well actually there was a war but this was even worse with Oswald because it was using names it was very specific and there were nine hours before the event even happened.
And by the way Kennedy was told that day to that it was there was a TV airing you could still be found three hours before he went in that motorcade talking about presidents being assassinated on public television do you ever picked up on that.
No they did us to a special on assassination of presidents and he was told to be weary but anyway okay so I like using the Kennedy Association 9/11 all these things that there's actually many other things that have happened of course you know in society as a false flag and these people actually believe in it and they don't read the text.
Now when they read the New Testament you have to realize the language Frank up back in those days was Aramaic not Hebrew the classic writing was done in Hebrew but is typically Aramaic about a century later they Greek translations and and from the Aramaic and then it became Latin and became English as a matter of fact in the King James the New Testament is so poorly presented that they wanted to say.
That we are translating it from the Greek but they didn't have the Greek so they got it from the Latin they translated the Latin back to Greek and then translated it back to English but it was always in Aramaic for example there was a pope in the 1700s who wanted an inventory of all biblical documents in the Vatican basement.
I'm going to say that again there's not a lot of talk about what the Vatican has in their basement but I think premen and your listeners understand there's some pretty important stuff down there right from every side that they suddenly closed it as well.
Yes exactly well yeah and close meaning completely right yeah like there's no possibility of getting in there right now so so the when this pope in the 1700s had a multilingual group of scholars.
Look at everything they had in the New Testament from the first century was all in Aramaic all of it so when you even when you study the Greek the word forgiveness of the word miracle these things are not in there right the word forgiveness means to get yourself set yourself apart from get away from it you know and the word miracle is the word dynamis which means dynamics so when he says the he performed miracles it doesn't say that it says he performed dynamic.
So it says when your brother sins against you forgive him it's actually say it actually says when your brother sins against you get away from him separate yourself from him in other words don't be a satomasicist right so so we have this cover up that the rabbis financed and procured for over a hundred years to cover up they acknowledged the must they had killed their Messiah would came in secret.
And they said what a better way to do it than to tell everyone that the Romans did it and support this quote unquote Christian sect that was coming about if you know what I mean now the fast forward to Islam if you know anyone who's Muslim by the way.
Oh by the way for go back do I need to you know they celebrate Christmas no one even knows that Saturn ailey i'm sure you do another listeners do but people at large don't and neither do they care.
Do you know that if you're gonna make a time capsule and you put box of tissues is as clean x on it when they receive it on the time capsule two thousand years later they don't care that it says clean x that could be like some goddess name or something they just want to know that it's would pop so you don't say.
Clean x you say this is fine would pulp for facial wiping in a time capsule right because it's would pop right you don't say this is a clean x right it doesn't mean anything so if you're gonna make a time capsule time you have to use astronomical because the astronomy and the sun the moon in the stars keep their clock so when you have a time period you give where the constellation where the sun in the moon was during that time.
So if you if you look in the scripture it was the constellation Virgo cloaked with the sun with the moon at her feet and twelve of the draconian stars at her head well if you look historically there was the time period let's say between ten BC and ten AD did that.
Let's say astronomical alignment which is five or six astronomical you actually take it to seventeen or eighteen astronomical bodies aligned you know the more astronomical bodies you include in the alignment the finer the timing you get it down to minutes that way right.
If you just have two astronomical bodies it could be a week but the more astronomical bodies aligning gets down to very very fine time keeping down to the minute.
Well if you go look between ten BC and ten AD when that astronomical alignment that you find in the book of Revelation appears you'll find that it's the year three BC the month of September the day of eleven back then.
Right.
So but it doesn't mean it's this year because the Pope's work schedule the Cagorean calendar is arbitrary September eleven two thousand one was on a Tuesday this year was a Friday.
It's arbitrary you see it doesn't work that way because September eleven by the way two thousand one happened on the tenth day of the seventh month.
Does that ring a bell to anyone?
Biblically in the book of Leviticus what is the tenth day of the seventh month that's the day of a tone it's one of the most solemn and harshest days feast days.
Right actually that's the only day in the Bible where the high priest enters the holy of holies and sprinkles blood on the arc of the covenant.
And the only one that knows that September eleven two thousand one happened on that day.
Heck no.
No.
Of course not.
Well yeah I know I guess not.
The guys that made King Herod shaking his bridges that their descendants knew that.
The Magi know it.
Right.
Magi don't go the Magi don't get a plumbers calendar with a barrel like bear chested girl and say let's see what day it is or look on their iPhone what day it is and laugh at that.
And there's in there that a lot of people would had seen 9/11 show up in movies prior to 2000 like the matrix and such or George H W Bush announcing the New World Order for the first time publicly in 1990 9/11.
The breaking of the breaking of ground of Pentagon.
Right right right the cornerstone of the Pentagon the cornerstone of the Twin Towers both laid on that specific day.
And when the cornerstone is like they were trying to announce you know the Twin Tower attack prior to it happening it's that this has always been a revered day.
Yes and when the cornerstone was laid for the Twin Towers that week or that month in the in 70 or 69 was when they the phone company standardized 9/11 is emergency numbers.
Right.
Because some places didn't have 9/11. Some places had 0-1-1 or 0 or they didn't have a standard emergency number.
Actually I was around someone who before 9/11 said 9/11 the emergency get it this is on September 2001.
He said it's 9/11 the 9/11 month emergency number.
And he said he told me he said how's your credit score I said I don't follow that that's a fictional money.
He said well it's important if you want to get a job in security you better get your so why do I need a job in security for.
So you'll see.
Because security was that was security industry right anyway enough about you know I want to share things that are anyone can access right.
Now let's go back to the Muslims if you know anyone who's Muslim.
You practice or not and say hey your Muslim right yeah okay not you not your father not your grandfather maybe your great grandfather maybe your grandfather practice taura islam.
Taura that pronounce it taura which means Torah and they look at you and they like yeah that's right we did taura means Torah.
Why?
Because in the Quran it doesn't give you God's law in the Quran it tells you if you want law you have to go and do and read what Moses was given to Moses.
There's 10 places in the Quran that tells you you must do what Moses says to do now how do we know Freeman what Moses had written and told us what to do well we got to go back to the first five books don't we.
This is ordered in the Quran how many Muslims do that.
The reason why you have Sharia and the Berkas and the face coverings and all the countries have in in Middle East if not most of them have their flags have green white and red right all the countries Egypt Iran all of them have green white red is because of loosely this is many treaties the muslow it's called the Angolo Muhammad in treaty in the 19th century.
They went in there and said this is how your religion is going to be from now on we design it for you no more of this Torah stuff right now let's go back to Islam early Islam do you know that when Islam was created around the six seven hundreds around there let's say even eight hundred eighty that that is coincides exactly with the Templar crusades when the crusades were happening and the domination of the western European Angolo pushing Christianity in the Middle East they said we need to make a religion.
We don't want these people here becoming Christian following this fiction we already know the Torah we already know yes you meaning us you know we know that when the modi comes he will rule with you know they say the Christ will return well the modi in the Quran will rule with him he will prepare the way right so they all there's some super being that's coming in their agreement with it right so they created this organization.
And then we don't want them to be the one who came to Islam to ward off the spread of Christianity the fiction. Not what the Bible says not what the New Testament or the Bible says or who Yahweh is or anyone in their Abraham but to stop the spread of let's say the war in commission or the 9/11 commission coming in you see what I mean.
So I said here's here's the war in commission and 9/11 commission for I was like no I don't need that my library right kind of thing it was just like bad information we already have the real information so modern day Islam was surreal law Muslim extremism the burqa you know the face covering you could even see this in Bugs Bunny cartoons was warned by women in a herm or a prostitute right even a Bugs Bunny cartoons you do bless the ability to answer where is the cover yeah so that was women in a herm it was so.
And in a herm it was it was to be submissive and all that the face covering so I dream a genie I dream yes exactly it was shows that you have already submitted.
Okay and you were someone's property.
So these religions again are political tools why early on early on first century there the rabbinical essence was not religious the essence of it was political when I mean by rabbinical meaning the today and authorities in the middle east were not monolithic to Israel they were used as scholars writers
and other aspects of their society by others just like for example you know get a Jewish lawyer how many times you hear that right you know.
Because they are known to be very scholarly and very strict and have a narrative that is very very difficult to contradict once it's established.
There were you know when you mentioned the Holocaust earlier you could look this up there were about a million almost half a million or so Judeans in Rome that were told to leave and if you didn't leave you were killed and there was almost a million if not more several million perhaps over the that were killed by the Romans in Israel right after the rebellion let's say right.
And if you if you were when you revelled against the Romans and by the way with the tibaryous Caesar to create that to get rid of the Judeans in Israel I said of Rome because they he got word back from Pontius Pilate what was happening that these guys killed their God and he says we don't these people are going to be not do nothing but bring us bad luck we better get rid of them.
This was the ideology you see so the real Holocaust quote unquote the initial one that's never talked about other than the book of Esther and things like that in Persia was in Rome.
We've done both in the mainland in Israel and in Rome so so this why am I saying this right now because how many people are going to their religion to for answers right.
Most are many I see are and what they're bringing overlaying is false falseness right how many times do you see a Christian website Christian with a crucifix as an avatar it's false take get rid of it right it's it's you're going down a dangerous path that's like putting might as well put a.
A republican elephant there or democratic donkey it's a political tool used by the rabbis to cover up what they know they had done for example there was a religious rabbi in the 90s and he left a coded message to be read five or 10 years after he died.
And they opened the coded message and it was something silly like you should return those folding chairs that we borrowed for our meeting from to these people and there's no way this is this is the message he left it's a code so they counted every seventh letter and it said the Messiah was yasha what he came and we killed him.
So everything is being done in secret so why does this what is this have to do with islam and Christianity Judaism all this other stuff is going to be changed as everything is is changing social engineering give me an example and I dropped what's called a truth bomb right and it's not my opinion this is the hardcore truth and it could go beyond what I just said if you study it on your own but but answer me this free free man.
How many speeches has the the pope done publicly since quote unquote the pandemic or scamdemic how many public speech to invite encouragement and leadership to the people you nonsense is hologram banished yeah right because they know their time is up right where like where the descendants of George what where the you see
it's just it's falling apart this is what's coming this is what's coming you understand when I say ritual I don't do to explain what that word means and when someone is performing a ritual you the next thing is which one because they all are very different but what they all have in common is they all have a particular way to perform it with a particular technique and particular what location
many rituals require that they're performed on certain locations like I was speaking to someone yesterday like many battlefields were situated over ancient ritualistic sacrifice grounds getty's burgl places in europe meds france you know on and on and on right so you are going to have a cosmic ritual
and this discussion also includes what we've discussed in the past in the members area which is when these asteroids are going to hit the earth right and they're going to be two major ones and you know for example let's make another biblical correction you know how I said they when you read something in an English Bible they went from aro meic to Greek to latin back to Greek so they could say they translated out of the Greek
I mean that is really like a copy of a copy of a copy but handwritten by people who don't know the language usually yeah this is really your phone yeah you are really bad but if you understand the essence of it you can make the correction right so
like if you sent me an email and said a cone instead of calm you know I know it means come because we're not talking about cones right c o m e versus you know you made a typo but most people don't know that these typos were misinterpreted so there's one thing that they say it will this the name of this asteroid or thing that falls to the earth will be called wormwood
and I will make the waters bitter right well it's absinthos in Greek but in aro meic it's obinthos they added the s they they thought the s was there and it obinthos is an ancient god that relies on asteroids
it's it's actually the name of the effect of a particular thing falling from the sky called obinthos in the ancient Assyrian acaid in our meic
but because they saw obinthos and didn't know that they put absinth which means were it's a drink and this is what you're getting you see so what do you know about obinthos nothing very few people start researching it it's an ancient thing now again before these things are thrown down and they're going to be those main those two main biblical ones and the reason I lean on the bible is because as the most detailed information and the most history
the Hindi paranos are very good by the way if you understand those right if you can get into those because there is roman i sandskrit that's translatable pretty pretty well actually better than many of the biblical stuff right but before these things come into society they have to wait for honor morality and dignity to fall lower and lower and lower then the timing comes you see
so you had the way for fox to become a network or or actually all of these things that you see actually the more people are leaning towards their established religions the more their morality is going to drop because they're not going to get anything from there and you see so what they do what what people will be doing in the future is going back to the biblical text of the Hindu paranas going back to history going back to
comprehension like we gave in the first chapter or first two chapters of genesis that should be taught to five or eight year olds not adults right that should be known that it's chronological so what we're what you're going to be seeing is not necessarily social engineering from a strict engineering like a monolithic approach now we're going to go this way with our social engineering no no no
it's social engineering that requires the drop of human morality dignity honor and so and lawfulness this is what you're going to see so coming into fruition also when this is also discussed in the khalyuga right in the paranas right that in the end mankind will have very low right molar at morality
it's very similar to what you see in the biblical text the only pleasure they get is through sex only wealthy people are considered important right there's no morale every you only become successful in society if you lie cheat and steal this is biblical this is also in the paranas the Hindu texts right now what you know what's another thing I want to lean on is that the Middle East
back to the ritual is a cosmic ritual is where everything started when when it comes time to stop the progression of this immorality unlawfulness lack of dignity and lack of honor it's going to take place in the Middle East again that's part of the ritual when the cosmic forces call them the gods because there is no singular God
they must perform their duty on a worldwide level at that at that area known as the Middle East you know which is western Asia if you want to call it that doesn't grandma say all things go around come around right something like that
so you have to focus on that part of the world because it's going to be very subtle changes where I assure you within the next five to six years all of your dictatorial powers that are going to be ruling the earth and the most charismatic characters that everyone is going to be looking up to will be from that part of the world
you know and you're going to see a loose Middle East union not like the European Union but everyone's going to be working together you could be watching the news now all these countries are warming up to Israel I've discussed is for 20 years now two decades.
I just had the Abraham Accord signed and you know of course Donald Trump's getting to know nominated for two Nobel Peace prizes for bringing the UAE and Israel together and I'm just I'm sitting here wondering why that happened like why did it take Trump to make this occur and yet we're given nothing about how the Abraham Accord came to be and right now it's it's there and here we are.
Right now here's the other thing I wanted to mention there are many many gods and they were put on the earth and the chief God that you read about in scripture is Yahweh now this is nothing to do what you believe I'm just giving you what the text says because no one else is right whether you believe it or not it's up to you.
He's the chief God now what's interesting is he's known as the God of gods and we have the three heavens for example the first heaven is the material world that we know we look up to the sky the second heaven is where the gods are they don't they are ultra natural right they could like I dream of Jimmy can pop in and out right.
Now if you go into that realm you can exist and they can bring you into that realm that it's immaterial it's pure consciousness and if you're walking around in the market on the street that they have their world or however it's set up and you say hey you guys are the gods right yes we are but do you have a God they say yes we do and that's in the other heaven another heaven and that's where Yahweh is he is the God of gods that's why when the Israelites were told to go up to the mountain on the side I said no no we can't see that God.
You can't see that God because he will die you see so you can interact with the gods in the second in their realm but there and their gods you cannot so what's going on with the biblical text is very simple these gods are supposed to do a job if you read in the book of Enoch they train mankind to do all these things right but no no no one was dedicated to Yahweh says you know what I I want I don't have a people I'm going to make a people.
So he gets Abraham and he says Abraham I'm going to make a people through you and everyone that comes through you and Sarah will will have allegiance to me how does that sound he says okay and that's where the biblical story is about so what does that have to do with you meaning you freeman or anybody listening on a superficial level pretty much nothing book has nothing to do with you
but even if it does or it didn't do you know the story do you know that fact what I just said was laid down a thousand years of biblical academia theology and ten seconds that's all it is you see it's so simple why don't you you know why don't you get your stuff together I tell people and
it just find out what something is about the biblical text is about the God of the gods creating a people who have allegiance to him oh by the way how well did that go for them not too well right they did with not too well at all right and they're not Jewish by the way Jewish anybody can be Jewish you could just all you have to do is go to a synagogue apply for it you take a test and it takes about 30 or 90 days they ask you again you sure then they give you papers that you're Jewish
right it's it's a political thing today and it's it's bloodlines and and on and on and on by the way you hear a lot of crap on the internet beware of those that claim to be Jewish and or not or that has nothing to do with Zionism that has to do with the anti Christ by the way which I think I've revealed who that is to a certain degree how to identify them right because that is an important figure we know the Christ for example the biblical Christ is a
example the biblical Christ was born in the year 4,000 since Adam this is known we know that the year 6,000 started around 1998 in the fall because the biblical year goes where everybody the lawful year goes from spring to fall right the antichrist was born in the year 6,000 because he's the 6 is the number of man one of you know
he was repeated three times and also 6 day man got it a new man he was born around September of 1998 so that would put him in his 22nd 23rd year right now right and we know from the prophets he is known as the Assyrian not Syrian Assyrian and we know that he is a deceiver and so Scripture says beware of those who claim they are of Judah and are not
so this Assyrian 22 or 23rd old man presently who is of us Syrian descent will publicly claim to be of Judean descent I hope that helps because I just laid out a tremendous amount of information
and that's the biblical identity of the antichrist how is this narrative going to fall apart we have about 10 minutes left
okay here we go this is a you what you're people are experiencing beginning 1998 and making more of a whoop to do about it in 2020 is a cosmic ritual
where cosmic ritual what I mean is in a sense yes it's a ritual it's pre planned there everyone is going to attend and certain things are going to be done known as quote unquote the end times
what you hear about being the new world order and by the way the number one priority of every quote unquote administration or government in the world is population reduction that is the highest priority over everything I hope you know that doesn't matter which government it is
and it's been that since the 60s and it's in high order right now but population reduction sounds over over simplified so let me throw this in anyone could reduce the population very quickly
but the thing is you want to reduce the population to what you predetermined to be and have the remainder not complain about it not notice it and be very compliant
because if you went out and overtly eliminated a third or two thirds of the population the people that are left a good portion of them are going to be pretty pissed and unwieldy and unmanageable right exactly
so you have to do it in a way that the remainder is ultra compliant and this you're going to get an ultra compliant society and it's going to be ruled by by propaganda
backed up by paranormal events out of the Middle East by a group of young people backed up by some older people right and this is the whole thing that's going to change what you hear about the new world order is not going to be like it is
for example all of these things cloaked in rights you're going to be going under a very harsh old law system in the future starting in about five or six years it is going to be sort of a mosaic law
so that's why when people would say to me Greek you're an old testament kind of guy you kind of live that way aren't you upset that they're giving all these rights to quote unquote gay people they're married they're openly innocent
it's a no because the Bible says you know that you shouldn't do that and if you insist on it you're put to death right it's a it's a death offense biblically and said well you're kind of an old testament aren't you upset it's a no because I don't think that way I don't think day by day I think in thousand year and hundred year sections I know that in the end they're going to bring back some kind of a biblical worldwide law
so why are you upset that the the the quote unquote people of same sex are being allowed to be public and married well very simple they're being put on a list
everyone is being put on a list so when the time comes they will you will have to figure out who is and who isn't there are already public
there actually what's interesting there is an activist a woman and she professors to being a lesbian and she says I don't trust it all this right stuff is something wrong she publicly says that she was a I think a California person to work with real estate she speaks about agenda 21 you might have even had her as a guest I think she's very very weary about all these rights things that are being given to people the same thing with people who are handicapped and all these other things you're going to have a very draconian miss you
and all of these things that are you there that are telling people now that you have rights don't trust it for a second you're being set up that's a major setup but it's a cosmic setup you see
so all of this stuff you hear about the new world order and the social engineering is all going to fail as it's being shown by the alternative media and the
colonel conspiracy theorist because I'm not a conspiracy theorist it's all none of it is going to pan out and it's going to sidespype everyone and you're all going to fall for it because you don't know what's going on and it's
happening so quickly and it's going to be very very weird because most people will not be able to identify the sources of why these things are happening
so this new world order that people are talking about with vaccines and population reduction and all that yes are people going to die from vaccines yes tremendous amount are our
our population going to be reduced yes tremendously but it's not going to happen the way that you've been told it's going to happen when you see a power
base in the Middle East based around countries like southern Iraq Israel and Lebanon proclaiming this very very sounds good to bring world peace but a lot of people are going to be let's say
eliminated through it it's going to be used wrong like water is good for you but if you too much water you drown you're going to be drowned in this thing of a
wise version of biblical law also the other thing you hear about an ancient text about peace you're always going to be enticed with peace how many times do you hear
Freeman through the years we have a peace treaty right okay this is not what I would expect and I'm going to put something out now that I've been
holding close for a very long time and I never speak of publicly one I just want to just say it right way it honest I'm going to give you an
example there's a let's say you're on earth and one day you wake up and you have huge motherships aliens show up in the atmosphere like Independence day
and all the people get scared and said oh wow we better get our ship together and they make peace on the planet
the moment they make peace on the planet all the motherships fire and kill everyone on the planet except for one survivor
and they bring the survivor up to the mothership and he says you guys came we made peace why do you kill us he says because we're a war like
species and we created you to become warriors so you could come out into space and help us fight but since you made peace we destroyed you we don't need you we need warriors
think about that for a moment Yahweh is a man of war right is a war like God he could stop all the wars I'm going to put this out and this is
only discussed in very high-level circles and I have confirmation on this and I mean very high-level circles and I'm not going to say who they are use your imagination
we know of creatures material creatures of all sorts millions of species and we know here of the gods the angels and the demons and at the top of that is let's say Yahweh in the biblical sense
when you say Allah in the in the Korean that's Ella law which means the God the law is not a name right just means the God and Brahma is a high being that's not a name
when we are resurrected meaning when there is no more death because in the future death will be eliminated when we're granted a much higher existence
will be made aware of an existential threat to quote unquote all dimensions and this universe by the highest gods that we must join and protect this universe in this entire existence
and when I say universe 99.99999999% of all existence is consciousness in immaterial what we see is tangible that gives off light and is physical is only 0.000001%
so we're going to be made aware of beings that are not gods non-human not material another type of consciousness that pose an existential threat to this entire existence which right now is not being even discussed
even in the ancient text because you can't handle it you're afraid of being thrown off of a bridge and dying so when you're brought back
and now you are no longer subject to death known as the resurrection then you'll be given the second part and it's not training it's just that this is how you form things
you know what's in the beginning yeah what's intriguing to be right there is that in Star Trek the next generation such a character exists and he's known as Q
yes but he's not but we're not talking tricksters and pranksters here but yes this is like a cute type character and I think Q is also made them in the Star Trek that there are universal threats if you stir them up right
threats to your entire existence yeah go have sex with the queen of somebody's other planet and you're going to start a war
oh no I'm talking about an existential threat to the entire universe right that is of another type of consciousness they're not gods are not human it is another completely different form of consciousness
and I believe that a lot this is my opinion which everything I said is can be looked up as truth and factual but right now I'm going to give a minute of opinion
okay all right let's wrap it up in just say now the opinion is basically the the malevolency that we see from the divine demons is a bleed through
from that other consciousness yes I that's managed a managed bleed through just like a government would let certain spies through to study them even though they're doing bad
shit so anyway let's wrap it up as you say and so what do we get to do at humanity is being prepared for this final final answer that you know they're not being they're not being prepared at all I'm sorry
all right you don't prepare something for a ritual you either know it and you go through it or you don't know it and you don't go through it and it's all one big ritual
you either know about it or you don't there's no preparation yet yes the preparation is indirect and no one knows about it meaning right
right relation at large because the reason they don't know about it is because it's printed everywhere because they can access it that's why they don't know
right yes I just so relate to that and it's shown to them through symbols everywhere right so you don't even know how to you don't even have to be
literate to see it this is how ridiculous it is strange times and stranger times ahead so we are definitely going to keep in mind all that you have said to watch for these signs and symbols to come
it seems that it's already happening like we are talking about the Abraham Accord and peace peace peace it's the you know some major transition is occurring right now
well just a real short thing you'll know it's going to be in full swing when you see a new country being formed in northern Iraq that takes land from Syria and Turkey known as new Assyria
and I'm a record ten years ago saying watch out for conflicts with Syria northern Iraq and Turkey because that's part of Assyria and that just before any of the conflict started right and also you're going to watch for the
the completion of prime ministers in Israel they only have two more prime ministers and they're going to have a monarchy and when that comes into play then you're ready
well there we have it folks the signs and symbols and recognize that nothing is going the way that you think it is and everything that we have been guided to believe the villains that we've been told to watch for
this new world order the the the semblance of how this conspiracy is going to unfold is all part of the narrative and not the
factuality not the reality and so we're going to have to stick to our empirical selves be a perfect witness and and keep yourself without ego to to witness what's going on
and to to remove anything that's well if we can take from the the Mason's to Pufluss if I can get that word out of my mouth superfluous
we remove anything like that and recognize what's actually happening right around you right now instead of fulfilling and following the narrative that is constantly being projected into us
and nothing's going to go as the narrative states is what the Greek is showing us but there is a higher dynamic to everything that is going on
if I can use dynamic in the concept of miracles and so recognize all of this recognize that all the all the thoughts you're having all the anger all of the division is all just in your head
really is but as you're saying Greek you know 99.99.9999 the conscious of the world is consciousness it's outside of your head and you're letting it in right because you're subject to input
yes right because we're outside of you don't let it in there it is it's like a bad joke with no punch line a bad joke is bad enough but no punch line you really
believe in me hanging right that's what's going on yeah the punch line is what I gave you and you'll see it's the you're familiar with men does war with men but you're not familiar with men does war with the gods and when gods do war with the gods
so what do you know about that with nothing most people and learn about that and that's what you're going to see happening
yeah we're talking about beings that have an IQ let's just use that term of two million they know the answer to the test before you even wrote the test
right so you have there's no match don't fear whatever you do do not fear you're going to be fine and up the quality of your being
to live with honor dignity lawfulness and you'll be fine there it is well thank you so much for giving us all this time it's always fascinating talking with you
and it's it's definitely enlightening and I hope people got a lot out of this and they're willing to to open those books that you've mentioned
and actually see what they say because you know well there is no apple in the story about me folks so just you know once you get that through your head
you can see that the rest is also misinterpreted misunderstood and we have the ability to understand it so it's within us it's without us and we're we are here
I forgot to mention Steve but we always got to thank Steve and I don't know if you guys caught it but I did a show on 9/11 with Robert Phoenix
getting deep into the symbolism and bizarnas that's going on and Steve made an appearance so if you ever wondered who Steve Mercer is producer
associate producer here on freeman tv.com well you get a quick glance at him because he was only there in the first few minutes
but yes we did a show last week 9/11 or that and so if you ever wondered who Steve is well you can find out
just check out Robert Phoenix's program and you'll find us discussing this of course it's in my Twitter feed I hope all of you guys are following me on Twitter
at freeman tv because I'm trying to bring you the news and the information that matters I skip over all the regular stuff that you see every day
and I bring you the more intensive what's going on on planet earth there so I hope you all are over there following me
because I believe that you are and I believe that you have the knowledge that I'm sharing there so if you're not then you might be missing half the story
so I hope that you're over there and a lot of this is now going to the real freeman fly on facebook so if you're on facebook and you want to follow me there
thanks to good friends on facebook I actually still have a presence there even though I've been banned for seven years now
but the information is still making its way there because we work these circles and we work our way through
and thanks to you guys this show carries forward and will continue to do so
and I want to thank you for granting me last week to take care of diva
and I'll keep you guys up to date what's going on Greek how can people find any of your work and things that you're doing
well just like you have others that help your projects along there's someone that has a website called GreekSpeak.com
and it's info@greekspeak.com is the email
and that would be the easiest way to find many articles and soundcloud audios I think about 40 hours worth
and also my personal website is uncommonradio.com
and there's nothing I have that dormant for several reasons and what you will find there is just an image within email
personal email to myself and that's pretty much the best way to get in touch with me
alright there you got it guys lots to dig into and you know you need to because we're only scratching the surface in a couple of hours here
so thank you all and I will see you next week
[Music]
(music)