[Music]
Beaming out across the galaxy.
This is where conspiracy on the wall side
means the perspective of a lifetime.
This is the free zone, ghost, free men.
[Music]
You wanted to Greek and you got the Greek.
Welcome to the free zone.
We have gotten more requests to have the Greek back on so much that
we pulled them out of retirement.
Bring them out here for an exclusive talk here on the free zone.
And I am so excited to dig into this mind
because there's none other like it.
And I know this is going to be an intriguing show
as we try to discover really what is freedom,
what is sovereignty, and who are you?
What world do you live in?
So let's jump right in because I don't want to waste any time.
Greek, welcome to the free zone.
Well, thanks for having me, Freeman, and welcome to everyone listening.
There's lots of them out there.
I'll tell you, tens of thousands of people tune into this show every week.
I am so impressed and so thankful of all of you guys.
And I hope that you will go and give us a thumbs up on whatever player
you listen to this show on.
If you don't know, this show is on every player out there from iTunes, Android,
Google, tune in, Spotify, Stitcher, you name it,
the free zone is on it.
All you need to do is type in the free zone with Freeman.
And it will come up on any podcast player out there.
And there are tens of thousands of you out there listening right now.
You know, Greek, we, you know, I pulled the show from YouTube right now just
because YouTube's like canceling everybody's channels for saying things.
And since this is on our own private server, and I don't have to worry about saying what I want to say,
I've pulled it from YouTube because I didn't want to lose all that 15 years of YouTube content
just to put the podcast on there.
So we are free here to say whatever we want.
There is no censorship.
There's no worries.
This is my own private server, nothing they can do about it.
So welcome.
All right.
Yeah.
Well, you know, YouTube, but the form of censorship that's been exercised and complained about by many is actually being done by YouTube itself as a private entity.
And of course, it's a wholly unsubsidiarity of Google.
So, which is Stanford, E.D.U., which is, has, you know, federal roots.
So, but nonetheless, it's all private.
And we'll get into what that misconception of government and how the planet is being run.
Let's say, perhaps in the next hour or so.
Yeah, welcome to the technology, folks.
This is it.
I'm just dying to know where you're at in 2020, Greek.
This every conspiracy theory that has ever been put forward almost as manifested in 2020.
I would suggest that people heed what the ancients were talking about.
But the problem is that the two minds can't come together, meaning the comprehension of the people today.
And they can't call them people and giving a lot of leeway because if most people have realized they're just considered livestock these days, right?
Meaning the past 150 years or so.
And I mean that literally you're living and you're, and you're a stock.
Yeah.
So, in essence, the ancient rits pretty much have it all because it's a series of cycles that repeat themselves.
But they're slightly different every time.
So where can we start?
I mean, do you want to start with the geopolitical, which is actually a very low level of addressing things?
But it's a, you know, we have to start at the bottom, maybe.
Or do you want to start on the cognitive level and people's lack of perception?
Which one do you think we should start at?
Oh, God.
Is there a difference?
Let's just start, let's just start on the lack of perception. It's kind of like warming up before you go for a two mile run.
There you go.
Is that okay?
You don't want to pull a muscle because if you lay on them, what's going on on the, on the bigger, which is actually still the smaller.
And the smaller, which might be the perception is actually the bigger.
So let's start on that. You know what's interesting is I usually call the university physics department.
I used to, on a daily basis or weekly basis years ago.
And I would call the HVAC people, HVAC is heating, ventilating ventilation air conditioning people, right?
And I would ask the physics department and the heating ventilation air conditioning engineers.
How many calls did you get yesterday about the public at large, calling you and requesting that you design machines that make.
For their cars, homes, planes, whatever, to cool and heat, where the cool is, the cold is verified and it cold rises.
And the heat is densified and it descends just like the human body.
You want a cool head and warm feet or when you look at nature, it's hot in the valley and cool at the mountaintop.
And if you go closer to the sun, it gets colder and colder, not warmer and warmer.
So how many people in the public at large are requesting their engineers and physicists to design equipment for to cool and heat their homes, where the cold rises and the heat descends instead of the heat rising and the cold going down.
Because if you, if you do the ladder or the way that it is, you have a hot head and cold feet.
And they always answer, I don't know what you're talking about, no one's asking about that. So I hang up and say a planet full of morons.
How can you not notice that you should have a cool head and warm feet and not demand that the cooling and heating equipment that you employ is in accordance with that.
No one is noticing that, right?
Now, there's a bigger thing, you know, when you chemically degrade something like if you have a campfire, you'll say, well, Greek, you know, the heat rises on a campfire.
So look at the, the wood that you're burning in the campfire, is it being degraded or is it building up? Well, it's burning it down. It's being degraded.
So whenever you degrade something, you have a rarefied rising heat and a densifying, a lowering cold.
But when you're building something, like in other words, life is being employed to create chemical, let's say a glomeration where things come together and they grow into a higher order.
It always descends in the cold, always rises. This is a set true in the atmosphere. This is true in the human body.
If you called a medical technician in a lab coat and said, I have a hot head and cold feet, you'll say, son, you're not feeling good.
But I thought he's supposed to rise and cold is supposed to go down, but it's the opposite, right?
This ties in, you know, when you go to supermarkets or grocery stores, they have nutritional information on packages, right?
And one of the major ones is calories. You know, I don't want that. That's too high in calories. I'm burning calories. Well, let's just take a moment.
You know, the calorie is defined as a thermal unit, you know, with how much heat a material gives off when you burn it.
And if you've ever seen the calorimeter, one of the ways they do it is they put, let's say, the food of banana, let's say, a 60 calories.
They put it in a glass tube and they put pure oxygen in it with something that looks like a spark plug. It goes boom. And it burns into complete ash or charcoal.
And the heat that it gives off in a water bath is measured as how many calories it has, right?
But let me say this, that's a valid scientific process, but it only applies to anyone who's pooping charcoal briquettes, right?
Because if you eat a banana at 60 calories and poop it, you could still burn that poop. So how many calories did you get out of it?
You could burn a piece of wood and plastics got a lot of calories in it, but if you eat it, right?
So calories have nothing to do with food. It's like if I ask you how much does that weigh? And you say it's 19 inches. You're using the wrong unit.
And no one is paying attention to this. And they all start saying, I'm burning calories. Right? This just goes on and on and on.
How about your calendar? It's really funny. You know, september means seven. Octo means eight. Nova means nine. And desa means 10.
So how are you getting off writing September as the ninth month, October as the tenth November as the 11th and December?
So on and so forth as 12 when it actually means 10. Because four times out of the year they actually give you something similar to what the true month count should be.
You know, you ever wonder they only selected four months out of the year to actually have the nomenclature correct where september means seven. Octo means eight. Nova means nine. And desa means 10.
You know how that also follows suit when you take a multiple choice question and answer test. There's always four possible answers. You ever see how things coincide to show how no one is paying attention?
It's kind of funny that way, don't you think? You know, but anyway, since we're on time anyone that takes astrophysics or astronomy in university, I think it's a 101 course. They tell you the day starts at solar noon. But for the people, it's it's a civil midnight.
That's kind of like when they didn't know how to define things in the early dictionaries. If you look at some of the old dictionaries that were printed in England or published in England, they said, oh, oh, okay, oats. It's a grain that people feed to horses in England, but it's the staple of the people of Scotland.
Meaning it's such a put down, right?
Now, if you understand how to keep time lawfully, for example, you know, the all put downs aside, solar noon is when your day starts. And if you understand that, high noon, if anyone remembers the old banking conventions, if you're old enough, when you deposit it a check afternoon, it was counted as the next day.
Does anyone old enough to still remember that? So maybe you are free, no? But the the essence of it is that's what I call lawful timekeeping. And for thousands of years, people settled their debts with the full moon. That's why today you get a monthly bill in astronomy 101.
They will tell you that the moon rules the month. So again, we have so many anomalies that go on and on and on and on and on that we don't know where to start with perception.
So we just relax into what we've been told should be our perception.
Yeah, that's never been sure then right now that's for sure you can believe whatever you want at this moment, which is kind of a positive and kind of a negative. And I'm in the same way.
Sure. Well, we yeah, well, the thing is also you said 2020, you know, the year count, you know, it's funny you watch prehistoric stuff, the dinosaurs 60 million years ago, they're constantly.
Whenever the dinosaur meme is brought up, it's always six, they have to say 60 million years ago, but how come it's not 60 million 2020? Where does timekeeping start?
You know, what's interesting is if you study university or let's say not university university, but study what the academic convention is, in other words, that the academic convention is what transfer is what's transferred over to the standard.
Social convention, right? In other words, when you start to look at the conventions and why what we're doing not why we're having forbid why we'd never ask why you're doing it, just do it right.
But if you look at everything that's being done, it has some academic route to it. Always it's stemmed you could always go into university library or a library per se and look up some kind of source material that'll tell you.
You know, how this came about very rarely accurately why that that's where you're going to have to figure out why, but if you start to look at reference points and what things mean like what words mean, you know, I'm not a Scientologist, I'm not into the all around harbored or whatever, but one thing that he stressed, which is actually correct is learn what words mean.
It's a form of communication, think about operating a computer. If you don't understand what those all those little cursors or things that you click on mean, you can get yourself into a lot of trouble or not be able to use it.
And that essentially seems to be the problem. So learn what what words mean, how things are communicated and how they should be communicated and then go back to your resource source information, which is unfortunately.
So you've been painted in many ways because of academia as a business and part of the social engineering, let's just say, but if you do go back and look, you'll see a very different world that could have been or another world that is still operating parallel to this one.
And learn what words mean like anyone could do a cursory look up on etymology, which is the root meaning of words of the word nice like Freeman, you're a nice guy.
Haven't you ever heard anyone say have a nice day, right? If you ever look up the word nice, it actually means foolish, stupid and senseless. Now, how could it be twisted into something as a positive greeting.
That would be that would be an interesting question. How did it go from its true meaning to how it's being used today. And you know what my suggestion, my advice is to people don't even bother finding out how it got twisted.
Just look at it's, you know, how it changed.
Just look at the, where the point of where you discovered this and where you are now and what you're going to do about it now in a way that you separate yourself from any malady that might come from that twisting, right.
So that's very benign, meaning using the word nice as it's being used isn't going to hurt anyone is it.
But if you start moving forward to other terms, it, and then you might say, well, then it could become quite hurtful like if you study what's called the legal society.
When you hear words like person or presumption or fact, those words do not mean anything as used normally it is another language, right. It's coded.
And then you look at, for example, of what's put out in the media and what's put out to the public that is all coded language, right. You constantly see.
It's a lot of loose terms. But yet they're specific, but don't make complete sense, but make enough sense to get some point across when you sense that that's because there's some kind of a code there.
Any code is you have to go back to the Primer. And if there if you words that are being used in your in the language that you understand, you must know what they mean intrinsically like from an etymological point of view and not how they're being used because that's in in fact where the code lies.
Like the ideas of democracy being mob rule and government being mind control.
One way, well, think of democracy, crossy is the suffix Greek, which means to rule or governing body. And demos is usually used as the people, but demos is also one of the moons of Mars, which means terror or fear or dread.
So democracy can actually be taken to to mean to rule by fear and dread or terror.
That's why years ago I'm not political on a political Hillary Clinton said we're going to bring democracy to Libya.
Or we're going to bring democracy to Iraq, right. And she even threatened South Africa with democracy and he says, OK, I'll do what you want.
So meaning the government there. So this is just an idea. I'm not she's she's just an officer of an organization. She has no power.
That's another thing I wanted to suggest. We're kind of semi linear here and because we're taking parallel. This is a parallel conversation.
I don't know if I can tell you how much time I say something and we could go into another direction. What what people don't understand is if you've ever heard of anyone in history or currently or seen them, they have no power.
And yes, Julius Caesar was in an administrative capacity. He was his official role was what emperor Rome Rome and later on the Senate actually voted on decreeing that the emperors were gods, didn't they?
So not only was he an official of the administration of Rome, he was also a god. So now we're stepping into a whole other category. But if you've ever heard of them or seen them, they have no power.
Meaning the the world as you know it has been ruled from behind the scenes by a conspiracy, not a theory.
If you if you understand that it is is not in a lawful manner or a positive manner, you can call it a conspiracy or you can if you don't like the word conspiracy, you can call it a power base or a power group that operates in secret.
And if you understand all of the if you do any history and understand any of the ancient texts, it's the they always state there are secrets, quote unquote mysteries constantly.
Freeman, you've heard of the mystery schools and how many people have you heard of that have been to mystery schools and like it wasn't what I thought it was it was really a lot of the stuff was quite obvious and in front of us the whole time we just they all they did was added definitions.
Right.
Yeah.
So the same people here here's an example the same people have been operating through genealogy on the planet for thousands of years you can say safely 4000 years.
Let's give you an example you know with the academic historians and we're talking about atheists now this is considered the Christian era the past 2000 years it has nothing to do with religion it just dubbed the Christian era right.
If you study that well where do you get that the they're supposed to subscribe to the biblical text aren't they they're supposed to you know specifically the New Testament which is not a sole document there is no separation that was done much later.
But nonetheless even if we were not.
if fistidious and students of the Bible. There's a scene there where we have these
characters, there's a caravans that rolled into town called the Maggi, into King Herod's palace.
They came and visited King Herod in his palace looking for a king, they said,
"And if you read the biblical account," this has nothing to do with religion. We're just
talking about what's in the account. These Maggi, this caravan rolled in, "In visit King Herod in
his palace," I've saying this several times because I just want to get into people's mind what
the setting was like. The continents or King Herod were shaking in his bridges, he was terrified of
them. In his own palace, here we have a king. Now let's just stop from in it. When you're a king,
you're not like set up in a hilton or something. You have a palace with guards,
pretty heavy ordinance, heavily guarded. Your word can mean a matter of life and death.
You're the king. So here come this far in caravan from the east and they're speaking to you
and you're shaking terrified of them. Think about that for a moment. Who are these people?
Yeah. Do you see what it means? Let me make some Maggi.
Yeah. Do you recall that story? By the way, maybe you don't recall exactly that he was terrified of
them. But how can you be a king in your own palace and be terrified of a guest? I mean, you're the king,
right? Right. What kind of power do you have to wield or be known to have to have a king basically
peeing in his bridges? That's very, very powerful. Who are these people? Are they part of a conspiracy?
Absolutely. Are they still around today? Absolutely. Do they know about the motion of the heavens and
their effect on the earth? Yes or no? Of course. Do you see? Yeah. Okay. So these Maggi are not
Maggi per se. That just means there were there were astronomers. They were people that knew of higher
order things, right? Magistice is a term that's used in ancient times for many reasons. It could be
someone who is a master of any field basically and exudes that where he garners universal respect.
The Maggi were not just astronomers. They were masters in economics, masters of medicine,
masters of the sciences, masters of weaponry, masters of political mind control and social control
and engineering. Do you see where I'm going with this? Now they're not a monolithic group and I'm
not saying it's just the Maggi but we have a biblical account which is an old account. It's proven
that it was written around that time and there are many other accounts and if you go back to
the time when Julius Caesar was assassinated or any of these other assassinations or other
political things in the ancient times, do you think that was just done ad hoc?
Do you know for example to have a in the past few thousand years to have a high political figure
officer of an administration assassinated, that is an order that has to be mold over voted on
and considered and executed from much higher than that.
Because the plan has to be put into place. Now what do I mean by this? Well, it sounds like the
Greek is just rambling. Many people talk about let's say the government and all this
dominating force in their society. We have to consider in light of
King Herod shaking what the appearance of the Maggi is it possible that there is such a group today
in that light? I would have to say yes. Right. Now do we let our imaginations run wild or do we go
back and start looking up what things mean and seeing what the academics have put out in their
reference material that's loosely publicized? When I mean loosely publicized, I'm talking about
doing a search on a browser on the internet that's loosely publicized. Do you mean because there's
information you can get within university libraries and government libraries that you must
sign in or actually walk into, right? That still exists but loosely would be the internet.
So if you understand how things are set up today and you have to understand this
coincidentally coinciding with what the age of Napoleon was. You know the Napoleonic Wars,
let's say about 200 years ago, coincided with a lot of the revolutionary wars that you saw.
The American Revolution and the War of 1812 and all that was the Americans joining with the
Napoleonic Wars if you understand that, right? As a world war per se. Well at that point, roughly 150
to 200 years ago is when it was decided that we don't, we've already sent out all of these
contract discovers, you know you've heard of all the people that Columbus, Magellan,
Vosko, Digama, you know they discovered all these places. Those were contracts that were sent out
to get those, you know, the world under contract let's say, to be discovered which is a legal term,
right? Discovery means evidence. Had already been done, we have this Napoleonic
World War situation and revolutionary atmosphere going on. This is a real good time through
this mild to extreme chaos to take control of everyone but not how we did in the past by region
but the whole world at large. And one of the few places that this was done in was the American
Civil War which was not a Civil War. Abraham Lincoln was approached by, let's just say the Freemasons
and the Southern states were approached by the Knights Templar. Let's just say. And Lincoln was told
you have all these resources here meaning what you call America can feed the entire world and provide
all the raw materials for industry for the entire world. Do you know what you're sitting on?
And obviously he's like, no I don't, I'm just the president, right? Well we're going to show you
what to do. It's all of a sudden a fort magically explodes, all of a sudden the south has
extreme superiority militarily, you know, they've invented weaponry, machine guns, submarines,
arsenals that were far superior than anything anyone else had but they still quote, unquote lost,
didn't they? How is that possible? Didn't you see a repeat of that with quote, unquote Nazi Germany?
You ever study even a cursory study of Nazi Germany? Wasn't there a weaponry far superior? You've
ever heard of the B2 stealth bomber? Sure. Have you ever heard of the Thornton flying wing? Yeah.
Okay. And so why did they lose it? They didn't. It's just a display. So make a long story short,
after the Civil War which is not known as the Civil War until 50 years later was the war of the
States. It was about centralizing the American continent as such. And Abraham Lincoln being the
simple ten attorney that he was, didn't understand so they had to get out of the way, didn't he?
Right? Right in the way. Very simple. Now a few years later everything becomes a corporation.
Quote unquote a sovereign state. So let's go back to see back to the definitions. That was a big
interjection. When you go look up on the internet or even YouTube's what a sovereign state is, the best
is the YouTube's. They have these professors and they can't define it. There really, there could be
this could be that. But if you look up what a sovereign state is ultimately you'll find out it's
neither sovereign and it's not a state. Just like if you look up the Federal Reserve you'll find out
it's not Federal and it doesn't have any reserves. So when you look up what's called a sovereign
state the general definition everywhere openly is it is a political, juridical fiction. But what
else is a juridical fiction? Corporation. Yeah. It has private shareholders. And let's just say you're
a president of one of these sovereign states and one of the shareholders walk in. You think you're
going to be peeing in your pants? Like Herod did? King Herod? Absolutely. Yeah. Who are these guys?
Yeah. Who are these guys? We don't know and we don't have to know. Have you ever heard of a private
trust? Of course. Right. Who owns it? We don't know. That's how it's set up. So
but this is where you're set up in. Now you either fall for it or you understand the calamity that
you were born into. Thanks, mom and dad. Right. So if you're going to be kind of upset at the state of
affairs at anyone it's not your government it's not your priest it's not your mayor's not your
governor it's mom and dad. I'm not saying you should be angry at mom and dad but you know what they
didn't they didn't even think once about it. You know they didn't even have the information they just
went at it. Right. So anyway do you see where the blame is? Right. It's where the source is. Right.
And there's no blame there either because they just didn't know but the fact is ignorance is not
an excuse. So that's another story and I could show you how that could be understood as well
someday maybe not on this one. But if we understand these the that everything is basically
incorporated and incorporate corporations work on stock and and inventory the rest I'm sure
of Freeman you've had many people discuss the birth certificate registrations the money system
and all that I don't need to get into that. The the aspect of the sovereign state for example can
also be examined with Switzerland. You've heard of those wonderful people that tend to be neutral
right? Yeah sure. You know when you're watching a sports game the referee he's what?
neutral isn't he? Right. But being the referee what does he do? Doesn't he call the shots who wins and who
doesn't he call if there was a foul and the game needs to be redone or was in the play was in
valid doesn't doesn't that what the referee does? Yeah. Doesn't doesn't the referee make or break the game?
Yeah. Big of thanks Switzerland for that or one of the ways that's an overt way where the the
controllers stick their head out. Now when did Switzerland become a sovereign state? 2002 is a
rhetorical question September 10th one year after one year and less one day after September 11th
they became a sovereign state. Why weren't they a sovereign state before that incorporated? Think
about that. You lived if you were if you lived in Switzerland every each individual man, woman
of adult you know was sovereign meaning they were people and after September 11th 2001 and 364
days later on the Pope's work schedule known as the calendar they decided okay we'll fall in and
become like the rest of you guys. Go incorporation because you couldn't have Switzerland become a
member of the UN which is an association or club of these corporations because each you would have
to have I don't know how many they're 14 million or 12 million people live in Switzerland.
Each one of those people would have to send a representative to the UN.
Anyway something to think about. So this is one of the last the other places where you don't have
sovereign states is places like Somalia. Oh they're bad. Parts of the Congo the Tureg people the
nomadic tribes of southern Libya the postunes and Afghanistan. Those are the last remnants of
free people on the planet as such. By the way you know when this latest pandemic thing started they
started bombing Somalia because there was reports of one ISIS person there they just bombed the
shit out of it and you didn't hear anything about it in the news right. Yeah right because of course
they don't get viruses they get bombs. So anyway it's a very interesting thing it's a very the earth
is a very very dark place it doesn't mean you are dark or have to participate in the darkness is what
I'm trying to say. Forbearing with knowledge of the current conditions is what's taught to what's
called special forces people and when I say special forces they don't only exist in the military they
also exist in business you ever heard of corporate espionage. If you're a retired spy don't you
you know you get a lot you get paid a lot better a quote unquote if you work for a corporation there's
such a thing that's corporations spy on each other right. Now when you hear special forces people
doing extreme things why does it have what is everyone's mind always have to go to the military
or paramilitary why can't you be a commando in a sense a piece or a special forces operative within
your world yourself and operate on a higher level why can't you do that and why shouldn't you.
Yeah I'm a little lost on that. In other words if you have special information and understand
how things really work would you function like your everyday Joe Schmoe or would you or would you
just appear to function like a Joe Schmoe but internally be on a much higher level where you're more
self-sufficient more defensive you see and more beneficial to those around you quote unquote friends
family. You see when you have a special operative let's say a Delta Force guy or commando in society
does he where all of his bars and stripes and say I'm a good or does he blend in with everyone else
you see or aspire whatever so basically when you're visiting a place and you don't want to stick out
like a sore thumb and be noticed it doesn't change who you are whether you're undercover or not or
overtly different actually if you in this society in the past 150 years or so come out and appear
to be overtly different you'll be dubbed as an insane person won't you. Yeah pretty much that already.
Yeah but that's all right so how do you perceive things and how do you understand things is based on
a the homework that you've done and the ideology that you live with so you know it's not defeat us
to say that the earth is being controlled by some very dark forces for the past I don't know
if Freeman you want to fill it in 100,000 5,000 10,000 do you want to fill in the number it doesn't
matter you're not that old let's just say within your lifetime your the earth is being controlled
by some pretty dark forces now in order for them to be successful do they walk around like Darth Vader
uh or some uh grim reaper through the streets or do they appear like everything is hunky-dory but
really dumb down right so one of the reasons why you have all this funky perception is because the
stuff that's put in front of you is just contrary to reality it's unreal calories for food you know
the the way you keep time being so disconnected you know if you took all the calendars away in all the
smartphones and even ones in print if you ask someone what date is they won't be able to tell you would they
like today is the 16th actually it's the 16th day of the seventh month it just so happens this year
it's pretty close right lawfully so how do we move ahead as a as a people you don't because what one
thing you have to understand is that um these you have these many cycles you've heard of 40 year 100
year 500 400 year cycles were part of a grand cycle kind of like the collie yoga but if you even say
the collie yoga you know collie is the goddess but the if you actually read the piranha is very
carefully the collie that comes to kind of like drop all the stuff on the society because society's
gone south let's say is a demon it's a it's a contrary to the goddess you see but it is also called
collie like for example for every positive spirit there is a negative spirit a counterpart to do
quote unquote you know to act judicially on a on a group of bad people how many times have you
heard of god versus the devil right well they both are divine so uh you know you have this aspect
the you know in this grand cycle but again um you you learn to separate yourself by understanding
what things mean how things work um there's no one to blame except for your parents which is futile
I'm saying that as a rhetorical way right because how did you get here biologically right um even if
you were hatched someone had a lay an egg and they should have thought about it before they did that you
know um on the other hand uh you can say uh if there's no one to blame really then and the
the you know and what do you do in such a an environment you know we're basically captive uh uh
and and limited is you explore um all the possible you know movements and freedoms that you do have
and you dwell on that and you make the best of that that's why I always suggest that people say
quick what do we do I said food clothing shelter food clothing shelter in that order you know you
have to have food and then clothing in the shelter in order to survive right and um somebody once
said to me creek that is so simple and oversimplify that's almost dehumanizing I said no it's not because
it's not just about food clothing and shelter when you're looking for food you're looking for the
highest quality food you can you can afford or want to afford it can obtain when you're looking for
clothing you want to get the best fitting highest quality clothing when you're looking for shelter
you want to get what you want to afford in the best and highest quality manner you see so pursuing
those things and amongst pursuing the highest order of things in food clothing and shelter you will
encounter many other aspects of what it means to be alive for example if you're uh trying to acquire
the best um food quality you can let's just take that as an take what could that be as an example
what do you know about the day uh and life of a chef in a in a three-sup Michelin star restaurant
well he gets up before in the morning goes to the market gets the best possible produce
goes to the restaurant thinks of how he's going to prepare the meal and hopefully has something by
lunch and serves dinner goes to bed after dinner at 11 or so and then gets up at four in the morning
starts the whole thing over again seeking the best quality out i'm not saying you should be a chef
but that's would be that would be an example you see it's and all of those things that the chef is
doing to get this highest food quality and preparation he encounters many many other aspects of
being alive on this planet you can't just pursue the highest quality food and you're not going to run
into other aspects of what it means to be high quality existence currently returning to others to
tell us what we should get how we should do it and where the highest quality is you know we were
constantly well especially right now uh looking to the experts to tell humanity what is good for
humanity yes and unfortunately if you believe that that and you function that way it is unfortunate
it doesn't mean it'll compromise your survivability but it is unfortunate you will not get the
high quality one thing i say to people especially the younger the better is that all fields of study
are completely open right now what does that mean if you want to study let's say for example
what's called medicine the human body healing health biological you know how things animals people all
these things you know what what it means to be alive by-law biology that field is completely open
when you go to school to study that whether all the way university that is grunt level ditch digging
work that they've done and then it gets very misleading you know if you want to study astrophysics
that field is completely open i have not seen a real photograph of anything pointing towards the
sky in over 10 years of you unless someone's posted one it's all CG computer graphics you know
if you want to study for example mechanical engineering that field is completely open i mean
cars that you have to put gasoline in that pollute i mean that is insane that is
that is not how we should be moving around right electrical cars with lithium ion batteries come on
you know i mean all the fields are completely open so you know one of the most important things
obviously is if you don't have understanding of how the human body works and you need to mitigate
something because of disease or injury you're you're basically shooting around with false information
your chances of being successful in mitigating disease or or injury drops the more fiction you incorporate
right the more realism you incorporate the higher your success rate will be in mitigating disease
in injury right one thing that people very few people understand is that the human body is under a
slight biological vacuum like if you look at all of the fluid in a body whether it's a plant a
dog cat bird or human let's just use that term man or woman there's no way that the blood vessels
and everything else is supporting all of the liquid when you're standing up going all the way
from the top of your head and to your feet evenly it's not possible the heart isn't pumping anything
so you have to have a slight vacuum because if you built an exact exact replica of the human body
and filled it with liquid all of it because of the flexibility of the skin and the vessels would
drop to the bottom no matter how much of a even if you had a 1200 horsepower pump for the hunt for the
heart none of the liquid would be rising in equal equalizing as it is when you're alive it'll all
go to the bottom lower half of the knee and explode right doesn't matter how much you're pumping
the body isn't a biological vacuum that's why when you cut yourself you have to count you
know several seconds for any kind of fluid to come out so once you understand the blood that
plants animals and human bodies under a slight vacuum well now we're dealing with a whole different
perspective right just like for example if you look at a cross-section of the human intestine and
the lumina which is the opening look at the walls of the intestine does it look like anything actually
gets absorbed through there or there are three hydrophobic layers that look as durable as a fire
stone steel belted tire it's the latter so how does the food get into the body by and
induction i have a cordless toothbrush has no metal contacts i put it in its charger and it starts
charging it's plastic against plastic how does that happen right there isn't something called an
induction stove it's a glass stop i have a pot of boiling water i move the pot to a side put my hand
right on the stove top through temperature i put the pot right over the induction heater immediately
starts boiling again how does that happen why isn't that studied and applied to the human body for
example when you speak to any gastro intestine intestineologist or whatever people that study the
digestive system doctors do they always say if you ask them how does it work they say it all works
by electrical impulses if you talk to speak to a neurologist how to tell me in 10 words or less how
that works in the body it all works by electrical impulses let me ask you Freeman since those two
categories which represent maybe five or ten or twenty percent of the study of the human body
how much electrical medicine are they actually prescribing to people there's certainly given
Donald Trump a lot of crap about talking about using infrared light on the body okay but you see none
none yeah yeah exactly you know it's like going to a car mechanic and my car needs to be fixed and
given the keys just come back in a few hours oh by the way before you leave can you tell me where the
steering wheel is and it's fine right this is exactly what you're what they're putting in front of you
so yeah well the thing is again Donald Trump has no power he's an official it's just not point him
out but your mayors your governors those are officials of the administration simply
well according to like I'll give you here's a little here's a little insight information and this
might help and the inside meaningless a cultural inside when the mob you ever heard of the mob the
they no longer do just drugs and prostitution stolen cars and things they stretch out into the
corporate world they shut set up shell corporation you know shell corporation not the oil shop
but a shell corporation do whatever they want to do and they just collapse the corporation right
so they're like well set up a corporation we need a president a CEO I say real simple is a homeless
guy right there he looks pretty good give him a thousand bucks he'll go sign all the papers and act
to CEO you see my point he doesn't care all right how many officials police chiefs governors or whatever
that were congress people that you don't hear about what happens when they're finished they leave the
country here not all of them but but here's the thing okay George Washington the apotheosis of
George Washington they show them in a throne like Zeus right if you're familiar with that look it up
and he's deified in a sense almost like in one statue he looks like a gust of Caesar with his arm
upright and all this so that is American royalty this is before Kennedy and Kamalat right not only
George Washington we have Adams Jefferson and all that where are their descendants where are they
yeah they had children we know they had children yeah where are they yeah how come on these national
holidays we don't have them up on a podium this is fifth generation Thomas Jefferson junior junior
junior junior where are they where are they we have that with kings and queens sort of
actually with the current monarchy in England you can't go back too far before you find that oops
but anyway uh where are they preeminent where they had children right because they weren't
aims Washington Jefferson uh it's it's often afro-american right right yeah exactly yeah if you look
in the phone book anywhere in the east coast southern states and you look under don't look under
j because if you measure it it's about three quarters of the phone book under Jefferson right or
w. Washington right and they're african-american but where are their descendants see because they never
were in the first place you know here's the interesting thing no one's paying attention and I say this
and I have to say it George Washington was a normal kind of guy but after a certain battle where he
went missing for a few days and was found all of a sudden the biggest concern about George Washington
was getting teeth in his mouth you heard of that they had wooden teeth they pulled teeth from slave
why because the guy that looked like George Washington so much that would pass for George Washington
because George Washington is no longer with us we found his frozen corpse in Brooklyn but that
would be too demoralizing this guy looks just like him sounds just like him but we gotta get some teeth
in his mouth rena hurray not only that when they brought this guy who finally got some teeth in his
mouth to one of the freemasonic rituals he says what the f is going on here freaked out
where the regular George Washington was just fine with it so he said this guy's gonna talk so
we need to bleed him to death do I need to say any more about that I mean how obvious is that
do we heard of the battle of Brooklyn anyway don't say this too publicly because you're a nut job
and how dare you say that right now if you go look at Abraham Lincoln the pistol that shot him
it's in a museum what what pistol is it it's a ladies pistol you know why it's a ladies
pistol because it was made for ladies and only ladies carried ladies pistols so do you know any of any
lady that was near him Abraham Lincoln when he was shot what do we know about the closest lady that
was to him that night was she going through some morphine or opium withdrawal symptoms and was she
very upset that her husband had syphilis from all the prostitutes anyway do I need to continue
any further on this no right you know what's I like the with the Kennedy you know when you go up
to the book depository you know where Oswald it was a comedian that made a good skit about this
forgot who it was some people actually think I sound like him he says I visited the memorial in the
library the book depository where Oswald supposedly shot Kennedy and everything's very accurate they
have the area cordoned off they have the rifle this that in the other there it's very accurate because
there Oswald's not there right right I've been there I've been on the grassy know yeah yeah so you
know it's the magic bullet goes through his head it goes through the windshield hits the other guy
comes back hits him again so look about what words mean ground zero now is a technical term if you
look it up it's the location on or below the earth where a nuclear device is detonated well that
makes sense you know there's been many packs through the years that no more atmospheric if you go
study about 1200 to 15,000 tests that were done depending on whose numbers of record keeping you
look at they've only only 5% or 2% of all nuclear testing has been done above ground the rest of it is
underground you ever notice that you know they only blew about four or five of them in Nevada
and then they blew above ground maybe 10 and the other 1200 were where nuclear testing underground
because that's how they're used that's why in downtown Manhattan you had a surface temperature of
2500 degrees and about 150 feet below the surface was around 5,000 degrees enough to melt granite
and steel that's why when they cleared the floors of the world trade center you saw this big molten
conglomerate thing coming out of the slab and they told you that was stuff that was deposited from
the glacier age and you'd say well wait a second the guys who poured the concrete slab and smoothed
it out actually smoothed went around this thing they didn't notice it back then anyway
this is all easily just establish and but you're crazy right it's insane right
right so if you just take an empirical view of reality and say you know
like like we opened with the idea of cold going up and heat going down empirically that's just
incorrect well it dole hold on it's it's correct if you're chemically degrading something
like burning wood not growing wood growing wood the cold goes up and the heat goes down burning
what the heat goes because you're breaking it down but go ahead right well it's just empiricism is
out the window I mean we're at a point where you know Donald Trump and not to get political but
you know he's being blamed for earthquakes fires hurricanes it's as if you know there's no
signs based reality at all going on in our current state you can just blame whatever villain you
want for any natural disaster that's occurring and empiricism is out the door well there is no
there is no science anyway since the poppul bull anyone could look this up you know the poppul
bull of Pope Gregory which gave us the Gregorian calendar right the revision of the Julian calendar
there was a previous Pope that did another poppul bull in the I think it was in the late 1400s or
the early 1500s and his statement in that bull was anything that does not have a material component
is domain of the Vatican so all of you natural philosophers and scientists you can talk about
anything you want as long as it has a material component so what does that mean if you want to talk
about light it must have a particle if you want to talk about electricity it must have a particle
if you see it has to have a material component but yet 99% of the world is immaterial it's consciousness
it's energy it's in a sense of you know not tangible physical stuff you know it's so ridiculous you
know photons you know for light I spell them FAU X T-O-N and what the electrons you know I still have
this experiment you know no matter how small or how large the equipment I use always get the same
result I have a wire and I pump a lot of voltage and current through it so I know the electrons are
really pumping that thing is buzzing I quickly put on some rubber gloves in an insulated
cheer and I cut the wire and I immediately have a dust pan underneath to catch all the electrons
pouring out and I still haven't caught any electrons right so inside so you have particles inside
of a light bulb right which is supposed to be a high vacuum because if it's not it burns up right
so the photons are particles inside of a vacuum that are moving at the speed of light they go through
the glass where they slow down about an order of 50 times or 20 times and then when they leave the
glass bulb they speed up to the speed of light again hey how come we don't harness that for our
automobiles man that's really cool because I want to be moving at the speed of light come to
a red light and then go back to the speed of light like a photon does how come they don't
because it's all a crock of bull and you're still operating that's a pun you're operating on
the pop-up bull which is if it does not have a material component you cannot speak of it that's why
when they built sir in the collider which you can go many directions is it really a scientific instrument
or is it is it something more like in other words a religious artifact that's being reconstructed
right you can go either way and they're both accurate and not because I say so because they say
they show it that's right so so actually what are they looking for the the god particle
technically god damn particle but yes right but they can't say they're trying to create an energy
quote unquote field that that affects the rest of the energy fields in a way that where they have
control of it they have to make it a particle so even with the idea of dimensions yes well there's
only one dimension but it's so think of it this way what we see is when I say there's only one
dimension meaning when you're dealing scientifically because for example you can easily understand and
that what we see with the visible eye is everything we see around us is less than 1% of the actual
light that can be seen most of it is outside of our visible spectrum and we don't need high
and it's provable okay animals that are not quote unquote that can discern color for example can
can can can discern colors of things in pitch darkness this has been proven with animals from
the forests that only go after a specific color because it's known as their food and they put
them in complete absolute dark room and they still can go to that object you this has been this is
easily found by anyone right this information so we see so we can say for example if something
exists outside of our visible spectrum in taps us on the shoulder we can easily say colloquially
hey Freeman it was a creature from another dimension came in and tapped me on the the shoulder
that's acceptable but it's not it's just not within our visible spectrum you see right so once
we start working with that we have to understand that most of the things are just not perceivable
like the perception so for example you know if you understand that nothing goes in and nothing
comes out of the body the human body you have an open track by the way you have several ducts
but the main track of the human body is from the mouth through the anus you could drive a little
miniature choo choo train put it in your mouth it'll come out your anus right you could take a long
trip through there right okay that's the only opening through the body but if you look at the mouth
and if you look at the throat and the all the intestinal system all the way throughout it is
completely sealed you can go online look at anatomical books look at the profile cross section of
the intestines there is no absorption all of those cells are so tightly packed they're hydrophobic
actually what I mean by that is if you go out to the garden right now pull out a plant very carefully
and look at roots are nice and shiny or whatever take a water bottle and spray it on there just
does the water get absorbed into the root like a sponge or does the water beat up like your
spring water on a freshly waxed car all the water beads up like a freshly waxed car so how are the
roots absorbing because plants are also under a vacuum when you water plants you're not watering the
plant you're watering the soil you see so everything is working through induction here's another example
of how things work when you do have something physical it's always in motion for example take a
a tabletop fan or a bicycle wheel with spokes when it's still you can put your hand in between the
spokes or you could put your hand in between the fan blades but once you get that in motion
you can no longer put your hand where you did before no matter where you approach the spinning
bicycle wheel or the tabletop fan it will appear a solid to you on it when it's in motion so it's
not because it's another dimension it's because you're beginning now to understand the fundamentals
of what we perceive as being solid and so on and so forth but going back to the human body if it's
under a vacuum right which you know I'm kind of dropping this on without giving more examples and
more explanation because I think at this point like you said 2020 it's a little too late for schooling
from the basics and that can be done but if you understand that the body is completely sealed and
everything goes in and out by induction right immaterial how does a contagion or a pathogen enter
the body and appear in your blood well that's because the body has to recognize it as something it could
reproduce internally right that's called formatting if I if you remember back in the days they asked
you are you Apple or Windows you know I have a disco I'm Windows this is Apple shoot you know
can't use it right that's called formatting so you know this has always been said for a long time
that people who are sick get sick right so for example if there is quote unquote a pathogenic
condition in the environment either transmuted by people animals or just in the environment if it
if you breathe that in and it sits in the cul de sac known as lungs the cul de sac is a place where
you go in and you get the only way you can come out is by turning around going back out where if it
goes through your intestinal tract or on your skin the only way that could appear inside the body is if
the body recognizes that is something it could replicate right so if you change the format of the
body where it does not recognize it as something it could replicate it will not replicate inside the
body most diseases are classified as someone being diseased by the symptoms usually exhibited by
the body internally right appearing externally whether it's a fever mucus sores what have you right
thrombosis thick you know blood clotting is actually a major thing so so how do you change the formatting
well it's been known for thousands of years that for example silver does it i don't recommend colloidal
silver but i recommend something called an aqueous Argentum where you have water just exposed
to the material this comes from the idea of homeopathics it's not how much of something you have
but how little of it you have is more effective right so the other thing is if you there's a youtube
on there about the 1918 pandemic and they're interviewing survivors quote unquote and one of the
women says everyone on our neighborhood died and the reason why we didn't know when in our
family did because every morning our mom would get up and take a teaspoon of soda you know the baking
soda and put it in water and have a soul drink from it well when you drink sodium by carbonate or
anything like that already type of a by carbonate it changes your body chemistry and you no longer
format than the people who weren't you see so you form things you couldn't get when the the pandemic
hit and everybody was stockpiling that baking soda was was high up on the list it was hard was it
very hard to get yeah i find that that alko rubbing alcohol still is and i use that as in spray bottles
in spray bottles yeah not for the body because i don't think it's if you're gonna use alcohol on the
body get moonshine or grain that grain alcohol right but nonetheless it's all about formatting like
for example anyone that knows anyone that works in virology or epidemiology or with pathogens
even though they take the strongest measures to separate themselves and be sterile about 20% of them
usually come down with diseases anyway just being exposed to in the environment not not physically
just being near it by proximity you see so this is an advanced aspect by the way i i don't know how
well-versed people are your audience or yourself on what's called the secret space program now i'm
neither a believer in it or an ace air but i've been i've noticed there's a lot of that stuff going
on for the past few years more now than ever well it's really fascinating that they just came out
and announced china and russia having these space weapons and directed energy weapons that it's now
become an official statement is as pretty intriguing but that's even below what people consider
the secret space program yeah but what about let's say the germans through maria or sick or whatever
in the thirties were able through hana bucraft and other like the nimza you know the the pressions
that came to the sonora desert in california in the 1800s developed a right stuff a Walter
Bosley is a done good research on those guys that's the norah group yeah the dark club grandfather
in the yeah i think actually some of the artwork that would survive that time period does say
trump on it yeah uh... so you you understand you you've been exposed to this but in other words when
i'm trying to say okay let's just say that's an interesting thing to look at to pick with discernment
what's being said but on the other hand let's just say uh... you've heard that the bottoms of the
oceans are less explored than outer space for example you know in other words looked at forget
about going there at this point um right so so if you are going to go set up a habitation at the
bottom of the ocean or in outer space you cannot bring nonsense like uh... calories of your body is
absorbing nutrients viruses bacteria theory and all this stuff that is absolutely ridiculous right
this is just the stuff that's fed to the masses to keep them just going you know um you cannot use
any of that what you have to understand is the bodies under a vacuum uh you have to understand
that the heart is not a pump it's actually a breaking mechanism and you know it's funny when i
spoke to a cardiologist you know he went silent he says yeah what you're saying is true i just can
acknowledge it you know i've got too much invested in this and my children are in medical school you
know this is the typical thing people say but basically says in what pumps the blood what gets the
blood moving it's the capillaries you have two thousand miles of capillaries that when gases and
fluids are exchanged within the body itself it creates a pumping action and is like well gases
and fluids exchange don't make a pumping action sure they do actually there's a very simple pump
if you where they just blow an air bubble underneath the straw and as the air bubble rises through
the straw it discharges the fluid and then you repeat the process are you familiar with that it's a
very simple pumping system you could use it for aquariums can you imagine that you have a small
air pump underneath the tube and you know as the bubble comes up it pushes the fluid over to the next
tank very simple right so there's a guy called frank chester who's done a lot of work or he actually
took material that resembled blood and thickness and temperature and tried to move it down a quarter
inch tube he needed like 20 pounds of pressure to move it three feet and that you don't have 20 pounds
of pressure blood pressure is an interesting thing it's what you know he give me an example you know
these a lot they have a lot of pharmaceutical outlets set up in typical grocery stores you know you
see them in the back usually and all these people eager to get their meds right I usually walk by
there and they have I asked the people behind the counter I point at the blood pressure machine that
you put a quarter in or a dollar in to get your blood pressure while you're waiting if you see them
those and I usually ask them where do I get one of these he says I don't know we rent them and I
said was the guys is by the way why do you want one I said while I'm opening a museum on medical
fakery and quackery and I want this to be one of my prime exhibits yes and they all kind of look
at me like what yeah blood pressure is part of medical fakery and quackery let's just do this
way we you go to a doctor and I want to diagnose you sit down we're going to diagnosis right so he ties
a string around your finger and you last you know your four finger first digit area you know or bends
and he can't be a regular string it has to be a medical string that costs about 30 bucks right
and then he has a medical timer because he can't use a regular timer of course and after a certain
amount of time your finger turns a color anywhere between dark flesh to blue to purple and he has a
medical chart that goes from dark flesh to blue to purple and he holds your finger up against and
depending on what color shade it is is what level what type of stupiditis you have right and you
believe it and because it actually he had a medical timer and a medical string in the medical chart
that proves it it says it right on there the color matches perfectly so you have stage 18 stupid
forget yeah sorry but anyway I'm not sure but yeah so you walk so in other words what he's doing is
implying that this unnatural condition is a condition that you should be concerned about and
should be addressed in pharmaceuticals right now let's just come down to this world because this
is in another world right because that's maybe a world a little worse than this one in this world
you walk in he wants to diagnose you he puts a cuff on your arm and starts inflating it that puts an
artificial pressure on your arm that if you put on a shirt or a glove or anything that had that
much pressure you would take it off because it creates an unnatural condition on the body like
jamming your toe on the kitchen table at three in the morning that's an unnatural condition so he
puts the cuff on there anyway and you're sitting there because your mom and dad says well he's a doctor
you do what he says so he keeps inflating this so he starts measuring and seeing the pulses between
heartbeats and judging a ratio to tell you you have higher low blood pressure and you believe it
and you believe it's so much that 20 to 30 million of you are taking dangerous toxins to lower that blood
pressure yes yeah okay and they're taking your temperature do you know by the way that
in temperate zones you know north and south of the equator when you have a fever it's hot
but when you're the equator when you have a fever it's cold your actual body temperature
dries you're probably seen it in films people with malaria they're shaking and they're sweating and
they're freezing why is that you see and I'm not going to get into the why but that's a whole that's
more advanced than just a two hour call I mean to our definitely we're we're we're wrapping up this
first hour now okay so boy my brain is just having to cycle through a lot of what you were saying here
and what's going on in this in this current program and try to bring it to a conclusion for us to
move on into the member section and get a bit deeper and basically what what we're pointing out
here is the lack of empirical data that the world deals with and that mostly everyone is listening
to authority and just not ever ever doing any of their own science doing any of their own understanding
trying to logically put together what's going on on planet earth I mean just as one empirical
statement for this conclusion is that there is nothing going wrong around me right now nothing
my life hasn't changed my people around me children are playing in the streets life is very normal
around here I I don't get sick I don't know anyone sick I don't there's nothing here in my empirical
reality to determine that there is something bad happening in the world and I have to reach out I
have to look to the internet I have to look to the world and and then say oh I should be frightened
right now because things are really you know bad oh everything's going wrong right now but yet
my my reality there is absolutely nothing going on there's nothing
no nothing to worry about no fear no scares no nothing and yet the the world has me uptight
without question and yet there's literally nothing in my reality to cause it in many cultures where
they would play a trick on someone let's say walking to town or walking to market they have three
friends separated and the first friend greets the victim and says hey how are you feeling
I'm feeling fine but you don't look so good is this okay I'll see you later then they have the second
friend spaced apart and they see the victim again and he says hey how are you doing today
is I'm feeling okay he says no you're not looking so good and all of a sudden the person starts
doubting it you know he's like well I feel okay and the other guy said it wasn't looking so good
then he walks up to the finally at the end of the road or another stretch of road the other guy
that's the three that are playing the trick on this guy says hey how are you doing this is
I'm okay I think he says yeah you know you don't look good at all and all of a sudden the guy says
you know three people told me I don't feel well so I guess I don't feel well and he goes home saying
I'm sick you see what's going on yes yes so you have the three they have everyone telling you
that you shouldn't be feeling well well how can you feel well you must be insane yeah
yeah welcome to our works yeah it's the power of suggestion you see we don't have a direct
downloads I think we've talked about this in the past we are creatures that require learning and
adaptation for example if you had a puppy dog that was raised by gorillas taken from its mom's
litter and you adopted the dog two years after it was raised by gorillas it would bark like a
regular dog it would chase squirrels and chase a stick like a regular dog it would sit you
wouldn't know was raised by gorillas right but if you gave a three-month-old baby to be raised by
gorillas after two or three years and you brought him home guess what that human's going to act like
it's gonna sit on your table and take a poop right it's gonna act just like a gorilla right why because
that all the animals have downloads and how they should act for example I had a litter of cats and
after you know the kittens after a few weeks after they'd eat they were all stand around and lick
each other they would wash themselves exactly the same way as if they were trained very very methodically
no one ever showed them how to do that right but humans we need downloads and we need schools I mean
there's a school of fish but that's different we so we are subject to external input and we were
made this way and maybe on the second hour or so we're gonna talk about the difference between
making or creating and forming and what you're experiencing right now is not a creation aspect of
society of social engineering but are reforming and what that means and go back to the history of that
all right that sounds really good all right guys so we're gonna we're gonna tie this up right here
and take it into the members section to get much deeper because you know the members they support this
uncensored broadcast the members are the ones that keep us on a free on our own private server so
that we don't have to be concerned about what information we share so that we can bring you whatever
we want and that's a true beauty of having this self-sustaining system here so I want to thank all
the members for being there for us for so long you know there's people have been with me for 15
years and still going I am so thankful for each and every one of you and I hope more of you will
come over and join in check it out get deeper into this knowledge and get so much out of here this is
a very original broadcast that you will find on the worldwide web we don't follow anyone we don't
share the knowledge of that you the common knowledge you get deep here you get you know real new
information around here so thank you all so much and well we will see you next week
(upbeat rock music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]