We're live and recording.
Yes, so...
Hey, what's on your mind?
Well, to let you know, I've got a domain, Rodrigo in the Greek.
Just to, basically, all these, the waiting room recordings that we're doing now will be on that site.
You can also put it on common radio, you know, there's no problem there.
But just to keep it relevant, I suppose.
So, basically, what's coming up is all the kids harping on about Christmas.
I want to discuss the concept of where Santa Claus came from.
What is this whole reason for festive seasons in the original reason, like the very most basic reason for it?
And why do we continue to celebrate it to this day?
Because it's not about Jesus' birth, or Christ, or Mass, or...
You know, I've heard you talk about it before, so where does it stem from?
Okay, well, the reason why it's still going on today is obvious.
And I'm saying that facetiously, is that no one cares and no one's paying attention.
It's a planet of morons, or a planet of apathetic people.
Now, on the other hand, does one understand the timeline of these things?
You know, just to preface, when one starts being objective on any body of information...
Let's say we're going to talk about the divine, the gods, you know, what religious matters are supposed to be based on.
Not what the word religion means, really, because it means to do something regularly.
But people usually subscribe to a conventional religion, tend to change their lives and do things regularly anyway.
But if one starts to actually objectify, let's say, loosely starts to read and comprehend the holy writs of the world.
Whether it's from any indigenous tribe, their writings of ancient things, interaction with the gods, creation and prophecy.
All the way to the major, what I call secular religions, because they are secular.
And then we can swing it back around to show that if people are going to these concepts of religion and spirituality,
if they're secular, well, what does that mean?
Well, they'll tell you that it's always based on tradition and culture, that's just how we do things.
Just like any other industry.
But, again, just to be specific, if one starts to do research and tries to objectify what is memorialized about the gods,
and I'm saying gods because you'll find it plural everywhere.
And we're not talking about the convention King James and Bibles that are put out in version form.
Those are all erroneous.
So what springs forward is all this erroneousness.
But the concept to consider is that when you do look at what's been memorialized about the gods,
it is a very rich body of information, albeit it's them communicating with humanity through written form,
let's say through agents known as prophets and such, in a very simple manner.
And, again, they don't act in futility.
These are meant to be understood.
And all you see is argument about, well, that's your interpretation.
I don't believe that.
You've got it wrong.
So you've got to understand that this type of human nature is very clearly described in these ancient texts also.
So you must consider it.
Now, being kind of long-winded to get to a point, and that is that you will find the information that's memorialized about the gods
and or spirituality and all the other things that are affected by that to be very rich.
But what you hear, and let's just bring it fast forward to contemporary days like today, let's say,
and what you see being discussed is very, very poor across the board.
Now, there are a few people here and there, and none really come to mind that have come through in passing
that I could recommend anyone to go read their writings because, ultimately, they tend to find a golden nugget
and then they wrap it in bullshit.
So it's kind of like a metaphor I give.
You don't want to go, if you're hungry, you don't want to go sifting through somebody's shit to find poo that's undigested to eat.
Even though the corn looks viable, you shouldn't be doing that.
And that's what I see.
And I'll give some examples.
And let's do it a little backwards.
Let's not go to the mainstream convention about knowledge of the spiritual realm and these holidays
and what people consider law form and just knowledge of the gods.
It's all the same, right?
If you go backwards, let's say, look at, let's say, on what they call the internet
or even publications that have been in magazine form or whatever in the past, let's say, several decades,
you have these people crying about these Satanists.
Oh, this is a Satanic cult.
Oh, they're a Satanist.
Oh, they'll tell you they're a Satanist.
Or they have a Satanic church or a Satanic Bible and all that.
That is completely erroneous.
Whether you're a participant or describing that condition, it is erroneous.
That is not Satan, meaning the adversary as memorialized as such.
What these people that are being dubbed as Satanists are, essentially,
and this is objectifying it and this has nothing to do with what you think about it,
but this is the truth of the matter,
all they are doing is reviving some ancient minor imp or demon from ancient cultures,
whether it be Egyptian or Babylonian or even some local geographic position on the planet.
That is not what is known as Satan or the adversary.
You also hear this being expounded by people that sound reasonably intelligent.
And because they seem to say things that are reasonably intelligent, this must be accurate.
This is one of the pitfalls of listening to academically styled presentations.
Because remember that these academics stopped developing at around nine years old.
They've just been trained to sound smart.
There's a very big difference.
They know how to string words together in a way that you would be familiar with hearing in a university lecture.
And then they always tell you that they have some kind of formal education
or been, you know, somehow addressing something along those lines that really keeps the human group,
let's say, in this piss poor quality.
Now, I just mentioned, I'm in no sense defending these people they call Satanists,
just like I wouldn't defend any group, because by any examination, any of these groups are just piss poor.
And you have, again, this is a contemporary thing.
You've heard of, there's a cultural, especially on the conspiratorial or alternative media or alternative discussion.
It's become a topic that does overtake the conversation many times.
This thing about being, you know, the prevalence of Satanism, you hear that.
And it's inaccurate.
And the reason, we'll probably maybe do a discussion on who Satan is and what that means and what the adversary is.
And I would actually send anyone back on YouTube, on Ocelli and the Greek, who is Satan or something.
There was an episode we did about what is Satan or Satanism.
And accurate, right?
So, there's this piss poor thing, you know, on that.
And even, please keep in mind that even the participants of the Satanic culture or whatever are ignorant.
Right, just like you will find the participants of any of the world religions to be ignorant.
And why do I say that?
Because if you subscribe to any of the world religions and you actually start informing yourself,
either from the texts that they allege to subscribe to and or the history or convention of these world religions,
you will, if you are a sane individual, and this is not just a criticism or being sarcastic,
but if you are sane and have any sense of morality, you will abandon that group and be more specific.
Talking about Christianity, Islam, Judaism, Hinduism, Buddhism.
That pretty much covers the majority of what is spread out through the world.
If you are a member of any of those institutions, organizations, faiths, beliefs, whatever you want to call it,
if you start informing yourself, again, regarding what these religions are supposed to be based on,
meaning the texts or the holy writs that they allegedly subscribe to,
and or the history of how what they're doing and what they subscribe to their believers as being the faith came from,
there is no way you can be sane or have any moral aptitude or morality and still adhere to these groups.
It sounds like, Greek, you're being a little harsh.
Well, you know what? It's just a very simple measurement.
And it doesn't mean that if you profess to be a participant or believer in any of these religions,
you need to abandon them just based on that statement.
That is even worse, because now you're aimlessly moving around.
But I assure you, Christianity, Islam, Judaism, Buddhism and Hinduism, the major ones there, and Judaism,
have absolutely no relevancy to the texts that they allegedly subscribe to,
and also have a very high relevancy to anyone that wants to do the work and study why they do what they do
and what they say what they say, and finding out the relevancy and where it came from historically.
And you will find that it is nothing more than several revived, let's say, mishmash of pagan religions
that were geographically based within the areas that these religions still seem to be coming out of.
And these are just very minor, and it's a major distraction.
Greek, why are you saying this?
Well, someone might ask, and I'll say very simple, because you're being censored as a group.
Now, the erroneousness and the piss-poor quality of what humankind is involved in in spiritualism.
I actually did a call yesterday, and one of the co-hosts was proud of being a Wiccan or a witch, or whatever.
And, you know, when you're in public and making conversation, you tend to want to keep the group united.
But, I mean, I really had nothing to say to this person, because the level of lack of discernment,
and the lack of information, and the...
In other words, when someone approaches you and says,
well, I'm a priest, or I'm a witch, or I'm a spiritualist, or I'm a psychic,
you kind of have to... This is good advice, by the way, folks.
You kind of have to shake your head and sit back and say,
this is all for entertainment purposes.
What are you talking about? Are you kidding?
In the state that the world is today, in terms of the quality of these matters,
it is so piss poor that it's just ridiculous.
It's what I call a dummy load.
It's just a load put on you, because you've got a certain energy you want to put off in a certain direction,
and that energy needs to be dissipated.
So you just pick something, and people like it.
I mean, that's what the entertainment business is based on, you know?
The Hello Kitty stuff, and all the...
Sorry for interrupting there, Greg.
The way that I perceive it, it's a little bit like a big marketing campaign between Beta and VHS.
I mean, we've got the shitty quality, and it's marketed as being the right stuff,
but it's actually crap.
The original, the Beta, was supposed to be the better quality.
Yeah, that marketing thing that you just brought, it's kind of a two-way street.
It's what will the people find acceptable,
and then if it teeters and totters within, let's say, two choices,
then it just takes a little bit of the other side to market it and push it in that direction, right?
It's almost like a seesaw that's very close to being balanced.
A four-year-old can push down with their finger and move it.
So there's this teetering and tottering.
But the point that I'm trying to bring up is that the realm,
like you started saying this Christmas thing with Santa Claus and all this.
One must consider that when you, let's say, narrow it down to a topic as such, right?
Because it's the apparent season at this time of year for that.
One must give an overview of the entire condition,
because when someone is listening to, let's say, if we were to go and directly describe
what that symbology is and why they do it and all this,
without giving an overview on how piss-poor the quality of the state of humanity regarding these matters is,
that's why I brought up the trivialness of what they call Satanism, right?
Which is just the revival of these ancient minor imps and demons.
Like the most popular one is what they call the Temple of Set,
and anyone can research this in less than 30 seconds flat.
Set was the dark lord of ancient Egypt.
It was an entity, a demon, a minor one, in ancient Egypt.
I don't know how that can be confused with Satan
any more than Tiny Tim would be confused with Arnold Schwarzenegger, right?
Tiny Tim and the Dickens. It just doesn't make any sense.
In my mind, though, I'm just saying from my observation,
Set is glorified as one of the biggest or the largest entity with the most power,
so that's censored, isn't it? That's censored information.
Misdirected.
It's misdirected and erroneous.
It's unfounded, but this is the nature of how things are.
Then we move forward to the major conventions.
You have all the little tiny other occultic subgroups,
even going down into the Buhiria and Santeria aspects of the Afro-Latin communities in South America and such.
They have their own little deities as well, right?
I think the various Christian spin-offs have other deities that they've either recovered to revive or just flat-out made up.
But it's really hard to make these things up because the multitude of the gods is so massive
that there could be 5,000 of them for each human.
I mean, there's that many, so making them up is not really the issue.
It's that multitude of existence of these things.
But again, I just want to really stress, and I don't know, even if I just dedicate the rest of the hour
to just stress how piss-poor not only the conversation and the imparting of the information
regarding the spiritual world is across the board throughout humanity.
This goes for east to west, north and south across the planet.
One has to just really shake their head before they address anything regarding this.
Again, there is no conversation that I have found viable or reasonable or rational
that is based on anything that is within the spiritual discussion of what holidays are based on,
who the gods are, or these religions or anything.
You will find nuggets and bits of truth here and there.
But now, you don't want to be sifting through poop to eat some corn, do you?
So if you can stomach that, go for it.
There's plenty of places where you can do, for example, go to YouTube and search
The Pagan Origins of Jesus Christ.
And there's a guy up there that throws up a three-hour video.
It's pretty good. It's close. You've got to sift through some stuff.
Or you can do a search on The Pagan Origins of Islam.
Or The Pagan Origins of Christianity.
Or you can write Hinduism and Paganism.
Or Satanism.
And you can start researching what's been memorialized on the internet.
Or go to a library and see it in print form.
And if you want to start sifting through all the poop to find something to eat, you'll be fine.
But otherwise, it's a really difficult subject to stomach at this day and age right now.
But fortunately, that will change.
So again, most people, if you realize, are so lazy.
Not only regarding this topic, but all topics.
The fast food, junk food scenario.
The poor quality of products that industry puts out.
All of this ties in.
Whether it's health or medicine, religion, politics.
I would say the political scene, governmental scene of the world right now is very poor quality.
The legal society that's supposed to manage the law of the nation, very poor quality.
It's just poor quality across the board.
And if you were to do a critique, not just on what we said we might discuss, which is Santa Claus and the origins of Christmas coming up.
But a critique should be levied upon the human society for acceptance.
Across the board.
Now, once you start seeing that humans are readily accepting crap across the board.
Whether it's industrial products.
Things that are based on health and medicine.
Things that are based on law forms and the legal nature of things.
Things that are even in the entertainment business.
I can't watch what's put out in the entertainment industry at large.
I just find it to be absurd and ridiculous.
And it's of quality that it's just substandard.
And this holds true also for their spiritual matters.
Now what's interesting, I'll throw this in, anyone can look this up.
When you bring up spiritual matters, there's a good and evil thing that comes up.
A very simple black and white.
Well, what people fail to realize, and you hear no discussion on.
That many of these ancient writs not only discuss good and evil.
But they also discuss another category that is just as dominant as good and evil.
And it's called worthlessness.
And it actually, let's say if we go to the biblical text.
It is very clear, beyond clear, it is razor sharp.
That the world religions are in the category of worthlessness.
They have no value.
Like Deng, right?
And actually there's many metaphors that are not.
Actually, yeah, they're pretty vile.
Viewed by as the gods.
Now of course, well then what are you saying?
Well the thing that I'm saying is.
The most minor and the most vile of the spiritual entities.
Are the ones that have been dishing this out to mankind.
And this is all just a preface.
This is all a build up to the Santa Claus thing now.
Very often, especially in the western world or eastern world.
Most people now are speaking English.
When the topic comes up.
What is, you know, regarding spirituality.
What is the first thing that they ask?
Or how do they broach the subject?
They say, do you believe in God?
How many times have you heard that?
In your lifetime, right?
And it's everywhere.
This is the most basic, most common question.
Do you believe in God?
Now right there, you've got to stop.
And let's just substitute the word God with the word army.
Do you believe in the army?
Now, the reason I'm using this is to illustrate something.
When you hear the word army.
Do you think of just a single toy soldier sitting there or standing there with a gun or whatever?
Or does that word in its singular form actually represent a multitude?
A multitude of different factions of various armies.
Yeah, or within the army.
When you say, let's say the Australian army or the American army.
Do you think of just one individual?
No, no, a multitude.
Exactly.
So why is it when people ask, do you believe in God?
There is a singular and a plural.
And they tend to just limit it where it's in defiance of everything that's been memorialized about them.
Okay.
Now, let's just tie this in.
Have you ever heard of what they call monotheism?
Yes.
That has really screwed the people up also.
Why?
Because, well, you know, on one side it might be virtually correct.
Where you have to pick a God, right?
Because you can only serve one master.
You've heard that.
Yes.
But on the other hand, what that monotheistic aspect does is in denial of all the others.
Existence.
It doesn't mean you have to believe in them or be a servant to them.
But you're in complete denial.
So either way, again, we go back to what I said a few minutes ago.
Humanity is sick regarding this subject.
And sicker than sick.
Just like, for example, if you were to look at how what's called health care, in parentheses, air quotes,
and medicine is dished out to people in society, you have to be sick to adhere to that.
Because every one of these drugs has a harmful effect and very few have ever been proven to be effective in any of the realms that they profess to be treating.
So they're sick across the board.
Now, let's go back to when someone says, do you believe in God?
Now, what would be the most accurate, relevant, and rational answer to that would be, which one?
Right?
Well, right away, now, someone asks you, do you believe in God?
And you reply with, which one?
You're not even maybe five or six seconds into the conversation.
And I assure you, that ship is sunk right there.
There is nothing else to talk about.
You know?
Yep, because it takes it in a direction that they weren't expecting, and they have got nothing to say when you mention something like that.
They've got absolutely nothing to say.
It's just like when I once was in the shops, and they have these pharmaceutical, like a little pharmacy in the shop,
and there was this old man there, yelling at the pharmacist behind the counter, saying,
I'm going to die if you keep delaying my blood pressure medication.
You know, and he's really getting irate with the clerks, right?
And they're like, you know, telling him, you know, well, we'll have it ready soon.
We just got, you know, the batch in.
We have to sort it out.
And he's yelling at them real irately.
And neither one of them are, I'm off to the side, and I'm thinking, what a pack of morons, because there is no pressure in the body.
There is no blood pressure.
And this guy is actually convinced.
Because if you actually look at the definition of blood pressure, it is a momentary pressure that is measured when the restriction is put on the limb
or the blood vessel between heartbeats to judge, you know, the heart's viability, let's say, right?
It's a very abstract synthetic construct.
There is no pressure, positive pressure in the body at all.
It's under a slight vacuum.
So how do you address, let's say, go back to these morons in public that I just brought up,
the imbecile that is yelling about he's going to die if he doesn't get the blood pressure medication prescribed to him when there's no blood pressure,
and then the other imbecile behind the counter who is a certified, state-certified clerk to dispense prescriptions saying, well, listen, idiot, there is no blood pressure.
Just relax.
So both of them are imbeciles on both sides, right?
That's why very often, let's go back to describing how piss poor and crap the human situation is.
How many times have you heard something put out on YouTube, let's say, or the Internet, which is the easy media, or Internet radio, alternative media,
and even maybe in some mainstream circles, I'm a survivor of a satanic cult, right?
And they give their testimony.
Or I've been around satanists, and this is what they do.
This is the metaphor that I just gave about the clerk behind the counter and the fellow.
So either one of them don't know what they're doing.
In other words, the satanists don't know what they're doing.
Or the person going out and giving testimony about it doesn't really know anything, even though it's clearly in front of them.
They can't communicate it viably.
The people that he was participating with or whatever didn't know.
And the audience doesn't know.
It's all erroneous across the board.
Now, it doesn't mean that a group of people can form a cult or a group, whether recognized or unrecognized,
cannot gather information about how to evoke or invoke or revive a minor imp or demon from the past,
and have that demon, let's say, manifest either amongst them or get them to have the demon manifest other things.
Because it's quite powerful.
I'm not denying that that happens.
Of course that happens.
But the way it's being communicated and the viability and the quality of the information is shit at this point, across the board.
And it's just pathetic.
Now, how does this tie back into Santa Claus?
Well, if you look at Santa Claus and all that, let's just really narrow it down very quickly.
If you were to describe, let's say, the question that we started off with earlier, how does it come about?
How can it be that this is being done in public as such, right?
It's in the shops.
It's in entertainment.
It's done by – it's even government sanctioned, right?
I mean, it's all the way around.
How can it be?
Well, let's start looking at what's going on on the planet today.
You've heard of, like, Ice Age and Bronze Age and Iron Age and all these ages, right?
Well, this is known as the Christian era, the past 2,000 years.
And this is not a religious category.
This is a secular historic category, the Anno Domini, the way the year clock is kept, right?
This is all Christian, quote-unquote, based, you see.
Most of the governments in the world acknowledge it.
And the ones that don't still acknowledge it because they're either allied or do business with them.
So this Christian convention that has been put in, it has been around for about 2,000 years.
Actually, more like 1,700, about 1,500, mostly.
Actually, this type of category that's called Christianity first became prevalent in ancient Assyria around 900 BC.
Now, what do I mean by that without spinning off the conversation?
Anyone can go to a computer and do research on Assyrian, that's A-S-S-Y-R-I-A-N.
Assyrian, not Syrian.
Just do a search. Put in Assyrian king wearing crucifix.
You will see a stone stela, which is a stone carving.
I think it's in the Museum of London or something.
And it's an Assyrian king around 800 or something BC, and he's wearing a crucifix around the neck.
Very much like any conventional, cultural, modern-day Christian does.
Whether it's a rapper on stage or someone in one of these European countries, they tend to wear it as a symbol of their faith.
So that's why I'm saying what you see about Christianity is a cultural, political convention.
It has nothing to do with any specific god at all.
They even tell you there is just one god.
I mean, if that's not a crock, I don't know what is.
So we have a really big problem as a human race.
Now it is so big that you can't see it.
No one can see it.
I mean, it has been seen, and the people that do see it, by the way, and I'm saying no one can see it,
is ultimately when you do see how severe this is throughout the planet,
it should disable one's ability to act on anything about it and just set yourself apart from it.
And the reason I'm bringing up this comment is very clear.
How many times have you heard of alternative Protestant movements and breakaways from the Catholic Church?
And we'll bring up, you know, the Catholic Church is the founder of this in the modern convention.
You hear of all these spinoffs.
I think there's 40 or 50 or even more, 100 spinoffs of Christianity, right?
Okay, well, that's what I mean.
See, these little groups, they said, well, we really don't like this thing, so we're not going to do this thing,
but we're still going to do the rest because we're so...
Like the Anglican and the Protestant and all the various denominations.
So if you want to end up in a group like that or whatever, that's fine.
So now you're not just eating corn out of someone's poop.
Now you just found a piece of carrot, you know?
So it's really, humanity is just in really, really bad shape.
Now, this has nothing to do with the people, though the majority of the people in any group,
everyone wants the same thing regardless what religion you are,
is you want a roof over your head, you want to eat food when your belly is growling,
you don't want to be sick, and if you have children, you want them to be safe.
This is the commonality of everyone on the planet.
And people that typically pursue those things in some virtuous way, with some moral standard,
are to be considered as roughly good people, in air quotes, right?
How many people like that, or good, quote-unquote, people, consider themselves to be Christian?
Many.
How many, quote-unquote, good people consider themselves to be followers of Islam?
How many consider to be Buddhists?
Many.
Many, you know, in air quotes now, generally people that seemingly behave,
are considered, through their behavior and intent, good people.
When they have been joined through, you know, in this convention of modern religion,
or even ancient religion, they don't know what's going on.
They're just doing it to get along.
And within these groups, there's always a reformist group, right,
that says, we're better, and they'll make some...
They drag a group of these people over, right?
They drag them over, and then, you know, whether it's, you mentioned a few, and there's more,
I mean, there's many, we could spend the next hour just mentioning the list.
And any religion.
So we have a very, very big problem.
And the common denominator with all of these religions,
is the quality of the information is so low,
that it almost drives the information into irrelevancy.
What it's based on is conventions, tradition, and behavior
that has been in place for thousands of years,
even before the inception of these quote-unquote faiths.
So what would have been...
Now, just to go back to the Santa Claus thing,
if you actually look in what they call the United States of America,
you mentioned the Christmas,
that was considered illegal and unlawful up until the early or mid-19th century.
It was considered immoral.
The actual...
Now, whether you want to call it Saturnalia, or Christmas, or the Solstice, or whatever,
there was enough information about what that meant,
what that symbolized, whether it was working on the calendar,
the actual festivities, or the intent behind it,
was just unlawful and illegal, in what they call America.
I'm not sure about the European history on that,
because they had an emperor up until the early 19th century,
the late 18th century, that made sure these kept going.
But I would say that shortly after that early 19th century period,
it was brought in by some of the northeastern states,
and it became more traditional and more...
Now, I think around...
There is an identity crisis regarding what's called St. Nicholas and Santa Claus,
and how it's personified,
and various other, let's say, all the way from Nordic Druid cultural aspects of it,
known as Woden or Odin, have been mixed in.
And then you go down and look at the Proto-Canaanite, Phoenician, Babylonian entities of Moloch thrown in.
It's this morphing.
But if you actually look at it,
it is a revived Moloch worship,
or a revived Odin worship.
That would be the northern versus the southeastern part of culture,
southeastern being the Proto-Canaanite, Phoenician, Babylonian,
and the northern would be, let's say, the Celtic Nordic, northern Europe,
and western Europe, the god Odin.
And let's just throw in a little bit of smattering here and there.
Let's start maybe with the...
Do you want to start with the top left corner or the bottom right?
The bottom right being the Middle Eastern or the top left being the European origin of these things.
Let's try the European.
Okay.
Odin. This is loose because now, just like, for example,
let's just bring back the Christian thing.
There's like 14... People say, are you denying Jesus Christ?
Greek. And I'm like, no.
Do you believe in Jesus Christ? Greek.
And I say, no.
And they're like, well, what are you doing?
I'm like, well, you don't understand.
So you have to be more specific because there's about 14 Jesuses that I've seen in popular culture.
Right?
You see one that tells you, if you don't believe me, you go to hell.
You know, the followers.
And the other one says, oh, you can do anything you want.
It's all been forgiven.
Right?
And then you've got, you know, one group says, well, you know, this is how he died.
This is when he was born.
One group says he's black.
The other one says he's white.
The other one says he's Asian.
Well, which one?
Which one are you talking about?
You know, I'm confused already.
Right?
But none of them are biblical.
Zero.
So when we discuss Odin, we have to bring this up as well.
There's various traditions that have personified that character.
But let's just tie it back in for the discussion that we see how people might define what they're saying and doing regarding the Odin myth or the Odin explanation.
Like, for example, real quick, Odin, this is, anyone can start researching, or Woden.
I'll just make it short.
See, Woden, he was omniscient.
He knew what everyone was thinking and what everyone was doing.
And he flew through the sky with stag horned creatures occasionally.
And he rewarded the good and punished the bad.
And the way you worship Odin is by bowing down to a tree because trees are made of Odin.
You know, Woden?
Yep, yep.
Yep.
So this is part, a small part of it.
So you have some of the personification there of this bearded whatever, you know, it's a mishmash of stuff.
So the way that I can perceive it, it's like bits of this and there, here and from, and an amalgamation of different ideologies and different bits and pieces.
And then wrapped up in a lapsang and call it Christmas and Santa Claus and the Christmas tree.
Yes, yes.
It's kind of like, again, going back to, it might sound distasteful, but I'll keep using this metaphor.
If you're hungry and you want to pick corn out of somebody's poo, you might find a piece of carrot or pea in there partially digested also.
Right?
You see, it's really crap.
But here, let's continue maybe.
You ever notice how in the Christian convention they have, jokingly I'm just going to say that because what they're doing is an absolute joke, what they call Bible study.
You ever notice that conventionally they do it on what they call Wednesday?
They always do their Bible, across the planet.
Why?
Because, see Wednesday is not really Wednesday, it's Odin's day or Woden's day.
So they have to still do it on Woden's day, you see.
These are ridiculous, I mean, stuff.
This is just, the quality is so low of what is, in other words, what people regard as their faith and their culture and tradition and their God is so, the quality of it is so low across the board in humanity right now.
That it's just, actually, I feel actually ill, like I want to take a shower just thinking about what humanity is involved in right now.
All the way from the inaccuracies of calling those that have revived some minor imp or demon from ancient times Satanists, actually gives Satan a bad name, which he already has anyway.
But all the way to what they consider to be their venerated rites and rituals, which is so low that I don't know how anyone can really want to pursue and describe this culture without stooping down so low and just crawling on the ground.
This is your fellow man, folks.
This is where either you've been or where you are or the general state of humanity at this point.
It's just so pathetic.
Now, it doesn't mean that I don't want to speak bad about Odin worshippers.
There probably is a group that has stayed true to that cult or that particular, that is their master, that God.
Now, I'm not sure, I haven't done enough research on Odin to have discovered if he has been killed yet.
Now, yes, you heard me right.
The gods can be killed as well.
So, I'm not really up to date on what Odin, if there has been a declaration formally that he was eliminated from the existence or he's still around.
So, yes, I know it sounds kind of crazy to most to hear this.
But, you know, so there, okay, so that's the northwest corner or the northwestern part of, let's say, what's called the Satanic or tradition.
And also they say he comes from the North Pole.
You notice that's why I said maybe let's pull it from there first and add that as well, right?
Yes.
Flying through the sky.
Now, you want to jump down to the lower, you know, the Mesopotamian region, the Proto-Canaanite, Proto-Phoenician?
Well, that ties in also to the metaphor of what do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common, right?
Where the priests then had made the decision to, and inspired by these imps and demons, by the way, to have their followers sacrifice children to these lords.
That's why even today in the Christian convention you worship what?
Who?
The Lord.
The Lord is a very, it's a ball.
And it's just amazing.
Again, remember, to get into any more detail I feel it makes me very unnerved because it's a very low level of existence, a very low level.
It's vile in its most, probably most optimistic sense of describing it is actually a very vile thing to discuss.
How people have been enthralled in participating in these conventions and traditions.
They're just all vile.
Can I just interrupt there?
What is the purpose of continuing to subscribe to these faiths or worshipping, like Christmas?
What's the point of Christmas other than the default for me is the capitalism of trying to get money from the people and just full gifts and stuff.
I mean, does it provide any energy to the worship or celebration?
Yeah, it's a dummy load.
I've done a show on Ocelian Greek also regarding the dummy load.
What I mean by a dummy load is as living beings we have energy that builds up in the body or in the mind.
And we have to expel it, you know?
That's why people say I'm going for a run or even a sexual energy, right?
They have to, it has to be discharged.
You know, hunger is an energy and it's discharged when you put food in the stomach.
We build up energy as living beings, right?
It's chi, prana, you know, it builds up in us.
And if we don't release it, it can cause harm.
Okay.
So is it like a global ritual of some sort then?
Everybody focusing on the same day and then there's a release.
Yeah.
So maybe let's go back to the Eastern side.
I brought up the cannibals' birthdays and dolls and such.
But the Moloch, let's just bring up Moloch.
People were told to make a wish of prosperity and offer the child to, by placing the child on the seat or the lap of a bronze statue.
It typically had the head of a man, a goat, an eagle, a bird or some other animal.
It might have been human as well.
And this statue had been red hot because it either had a hearth within it or a hearth below it.
And the child was placed in its lap and seared alive.
And what you were able to see is a large red colored object with a baby or a young child placed in its lap searing alive.
And this was not done in private like many of the ways that people are suggesting human sacrifice is done today.
You know, in the basements of old court buildings or banks or hospitals or out in Bohemian Grove or whatever they might suggest, right?
And hint, hint, I've actually just brought up some of the things that anyone might want to research.
But this was done in the public, openly.
And if you wanted a wish of prosperity and you didn't want to sacrifice the child that was of your own, you just purchased one.
They had plenty of children that the poor supplied the providers of children.
And you will find this society was prevalent in the Old Testament, right?
And that's why the, I think we made a discussion, might have been maybe in another interview or discussion,
why people can never understand why the Israelites were told to go in and kill everything.
Because these people would not change these habits, you know?
Just like today, how many times have you heard of people say, well, this is what I believe and I will believe that to the death, right?
Well, guess what? You keep saying stuff like that, you just might be accommodated, you know, someday, right?
So, yeah, and they were back then.
So it was open to the public and this was common day practice.
Oh, yeah, it was common day.
Yes, and it was even on a non-common day as something that was an observance, it was even more prevalent.
I mean, they would probably do a few thousand children in a day like that, right?
And also, just bear in mind that when you're in the public square, you're having conversation, you're doing business,
you're getting along how people get along in public.
It's very unnerving, even though you've accepted this as being, you know, part of your culture,
it's very unnerving to hear a child being burned alive.
It's a blood-curdling scream, I would imagine, right?
Because it doesn't happen instantly, I'm sure it would take more than a few seconds or a few minutes.
And the child being conscious within, unless they clubbed them, I don't know how really they did it.
Maybe they made them unconscious or whatever, but there was the potential of screaming.
So what they had was they had bells ringing to drown out the screams.
That's why you see the bells on churches, that's why ringing consistently,
that's why you see the thing called jingle bells on the slate.
It's all been incorporated, you see.
So do you feel like you're eating corn out of someone's poop?
Because I sure do when we're discussing this kind of stuff, right?
To a certain degree.
Because again, how many times have you heard of censorship or things being hidden?
Any accurate records depicting these events have been absconded from public view, by the way.
So this sort of information is hidden away from everyone to try and find it,
unless they actually go digging and looking for it.
Yes, in its whole form.
So the only way to do it is by very good detective work here and there a little,
just like when an assailant performs a crime, he tries to cover it up, right?
By cleaning up the body or tracks or whatever, right?
But there's always going to be, let's say the forensic investigator might actually find some traces.
Sequel kernels.
Yes, a fiber, a footprint, something.
Corn kernels, yes, unfortunately in this case.
This is a really rotten subject.
And by the way, anyone who does a little bit of research,
they will also discover that the gods look down on what humanity is doing.
The hypocrisy of anyone to say that my faith is better or your faith is not is just ridiculous
because they're all in the shit, big time, all of them.
And the ignorance, now what's good about this is the ignorance of this will be lifted in the future.
Because you've got to realize there's three truths to this matter.
The truth, the basic truth, which is what the people believe in,
they don't know it, they just believe in it because it's convenient.
When someone puts something in front of you, just pick one and go,
that's what they do or it's within their family.
The second truth is a smattering of how to administer the public that believes this, right?
The second truth would be, let's say if you're a priest, an imam, a rabbi, a guru,
you have to know a little bit about not only what these morons were told to believe,
but you also have to know how to administer it, keep control of them.
Because they're going to come to you on holidays,
you're going to have someone that might seem radical and question it, how do you answer?
You're going to have to have a pretty firm understanding on how the society is based on this,
to administer these idiots, right?
That's the second truth.
And usually when you get to the second truth, when you're having, let's say,
a conversation with a rabbi or an imam or a priest, a pastor, a minister,
not some of them, all of them,
or a guru from the eastern sides, or one of those monks,
they're very easy to confound, by the way, because none of them,
I mean, remember, they're just there because it's the way they make their living, right?
But they have to be able to defend what they're doing.
And also they all defend it in a very, very simple manner that's beyond childish
and almost arrogantly stupid.
But once you start getting to that point, they also have to have access to enforce their position,
where they usually, when you start asking questions regarding why are they doing what they're doing,
where did they get it from, and do they know what they're doing,
they tend to go purely emotional, and then they come in and basically say,
how dare you ask me what I'm doing, I have all these believers,
and there's a billion believers or whatever, how dare you, right?
So they have to know how to keep that administrative position through some,
a little bit more truth, when I say about how these things are to be administered.
Now the third, at the top, is the reality of it all.
And once you get to that point, you realize that the other truths are basically
picking corn out of someone's poop, right?
And you don't want anything to do with it.
That's why I really frown down upon, there are people that actually make a living
or make concerted effort to either write books, magazines, or go on radio or television or whatever
and expound how bad Christianity is.
And you gotta do X, Y, and Z, or A, B, and C.
Or other people do the same thing about Islam.
Don't even bother.
Why would you even go to that level?
Because the situation of the human spirit right now is so poor,
that you'll just either end up forming a cult or you'll just be squashed out.
Now let me just throw something in here.
Because we started off asking about Santa Claus and the second part was me bringing up how piss poor the information is.
And the first example I gave was how people are touted as being Satanists and all this, right?
When you start to examine how they're explaining and how they're describing things,
when you actually look at this entity known as Satan, this spirit being,
this is a fact folks, and this is not something you're allowed to make up or believe in.
You have to go look these things up.
This entire world culture, whether it's religious, yes,
let me just be very clear, Christianity, Islam, Hinduism, Buddhism, and Judaism
is under the auspices of Satan.
So when you say Satanism, right away you have to be more specific.
Because when you say Satanism, I'm thinking, are you talking about Christianity?
Are you talking about Judaism?
That's what I'm thinking.
Are you talking about which form of Satanism?
Because all...
You see, Satan doesn't mess around with a bunch of little guys wearing funny eyebrows and black robes
in the church of Satan with an upside down cross.
He doesn't move around that way.
What he does, he takes control of the major institutions.
So if you're planning on having a discussion about Satanism, please be specific.
Are you speaking about Christianity, Islam, Hinduism, Buddhism, or Judaism?
Which one? Please.
The second thing is not only is Satan in control of all of the religions,
the main religions of the world,
he's in control of your entertainment industries,
your circuses, which is your church,
your films, your theater.
He is also in control...
Not some little high school play, or little small film,
but the entire industry, right?
The core, the power base.
He's in charge of all of your political systems.
So it doesn't matter if you're in Washington, D.C.,
or in London, or Moscow, or Athens, or anywhere,
okay?
He's in charge of all of your judicial aspects.
He is in charge of...
It has been given to him by the Most High
to have authority and control over all of your major institutions.
He doesn't petty and play around with some little group.
Or individuals.
At all.
There are minor imps and demons that do that.
Now, if there hasn't been anything more accurate than that said,
I don't know what.
Because this is about as accurate and as precise and as true
as this topic can be explained.
So, now, here's the thing, Rodrigo,
just between you and I right now,
and I know this is recorded and going to be put up,
let's say, on YouTube,
how many people listening to this are able to walk away
with information they could actually use?
And if the answer is zero, that is correct.
Because where and who are you going to go to tell this to?
Be mocked in the process, if you try.
So they're going to give you a mouth shot.
Even the most alternatively based,
knowledge, quote-unquote, seeking individual
will not be able to handle this information
because he'll turn to the person next to him and say,
that sounds too radical.
You know why it sounds too radical?
Because it's true.
Anyone can research and look into...
The amount of time that you're spending listening to what I'm saying,
using a keyboard or whatever,
you can actually look up and validate everything that I'm telling you.
If you go to the source, like if you, for example,
how many times have you heard people use things out of the Bible
but they do not use the biblical definition?
How many times have you heard people say,
oh, the number 666 is satanic?
No, it's not.
It's not.
No?
Well, what are you making up there?
Oh, that's the Antichrist over there.
That president...
No, because the Bible is very clear on defining who the Antichrist is.
Or this is, you know, that's the apocalypse.
Well, you know, I don't know.
What do you mean by apocalypse?
Because the Bible defines it.
So what they're doing is they're taking catchphrases
out of a certain body of work,
and they're not using the definitions that are within that body of work
to define it.
They're making up the definition for it.
Yeah.
They're collecting the scores.
Yeah, they are.
They're really, really bad.
And this goes across the board on the internet.
You have a lot of people saying they're, you know,
alternative researchers or academics, let's say,
that are mainstream and alternative, let's say.
You have religious people, religious scholars.
They're all in the shit right now.
And this is why you and I are saying what we're saying.
And I've said this publicly before,
and that's why the numbers are so against the individual
that discovers what is going on on this planet
that it's almost disabling.
Not disabling where you're going to be, you know,
sitting in the middle of the floor in a pile of poop,
but disabling where you really shouldn't do anything about it
other than separate yourself from it, quietly.
Because the people on this planet are wicked and vile and evil.
But fortunately, they're wicked, vile, and evil in a juvenile sense.
They lack the maturity to develop that wickedness, that vileness, and evil.
What I mean by they're juvenile in that way is if they want to get something...
Kindergarten stuff, yes.
They have to go, if they're going to act,
if the masses are going to act on anything or approach on something,
they always go to the entitled classes.
In other words, they're so juvenile that if they have a legal issue,
oh, I've got to find an attorney,
because of course I don't know how to read or know anything about it.
I spent 12,000 hours in public school
and not even have one hour on how the legal system works.
I'm fine with that.
I'll go hire a moron to tell me what to do.
Just like with the body.
Oh, I'm not feeling well.
Oh, you've got to go see a doctor.
How can someone else tell you about what's going on in your own body?
When it comes to spirituality, you've got to go find whatever.
Whatever entitled authorities in whatever realm you've been suckered in to be part of the faith of.
And yes, you are suckers.
Smokers are suckers too.
People say, are you smoking?
No, I'm sucking.
The cigarette smoking.
Smoking hurts, because when there's smoke, there's fire.
So the thing here is this.
There is no audience for what is being said here.
This is maybe revelatory, meaning exposing the reality that anyone can look at.
But there's no fun in being accurate, Greek.
There's no fun in being precise.
That's your truth.
That's your viewpoint, you see.
It doesn't resonate with me.
Yeah, it doesn't resonate with me.
Yeah, just go for it, man.
That's why the purpose of knowledge is in itself initially to get the information.
You don't have to act on it.
But if you are going to put energy into anything to act on anything,
it better be setting yourself apart, learning how to pull yourself apart first.
Right?
It's kind of like if you're going out in the woods and you're looking for bears,
before you start doing that, you better learn how to climb trees real well.
Right?
You better make sure you can do that.
Because you want to set yourself apart from the bear occasionally.
You don't want to go out there touting this particular episode and say that you know,
and try to separate yourself from everyone and touting it,
because you're going to get stomped on.
Well, you're going to get stomped on, but here's the thing also.
Have you heard of like, do the right thing?
Now, what is the right thing?
Well, everyone says, well, that's my opinion on what's right or wrong.
There seems to be through the ages a saying or a feeling that has gone through that says,
you should, if you know the truth, speak it, do it, say it.
Right?
Just put it out there.
If it is true, it will stand on its own.
Now, what I'm discussing here is not what I believe.
What I'm discussing here is what I've discovered and it is a rock solid report.
My belief is personal and private.
Now, what I mean by that is beliefs always have to be based on things that are going to happen.
If you believe just blanketly on something and it's not founded, you're an idiot.
And this is typically the category of your typical surface dwelling earth inhabitant.
They don't need any proof of anything.
Because somehow they've been convinced of that.
When I say my belief is private and personal, it's because the beliefs are constantly changing.
If I get a note from someone saying they're sending me a grand in American credit currency tomorrow,
well, between the time when I get the message and when I get it, there is a factor of belief there.
There are so many beliefs that we operate on.
The weather forecast is a belief.
Hey, looks like it might rain tomorrow.
So between now, when I've found out the information, and when it rains, I'm operating in belief, aren't I?
So if it doesn't rain tomorrow, that was a false belief.
And if it does rain, okay, it is a true belief, a good belief.
All of your religions in the world that are based on faith with morons that are participating is unfounded, baseless.
Don't even bother engaging them on that.
Because it's just worse than a baby vomiting chocolate pudding.
The reality of what is memorialized in their texts is very simple.
That the gods exist, the gods do things, and to prove that the gods do things,
they're going to tell you what they do before they do it, and that's what your belief is hinged on.
I've had actually the worst of the older people because, you know, why?
Because if you do something wrong five times, you might be able to, you know, turn around.
But if you do something wrong 500,000 times, you've already facilitated it, and it's the only thing you know.
That's why the older people are worse when it comes to this.
I've actually had conversations with an old Catholic man, and I brought up certain points in the biblical texts.
Like, you know, you really, if you read the Bible every day, and you spend an hour on it every day,
how about maybe spending 45 minutes on it, and just 15 minutes looking at an interlinear,
we actually see what was really supposed to be translated into English versus what.
You know what, Greek? I really don't need that, because I'm fine with that.
I just believe that I'm getting the truth in the King James.
When any moron in less than five minutes can easily pull up an interlinear anywhere in the Bible
and see that within a few verses is at least a half a dozen mistakes from the original text, right?
Anyone can do that very quickly, very rapidly.
There's even harsh criticism on what's been put, but no one cares.
So this old man, what did he say?
Oh, basically, I don't really care.
I just, because I believe in it, there's no mistakes in it, you see.
That's why I tell the young people, you have no future around this.
You know, years ago you were supposed to look up to the older people, right?
See, that's why people don't understand what's going on around them.
That's why they're stuffing all these old codgers into nursing homes.
Years ago, the older people were regarded as being wiser.
So, well, let's just say.
And now, what are they doing?
Oh, they're getting old.
Stuff them into a nursing home.
Fill them up with drugs, right?
Because they're worthless.
They have no value.
In the culture, tradition, and the gods say they do.
But the actuality of the matter is they have no value anymore.
Listen to them.
And, of course, there's an exception.
It's very hard to meet any.
But just look around, you know, whether you have family or relatives or friends or associates.
Go up to these old people that have been on this planet for either twice as long as you or much longer than you.
And ask them any of the questions that are actually relevant to reality.
About things like, maybe you might hear the Greek talk about.
And watch how quickly you'll see they recede back to the mind of a nine-year-old ignorant.
So, this is the, you know, are you paying attention?
What is going on?
These old people are being stuffed into the garbage can, basically known as a nursing home or whatever, for a reason.
Because the gods don't approve of it either.
There is no way you could see what's going on on this planet, whether you consider it good or bad, without the gods interfering.
So, what do you mean about that?
Well, let's tie it back, you know, with the Santa Claus.
Where is the interference with the gods with Santa Claus?
Right?
Very clear that revived aspects, Santa Claus specifically, I would tie it in, being that it's red, fat, and a child placed under its lap,
would be more of the proto-Canaanite, Phoenician, Babylonian, Moloch.
Right?
Seated creature.
And the rest of the Santa Claus meme, you might want to throw in the Wodenism.
Ties in very deeply to Christianity.
Those that are supposedly active Christians, what do they do?
They go on Bible study, when?
On Woden's day.
Right?
His day.
Now, the other thing is, you know, there's the, let's say Phoenicians are a northern part of ancient Israel, you'll find memorialized in the Biblical text.
There was Baal of the Grove, the Lord of the Trees.
And it's interesting how they put the presents underneath the Christmas tree.
How do you get them from underneath?
You kneel down, don't you?
So, if someone were watching this at a distance, they're not looking at you trying to get a present from under the tree.
They see you doing what?
Bow down.
Kneeling down.
It doesn't matter why you're kneeling down, as long as you get on your knees.
You ever watch some of these sci-fi films, where this, you know, supposedly an authoritative alien comes in, or something,
and they get all the subjects to bow down, or kneel down,
and if you don't want to, the guards will hit you on the back of the knee with a club, but you can do it anyway.
Stargate.
Yeah, right, there you go.
It doesn't matter if you want to do it or not.
It's that you are kneeling.
You're in the proper position.
Submissive.
Is that right?
Yes.
Being in the submissive position, and basically giving all authority to the person you're bowing down to.
Right, and it also makes it very convenient for the person you're bowing down to to do what they like,
because if they were to do a quick move on you, you really can't move that fast when you're on your knees.
That's right.
Okay?
Now, all this stuff might sound negative.
I'm telling you, we've discussed the most positive side of it.
That's why we're making all of the world's religions akin to picking corn out of someone's poop.
Now, it doesn't mean that the text...
Here's the complicated part.
It gets complicated, and the average surface-dwelling human inhabitant, or whatever you might want to call it,
lacks the aptitude or the skill or even the desire or the bravery to go into this direction,
and spend time and look at what these religions, their texts, are allegedly based on.
Right?
If you look at the various Sanskrit writings, you might go in the Eastern cultures,
and you come across all the way through the middle.
You might want to look at Hebrew and Arabic, and what's called the Koran in the Old Testament,
or the biblical texts, or in the Christian meme.
You might want to look at what's called the New Testament, Old Testament, and all that.
How many people have actually found a holistic foundation in these texts?
None.
You can't.
It's impossible to be sane and pursue these things with no understanding of what's in the text,
because I've said this previously, that pretty much what these religions are doing in practice
is in the forbidden or abominations list.
It doesn't matter which religion it is.
You'll find this to be true.
And that's why it's so disabling to do this, because who are you going to talk to about this?
It doesn't matter.
No one wants to hear it.
It's the bizarreness of it.
And when I say religion, religion just means things you do regularly.
Now, it's gotten so discounted.
Thankfully, from one perspective,
if you speak to most people, regardless of what religion they're in,
most people, actually,
and you start questioning their faith,
putting in quotation marks,
within 30 seconds to 3 minutes of the conversation,
they almost self-profess.
The only reason they profess that faith is because either their parents did,
and they're not really into it.
Oh, I'm not really religious, even though I'm Christian.
I don't really know anything about it, really.
I'm just okay with going along, you know?
This is 99% of the quotable faith.
It accommodates their current lifestyle,
because if they chose a different faith or religion,
they'd have to change what's where they're complacent on.
Maybe not even.
They conduct their lives like they're staring at a government form.
You know, like, check your name, what sex, which religion.
Just check the box.
So, yeah, you know, I'm Christian,
but I just need to check that box and get over it.
I really don't need to know anything about it.
Or, how dare you, Greek?
That's what I believe in, and that's good enough for me.
Here's an example.
Every Christian, bar none,
when you corner them and say,
hey, how come you're doing A, B, C, or D,
or don't know about A, B, C, or D, or X, Y, and Z,
they, within, again, 30 seconds or 3 minutes,
just about every time, there's a spirit behind this,
what they will do is renounce the text that the religion is based on.
The majority of them will start saying to you,
well, who knows who wrote the Bible anyway, and who cares?
I don't need a Bible anyway, to base it on.
Oh, so what are you basing it on, Walt Disney?
But you don't engage these people, because they're insane.
You know?
The same thing with Islam.
If you start engaging them, hey, why are you doing this,
why are you saying, oh, well, you know, what you're telling me,
they all say this,
what you're telling me can't be in the Koran,
because the Koran was written to be simple.
And they'll say, oh, well, you know what,
I have a copy right here, let's go take a look at it.
Oh, no, no, no.
That copy is not the one that we have in the mosque.
No, no, no.
That can't be good.
This is like across the board, man.
So, for example, if you speak to a Christian,
and they renounce the Bible in 30 seconds or 3 minutes,
and it happens once, it happens twice,
it happens three times, it happens a hundred times,
no matter who you're talking to across the planet,
you're like, wow, there is a spirit behind this
that has tied all these people together like the Borg, right?
In Star Trek.
Where there's this collective that they've been captured into,
and what might that spirit be sourced from?
Yes.
The great adversary known as Satan.
What makes him great is the magnitude of his influence.
That's how Satan connects to these people,
by sending in that thread like the Borg.
I guess they had a tube in your neck or something,
and there was a mainframe that was broadcasting.
So go ahead, Rodrigo.
So, yeah, no, just what I learned today is,
in summarizing all of the world's institutions,
whether religious, judicial, is all orchestrated or founded
upon the adversary or Satan, right?
Yes.
So if you say you're a Christian,
which is supposed to be non-Satanistic,
is the very thing that you're adhering to,
which is the Satan influence created?
Oh, and actually more so because this is known secularly
as the Christian era.
In other words, the entire world is dominated by the Christian era.
When I say the Christian era, this is the academic worldview.
And most of these people are atheists anyway,
but they still use it.
So you would see that as the chief,
and some people might say, as the chief religion of the planet,
some people might say, well, that's the Western,
the Eastern is, you know, other.
And I say, well, no, actually, from an academic marking,
the worldview is considered a Judeo-Christian ethic,
which none of it is based...
Yeah, so if someone says they're in Islam,
that is 100% also under that control,
because it is a major religion.
This is not the time to expound the truth.
I mean, look at your...
Let's just change the subject for a moment.
How many physics departments are there
throughout the world in university?
Many. Every country, every city probably has a college of some sort.
And they're all talking about what?
The atom and electrons and protons.
Now, hold on. All of them, right?
You know there's no such thing as an electron or a proton or such, right?
This is a made-up construct.
It's a mathematical equation that they think is the basis of them.
Yeah. And they talk about it like it's physical.
So are they all insane? Absolutely.
But are they prevalent everywhere? Absolutely.
Does that make them true and correct? No, it doesn't.
This is the state of humanity, and that's why I say it's disabling.
If you find out the truth, if you've got all this pent-up energy,
don't necessarily keep it to yourself.
You might want to talk about it somewhere publicly.
But spend the time separating yourself from the rest of it.
Insulate yourself. Learn how to bring humor.
So when a moron comes up to you and starts talking about electrons and protons,
learn how to bring humor into the situation, and then disembark.
Because if you start engaging these idiots with the reality of things,
they begin to get a look in their eye like they want to bring physical harm to you.
And then you should learn how to read those things.
If you start discussing anything with a Christian in person,
start to read their body language.
Because they actually start getting to the point where they want to bring bodily harm to you.
Have you ever heard of burning at the stake?
Witch hunts or whatever? Yeah, yeah.
Okay, same thing. If you're in court over a traffic ticket,
you'll see the guy in the black dress behind the tall thing there, podium.
He has a look in his eye that looks like he's ready to bring physical harm to you.
You better learn how to read these subtle things.
You could even be in bed with your loved one, bringing this up.
You better learn how to read their body language when they're looking,
because they want to bring physical harm to you when you broach these subjects.
This is very important. That's what I mean by set apart.
Not only in your thinking, but in your physical reality.
In my experience, a long time ago, the reason why I detached mainly from major religions
is I had a group of friends. One was Christian, one was Muslim.
Actually, a couple were Christian. And we used to go night clubbing.
But you know what they used to do on the Friday night?
The Christian would remove the cross from his neck,
and my Muslim friend would remove the insignia for Islam.
He had a ring. He'd take it off. Then they'd go night clubbing and take drugs.
And I'm like, the hypocrisy. I was very young then.
I was like, that's disgusting. That's disgusting.
They'd be Christian every day, and then they'd go clubbing and take drugs.
Here's the thing. Fortunately, yes, it seems like hypocrisy,
but it really isn't, because they don't know enough about what they're doing
to actually be hypocritical about it. They're actually just ignorant.
They're just taking up space, going through actions and acting on impulse.
In other words, they took up Islam and Christianity based on impulse or convenience,
and they're going clubbing and doing drugs based on what? Impulse and convenience.
So these are people whose lives are based on impulse and convenience.
Do you really want to go out in public and start trying to convey anything
that even approaches the truth to people who are spurred on to action by impulse and convenience?
The answer there, the rational answer is absolutely no.
There's only a very small group of people anywhere in any generation
during mankind that are actually worthwhile speaking to you.
It is worthy to speak to everyone, but I think we just gave a few reasons
why maybe you shouldn't.
Okay. Well, Greg, it's gone 15 minutes past the hour.
I wanted to wrap this up for today.
We spoke of a lot of truths, and not perceived truths, not my truth or your truth,
but the way it is. And just to summarize, we've discussed about Santa Claus
and the reason why it's a mishmash of various ancient, I suppose, rituals and gods.
We've established that there's not just a god, some monotheistic,
but that's the denial of other gods.
And yeah, I think we've covered quite a lot of track here.
So I wanted to thank you, Greg, for joining us on The Waiting Room on Rodrigo and the Greek.
And yes, you'll find this episode and others on Uncommonradio.com
as well as Rodrigoandthegreek.com.
Okay, man. Thanks. We'll do it again soon.
Yes, for sure. Bye-bye.