Still sound like you're coming out of a can or something, but that's all right. How are you? Are we recording?
Yeah, we're recording the live on the third installment of Rodrigo and the Greek
Rodrigo and the Greek in the waiting room waiting room. Yeah. Yeah
All right. Yeah, we haven't had a large attendance on the other two, but enough
I think the attendance that's there people are really ready for what's being said, especially when there's this voyeuristic approach
You know when we're just having a conversation. So what's on your mind? It's been a little while
And we had one inquiry about you know, are we going to do this again? And apparently we are so
Any thoughts anything you want to get into? No, I wanted to let you have the lead
Nothing's really been on my mind or anything. It's a terrible actually everything in this world is not the way it seems
So I don't know what we could start. I mean, I was gonna say happy new year, but in relation to who?
So it's not it's uh, we talked a little bit about keeping the time what the calendars for
It's a memoir memorization of events. Yes, right
But the thing is, is it lawful? It's not done lawfully and it hasn't been for almost a thousand plus years if not more
what I call
affectionately or
Disaffectionately the Pope's work schedule is just that it's for powerful subjects and it's not lawful meaning
nothing natural nothing in creation
Goes by that timekeeping other than the Pope subjects
Okay, so I mean there that's about as clear and succinct as it to I mean, I've got nothing against the Pope
I mean, it's all it's ridiculousness
If you put a pile of ridiculousness on one side and reality and lawfulness on the other
99 out of a hundred people will pick the ridiculousness
So who am I to say who what people are going to pick and choose, you know, but beyond making choices
what it is is
It's thoughtlessness
worthlessness and debased
Listen, it's lawlessness
So so how can people you know start?
Prejudicing
Their woes and their blame on certain groups, you know
I was having a conversation with someone recently about how the majority of the people on the alternative media and internet have fallen
for a bunch of nerds
that sit back and write up websites about Illuminati and
Certain individuals and certain agendas and they've got everyone in a tizzy where the basic the basic reality is we're here to
Prosper be healthful be healthy and
You do that through good company good food and good drink and hit the part of the conversation
Which you might find funny or not is that these nerds that sat back, you know
It doesn't or two dozen years ago to write up all these conspiracies, which I'm not saying they don't exist
But to escalate them to the point as a focal point of interest and discussion
If you were to visit these nerds that wrote this up they couldn't even prepare a boiled egg for you
They're they're not very they're not very skilled at what it takes to be human. Mm-hmm. They probably couldn't help you fix your car
They probably don't know how to clean they probably don't even know how to dress
So, you know, this is what's going on and it's why because it's worthlessness that mankind chooses to be
occupied or preoccupied
with and
Hey to each his own, but what happens is when you're completely surrounded with it now to each his own becomes
To your own self. How do you separate yourself from it and still function? Yeah
Where you seek prosperity healthfulness being healthy
Basically good food and good drink. I bringing this up because you know, we've reloaded Ocelli and the Greek and yesterday we
Continued the food talk which I had done on uncommon-sense radio. It was basically about quality of food and other things like that
We might go back. I was suggested to do recipes and things
But this is a statement that rings true if you really think about it that good food and good drink promotes good character
Typically people that have good food, you know consumables and good good food and good drink
Tend to be a better character than those who don't
Simple, you know, it's not an excuse. It's not a it's just a very simple observation that one can have, you know
If you look at people who don't know good food preparation don't mind what they put into their body
I don't know if they call it in Australia junk food, you know, yep. Yep fast food
Macca's
Yeah, yeah all those other things, you know not to bring up those brands
But but no harm done because this the the the corporate leaders of those companies will tell you you shouldn't be eating it anyway
So anyway, if you if you have a discussion and and really assess the character of individuals
you'll see that one of the things that you'll find is people of good character tend to mind what they put into their body and
Those that are poor character don't this is not a fact or the truth
But it's an interesting observation that one can let's say is part of the accumulation of what's going on here
So, I mean you can have a psychopathic killer who is a food connoisseur, too
You know, don't don't mistake it for an all be all whatever. But now what else do you put in your body is your thoughts?
you know you
You when you interact with people basically the way most interaction is done on international or distant level is
Digitally, let's say electronically sonically
When you interact with people through Skype or whatever
Chat rooms or whatever, you know, we're discussing the computer-based stuff right now
You you're not you're not only interacting with their character based on their what they consider to be important or what they put in their body
Topically or internally but also what information they take in
For example, you wouldn't believe how many people not many because I tend not to put myself out there but enough people
Always are most likely let's say are sending me information for approval
Yep, it's like well, why can't you discern it yourself? Why does it matter what I think about it if it's a right or wrong?
Are you asking me to give you fish or are you asking to learn how to fish, right?
so
I'll tell you just about everything that I'm sent from the outside in you know, the web-based stuff, you know everything from
Fukushima's gonna kill us all there's an old fool that goes around the internet
I'm not going to mention him by name and he and he's he's got a pretty good following which is good for him
but he there's a couple of old fools out there by the way that have been doing this for a long time and
No one holds their feet to the fire about when they say we're all gonna die very soon because of Fukushima
We're all gonna die. You ever notice that so I get a lot of this crap and I
Don't know how to send it back or reply to people if you're looking for approval
That shows a deficiency of character when it comes to your ability to discern information
You see yep, yeah
Yeah, and that leads to gossip. It leads to Chinese whispers. It leads to that and that seems what people really like
No, that's fine
Does that refer back to the point like no one wants to take responsibility as well lack of responsibility for their own actions and decision-making
They want someone else to make the choice for them
Because I mean they're wanting approval from you so that they might consider you as a guru status
and therefore if you
Agree to what they're asking of you, then they're patting themselves on the back
So does that mean that as I said before about not want responsibility for the choices they make?
But you know and it's not even that it's whether
The issue of responsibility might be too high tiered for most people think about it for a moment
I think what they're trying to do is shed liability
There's a difference when you're responsible for something you take on a certain
Let's say
Stance on how are you going to deal with something?
Another stance is who's going to be who's going to take the blame or who's going to be liable for something?
That's a much lower tier
Of accepting let's say the risk or the reward right and what you see other than people asking for approval
Is who is liable for this every returned on the mainstream TV, and they do a report
And they said we don't know who to blame for this yet
Well if you're gonna blame someone look in the mirror right if you're watching it
So so the thing is now it's not even forget about humanity is too far
Removed from anything practical or lawful to take responsibility for anything at this point all they do is shift liability
Which is who's going to get the blame and then again leads to the Chinese whispers and the gossiping and it just makes people rest
Better when they feel they can blame someone else for something that may not even exist, but they perceive as being negative
And you see this and this is nothing to really harp about
Because if you're going to look at it objectively
You could simply say this is part of the the human culture as part of human tradition
Part of the character of people right now, and it's very low tier very low level
And it's it's okay
It's okay, because that's how it is now
taking responsibility for oneself
Is different if you're mixed in with what's going on?
How do you how can you take responsibility when you're full of dirt?
You have to clean yourself up first you have to separate yourself set yourself apart
Right and then take responsibility that way yeah
You know how can people say what they say and do what they do
Regarding others when they don't even know how to position themselves amongst the muck you ask people
You know many things you know you hear people
Researchers and people pontificating on the internet, and they ever hear people use terms like oh, it's our government
Pay your taxes or our military our University our churches, man
That's a that is a very poor mindset when people say that because when you say it's our government our military our money our banks
Our whatever institution you are now taking the hit you are taking the liability for their crap
And it's very easy to establish that right now just about all actually
All of human institutions are either corrupt
miss
Misdirected or full of misinformation about all of them are I can't imagine one that isn't
That's that people know about whether you're talking about medical
social
Media judicial economic it's they're all in other words if you pull a common oaf from the street and ask him
Let's say what the judicial system about what he thinks
It's about is completely contrary to what's memorialized or written within the documents of how the judicial system functions
If you pull a common oaf off the street and ask him what the university system is about
What he'll tell you or she'll tell you is completely contrary to what the university trustees
Save the universities for the same with the medical system same with the government system same with all so right now
There is a huge disconnect and there has been for a very very long time, but it still exists right now
Was it designed that way to?
Yes
It was designed that way by de facto because whenever you're gonna present something to the public you have to accommodate the mindset
Which is a catch-22?
So all of these things accommodate the mindset right like I've heard recently had a discussion about the police state
It's impossible because the police are not really police. They're all freelancers. They're subcontractors. They're private agencies
They have nothing to do with the government
This has been ruled on many times over but your perception is different because everyone thinks their government
They even think they're government, but they're not if you look at the administrative policies and all that
That's why when a police officer gets in trouble anywhere in the world
They take his badge and his authority away and the his own bosses throw him under the bus
It's because the entire group can't take the liability because they're not what they say
They are right the same thing with the university professors the same thing with the doctors
What was the last time you heard of a doctor?
Getting in trouble whether he spoke out against something in conventional like vaccines or certain procedures or whether he was charged with negligence
When did you ever see all the other doctors stick up for him never?
What they do is they throw him under the bus?
Because what they're doing like again if you go to the universities
It's been very well documented that the university trustees those who run it
Basically tell you the purpose of the university is to produce good corporate workers
And it's a form of mind control in other words if you pass through the university with a degree it shows that you're trained a bull
Yeah, right. Yeah, and and they're not they're not there to teach you anything
They're there to see if they can instill a certain way of thinking
This is within but most people think that you're not educated if you go to university
I mean if you see even if you're just traveling down the street if you see university
You should go the other way even if you don't plan on attending it because it's such a negative place
so
In other words what right now and has been for a long time and the religious institutions are exactly the same all of the institutions
Of mankind can be objectified this way now if you start discussing this with your common person
Let's say a man woman or young or old
They will think that you're being sarcastic. It's not true or whatever because they have a perception now. Let's go back to
What you said about it being designed this way?
You know if you're going to incorporate or present the public with anything you have to accommodate the mindset now
Here's the catch-22. Let's go for example
With the education system if you go to a society that is ignorant
Can you present them with an institution that will give them knowledge no way?
Because it doesn't resonate with them because it doesn't accommodate the ignorant
So you have to create something that makes them feel better emotionally like oh if you go here you're educated
But you fill them with more ignorance because that's what they resonate with and that's what accommodates them as an ignorant society is accommodated with ignorance
So the university system is accommodating ignorant people. It's a catch-22
So it's not it's not a it's not an institution to make them more knowledgeable. It's just to give them more of what they already are
Right. Otherwise, it wouldn't work
Yeah
If it really was giving knowledge the people in the society would go there and say I don't understand a damn thing
They're saying don't go there
It would close down in a year or two
But if you make it sound a certain way the same thing with the medical system if you have a sick society
you can't go in there and
reindoctrinate them and how to be healthy because
The reason why they're sick is of all their practices you're gonna have to take all their traditions and cultures and all their the way
They do commerce and all that stuff and flush it away and they won't do that
So what you do is you say we'll present you with better medicine, but the more but it actually makes you sicker
Because you cannot present a sick society medically sick, for example
with true medicine because
There is no such thing
In other words, the reason why people are sick is because of how they behave what they eat what they drink how they work how they rest
How they think
So what you do is, you know, it's already within human convention to have these society
Institutions in society and they just make it worse. And if you don't believe me
There's a lady who had done
Research on socialism and she found out that when in socialist countries when doctors go on strike the morgues are empty
People stop dying and when the doctors go back to work the morgues get full again
Think about that for a moment now the same with the religious institutions people think
You know
They get spiritual by going to a religious temple of any denominator of any type of religion and that couldn't be further from the truth
the best
Religious institutions on the planets and the biggest all they do is bring you closer to certain minor imps and demons that have been revived
from ancient Greece and ancient Babylon at best at best and
Take you further away and further away from understanding how the society of the gods work completely
So they so if you want to be an expert in demonology go ahead and join either one of the 34,000 sects of Christianity
1,200 sects of Islam
400,000 sects of Hinduism. I mean they're all ready for you. They're ready to accept new members all of those religions are right
So you when you join those you become far removed from what is going on with the gods and
You'll probably be an expert in demonology of some sort
And this goes on and on and on and on give you another example
For example, let's say someone is doing research with spark plugs or sparkers or they call them I guess in England
you know, it's a fitment that goes into the motor provides a high voltage spark so the
Get ignition in the motor, right?
So let's say you design one, you know, basically spark plugs have not been
Changed much haven't changed much for about a hundred years
They were sort of standardized around what they call World War two because the military wanted a standard for all the thousands
If not millions of vehicles that were producing
So really hasn't changed since then. So if you simply reconfigure it and design it so it works
let's say twice as good as a regular spark plug and you
Encounter someone who is in the field
The first thing they'll tell you is that oh that doesn't mean much, you know, we can do that, too
And I'm like, well, then why don't you and they don't answer?
And then the next thing is you say well, you know when you configure the spark plug this way
You get less pollution less, you know toxic emissions and you know what their answer was their answer was well
You got to have some pollution. You got to have some toxic emissions
This is coming from people in your industry
Right, yeah
Yeah, so I mean this sounds unbelievable. Yeah
Yeah, I mean yeah, you're talking this is someone who is in the industry
I mean in in a righteous world this person would should be taken out back and shot blindfolded, right?
Because they're promoting the opposite of what is beneficial to humankind and you will find this
Across the board pick any institution. I think there's something called the Tomcats registry which lists all industries
Like if you're in an industry you get that there's volumes of books now
That's electronic and it has any industry you can imagine in it
I think man engages in over 30,000 different industries right now and institutions
You can pick each one and if you have an objective mind
You can show how they're all not doing what people think they are but they're doing exactly what's memorialized in their administrative paperwork
Right, so no one is paying any attention. So
How do you do I mean how you know
How many times have you heard people pontificate an alternative media radio and written word?
they pick a subject and they pick a
Conspiracy notice I didn't say conspiracy theory because many conspiracies are just blatant, you know
Meaning, you know two or more coming together to do harm
and end injury
So how many times do they get this narrow-minded focus and make it their focus for weeks or months on end?
and then
They pick another topic and they start shouting about that
right and back and forth right and that sort of legitimizes what we just said because you can pretty much pick anything humans are
engaged in right now and
Become a quote-unquote harsh commentator on it do a website radio show or whatever and most of the time you will be true
but what's not true about what's being said is
that
There is a false
Hope and a false desire to change it. They think that if they fix this one thing
Oh if this individual on the international this international billionaire is arrested not going to mention his name
You might it starts with an s and it ends with an s
If this individual is arrested the world would be better. No
You know what? Wait a second. You still have attorneys down the street. You have a university and a medical doctor
No one is addressing that
You know, you ever look at all it's the Illuminati's
Illuminati's are gonna get us. Yeah. All right. So get rid of the Illuminati's you still got a doctor and an attorney and a church
down your street
You didn't change anything
It's what's going on in your locale. Just look at it that way
It's very toxic and it's accepted
You know, if you were visiting the earth and cataloging the characteristics and traits of things here
Let's say you go to a place called the rainforest
You'll find that there's a the most colorful frogs and insects and some plants are also the most dangerous
As if nature has set it up that way to let everyone and everything know look
It's so beautiful and colorful for a reason right now
If you go into where most humans get their food in urban environments, you'll find that the most colorful packaging
that they offer for sale is the children's food and
If you can concur or anyone can if you look at what's in that children's food, it also happens to be the most what?
Toxic sugar most toxic. Yeah. Yeah, so you see how things are in accordance with each other whether you're in the rainforest or at the shops
There's this underlying thing. That's very easy to see that follows through, right?
So, you know and then he just to tie it in, you know, this is this is not a rant or anything
But when you start studying
Objectively that humankind has been obsessed with human sacrifice and the destruction of children for thousands of years and it hasn't changed today
It's just not in the forward-thinking
aspect of people's conversation
It still exists today
You know
if you start piecing it all together you have people that on the planet that essentially always will pick the worst if it's
If it's packaged as being just good
And also are heavily involved all of their traditions holidays and religions and stuff on the under undertone is
About human sacrifice particularly that of children
What would you say about a society like this can you say we have to make the world a better place
Are you joking? It needs to be scraped and redone. Yeah, there's nothing to fix
So what I'm actually viewing the world in from this
Glasses that I'm looking through now the way you're describing it. It's like it's oh, it's one
It's obvious like it seems obvious like it's run under my nose and I haven't even seen it
But two it's like you can't sort of fix something
To make it better because it just wouldn't work. It seems like it needs to be like another flood needs to happen
It's just kind of
Right, right. It's it's gotten to the point where I've seen you've perhaps heard me say it's unrehabilitate able
Yeah, now it's just because something can't be fixed. It doesn't mean you have to discard it right away
You can still keep it around as a paperweight or just to take up space and that's exactly what's going on right now
And mankind will not do it right now
They've mankind has fallen for everything the gods are in control. The gods are going to do it
They're going to clean it up and they're going to use nature to clean it up
And I was discussing this with someone recently and they said well, what do you mean nature? I'm like, okay again
Do you know the remember the analogy?
I just gave about the bright colored creatures in the rainforest and the bright colored
Food that man prepares for children is or boasts the most toxic both the most toxic
Look at look at this when I proposed if you understand prophecy of all culture
the gods will use nature to take care of it and clean up the earth and
Fix, you know get rid of most of mankind so they can get a limited gene pool to start with again
They're going to use nature and this person didn't see it and I said well look
If if one countries or one group of humans are going to go to war with another group of humans
They also use nature to do it and they and I gave them the full complete analogies. I'll give it here. Okay Rodrigo
let's say Australia is going to go to war with Chile and
The first thing they do is they want to build airplanes. Let's say what do they do?
Don't they go out and have to need a bunch of aluminium?
Where and where do they get the aluminium isn't it? Don't you have to mine bauxite and
Refine it to aluminum from the earth and then mold it and shape it and engineer it into an airplane
right if you're going to make a rifle aren't you going to mine iron and
Cast it and machine it into the form of a barrel and maybe make the stock out of wood
You know the stock of the rifle that you make out of wood from a tree
Maybe if you make it out of plastic, don't you have to refine the the crude petroleum into plastics?
So in order if you're going to make a spear or an arrow or a crossbow
Don't you have to get those materials from nature?
Yeah, you see the analogy see how it's complete
Can you show me anything that mankind uses to go to war that they haven't gotten from nature?
No other than their mind on how to do it so this is a strategy and the tactics are different now
So the gods are going to use nature and like I've mentioned there's going to be three major kill shots
There's actually more than that
but the basically two strikes upon the earth what you call asteroids and the other one is going to be a major solar event and
And then the rest of it's going to there are about seven major events
There's going to be some major events when certain laws are instilled the people will will be
doing a fine job of
Eliminating each other and it won't be some dictatorship or police coming and doing and the people will do it themselves
You know family members to each other and all of this we will discuss more detail
Maybe in the next year or two on that because right now it just doesn't quite make sense to most
But let's just refrain from saying that you know
The people that come and listen to these types of sonic events, they've really got their shit together. I'll use that term
Fortunately there aren't too many people that come across that are
Trying to profess how wonderful a life of baselessness is right many people that come to these sonic events and listen
I'll be a few
Let's say several scores of people they tend to be thinking men and women they tend to be people who let's say
Are looking for substance or looking for things to measure other things by instead of this?
He said she said let's just hope for the best you know kind of thing right yeah
So it is fortunate
And I do feel fortunate that when I put out sonic events the people that are typically attracted to it are substantive
They are looking for lawfulness. They are looking for substance. They are looking for reference points you see so
The from that point of view still I think many things cannot be discussed at this point in great detail
For example I had someone that you know I won't mention by name as well. They came to me very excited about several weeks ago
Speaking to someone else that you know of and saying that you know the Greek is right the Greek everything has been saying is coming
Along and I was kind of glad to hear that because it's kind of like confirmation
You know that other people are seeing it and I asked this individual
You know you got into this conversation about how what the Greek said was right, and it's coming around
What was it he'd give and this person couldn't give me any specifics on anything you can't
So what does that mean so that means do we disregard the entire thing?
You sort of have to because they didn't they didn't come back validating with any substance or any references
So but emotionally made you feel good, right?
Like if someone said hey Rodrigo's right about what he said a year or two ago
And and then you go and ask them well, what was it specifically and they don't know well
You have to discard it because it made you even though it made you feel
Really good at the moment because it's like wow you know it's like. I'm actually it's like payment for what I'm doing right
Yeah, it's like you know people appreciating it not just liking it and then when you go to them to for them to validate
You know let's give you some substance behind it. They can't you must discard it because it's purely emotional crap
And
That's what you're getting right now. There's plenty of old guys young guys popular guys not so popular guys
Millions on the wet on the internet can I say millions perhaps?
That are pontificating all of these things and when you start looking into it guess what?
Very little substance and even even if there is substance. They don't know how to handle it lawfully
They don't know the lawful approach, and they and and what's their reward it when they become overzealous like they push too hard
You've heard of people getting very adamant about certain beliefs that they have on online and
They push too hard and that seems like you know very narrow-mindedness
If you push too hard, and you're overzealous about anything especially if it's unlawful or unfounded or on or baseless
You're going to be rewarded with error
You're going to find yourself tripping on things
Are you going to be and I've seen this over and over and over you find it a lot in these alternative religious groups?
that I think that they're going back and
Giving a true interpretation of the bible and they spin off and they're mixing all these pagan concepts
And what happens they fall apart in a year or two you've heard of that, right?
So because they're they're trying too hard if you try to go with maybe haste makes waste
Is that another way to say it if you're doing it too fast, right? Yep?
And and also if they if they don't understand timing there's a right time for everything especially information
So anyway, I've been kind of long-winded there
Give us it gives a little bit of
Rodrigo speak in the meantime
Now I was just thinking about
When you were talking about the institutions on how they're not
What they're doing is not the way that it's perceived by the general consensus of the population
It's it's they're giving you more of the wrong stuff rather than the right stuff
And what bothers me is that you said that child sacrifices that you they're still happening to this day, right?
I'm just one wanting to know what is in the mindset of these people that actually go and do it. Are they
worshipping some sort of input demon themselves or
It seems like it's gone underground in the last
You know thousand years or so
And yeah, what the world is perceiving as this bright rainbow, you know pot of gold at the end of the rainbow like this nice
Utopian society is actually being run by something a little bit more sinister
But I want to know what why it is that way
It's I did I did explain it several times recently if you like I can go through it again very quickly
It also you have to tie that in with the what's considered to be gynecophilic symbols
Or have you heard how there's architecture of the human genitalia and churches and spires and and you see that being used?
Even in what's called Disney. They used to actually outwardly show
Pornographic scenes
Yeah, they're they're obsessed with that but also, you know
it's not we're not really putting a certain group of people on the hook because the majority of the people feel good when they do a
birthday cake celebration and
Whether they know it or not that celebration is a parody of the human sacrifice. Also, so
you know
if you start
Pushing the issue of that you're now you're getting in between
Someone and what makes them happy and you're gonna have a fight if that happens, right?
Yeah, like if you ever interrupt someone while they're doing something that brought them joy. Yeah, they don't they want to get back to it
as soon as possible and
but if you push the issue they want to bring violence on you, so
that's the same thing with
The majority of cultures right now. They're engaged. They don't know it
Just because you don't know it doesn't mean that you're off the hook you're still not taking liability for it, right?
But where it started very simply is this and this is a I
Hmm how would you say this? I've changed the world I've changed
Not the world my worldview
But I've changed the way I describe things about the worldview and many of the things that I've been speaking about in the past few
Months publicly, let's say even conversations like this if you put a gun to my head a year ago
I said, there's no way I'm gonna say that but now I've changed the mind about that mindset and said
You know what? Screw it might as well, right?
Because you just never know
You know who it's going to affect and who's going to take the ball and roll with it a little bit further
And this is one of the things that I've always kept close not to discuss
Why because it took about 10 years of study to do that
So imagine you went deep sea deep sea diving for 10 years Rodrigo and you finally found a treasure
Would you start giving all that treasure away to just anybody?
No, you should get something for it, you know, I mean it's it's treasure, you know
I mean, you just don't hand it out like candy to just anybody they especially faceless anonymous people on a sonic event, right?
So but I've just I've changed the mind about that and this is one of the things and this is not the you know
The deepest part of it. Let's just go on a cursory part and keep going on that. What is human sacrifice and why it's very
Have you ever heard me say how savagery has been legitimized?
Okay, well think about that term what is savagery and what is lit legitimizing something
Just set the two together
Yes, but yeah and you could look up those words so right now you're in a society where things that are just
Appalling a moral unlawful are considered the norm not by certain groups in high ivory castles
But the irregular people, you know the population at large on the planet
Western Eastern Northern and Southern
But let's go back to why you asked about the human sacrifice
And this is an answer that can be given and believe it or not
I've said this with you at least once before and maybe two or three times on other sonic things
But we'll go over it again. And the reason I said that it's very important
I've noticed that what the deeper the subject matter gets and the truer it is the less tendency people have to remember it
Isn't that funny really?
Yeah, and that ties in with what I've discussed as cosmic censorship, yeah
Do you remember the movie men in black, you know, and after you saw the event thing
They say everybody look here and they flashed a little red thing and yes, they plant they plant a new memory in your head, right?
It's I found there's a phenomenon when I start discussing the nature of things people say hmm
That's great
And then when we change the subject go to the next thing it all gets washed away and even if they go back and listen
To it over and over again
They still can't remember it. I just find it to be
Kind of cutesy
Because the gods do have a sense of humor that way, you know what I mean
It's kind of a very juvenile way of affecting the mind from the divine level and I appreciate it
Not not that I appreciate it. I appreciate noticing it
But I don't appreciate it because it gets
Frustrating when you explain things to people and they and they ask you to explain it and you're like, wait a second
We explained this already. So after this long-winded bill, let's get let's cut to the chase
Years ago and really whether it's
religious philosophical or contemplative
We're talking ancient societies
They had people that were inspired by angelic beings demonic beings and minor gods and all these things
to be supported and to delve in things in matters of the mind or the spirit and
It's also stated in some of the holy writs of the world
That the human body from its physical side
Is very limited where the spiritual side is almost unlimited, right, you know a person's mind or spirituality has no limits when you think about it
But the physical is limited and we look at it as a container it's basically it's a heart structure of
skeleton wrapped in muscle
Containing organ and the whole thing is wrapped in a slight vacuum with skin
And you have protrusions of organs and ears and or things like that and it's very finite, you know
it can be defined and
amongst the definition of the human body
Amongst the organ functions. They said well, you know, there are certain organs that are most important and
the way they were deemed most important because those were the organs that human the progression and
The posterity and the continuance of humankind relied on and what organs would they be?
the genitalia
Because if you've removed everyone's genitalia in 40 years, there won't be anybody left
right
Just like a farmer. We've remember the analogy of the farmer the reason you farm to go to commerce and to produce food that you need
But also it's important to save some seed stock because if you don't have seed stock your farming career is over in a year
Now sans purchasing like did he say?
Well, you can buy seats, but the person that you're buying seats from also had to save them somehow, right?
So where's the seed of humanity held?
Well, it's the organs that are beneath, you know that lower part of the body
you know where you want to get into the testicles and the ovum and the sperm and the fluids and the you know,
Prostate and the fallopian tubes you get the picture right? There's an entire complex there. That is
And now we're just talking about the carnal side the material side and the ejection of fluids and all that
We're not talking about the desire part. We're just talking about the physical part, right?
so
They considered the human or the most important part of the human body not necessarily for
You to function because guess what? If you remove the lungs, you're not going to live that long
If you remove the heart, you're not going to live on those are very important to at the moment very important, right?
But in order what is most important is that humanity continues?
Have you heard the term the species must continue, you know how some their sacrifices even animals do so the young survive and all that
You've seen it
Memorialized and romanticized in Hollywood, you know, I'll give up my life so you can continue
why they there's a sense of
Continuance that that needs to be propagated spiritually and the way that is done again is through the genitalia
male and female man and woman and
Because they were considered so important what they did is they memorialized the through iconography through imagery through symbolic
representation and through architecture
The gynec symbol meaning the woman's
Genitalia and the phallic symbol meaning the man's
Genitalia in architecture iconography art pattern work. You've seen it all around, right?
Like for example, most of your traditional church doors
The door has that almond shape that is walking through the gynec symbol
Yeah, right once and above it you usually have a round window which symbolizes the rear view of a woman
Because the rear view of a woman would be the genitalia below and the anus above
now if you now if you'll see that persona or actually
Manifest in most of what's called your Western Christian architecture
right
Pretty pretty fascinating when you let that sink in let's not even get into more of that
Right, and the only reason why is it because if you brought someone back from two or three thousand years ago to a modern Western
City or village or town or whatever and when they walk through the area
They said I didn't know you had a sex temple in your neighborhood and guess what building they would be pointing to
Yes, and there's no reason I can get I can bury you with the details on that but why
So right now we see how it was decided from the spiritual perspective them
It's very important for a species or a group to continue
Multiple generation and that it and the the physical part that that allows that to happen is the genitalia
And that is the sole reason why you see the genitalia. I'm repeating myself. It's kind of redundant, but it's important to say it again
You see that manifest in architecture pattern work art iconography. I guess work, you know, you name it right Rodrigo
You've seen those symbols especially in the art and and it's censored as well because you don't think about that when you see it everywhere
It's sort of like it's everyday thing and it's like that. Okay, whatever. It's just architecture and it has no relevance or anything
But now that you're bringing it up and sort of thing. Wow, the world is inundated with this everywhere
Yeah, and because of the prudent nature of many mainstream religions
They a lot of filmmakers can't show let's say
If there's a sci-fi film and an alien is going to come out of an egg
They have to they can't make it you can't look gynec because they say well if we show this movie in a Catholic country
It's too prudent. They're gonna cut the scene out because it looks like a woman's vagina, you know
So that's still considered and the reason why you have that prudence that prudence not prudence, but prudish this
you know subverting the
The erotic or subverting the genitalia is because it's done traditionally because the the people that were in those institutions traditionally
They considered this to be very high occult knowledge
And if people acknowledge these things everywhere they would question it and then eventually they would discover that's why they're doing it
So there's no reason you look if it's considered a high occult secret
What a better place to do it on a minor conversation that might be published on YouTube
I can't think of a better place, right? So and also other sonic events
Yeah, now, how does the child how does this fit into child sacrifice? Well, what is the product of?
Genitalia
Population
After nine months the child. Okay. Now now the new child represents a new generation
limitless potential spiritually
Right anything that child can do anything that they still tell you Pete in a lot of Western societies
They still if you're in a non-feudal non-caste system
They still tell children you can be anything you want. You can do anything you want when you grow up
How many times have you heard that said right in feudal and caste systems?
They don't if you're born in a certain system like as a slave or a serf you can't marry out of it
You can't travel out of it either, right?
so and by the way, that's how they are anyway today and they don't realize it, but
Okay, let's now the child is the product of that now when people
It's very easy and very clear to see that all the religions of the world the major ones
Especially are nothing more than demonology what they've done is revived ancient pagan gods minor imps and demons
Now it doesn't matter how much you cry about you think you believe in some holy book that you they're putting in front of you
You know nothing in that book
In any religion and that's easy to prove
If anyone has what I'm saying in doubt
Go pick any holy writ of the world any of the major religions and study it a little bit and then go find someone who
Professes to believe in that religion and question him and quiz them a little bit about it
And then you'll see they will know absolutely nothing about it
It's a phenomenon it's an incredible phenomenon
It's all it's almost this cannot happen with rational people. It can only happen when people are under the influence of
something else
Okay, let's put that aside
when you look at the people's interaction with these imps and demons that
Have you heard of bringing a sacrifice to a god? Yes, right. They demand it sacrifices
Would do you bring yesterday's leftover supper to a god as an offering or your old shoes
Or do you bring him the best of your stuff?
Yes, so we just
Discussed what was the most important organ and what is the product of it?
What is the product of the most important organ that and it's that's been used in symbology and also in your architecture
What is the product of those organs?
And what so wouldn't the child be the product of the best of the best and wouldn't then the child be the best of
The best of the best. Yes
Do you see how this has been rationalized for thousands of years and I'm as far as I know
I'm the only one that's broken it down. I could have broken I've usually
Break it down in less than two minutes, but we've taken about 15 here to be redundant deliberately
Don't do you see how it all ties in together?
Yes, I do and I'm not I'm not this is not reading into it this is
This is actually what's occurring and for this is what's been occurring and it's become tradition now
So they're sacrificing to
Lower imps of demons or higher beings of some sort. Yeah, though
Well, they're higher than the lowest infant demon is higher than any human
Yeah, because they have the ability to go into the spiritual realm. Well, you don't yeah
They can manifest things that you can't right. Do you remember the genie in the bottle give me three wishes, right?
That that that creature was able to manifest your wishes in physical reality. Think about it
Yeah
so
And that by the way, that's a corruption of the jinn in them
another
Tradition. Yes. Yeah
so
This is this is not this is the level of insanity
like
Wolfgang Goethe said you need not visit an insane asylum to meet disordered spirits because the earth is
The insane asylum of the universe
So if you're born here, you're in deep shit
If you recall reading any of the Holy Writs, they tell you it's better to not have been born here
But the gods don't act in futility if you have been born here and come through here you will be rewarded for such
Well, you'll see later there, you know, you could look at all your you know for such an action in other words becoming here
There's a lot of information that we don't get about why mankind is here why he is the way he is
Well, we do get a little bit about it or enough. Let's say to satisfy and in someone inquiring
Well, we really don't have the full picture
You see of everything and that's because we're limited in maturity. You understand the concept
Yeah, well we have so very juvenile spiritually like for example
You can think of all the things that can be talked about in all forms of knowledge
And you have to look at who you're going to speak to about it
Like for example, if you have a four-year-old child
You cannot just pick any subject you want to speak on and speak to them about it
You probably could but they might lack the maturity
To further it right, you know, like if you were you have to go down to their level and give them a little bit extra
And then a little bit extra a little bit extra so that they grow. Yeah, you can't give them
Sure
You know, like if you lecture on astrophysics to a bunch of five-year-olds
They're all quiet after an hour you say any questions and they all raise their hand and they all ask do you have any candy?
right
And this is exactly what you hear going on in alternative media, by the way
yes, so
Yeah, and by the way, one of the unfortunate things that you will find in culture is the kids culture
You know the little goats, of course
They've created a subculture within the culture for children. They have children's television children's movies children's books
Children's clothing
Specifically, you know patterned a certain way for children, right?
And I don't mean that you should put a child in a large size adult clothing
I mean you should be fit to their body, but
the children's foods children music children this that is a big disservice because
they do not provide a
Transition period from childhood to adult they think they do but it's very corrupt and very negative
Yeah, it's like a jumpstart like jumping over a huge ravine to get to from childhood to adult with this
Yeah, and that creates a dysfunctional but that was said 300 years ago Goethe he says, you know
This is the if you're this is an insane asylum if you're living in an insane asylum
Who's to say what's right or wrong? Just give it two minutes the entire concept of right and wrong will change
In an insane asylum
Yeah, and the thing about being in an insane asylum if you visit one they have like certain days where you have a visitor's day
and
The ones that are not dangerous
They let them out into the open area and you know family and friends come and greet, you know
But there's several of them that don't get visitors, right?
so you go into one of these on visitors day and sit down to some of some of the people that are locked up in
There and you sit down and have a conversation the first few minutes to say I don't understand why this person is here
They seem very rational very thoughtful
But you continue for another three or four minutes and then you'll be like, okay now I know why you're here
Because you just fell apart
Right. Yeah, and you know, of course this doesn't this is just a metaphor because
these things these institutions prisons insane asylums hospitals are also used to buffer down those that
Are not towing the line whether it's political religious or philosophical, right?
How many times you've heard people going to what's called the judicial the judge?
Courts which are based on justicia the goddess religion and if you start bringing up law to the judge
He wants you to have psyche vow on you, right psychologically evaluated, right? Because you must be crazy
I mean everyone else is believing this. Why aren't you?
It's a very harsh tool. And by the way, whenever you see the PSY prefix
That means spirit. Yes
So it's funny to see how ignorant these people are if you go to a psychiatrist or psychologist
You just ask them what they do and the minute they profess anything with the PSY prefix. They also you're a spiritualist and watch what happens
They don't know what the hell they're talking about and they don't want to either so anyway
There's the other one there's PSY and then there's PS honor
Well the PN well the PSY means mind or spirit. It's the same thing. Yeah
Now in other cultures, it's the it's a rook like a rook
Okay, or rook
In in ancient Egyptian. It was the rook in Hebrew. It's a ruach in Arabic is rook. That means spirit
So but the soul I think you're referring to that's the PNU
PNU whenever you see PNU like pneumatic and pneumonia is silent the PSI
Pneumonia pneumatic that has to do with the movement of air. The soul has to do with the movement of air
The soul is interchangeable if you're breathing like if you have a dog a frog a fly
Elephant or a gorilla and yourself in the room
All of your souls are interchangeable. How do we know?
Because you're all breathing the same air. Yeah, if if the if the
If the elephant got arrhythmia and fell on the floor and stopped breathing you could try to administer resuscitation to the elephant, right?
And you could bring it back by putting your soul into its body, right?
And if it starts breathing on its own now it has its own soul
But in the while it's not breathing you're putting your soul is it so in other words, what's interesting?
You know how we started off how the things are not what people think they are
But they're self-professed
You know, we brought up the police the university and all that
If you ask anyone who's let's say a spiritual person or a contemplative person
Someone who says they're educated or ask them to define spirit and soul watch how they unravel
Yeah, and yet it's their self they're easy to define but they will go they'll give you a million reasons why it can't be
Defined but they will never go to see what the definitions are
They can't why because they're all put together like cheap sweaters and you know
One of the characteristics of a cheap sweater is that if you get a cheap sweater or a cheaply knit or crocheted garment
If you find a loose thread
All you have to do is pull on it and keep pulling on that one thread and what do you think happens to the entire?
Garbage, yeah
Yes, so when you run into these people that allege themselves to be
spiritual awake
Whatever psychic. I love those guys
I
Asked them to define spirit and soul and keep just stay on that point and in five minutes
there'll be nothing but a ball of yarn or a pile of yarn on the floor or
If you're in present if you're presently with them and if you look at their face
They they start to put on an expression like they want to bring physical harm to you. Now. Welcome to planet Earth
if you're if you're
Spiritualists your psychics and those that say I'm awake. I'm contemplative. I'm educated
Can be pulled apart like a cheap sweater, where does that leave the common man?
If those that profess to have exceptional talent and cannot back it up with anything
What does that leave those who say they don't have any they're not exception
Actually, it is. Yeah, it's even worse. But on the other hand, it's wide open for them is yes
It allows them to
Fit right in if they explore. Yeah
Well, it allows them to allows them to notice that there's that person that said they were exceptional advanced awake
Spiritual was nothing but a pile of crap
You know those gurus those teachers and I'm not saying some of them I'm saying just about all of them because you know what
If I have come across anyone who was really close to that position, I'm not saying I am in terms of being psychic
I would I would give their name. I would suggest go to the go seek them. I would I would not fully endorse them
Let's say unless I knew them. Well, but I would say go seek this person. I
Haven't found any
This is really a sad situation
So the thing is to be have you ever heard of the term being self-sufficient
Yes, what does that mean? You have to operate? You have to have you have to be able to be self-sufficient?
Everything that you need in some
Level not an abundance and not in want
You have to be efficient with it
And you have to know you have to be skilled with it to be self-sufficient, right?
So whether it's a matter of health whether a matter of knowledge education whether a matter of spirituality
spirituality or a psychiatry or anything
Isn't it? How do you feel if we say Rodrigo the people should be self-sufficient? I
Think that's a very good
advisory statement to make to anyone
Yeah, but based but based on the conditions that we described it is most prudent to be so
because if you go to a doctor you're not going to get much help if you go to a psychiatrist like any or a
Priest or an imam or a rabbi or a university education or even getting your car fixed
Because all of them think good enough is what they should be doing and you know what?
Think about it this way. Could good enough be the enemy of perfection?
Yes, yes because it leaves you like giving up and not wanting to attain perfection
Yeah
So I mean if anything the gods were considered perfection in comparison to us
It'd be like looking at a scum
looking at humanity
Right. That's why when you read a lot of the holy writs of the world nine out of ten times humans are described as such
That's no mystery now, is it?
Yeah, that's why you're only only 5% of the population is going to be here in the next two decades
Then I'm not say this is not a fear porn or scare tactic or anything like that because I tell people you people that
People that say they know the truth or they're looking for the truth or really not because if you're really
Discovering the truth you will probably lock yourself into a room and cry for a week and wish you were never born
So don't look for the truth folks unless you have the intestinal fortitude to do so
But on the other hand that's reverse psychology, right
Look if you're nine years old, you know, yeah, you've been around, you know when they have these family gatherings and
You have all the multiple generations from the young children the adolescents the parents the aunts the uncles and the grandma great-grandma sitting around for a
Feast or get together. You've heard of such things perhaps maybe have attended some yourself
And they go around sometimes and ask the children what they would like, you know after they're done, you know, whatever and
Imagine they go across to a nine-year-old child and said what would you like to get out of life?
And you say for example, I'd like to know what the truth is and auntie
Daddy, mommy and grandma take you to the other room and smack you around and say never ask that question again
Well, that means it's something very important and that's all you should be doing
Yeah, yeah, I mean I remember the age of 21
And the only thing that I asked myself I want to know the truth about everything and I realized that was a big ask
Because the more that I find out the more that I the more that I don't know then I realize it's actually
forever
Because even though I have
Minutely gone a little bit of truth since the edge 21 to now 37. I know there's a lot more that is hidden
To know to want to find out more if you don't remain like there's a lot more than I know that I don't know
Well, well, let's let's look let's look, you know, how we mentioned being self-sufficient consider this one of the holy writs of the world states that
If you want to pursue the truth, I'm saying I'm paraphrasing here
There are three qualities you have to have
And they're actually bestowed upon you like wisdom, you know, you can get all the knowledge you want, but wisdom is given right?
Yeah, there's a there's a goddess
Behind that and she's a benevolent one
Just keep that in mind
Three things that in one of the holy writs of the world. We call the scriptures
I'm paraphrasing here when in order to delve in the matter we call truth Alif. Yeah or Emmett in different languages
Or love it's not right. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes to
There are three qualities one of them is you have to have exceptional memory
You have to be able to bring things to recall
the other thing is
You have to have knowledge into all things and the other thing is you have to have knowledge of things to come
Right
Those are the three characteristics. I'm going to name them again
One is be able to bring things to recall which means memory
The other thing is knowledge into all things
And the other thing is things to come when you think of a let's say a good engineer
for example
Let's say a structural engineer civil engineer designing a bridge what makes him very good. He has those three characteristics
He remembers all of the engineering concepts principles
right
He
He has knowledge of all of those things
basically
You know the wide knowledge of all not only the bridges
But the who and what's going to be covering the bridge going over, you know, whether it's cars or people or trains
Knowledge of the earth, you know many other things
And also he's gonna have knowledge of things to come if the bridge is done, right?
How long it should last when it needs maintenance and or if it's not done, right? What will happen?
Predictable you see? Yeah the same in any field even with medicine
right
Only so those three rules apply to anyone that is a true quote-unquote professional. I don't like using that word professional
I like to define I like to define a modern professional as someone who is always learning more and more about less and less
So, I think we're about an hour in time, what do you think yes, it's exactly an hour
Do you
want to top it off with with a good ending or something and to look forward to because I mean a lot of information was
presented today and
I think we just did. Yeah, well three qualities that you're gonna have to good memory sitter to pursue the truth
And one of them is memory. The other one is knowledge into all things and the other thing is things to come. Yep
And that's a really and I believe this hasn't really been given out very much and clearly like that
I'll repeat them again a good memory
It would be maybe let's say it this way Rodrigo
Everybody's got a photographic memory, but most people are just out of film
Okay, yeah, the other thing is knowledge into all things
How many times have you heard that if you study something and you have a true desire to learn it?
You could probably learn it in 1 5th or 1 10th the time if you did it on your own
And you could probably be a local expert on that field within six months to a year a national expert within a couple of years
And a world expert on it in less than five years
If you really really got into a field or a subject, right?
So to have knowledge into all things, you know that if for example if you wanted to read a thousand page book
You just read three pages a day and you'll be finished with it in a year. Yeah, very easy
Very simple right now if you can read 30 pages a day you open 10 books
And you read just three pages out of each one every day and at the end of the year you've read 10,000 pages
right now
Very simple, but I'm not saying now to be book smarter because I've said
Several people said to me. Well, I don't need to get any information from a book
Well, they forget that the reason books and scrolls and computer files
Hard drives and things exist is for what?
to memorialize information
So it could be accessible to others. So whenever you hear someone says I don't need to get information about spirituality out of a book
Right. There is a space heater that person takes up space and they give off heat
So the next thing is you have to have knowledge of things to come
Right, look for example, let's say in terms of health if you see someone eating just sweets consistently and
You have knowledge in too many things. Let's say and you have good memory. Can you tell them about things to come?
Yes, of course with the knowledge that you have in the recollection of what you've studied
What did you tell that person if you eat too many sweets you might be diagnosed as being diabetic
You might lose your teeth. You might have
poor blood quality
Kidneys, right?
Aren't those things to come? Well, they might say well, I don't have that right now
Yes, but those are things to come just like the engineer. Hey, you know, I tell you, you know
They when they built that bridge they use faulty rivets and he's gonna say well that bridge will collapse where the faulty rigid rivets are
But it hasn't yet
So I don't need to read
Things to come and what's another term for things to come prophecy?
Yeah, you ever you ever wonder you know how we mentioned before
When you try too hard you're rewarded but the gods reward you with error
Yes, and if you're inefficient, let me add another thing if you're inefficient the gods take it away
But anyway, you ever notice how many of these let's just harp on the Christians for a minute how many Christians are
Professed proof they know prophecy and they don't they don't even know what day it is
By the way, it's the 18th day of the 11th month apparently and it's what they call December
What 30 is 30 ish something like that on the folks work schedule. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, and by the way
Australia is behind the Western world. We I have someone down there. You might know it by the name of John
We did some measurements and you guys are not a day ahead. Neither is New Zealand and parts of the world there
You're actually behind so they've really mucked it up. They've really screwed everyone really good on the whole planet
We've done that little through lawful measurement using the moon
Okay, right which doesn't the moon doesn't lie
Of course, yeah, and you don't have to rely on some Jesuit in the basement of the Vatican to draw up
Whatever, how are you gonna run your life now?
I'm not saying that there's some Jesuit in the Vatican do it drawing up the calendar
But it's a it's a it's pretty I mean if they're not who is
So basically that the new moon occurs way in the u.s. Before the Australasia
Does okay. Yeah
Visually say that the whole thing flips to the next day around the Levant around the east coast of the Mediterranean
Between between the east coast of the of the Mediterranean and a city in Iraq called her between there that distance of about
500 or 800 miles is where the transition takes place
the datum point so you see
Let's leave. I think there's a lot to be constructive about there's a lot to do
But you can't do it if unless you separate yourself. In other words if you're working in the sewer
And it's lunchtime. Are you gonna take out your lunch and eat it right there?
Are you gonna get out of the sewer wash your hands and eat it?
Yeah, okay, so
Whenever you hear about affecting the sewer the sewer
Purpose is to keep the waste moving and that's what you see online. That's what you see in the media
That's what you see in the universities. That's what you see coming out of institutions
They're keeping it moving right keep it moving move along move along move along nothing to see here
The only way you can be constructive is to learn how to set yourself apart from it and learn to view it objectively
And the reason it might sound dogmatic to some that's the only way well just think about it
If you really want to find out
What a hundred and fifty thousand volts and a thousand amps is you're gonna have to touch it
To find out the truth about it, right?
But what happens when you touch that you end up with just a pile of dust don't you become a pile of you, you know?
Doesn't matter what it is. You know those high tension power lines, right? Yeah
Yeah, if you short that out with your body
You'll just see a puff of smoke and some some black and white and gray and orange ash fall to the ground
And that's the truth of any matter
So that's why when you do the gods do not act in futility
When you go out into the public and you talk to a common oaf about the Pope's work schedule
And how you discovered these laws are contrary to how these institutions are behaving or whatever
They look at you with a blank stare like you're speaking a foreign language
Because the gods have shut their eyes and shut their ears and shut their mind
Until the time comes where it is to be open and right now is not the time yet
So
Enjoy good food good drink. It breeds good care promotes good character
I believe somewhere it was written there. It's all futility good conversation
Good drink good food a good time is all you can really call good here
you know with others so
Go build some bridges if you have
Yeah, so what do you think
By the way, thanks for coming back and everyone that's listening
Thanks for listening and we will try to keep these conversations going in their raw form. Thanks to Rodrigo
And yes others that won't listen and if if listeners want to contact you break, how did I read you?
The best way to do it most directly would be at go to
www.uncommonradio.com
you will find a email there, which is a
Uncommon sense radio one at gmail
You and there's a contact form there and I answer every email within a day or two fantastic
There there is also a Skype group
that is
You could contact on Skype called
Ocelli and the Greek as it spell it as it sounds Ocelli and the Greek
You could send a contact request there and we will probably either revive or begin small conference calls there
And how does that sound to you?
Nothing to mind here. Yeah
Thank you so much for your last hour of your time. Thank you for
And I do recall you telling me about the child sacrifice before but for some reason I had forgot
Yeah
That's fine no worries, I'm sure we will get into it again. Yep. Fantastic. All right, and many other things. Yes
Ciao