All right all the better
How have you been?
Could be better. But yeah, okay as the new year. I'm pretty sure it's the first month
yet, is it not or
What what's the date the proper date today?
hmm
Well, that's that's an interesting question because most people are operating as if it is the first month
So maybe we'll leave it at that. But it uh, it really seems to be
We're really into the second week of the twelfth month really, okay, meaning the when you when you say month, it's
Should be based on something
And what months are based on are the movements of the moon?
And what the day is based on is the movements of the Sun, but they've got everyone
Thinking that the the Sun is the movement the earth around the Sun is the movements of the year
It's not the months and days seem to be arbitrary because you guys I mean you guys meaning, you know, everyone else
Think the day starts in the middle of the night. Yeah. Yeah, it's it
well
Look, you know if if living a life of baseless abandonment brings joy
It will bring joy but what'll happen is when when you follow things that are baseless and
Fiat or fake or
Presumptuous to the point where they cannot no longer be found to be based on anything
It brings a certain amount of order systemic
Order, you know like a system you've heard of that. Yep
but it'll bite you in the ass because
You're going in a direction that has no
No start and no finish. So it's just basically
Baseless I mean what is there's any advantage to anything being baseless? It is only perceived and it's usually short-lived
This particular timekeeping
Convention has been in place roughly for 2,000 years, but mostly
500 maybe 300
And is it important to know how to keep time?
If you're going to relate with the dolphins the birds the whales the bees the goats the chickens the plants the rivers
relate as on a stewardship level or
Even from an observational level. You can't use that silly thing. They call
You know the Roman calendar Gregorian calendar or the World Convention
but you know if you look at the
World conventions and by the way before we get into that if we do
It's around the 12th moon, it's the first week or so of it. So so what that means is
It's it's it's pretty soon approaching the first moon again. You see because the cycle is usually 12 to 13
Moons and then we make a determination for the year. So before we get into other topics
Do you think that people calling it New Year right now are a little early or are they really late?
And the thing is to judge whether if someone is early or late you have to still have a reference point, right
so most people will
Yeah, it doesn't really matter
Because I think that so much baselessness fiat or fakeness or deceit when it goes
What we see when you have a normal or quote-unquote?
Healthful or healthy environment whether it's an individual or a political system or social system. You can impose on it a fiat or
deceitful degrace
degrading or whatever system and
It views it as a form of oppression
Because things aren't going well or suppression and then it bounces back, right?
It's as if you were kidnapped and thrown into a room tied up for three days
You're looking for a way to get out. You're looking to cut the rope and get out through the window or something
You know, but what's happened is it's been in place for so long that the actual victims
That's an interesting word, by the way victim
It means something sacrifice to a god in short you could look it up
The victims of these systems that are fiat whether it's the economic the medical the legal or the calendrical system
have now been
Bred into it and down bread meaning down bread meaning it has degraded
Their ability to defend against it and to rise into something that has substance
And when I deliberately use the word rise because it's a very low
Sense of existence to rely on things that have no basis, right?
something like that would be
You know imagine people add sweetener to their food and that sweetener is completely synthesized and it just has the appearance of being sweet
but it's really a
Very processed synthesized chemical that gives the appearance of sweetness, but once it enters the body, it's very toxic
Right, you've heard of things like that in food
Now it was those people that typically indulge not just engage but indulge
You know engage meaning once in a while that indulge make that their staple what what happens to their system it breaks down
To the point where applying remedy or getting away from it. There's so much damage. You can't get away. So
Yeah, I mean it's okay
You know and by the way
The year always started in the spring and always ended in the fall and the winter was an interim period and what's interesting
You know being here on the northern part of the world where it's winter, you know
You've heard of the saying the grass is always greener somewhere else. Well, it is down by you, isn't it?
Yeah, so it is greener by you yeah, you see so that that statement might hold true it's always greener somewhere else, right
Yeah, there's always some some other pursuit that if you have a desire to do such
but the worldview
Still is is a matter of baselessness and its victims meaning a mankind
you know, this is the
difficult thing for people to comprehend that
The the initialization of the species, you know, the humankind mankind
Was at its pinnacle when it was initialized and has been degraded since a
simple way to observe that would be
typically what you would see
Someone gets a brand new car, right? Yes. It's got that new car smell. The tires are fresh. Everything is totally fresh
Yes
Pair of shoes or anything now, this is a you know, we're talking about the gene pool now
What's happened is, you know, if one of the things that the establishment is is
terrified of
Allowing to be realized is ancient history real ancient history on how the lifespan of mankind was very very long and
the
Veracity of the of the human character was very very high. You know, I mean it was we had people that were
You know imagine someone who's extremely talented at what they do
super professional in any sport or craft or mastership the people back then they had a level of mastership and performance and
Based on their character and the fortitude of their character. That is nothing like we see today, right?
That's why you see a lot of the superhero the Zaro ism and all that stuff
It's still you know legends or the age the Greeks had the age of the heroes, right?
Hercules and all that so you imagine society take the best of the best of your society today
physical
Intelligence, let's say I mean everyone has the same intelligence, but you know wit
Being able to perform fortitude of character and that would have been your your average person back then
You're right. Just like the brand-new car again, right? So
So this is a these are things that really are not discussed and maybe shouldn't be discussed to an unaware juvenile mindset
But you know, here's the interesting thing Rodrigo and we actually if you could remind me we were gonna we brought up the time
We're getting to
Probably baselessness and things but we've always discussed that
But always meaning, you know
It's something that needs to be brought out because we're not talking about
You know being probed by space aliens time travel and all that other hoopsie-doopsie
Stuff on based on intention and quantum all these things that people have been sidetracked with
You know the main thing that you cannot sidetrack and the main thing that everyone and anyone can indulge in in this
ridiculousness that we're in right now is
The basic comforts and how do you know what makes you comfortable or uncomfortable?
Well, you perceive it in your mind, but you actually manifest it in your body, right?
Like you might like to sleep on a firm bed if someone asks you but you're not on a bed
But you know when you want to experience that comfort you actually seek out a firm bed to lay down on
Someone might perceive in conversation or you might perceive in conversation
They might like a soft bed, but they really don't experience that comfort until they actually physically do that, right?
You know someone might like let's say for food
I enjoy fish and
They're just speaking in conversation, but they really don't experience that level of comfort until they actually partake in fish
You see so one of the things people can express is if you notice very often is you know?
How to make the world a better place. What are we going to do? Why is this so bad?
How is it going to get better or this and that this is still the cerebral spiritual?
Communication of things to come or things that people prefer their heresy, you know what they like
But the bottom line is until those things are actually experienced through the body the physical. You know modality, right?
You know like when you say you're not feeling well or crook or whatever
Well it depends you know you might be in an uncomfortable chair or you might be in the most comfortable
Physical position and if you're still not feeling well, then it's something that needs to be remedied further
But typically when people are not quote-unquote feeling well if you actually change the physical setting
To the most pleasurable one they tend to feel better
You know just as simple as if you're tired go take a hot bath. You know thinking about it's not going to do it
You have to actually do it to be feel better
So one thing that everyone and everyone can still experience are this this wonderful thing that we call comfort pleasure
Well-being how else would you say it energizing the body you know or retiring the body to sleep if needed, right?
That's a simple way to reenergize also
You know all these things so how why why isn't there talk?
On how to remedy or not even remedy means that you have something that's specific, but the general comforts
You know why is it that we always are perceiving in discussion or in?
Media that it's the the very wealthy. You know that are being the jet-set
Let's say right that was an old term in the 50s because you know the Jets were afforded
Why are they the only ones enjoying themselves?
You know it's not true anyone and everyone can enjoy some kind of what they call creature comfort, right?
What do you like to do right?
What do you find comfortable? What do you find pleasurable?
What do you find in aiding in your recovery? You know from the day or the week or the year?
people go on holiday, so
one thing that anyone and everyone can partake in which I find lacking in general discussion is
And even in specific discussions because they're so it's very the discussions are too narrow and shallow
But how do you increase the quality of your comfort?
Level on this planet because basically let's take it that you're not
suffering some kind of ailment or a
Condition that you're in a constant state of pain or discomfort
But let's say you know your everyday people that work or don't work, or you know are up and about
Why not discuss things that just make everything a little bit better now everything would be what you eat what you wear?
What you drink how you rest?
How you travel how you communicate all these these little minor you've heard of like tips and tricks and things like that well
What are the most important things to being on this planet or any planet?
Let's say you jumped on a starship and went somewhere
And they dropped you off on the planet Rodrigo you'd say but wait a second
I need food clothing and shelter right in that order pretty great. I
You know I mean you know you can't just leave me here
And most people complain that it's just not good enough
Yes, I've got nothing to compare it because I haven't actually had anything better like you said before you haven't actually done it or tried it
So what is it that we're complaining about?
Hmm well not so much a complaint, but if maybe let's say some people how many people take it for granted it don't complain probably the
majority
there's a group of people that do complain, but I think that's also a
the
The the marketing gets a little perverted where they actually market to people the desire to go into the market and buy new products
through
Complaining you know like aren't you tired of this being this way?
You know whatever you know the marketing aspect, but how about just?
Optimizing what you've got is the point that I want to make is like food
How many people do you know or at least is a rhetorical question that actually take the care?
Today that in preparing meals as it was let's say 30 years ago. Maybe do you want to go 50 years ago?
You know an average meal. Let's say a dinner or supper took an hour to prepare on average years ago
Now it might be less than 15 minutes 20
Yeah
So take time. You know here's the thing
You know people get into their work into their projects and things and it's good to do that if it's a full-time endeavor and have
Someone else cook for you
You know slavery is a lawful thing
if you can afford a
Servant or a slave and you have to take care of them well by the way
And I'm using this to kind of eat some people on because those words have taken on bad terms, right?
If you have someone to wait on you
Or you have a someone in that is considered in the servitude position take care of them
And they will take care of you. We've been told that
Servants and slaves are always mistreated which is not true
There are many slaves that have lived in splendor and there were many sovereigns or kings that lived in squalor, right?
so
So the the thing is many people can't don't want to afford such
Company because that's what it is when you have someone with you regarding of regardless of their status their company aren't they?
they're accompanying you even if you're alone or you have a small quote-unquote family unit or
Accompanied by associates or friends or lovers or whatever you want to call the people around you relatives or kin
Try to come into agreement because what's interesting is if you want to do something and you're living in a particular household
It's best when everyone is in agreement with it because they might be either
Apathetic or indifferent to it or they might be in opposition. So it's always good to see if there's agreement on a thing on
The easiest thing to increase one's quality of comfort in life is to increase the quality of their food
Not only how it's prepared and how you eat it, but the actual quality of the produce itself or the materials that you use
so
You know when you go to the shops
Take your time
And buy the highest quality, you know, sometimes, you know, let's just speak to the more of the urban environment
These large shops these large. What do they call them down there? They call them supermarkets groceries
Okay, there you go
You notice that even the most of the things that are supposed to be fresh or wrapped in tightly wrapped in plastics. Yeah
And they seem to be fresh but you know what one well
Here's a little thing. I tell people is if you're just limited to that type of market
Why don't you they usually have a department whether it's the vegetable stock area the meat fish stock area
ask for some help in the service and ask if they perhaps something have something in the back that is not been
Wrapped in plastic and sitting out there and they might say yes, we do have
You know a grouping of this in storage cold storage back here
You know very often they there is enough courtesy in these places
because they do sense competition that if they know the managers do tell them to you know, give good customer service and
You will find out like
They might bring you out something that is you know, you might you might end up taking it
Home wrapped in plastic, but it won't be sitting around
They'll wrap it for you and weigh it and price it immediately, right?
Yeah, so always make the best choice
You know there there are tips and tricks like for example
There's certain restaurants have pre-prepared foods and if let's say the chips or something has been sitting for a while
You might just say I'd like to have that but I'd like it without any salt
Well everything the whole batch that they're presenting to the public salted
So now they have to go and prepare a small batch for you without salt, right?
I'm not saying that you should eat it without salt
You don't want to eat fried food without salt because the salt helps digest it
So once they produce a fresh batch for you, whether it's chips or whatever
You just take it aside and you go ahead and salt it
But don't let them see it too evidently because they might wonder what the hell you're doing, but right
Yeah, and this way you have something that's been more freshly prepared because things that are food that is freshly prepared or freshly
imparted from where it's
Harvested from always tends to be a little bit better than that stuff. That's been sitting around
So you can increase your food in produce quality that way the other way is to when you prepare it learn
How to be skillful in food preparation now that that's going to be difficult because there was
There's a thing called cable television, and there was a large boom of cooking shows that started about 20 years ago
Right if you're familiar with it, and I've been watching them
I haven't really subscribed to any of that for over a decade but ever since then and I and I've watched you know they look so
fanciful and so
indulging and
Enthusiastic to the to the viewer, but I watch them
I said you're not going to learn how to cook by watching these cooking shows because they never discuss the subtleties and the things you
Should do to to actually you know lead to a more digestible meal, right?
So learn how to do proper food preparation. There's some very simple tricks actually we did
If you go to uncommon radio archives
With I did with Seth Michael a way back
We did a show called perfect rice and we gave about a dozen cooking tips there
Anyone who tried them found them to be beneficial so anyone could go to
uncommon radio.com go to the archives
And you will find a show called perfect rice and then some more on cooking we've discussed over a dozen maybe two dozen
ways to improve various
preparations of foods from rice to veg to meats to stocks to soups to roasts and
Very simple yeah, very simple
You know one of them was called how to make the perfect rice and with the interesting thing the reason I mentioned that Rodrigo
Is I remember traveling and cooking rice off of the back of a vehicle in a camping situation?
And I told the people asked me. What are you making and they?
Said preparing rice, and they were shocked because they know they're thinking like you know that's almost an impossibility to cook rice properly
So it's very simple
You know and and you know things veg like potatoes you know baked potatoes tend to be some of the most delicious
Well, you know you don't have to fire up an oven you boil the potatoes unpeeled in water for 15 or 20 minutes
Depending on your altitude on the end the potato and then drain the water and just gently
Stovetop bake it in the in the pot with the lid on just turn the potatoes every five minutes
Let the pot get warm not too hot if it's a thin bottom pot it won't work too
Well, and you could do stovetop baking right?
I've even cooked a pizza on a Barbie. You know where you think that's something that should be you know you think a pizza
How well how are you gonna do that right?
Well, it's simple you you make your dough, and you put it right on the grill
Don't let it fall through right and have all your toppings ready to go and after 30 seconds when you flip it
You know you put the the side that was on the grill now up you immediately apply your sauce and your cheese
Yeah, and that's already very hot you see and
And you get a very quick pizza in a minute and a half on the Barbie
Which is typically when you tell someone you're gonna cook a pizza
You know that's you're gonna have to fire up an oven and that takes a lot of energy and time yeah
So I'm not suggesting you try to cook pizza a fresh pizza on a Barbie, and you'll and it'll work for you
But I just gave you that how to do it really quickly you can imagine that you can do it if you need to
and if you have to
Yes, you've got nothing else to wait and that's I mean not like you're gonna have pizzas laughing
You're gonna have in your fridge, but at least you are able to do it if you need to so yes
Flatbreads of flour is still relatively cheap just get some flour add a little bit of water perhaps an egg and some fat
Could be animal fat like butter or vegetable fat and just knead that dough and let it cool down
And you have a flatbread which you can actually cook on the grill or on a frying pan
You just 30 seconds on each side, and you have this wonderful fresh flatbread
It doesn't have to be leavened because when you say bread typically it's leavened
You know the yeast rises, and you have to temper it and all this
It's a lot of work, and if you don't do the yeast properly if it's too active you might have
Digestive problems you're gonna put this super active agent into your body
And you'll wonder why you're getting up in the night wanting to blow hot air balloons through your backside with it. You know so
It's not good. Yeah, so so there are lots of tips so the thing is learn about good food preparation
Don't be hasty with your food when I mean with your food meaning start learning to take time. It's a stress relief
Many people tend to focus you see they let's say they have what's called
You know their occupation and their family life and all this and you'll notice if you watch if you watch the silent
Videotape of your average human especially in the Western world you watch
They're very contemplative even when they're working and doing repetitive tasks or with their family members or friends
They're not they're idle. They're really just they're not doing much. You know I mean they could be still working
You know or again. You know at a job or traveling or whatever, but they're they're very so they think too much
There's too much
You'll see like a family you know now that prepares a dinner in five or ten minutes or 15 or 20 like we said maybe
They have plenty of time during the evening to actually spend an hour hour and a half to make the dinner
But they don't they sit around watch television they might talk that might each go to their own room or whatever why not?
Make it a point to spend at least an hour or even more to make a home-cooked meal
And the quality if you don't most people
Still don't know how to prepare food. I've discovered
There's a thing that I call it
I call it white people food right and it has nothing to do with the color of your skin and I have to
Bring this up. You know in ancient Egypt and in ancient cultures when something had no flavor or no lack of character
It was called white
Not not not based on its color like white rice or white snow or white robes
But when something lacks like it's it's
Yes, yes, like it's got everything out of it, so what's left is just it's no color right that was a popular ancient Egyptian term
So when I say white people food it does you could be Latin or?
Black or you know Asian it doesn't matter. It's just this lack of character
And it's taken out of connotation, but but quote unquote you know when I say white people food if you go to the American Midwest
Or certain northern Europeans where the people are more what they call waspy white Anglo-Saxon Protestant right that type
you know there's these are maybe pejoratives or whatever, but
You'll notice that their food is not very good like let's take for example England. Have you ever seen?
English restaurants being propagated throughout the world no
No one wants that kind of food right or American diner. You know and all that those are European
You know when you get to the southern Mediterranean rim certain parts of Asia
coastal cities, it's very the culture are more
exciting and
whatever if you go to like the northern latitudes of Europe like
Netherlands Norway Holland
England or whatever the food is just like you got to be joking. You know this is not very good preparation
You know what is the most popular food in England? It's Indian food. That's the national dishes chicken tiki marsala
Mm-hmm, right
so
So now here. We're crossing over in a white meaning. You know you know the white yeah
With some sense it is
That way to that the best foods in the world you'll find
Along the Mediterranean rim and the central parts of Asia coastal parts of Asia. This is a matter of taste now
This is being subjective right?
But if you look at the food combining and the skill and the level of flavors and all that you you you
want to avoid
northern parts of Europe Midwest America probably
Central parts of Australia as well these these areas the foods are not regarded as very well
Does it mean that there's still people there that can't cook or whatever, but the culture seems to be very base
Lacks and eloquence and it lacks of finesse and it lacks flavor right
So
You know that, but again. There's levels of it, so this again the you know pursue things that are pleasant
Pursue things that are what would you say?
From a subjective point of view you find pleasurable and the easiest thing to improve your quality of life
Is to pursue better food stuffs food preparation food quality?
You know and and whatever
so
Current lifestyle people eat just for the sake of
Just having to need to eat not because they need
Sometimes sit around at dinner table and converse with a family or enjoy the whole food preparation process
It's they just want to get in the gate and get over and done with so you can you do it when I've done before it's
not
Yeah, they deprive themselves
You know a lot of pleasure can be gotten through the mouth right as the ancient Greeks used to say meaning through food, right?
The Japanese call it umami, which is a very savory flavor. You know delicious. You know something very pleasurable
I
Have seen through going through parts of America here again the the white people food thing where what people were eating?
I found to have no flavor and the quality was so low and this was their staple
And when I would stay with them and eat like that for a few days
I really got sick. I felt very low energy
Sore throat kind of feeling like it, and this is how these people eat every day all their lives no wonder
They're dependent. I mean there's such a low quality of life based on what goes through their mouth and
You know it's it's it's sad sad by the way stands for set standard American diet by the way
So yeah, so food is the other thing the other thing is we said food clothing and shelter clothing is very important as well
You know wearing things that fit well. You know never
Never ever ever ever ever shortchange yourself on shoes
Right cheap shoes. You've heard that could you could actually
If you don't have a good constitution a skeletal constitution
It could actually damage the feet if the bones you have more bones in the feet than anywhere else in the body
You know in terms of the the size of the body right yeah feet and hands
So you you know there's a
Saying European saying that you if you can fit Italian shoes, you're blessed right. It's wonderful. You know
Italian made shoes, but also the Spanish and and
Portuguese they
Make wonderful shoes
So the with clothing to start from the bottom up you you never want to get quote-unquote a cheap pair of shoes
Now cheap doesn't mean price. It means the actual quality is cheap
Yeah, you always want to get the best shoes you can afford or want to afford
Right so and you most people would get a pair of shoes it might last six months to a year
I when I get quality shoes I can have them for 20 years
right and I
Have several shoes now for I've been rocking for 15 years
And they feel just as good as you know the the week that they were broken in so
The thing about making a move on buying shoes for example is let's say you do need a pair of shoes
And if you're not in a desperate place
That you absolutely positively have to have a new pair of shoes right now
start investigating what type of shoe it is and you know when in a
Purveyor of high-quality shoes see what the price is for something that you
consider to be high quality for yourself and
Start setting some aside for it
You may not be able to afford them you may not want to afford them right now
But if you think that way you might be able to
Afford them in a week or a month or so you see so think ahead when it comes to buying shoes
And just for using the you know the the common fiat currency
Upwards of a hundred and fifty to two hundred for a good pair of shoes is not unusual
That's where they usually start, and we're not talking about needless markup either
You know what I mean. We're not because some of these clothing outlets have a fivefold markup. You know what I mean
There's a there's a couple of stores. We have names for them like one of them
We I'm not going to name it, but we call it needless markup. You can imagine what it's
It's it's an NM is the is what the store is but so so yeah, but pursue and also with the advent of
Electronic commerce right eBay and all these other things you can actually you have more
Mode you say more leeway or more freedom to seek out a better price like for example on
yeah, like cycling shoes that I used to prefer were upwards of three to four hundred and
Kangaroo leather by the way kangaroo leather is very good because it's resistant to moisture
If they would ever get wet they don't shrink and they're very elastic when they're wet
You know some of the finest shoes are still kangaroo leather those ruse do provide good skin for that
So I would say
You know now I've heard that similar shoes like that can be gotten for less than half on what they call
We know some of the outlets on on the internet. You know you know commerce, right?
eBay and Amazon or whatever so
So a shoes and then from the from the bottom up there
You know you consider you know how we've discussed lawful food and things being lawful
When you when you start researching law which is dreadful to humanity all of humanity by the way
They don't want to they want to go and study what they they're told law is and if you look at
What you're told law is just like what you're told what the gods are just what you're told what money is or the calendar you'll
Find out it's fake. It's nothing, but you just have to do it anyway if you're going to function with these idiots, but
When you find out what law is it comes from your God even in the Western civilization?
They tell you the law is the justice system
Which is the revived goddess religion the Babylonian goddess it goes on and on and on that's so that's why you know when you get
Entangled with these legal monsters. You know you always it never ends up well, right?
but but nonetheless
You're if you go to the highest form of law that has been given by claim
It's not what you believe you just seek out claims
You know there are claims of low nature and then claims a very high nature
There's only one that claims that created everything and gives law right and it has nothing to do with your belief
This is from a literary point of view right
So when you understand what has been given or communicated you'll find that what is lawful for people
There are laws in there about food and and how to do commerce and even
How to keep time and even know what to wear and he says my people when you wear clothes on your body do not wear
mixed fiber
So and it gives an example like don't mix the wool and the linen
And you know some people miss you know most people lack reading comprehension and most people can't hear what you're saying
Because when they hear things or they get these visual impulses or sonic impulses
They're trying to compare it to things that they already know it's a comparative thing people really are really not open to new information
That's why it's so easy to
See how so much is being disclosed the people yet are complaining that none nothing is being disclosed right?
They don't pick up on it, but what I mean by what is lawful about wearing on the human body is not mixed fiber
So it would be hundred percent of a particular fiber and some people have come back say well synthetics
You don't want to wear them as well. It doesn't say anything about synthetics the thing is if it's a synthetic
It should be a hundred percent synthetic not you see a lot of shirts now
They're wrinkle-free and they're 80% cotton 20% polyester right you've seen that
Yeah, that's not lawful, but if you were a hundred percent polyester
It would be lawful or a hundred percent cotton and also you it says also that you can sew one
Fabric on another like for example. I have a 100% worsted wool
suit jacket let's say a
Sport jacket and the lining is made of 100% silk and the lining is sewed on to the wool outer layer
That's lawful because the lining is not mixed fiber and the outer is not mixed fiber
So you so you can layer different types of material now also. There's another interesting thing about it certain
Synthetic fabrics are all made from petroleum
you know like
nylon polyester
Lycra those are all oil petroleum products to a degree
There's that's kind of open whether a blend of those would be considered mixed fiber or not you see
So that's that's a gray area
But certain things that are very close, and if you want to get look in the chemistry that maybe like a 10% lycra
90% polyester it may not be mixed fiber, but even though it's being called that because inherently they're both petroleum products, right
So with clothing. I guess the shoes are important because can you think of another article of?
Clothing that could change the skeletal formation on a body, and you know create an ailment of some sort other than shoes
It's kind of hard to maybe if your pants are too tight your voice
Well I was saying underwear yeah, yeah, I have a reason like if you're if you're a man or not in Italian compressed
Right right the the male that needs to stay away from the body for regulation and whatever and for the women
there's the upper the the
Trusses and bras and things like that. I think used to be called trusses years ago, right
Yeah, those create circulatory issues thermal issues, right
Yeah
So
Yeah, and you notice the fitted aspect of clothing you know
With the buttons and the zippers and all that if you go back thousands of years
It seems that there was thousands of years where people had more wraparound clothing
You would have a sheet. You know like a toga something that was cut to your height, and you would wrap it
a covering right
Interesting isn't it yeah?
So you didn't yeah more free-flowing and more easy on the on the body. It's like it's not fitted
Yeah
Yeah, I know everything is really specifically fit and almost unfit you know
So consider really good clothing and really good clothing, okay?
the lawful aspect is
No mixed fiber and the and the really good shoes again would be a good recommendation and like Rodrigo said
The undergarments the way they're structured today could cause maladies in the body right so
So the next thing would be perhaps on clothing anything else you think on on how to experience
Comfort you know we got food
Pursue good food preparation good produce spend more time on it
A lot more time and then good shoes and good clothing if you can
Think about how to you know increase the quality and that on your own preference
And then we then there would be food clothing and shelter
Yeah, but
Furnishings may be in shelter. Yeah, uh-huh you don't necessarily wear them, but you lay on them or you you
Yeah, yeah, think about a bed a one-third of your life is spent on in bed
Isn't it if you sleep eight hours a day every day?
Yeah
So that's a third of your yeah, you made your bed now you got to lay in it right so
That's say no more
See what you prefer again things that if you're you know that's that's a good point Rodrigo the furnishing of the bed
You should also just like the shoes get the best one you want to afford or can't afford yeah
Right yeah, and there's a certain mattress
Suit all people like does a bed have to be firm or can it be soft and be firm is it just preferential?
Yeah, yeah
Like an example is someone who's let's say recovering from certain injuries might prefer or certainly has a certain condition
Sensitivity might prefer a softer
bed and
Someone who is more athletic more toned
More robust skeletal you know features might prefer a firm one
Much to say about beds. I don't know if we could even start beginning the topic and to cover it
but you know the one thing about beds are you know there's a
Fellow Abraham Kareem, I believe it gets into biogeometry
They did some study around turn of the century about people who had certain cancers
And they would go around with dividing rods like dowsing rods to find ley lines through the earth
And they found that like a lady who had died of stomach cancer in the 30s
They went around and doused the ley lines through the earth and magnetic and water lines coming up through the earth on the property
And they found that there was a very powerful negative energy one coming up on this property
And they followed it and it actually went across the house through the bedroom, and it was over the bed
Underneath the bed coming up through the earth where this woman slept around the region of the stomach
Interesting right
So actually I had recommended. There's someone
I know another part of the country and her husband was diagnosed with the C word right yeah
Cancer and I said well, why don't you start? It's early on why don't you move the location of where you sleep?
You know they didn't have much choice
I said we'll sleep on the couch sleep on just change the location by at least five or ten feet or another room
But not in line maybe a diagonal from the card in the line
Right cardinal meaning north southeast west don't you know and actually within two months later. She called me says he's recovering
You know he's getting to as he seems much better
so
Yeah, so where you sleep a third of your time would imprint certain things
Getting it getting into that topic. Yes, the earth does emanate ley lines
How would you how else would you see you've heard of this Rodrigo?
I'm sure the listener has perhaps might have as well those things could be checked out
Nothing to panic over, but just really simple simply from an innate perspective
If you're not feeling well, or you're you're plagued with a particular
What would you call it chronic thing change where you sleep?
This is the very old adage. I've discussed before when people go to certain people says you know
I'm not feeling well
What should I do and then the proper answer is how the hell would I know what you should do?
I don't know what you're doing. You know what you're doing. Just change what you're doing
The way you feel whether it's good or bad is is a product or a symptom of everything else
So if you're feeling really good, let's say you're in you're in good health, and you're vital
It's because of all your other behavior and what you like and don't like right if you're not feeling
Well, that is actually a product of what you're doing as well
So just stop doing what you're doing and your condition will change right yeah
so
That's just one of the simple
applications of
You know you know where where you sleep, and how you sleep
There's also a lot of discussion should the head be towards the north should the head be towards the south that's open for investigation
There's no place. I could really send anyone to start looking at it
But just consider if you're feeling a certain way
It's because it's a byproduct or a product directly related to everything else you're doing and if you don't like the way you feel
Or are just change everything else and that condition has to change also right usually does unless it's very heavily
Based on one's Constitution you know
So the conditions can't change so this in terms of the shelter being comfortable
Ultimately when it's hot out you want it to be cool, and when it's cold out you want it to be warm, right?
You want you there's a certain median temperature that is most comfortable so learn how to manage the temperature and air quality first
Of course you don't want leaking roofs and other things like that
But if you can up the quality of where you live the easiest way to up the quality of
Where anyone lives or their shelter is to keep it clean or cleaner?
Learn cleaning practices and cleaning practices does it mean going to the shops or the grocery store and buying all these?
Funky chemicals and spraying them everywhere
some of the best cleaning
Yeah, they have residues and some of the best cleaning
Products to use it's just plain water and just a very basic, so
Vinegar can be a vinegar tends to break down a lot of finishes, and it is pretty stinky
You could use a little bit of vinegar when you want acidic you could also use something called borax of 40 mule team
You could put a drop of dish soap in there
Also with soaps and cleaning things do you know that especially the synthetic ones have you heard that you these?
Industrial chemicals cause cancers and things like that. It's not so it's actually the fragrances that are the can't carcinogens
Have you ever seen like the commercial dish soap or laundry soaps and?
Things that are very strong are synthetic fragrances as they say they're supposed to smell like this
Yeah, yeah, it's really the fragrances that have been discovered to caught be the carcinogenic aspect so fragrance free tends to be
cleaner
Most of your if you have like rubbing alcohol isopropyl alcohol in a spray bottle is
Very good also for cleaning surfaces that are resilient or non-porous from grease and things like that
You could look up. You know natural or less
Industrial types of cleaning like windows for example. I've seen
Housekeepers go into houses and spray this blue liquid all over the windows
Window cleaner and all that well alcohol is
Sure alcohol is far superior with distilled water, or if you can't if you have rainwater. That's just as good
And just keeping a clean house if you have a vacuum cleaner
You have to mind that what's blowing out the back end is not always filtered as well as you might think it is either
Keep what I call a chemical shed
Even if you have an apartment if you have chemical cleaning chemicals and things like that a group them all together
Don't have them distributed through the house and storage and and put it in a box outside of where you live
Right yeah
Yeah, you know even like you mentioned the window cleaner if you do have any of these industrial cleaners
Put them in a box outside or a cabinet outside where you live
It's it's kind of difficult in a very urban environment in a studio apartment. Let's say to do that
But you'll always find some way to do it
Just don't have it where you live inside with where you live would be defined as you know if you
Where you live would be when you close all the doors and the windows that space defined on the inside is where you live
Right yeah, yeah, so that would include the closets right so you want to
Maintain what's called. I call it chemical shed
Someone asks me. Do you have such-and-such cleaner? I say yeah, it's in the chemical shed
And
That would be just a box or a cabinet outside of the living space a
Closet or storage within the living space is not outside the living space
It's still within that would out gas and right an interesting way to view
This is you ever go to the supermarkets when you start going to the house cleaning aisle and as you're walking down
You're being fumigated you ever notice that
stinks
Yeah, yeah, and the same things
It's
It's within the same building yeah, yeah, it gets sucked up and recirculated yeah
So that is also happening in a we even with just one bottle in the house
It's just that it's not as you're not as sensitive to pick it up
So keeping chemicals it's around you 24-7 if you do that as well
I mean compared to the supermarket you're in there for like 10-15 minutes
But at home right if you keep it in science 24-7 just that little bit is enough just to make you sick
Yes from from a homeopathic point of view even though
It's you know in homeopathics the stronger the dilution the more diluted the stronger its potency in one effect, right?
Yeah in the field effect, so yeah absolutely in
Considering that its presence is enough not the volume as well
And that could be considered as an absolute that if something is present it is giving it
It is affecting the field and the environment just by its presence
You know it's interesting in a lot of sports drug testing when they test these athletes for drugs
They test them for the presence of drug in the body right not how much right?
So it's the same concept here
You know is it present at all so so clean?
Avoiding things that would be intrusive to the system. You know the biological systems
The other thing is if you have
Animals in the house make sure they have access to outside if they're not their areas must be kept very clean
Because typically the way animals live is when they're out in nature. They do their business and nature takes care of it
Where when animals do their business in a cage or in the house there you have to take care of it, right?
So be diligent with that
the other thing about
keeping
enjoying your time at home
what you call home, let's say the place where you rest and you have your possessions is
Other than cleanliness and keeping a chemical free and keeping even the animals clean clean clean is that you enjoy going there?
you know for example if you have
Relatives that might live with you or roommates or even a spouse that you don't appreciate their company
eventually
You will not
You will find that you lack the comfort that can be gotten from a peaceful or happy place you might call your abode
It might even go to the point where the where you the actual abode itself is fine
But the neighbors are not where you what you you know they kind of stress you out
How many times have you heard people you know I'm not going home after work
I'm going to the pub because going home stresses me out right have you heard that you know?
So it's all too common
So those things need to be resolved
It should be a place that you find welcoming to yourself and others and is a place that you
Enjoy going to and you find pleasure
in
So that that would be the spiritual or the psychological site. You know PSY again
Same thing make sure that those things are in order and believe it or not
It's real easy to clean the house real easy to put all the chemicals outside
But sometimes it's nearly impossible to get that side fixed
You know a bad neighbor or a spouse or a family condition or roommate condition that is
Something that I don't wish on anyone, but those things have to be
Addressed because you know what if it's if you feel like where you live is not a good situation
It's going to fall apart eventually, or it will make you so sick that you will fall apart eventually
So it's always best to start addressing those things the emotional spiritual. You know aspect first
Yes, it doesn't mean to be transient it just means that if you need to move sometimes that's the best thing
It's always hard to move and restart somewhere
But when you settle in just make sure you have everything in place that your mind and your spirit
You know or spirit right same thing can rest there
And that is what makes what they call a happy home or abode is ultimately the mindset, right?
So I mean, I think we've covered quite a bit there. Yeah
Those basic things food clothing and shelter do you notice how I mean you've been around
radio and whatever
This this digital format on discussions and countless hours about this than the other
I think we did a tidy little explanation that could applies to everyone and could probably help everyone don't you think the last 50 minutes?
So it can be of them basically this
50 minutes for the discussion you don't have to be a believer of follow-up anything. It's somewhat common sense
Yeah, and even if the Illuminati are threatening to kill everyone who cares if you've got a good meal good good shoes and
Good a good place to live. Yeah
Right, you see what I mean?
Or if those bad aliens are gonna, you know fold the space-time continuum or whatever, you know
It doesn't matter really, you know
And if they do come to the house invite him in for some, you know
Freshly baked flatbread or something or a pizza that you made on the Barbie
And by the way, just just to throw back to shoes never buy shoes. You can't run in think about that
Yeah, right why would you buy a pair of shoes you can't run in and I'm not mean
Yeah, you might want to run to something or you might want to run away from something. Yeah. Yeah
So what's the point? Well, you you tell me Rodrigo. Have you seen you know, I was out at the shops yesterday
And it was quite a shock. I try to keep to myself, but I was at what they call a mall
And where I'm at
Yeah, they have a real they have some really elaborate
I mean, I I tell you was as soon as I walked in I found it to be very pleasurable
Because it's some of it's like some of the high-end casinos in Las Vegas where they pump this
Smell of fresh sea air, I guess they have a concoction
you know have you been to any of the these casinos where it smells like you know when you go to the beach you have
That salty fresh air and the the faint smell of cocoa butter
suntan lotion in the background, you know
It's kind of pleasurable and you walk into this mall and the ventilation is very the air is very fresh almost perfumy
But not sickly pleasurable and I'm walking through there and I'm looking at the way
People looked and how they oh, man, I was just humanity you're in really but anyway
I was in quite a shock, but and I looked at what people wearing on their feet and you know
There's a big fat about these things called sneakers. I guess like what do they call them running shoes and other things, right?
Yeah, those things are not very good for your feet. There's a few I've actually purchased one years ago. That is a
Forgot the name of the company, but it was purely ergonomic. I mean the laces don't go up the middle
They kind of go on a diagonal the cover, you know
Because the top of the foot is not high up across the middle the last kind of turns towards the ankle, right?
And they're they're very ergonomic
But most of these shoes that I see these people don't look like they're walking to this around on earth
They look like they're ready to walk on the moon
With them, you know
Yeah, those things that yeah, so
Yeah, even those I and I've seen some that's been a fact where they wear them with no laces or not
I'd you can't run in that either folks. So and then some of the high-heeled shoes. I've seen women wear
Things like that, I'm not saying don't necessarily get them but have you ever seen even in
Shown and memorialized in film where there's a scene where there's let's say
Some well-dressed people let's say in an evening affair and though and it's time for everyone to run because the the big monsters coming
And the women take their shoes off and run barefoot, right?
Yes
So there's always going to be a need that you should have very functional shoes and the food of course take more time and
Make your abode or where you rest your head for a third of your life when you're sleeping
And we're not talking about those other people that partake in really
Substances and lifestyles that where they don't sleep used to that will and by the way, you can never make up for lost sleep
Once the body is taxed or degraded from it
You can sort of recover from that condition, but it never you could never you see right
You could never really recover from even though you might get a little bit better and seem better
It's it's very important to get that rest
So yeah, so you see we can actually continue
We could have done an hour just on food an hour just on clothes in an hour just on the house, but I think
Putting a little thing like this together
where we just
It I wouldn't say it's really happy talk
I wouldn't say it's doom and gloom, but I would say that it's very practical that anyone everyone is
yeah, and I need to think about these things more than they than their thought a lot of the
People these days are going to the internet and they're thinking looking for what's called current events politics or things that share their point of
View, but I noticed there is extremely lacking on how to make their lives better
And and a lot of people have mistaken, you know going and getting a product like some special drops that they take
or some powder or
You know, whatever
Joining a website or whatever is going to improve their life quality
if you don't have a concept of good food preparation and actually taking the time and good good shoes you could walk in and a
Very comfortable house. You're you're yeah, you're not
Being dummy loaded so there's much to do again uncommon radio.com you'll find
Archives perhaps under with the Greek and Seth Michael on the perfect rice is the episode and the one following that also we discussed food
Had gotten a lot of feedback on
People preparing the perfect rice where they were just definitely scared of making rice
It was whenever they try to make rice Lee having to go given it a crack at making that. Oh
Yeah, I've gotten many many responses back. That was terrified of making rice whenever I do it
It was just a lump of starch and this is just perfect
Also the stove pot we actually had a caller in on Ocelli in the Greek about
I told the wife about the potatoes and that's how she does them from now on, you know, the stovetop baked versus, you know, and
You know just
Certain preparations also when you're let's say cooking a pot of beans or a stew or a soup
From scratch you ever notice when you initially bring it to a boil
There is like a froth or a scum that comes to the top of the pot
None of that. Yes
Yeah, you want to scoop that off? Maybe one not only once but twice but three times
There's a joke in America where if you eat beans, you're supposedly it's supposed to bake you gassy. Have you ever heard of that?
Where in Latin cultures that is not to joke
They don't even consider it because they tend to take these things in consideration
Whenever someone jokes about eating beans and having being gassy or flatulent is because they don't know how to prepare them properly
And the preparation thereof whether there can be prepared or from scratch
When you initially bring the pot to a boil, you'll notice this whatever you cook. There's a froth that comes to the top. What is that?
Skim that off. That is the the gas that's being produced in the liquid
And if you don't skim it off that will that will probably sink that
Constituent will go back into the pot and when you eat it, it will make you gassy or heartburn or indigestion
So just skim it off whether it's a chicken soup or a beef stew or a vegetable soup or beans
when you initially bring it to a simmer and you when you bring it to a simmer depending on how big the pot is you
Want to wait a little bit because that initial simmer is just the outer edges of the pot bringing that you want all of the material
Too that's why sometimes a three-time
Skim is a good procedure
Separating the weight from the chef and that's just the chef as well and just reusing it like it where the crap
Can be yeah
so these these are some of the tips on the stove pot baked potatoes versus and also how to prepare flatbread and the perfect rice and
So put on your running shoes and check those archives
I
Brought up with Ocelli in the Greek going over food again
And I asked Chuck whether we should cover those again or direct people to the archives and suggest
Both people go to the archives. Otherwise, we might be redundant, right?
But see we'll see how we
Fair on that. Maybe I'll do a review on those food
Shows, let's say and see what else could be added or taken away
But food clothing and shelter. Yeah
Okay, so
Again soon. Thank you for your time. Yes. Thanks for Rico. Ciao