Rodrigo. Yes, Stelios, how are you? Good, todo bien. I was outside, yeah, so I read
message and I just went out. I didn't think we're gonna go on, but yeah. So
what's up? How are you? Yeah. What's on your mind? Something I wanted to speak to you
about. I wanted to ask you if you know much about dreams, if they mean anything.
Just like you said that there's no such thing as the subconscious, so what would
dreams entail? I wanted to discuss about that and also I do, I am wanting to know
more about the Jewish traditions, you know, of sacrificing to the gods or, you
know, like the Santa Claus thing, that that's actually pretty pertinent on my
mind. It's human, it's not really Jewish, it's basically the human thing, whether
it's every native culture on the planet has that. It's part of the human, one of
the things that they brush under the rug, and that's just to tie back into what
we said earlier about there's no such thing as a subconscious. Well, let's be
specific, that whole id, ego, conscious, subconscious, dreams, all that stuff now,
you're stuck in the realm of how I often discuss people think everything was
created a hundred years ago. So within that realm, that's a very Freudian, Jungian
construct, when what you actually, you cannot objectify anything that they're
saying, all you can do is subscribe to their ideology or their philosophy about
it. Now the reality of it is that you're either conscious or unconscious, just
like you hear multiple dimensions, those are technical constructs, there's only one
dimension, it's the raw crude dimension of space and everything in it, either
seen or unseen, perceptible or unperceptible, the concept of third
dimension, fourth dimension, fifth dimension, all that stuff is technical construct, like
architects use when they do a floor plan and elevation of a building or 3D, that is
absolutely, those are synthetic constructs for communication purposes
only. So going back to the dreams and the subconscious and the conscious, those
are synthetic constructs to basically communicate. So when you
start, let's say, bringing up the subconscious or anyone does, usually it's
within context that, oh, that person doesn't realize what they're saying, but
obviously they have something in their subconscious that's gnawing them away
and they're sort of revealing it, you see, in their conscious, that's not what's
going, I mean, that's fine if you subscribe to it and you can, if you
can make technical progress and technically communicate using that, that's
fine, but that's not objective enough for what I like to discuss. What's objective
is very simple, is you're either conscious or unconscious, and a state of
unconsciousness is temporary and permanent, temporary being when you're
asleep with your eyes closed and, you know, or permanent is when you're asleep
as in dead, and you're excarnated, right, and the soul is dead as
well, the spirit goes back to where it came from. So now let's go back to the
conscious part. What's happening is that people tend to tag things as not
being significant or being significant within a conversation or communicating
something, and that's how they are judged and whatever, like you see a protester,
they're yelling, well, stop this, stop that, the reason they're screaming about
and protesting is that's what they consider significant, where someone
passing by might say, oh, that guy's an idiot, I don't care about that at all, to
them it's insignificant, right? Yeah. So that's your basic communication, you,
people tend to go and talk about things that they think is important. Now, how do
people get that base? Well, I've discussed this publicly for years now,
what is important to you comes from, you know, your deity or your God, and, you
know, so the point here, this is not religious, of course, but the point here
has to do with the operating system. Going back to, again, the subconscious and
all that stuff, if you want to subscribe, I call it the quacademic, and others call
it quacademia, it goes across the board. How many times have you heard, for
example, electrons, you know, you go to a university, fire up a generator, and
they'll tell you there's electrons moving down the wire, really? Okay, so I'm going to
do an experiment, I have a live wire, and I cut it, and I have a dustpan in hand and
a microscope, so when I cut the wire, all the electrons will pour out, fall on the
floor, so I could sweep them up, right? And once you start saying that, you know,
they say, oh no, that's not how it works, and they cannot explain how it
works, they just give you a description, you see? Because there's no such thing,
blood pressure, viruses, electrons, protons, just about everything, money,
right? That's credit. Everything we're talking about is fake. Fake breasts, fake
teeth, fake hair, fake houses, you know, houses are fake because they're
built out of compressed sawdust. So, specifically, trying to
identify something by its description, rather than what it actually is. Yeah, and
let's stick with this, since you brought up the subconscious, and you have an
interest in consciousness, I think you've gone on public various sonic events
talking about that, and the thing is, here's the thing, whenever you're
speaking in public, and even in private venues, you have to remember that if it's
more than one or two people that you're addressing, you must accommodate their
thinking. Okay. If you don't accommodate them, they just either glaze over, tell
you I'm not interested, or they walk away. So, if you can garner objectively that
the entire human society on this planet right now is generally a group of
morons, all seven billion, with a very small exception, what makes them moronic
is they lack any, they're imbecilic, idiotic, moronic. They lack the ability to
objectify, and they're not interested in it either, you know. So, when you kind of
look at the society as a whole, it doesn't matter if you're in Russia, Iran,
the US, Australia, New Zealand, Germany, they're all morons. You can
wholesale group them as idiots and morons on this planet right now,
generally. I mean, that's a very accurate and very safe description. It's, no one
wants to hear it, obviously, but it doesn't matter. We want to be objective. So, what do you do
with a planet full of morons? Well, you have to accommodate them. Well, how do you
accommodate a moron, or an idiot, or an imbecile, or an uneducated, in other words,
a pagan, someone who's ignorant? They just, you know, they don't want it. Now,
here's the thing. You can have a conversation about objectifying things,
and people all of a sudden, you know, that no one wants to scorn any, about any
information, because most people say they want to learn. That's what they say.
They say, oh, you know what, you know, I really didn't know what you're
talking about, but you know what, I really don't want to know what you're
talking about, and I don't care. Because they're still going to base it on their own, on their
own beliefs, and their own ideas of what they think you're saying, as well.
Well, yeah, because you're dealing, you have to, what you're saying in public has
to accommodate the audience. Again, if you are... Isn't that a catch-22? Sorry for
interrupting, is that like a catch-22 situation? It's like, you're trying to
accommodate them, and trying to educate them, but they don't want to learn anyway,
because it's not part of their own mentality. It's a vicious cycle. Yeah.
They're stuck in a vicious, dog chasing its tail. At least the dog will run out
of steam eventually, and stop, but humanity, they keep making more and more
generational moves in the same direction. Yeah, yeah. So, but fortunately, they don't
have a lot of time left, and unfortunately, they don't have a lot of
time left, but that's the same, but it's not going to be unfortunate, because in
the next decade, they're going to be garnered with the ability to have a
perfect society, so when the earth is cleaned up, no one will be
without excuse. They can't say, well, we never had a chance, right? So here's the
point. If you have, let's go back to the, beat this a little bit. If you have a
concert, two concert halls, one is for a heavy metal rock band with an audience,
and the other one is for a classical, or an opera, with an audience. You have to
accommodate the heavy metal rock band with a heavy, audience with a heavy
metal rock band on stage, and the opera, and the classical music audience has to
be accommodated accordingly. Now, if you switch the orchestras, or the bands, and
you put the heavy metal at the opera, and the classical at the heavy metal audience,
what's going to happen? They're all going to start shifting, and move towards their
other... It doesn't work. Yeah, yeah. Now, so let's go this way. If you have two concert
halls, and one is completely full of morons and imbeciles, and the other one
is full of, completely full of morons and imbeciles, generally, as a wholesale
approach. Now, there might be one or two out of a million, or one or two out of a
hundred thousand, or even ten thousand. You're kind of pushing it, that are not.
So, if you have, no matter how many concert halls you have, it does, if you
see, if they're morons, you just have to give them their moronic stuff, their
idiotic stuff. Now, what I mean about that is, they lack objectivity, and they
lack the ability to see what's just right in front of them, and they go
through this hypocritical process, where they think there's always something out
there, at the bottom of the ocean, or out in outer space, and they can't even
realize what's happening within arm's reach. So, this is the problem, also,
the hypocrisy. Now, okay, this sounds like a rant, but it's not. It's actually quite
accurate. The point here is, when is there going to be a level of spiritual
maturity, meaning the spirit, meaning the mind, because the spirit is the mind, and
the soul is the breath. We've defined that many times, anyone can define it, but
they don't want to, because we just explained what they are. So, but here's
the point. The point here is very simple. The point is, if you're going to feed the
mind, are you going to feed it with things that are not in accordance with
the physical world? No, you can't, because eventually it's going to catch up. Now, how
do you prevent it from catching up? For example, if you have a generation on the
planet, it's not just one Western world. The Easterners are just as deceived as
the Westerners, and just as the Northerners and the Southerners, in every
latitude or longitude. Here's the point. The point is, how often can information or
communication be conveyed amongst the people that is false, where eventually
that falsehood catches up and becomes detrimental? Why aren't they matching
what they are being told and what they're thinking about with what they
actually see in the physical realm? Why not? Why aren't they doing that? You see,
well, we... I'm stuck with that question, but that's actually quite an
accurate description of how it is. I just came back from the shops, and I said,
what did you just slide through that machine? It's a credit card. I said, how
come they don't call it a money card? I don't know. Well, because it's a
credit-based economy. Well, where does credit come from? You know, little babies
ask where money... where babies come from to their parents, and... but how come
adults never ask where credit comes from? Yeah. Well, I did actually ask that
question myself, but I never got an answer, and I never really found an answer
to it. Yeah, it's very simple, but the money system is very simple. Okay, if you
ask questions regarding the physical environment, how are you going to do that
reasonably when everyone is walking around with a hot head and cold feet? Why
is it that when you heat or cool a room indoors, with the systems that are in
place provided by the engineering community to the rest of the population,
that whenever you heat or cool indoors, the heat always rises to the ceiling, and
the cold always descends to the floor? When... when it's hot in the valley, you go
up into the mountain, and it's cold. Now, if you called a medical technician and
said, my feet are cold and my head is hot, he'll tell you you're not feeling
well. Well, I thought heat's supposed to rise and cold is supposed to descend. How
come the idiots on this planet are not demanding from their researchers and
their engineers to... to create climate control devices that replicate the
biological condition of a rarefied rising cold and a densifying descending
heat? Why aren't they demanding those devices so they have a cool head and warm
feet all year round? Why aren't they demanding that? I think because people
are just complacent. Yeah, complacent. They just want to leave it the way it is, or
they don't want to question something that may be perceived as being
different to others. I mean, it's like just accepting things for the way they
are, and that everything is supposed to be perfect the way they are. The only
reason I don't ask... Yeah. You sound like you're an attorney for the
human race, or you're making excuses for it. I'm making excuses for myself, not for everyone else.
Well, here's the point. The point is, yes, they don't... Okay, let's stop
ranting about humanity, because that's been done. If you want to know how crappy
people are, just pick up... you don't need... it's not a new thing. Just read an old
book. It'll tell you how crappy people are across the board, through all the...
But here's the point. The point is, again, going back to the subconscious. It's
not a matter of being conscious or subconscious. It's a matter of, are they
paying attention? Are they censored? Yes. Have you heard about the 800-pound
gorilla in the room? Well, there's... you know, that people can't see. Well, there's
10 800-pound gorillas in the room that no one's looking at. How can that be?
Because don't you have tactile function? You know, don't you have perception? I
mean, you can smell it if you can't see it, right? Yeah, yeah. I mean, all right, they...
Okay, so what's going on is that they're being censored. There's a... what I call
cosmic censorship. And I had one... I did a sonic event with someone once, and he
kept asking me on air, what is... what do you mean by cosmic censorship? And after
a while, I just gave up. I said, if you have to ask that question, guess what?
You're censored. It's very difficult to explain. Yeah. It's difficult to
explain, but it's very simple at the same time. Yeah. A governor has been put on
humanity where they cannot perceive right now, and they have... it's been this way
since 500 BC. That was the last axial period. You actually had an axial period
here in the States around what they called 9-11, meaning an axial period is a
time period when, after this time or this event occurs, it changes the
worldview, right? If you heard now, this is a post-9-11 world, right? Or post... the
world wars tend to be axial periods. You know, this is pre-war construction or
post-war construction. It's like a tipping point, tipping point into a new
direction, and I suppose a new way of thinking. Because since 9-11, nearly
everyone has become a conspiracy theorist, if you want to sort of label it
that way. Well, axial periods changed worldviews, essentially, and the major
worldview that people are still really operating under, it was changed around
2,500 years ago. That's when all of the major religions in the world and the
major philosophies emerged to kind of cover and distract. Now, what do I mean by
that? 2,500 years ago, the maiden axial period, at that point and prior, there was
full knowledge of where mankind came from, his purpose, and all this, commonly
known. If you do a little bit of historical research prior to that time,
that was also the time, by the way, that the... you've heard of the Library of
Alexandria? Yes. That was destroyed around that time. Most of the information
depositories of the world were eliminated from the public eye during
that time, okay? That was also the time of the Greek Golden Age. This is when all
this philosophy emerged. I hear a lot of people say, oh, the Greek philosopher is
this, the Greek philosopher is that. I say, okay, you moron. If the Greek philosophy
was so good, how well has it served you? Not. It hasn't. It's not. So, it's
just filler. You're in the waiting room for 2,500 years. Think about a
waiting room. You have a purpose during the day, but you have an
appointment, and you're sitting in a waiting room for another event to
occur, but it's a threshold moment. You're either... you're not doing what you
want to do, and you're not doing what you're supposed to do, because you're in
the waiting room right now, or the credits part of the movie is another
part in terms of wrapping things up. So, these things now are going to be
bubbling to the... things that I've been discussing for over a decade publicly
are going to be bubbling to the surface and starting at the end of the seven
year period now, which is going to end around 2018. Then, it'll be time to have
more of a reasonable discussion. Right now, even though these topics are very
important, it's no different than going and discussing a Windows computer
program in the 1890s. You know, they know what computing is, because they can do it
on paper, and they know what a window is, but they don't know what you're talking
about. Yeah, understood. You see? Yeah. So, I'm going to take a 30-second break. Go
ahead. Take the... fill up some time. I'll be right back. Yeah. So, um, ladies and
gentlemen, this is the waiting room discussions between myself, Rodrigo, and
The Greek. We're going to be talking various topics to do with the world as
it is today, and the world that may be coming. As The Greek said, we are in a
period of, let's say, the credits, and we're waiting for the end of the movie,
and possibly the beginning of a new one, but what is going to be the new movie?
What is that? And I suppose we can't... we've got to wait till the end of the
credits, right? The thing is, can you discuss the specifics deservingly? No.
Right now, you can't, because you can't take a pig to a debutante ball. In
other words, they need to stay in their pig pen until, you know, whatever, until
they take the bacon off their back or whatever, right? Right. So, here's the
point. The point is, any time you preach doom and gloom or change, any time in
society, it sounds correct, because what they do is they try to read into what's
going on, right? Yeah. You know, you could always, just like horoscopes, you know, you
could show someone a horoscope and they'll say, oh, does this apply to you?
Yes, it does. And just hand it to the person next to you, does it apply to you?
Yes, it does. It's just written in such a way that... Okay, so the thing is, can you give
specifics? One of the specifics is that right now, part of the axial period and
the dumbing down... I wouldn't say dumbing down, but this cosmic censorship is that
the entire world is under the auspices of what I call the Pope's work schedule.
You're using the Gregorian calendar, which is nothing more than a work schedule. It
has nothing to do with keeping time. It has nothing to do... the year going
around the Sun is not a linear function. The moon-type calendars are not linear
functions. None of these things that they're putting in front of you are
linear. Like, for example, if you look at whatever day you might observe or date
during the year, you'll notice that the previous year and the
next year, it's going to be on a different day of the week consistently.
And why? Because it's a work schedule. You cannot keep time with it. I'm not
saying... look, it's fine. If you're under a corporate culture, they
hand you a schedule of when you go to work, and they can name those days with
numbers or colors or names of horses or whatever. It doesn't matter. But when you
look at what is going on right now on the planet, where time is necessary to
navigate, and you are not able to navigate because you have no time
function, you know, how are you going to... you see? So let me just reiterate that
again. You cannot keep time with the Gregorian calendar. It is a work schedule.
And when was the Gregorian calendar implemented? It was a
continuation of the Julian calendar. The Gregorian is around the 15... the
papal bull in the 1500s. These guys actually gave nations that
were working on different time systems ultimatums. You know, we'll wipe you out
if you don't accept this time system. Oh yeah, that was the last one in the 1920s. They were
demanded that, you know, we'll take you out as a society if you don't accept our
calendar system and all of your men and families take on surnames. But here's
the point. The point is, time is very important. And by the way, time is just
the recordation and memorialization of events. There is no such thing as time as
many of these New Age idiots talk about. It is just a record. And it's
important because the natural world that you're attached to, meaning the whales,
the tigers, the bees, the roaches, the flies, the rivers, the oceans, everything
natural, goes on a natural timekeeping which is basically the sun rules the day
and the moon rules the month. If you're not aware of memorializing that, you're
not going to be able to deal with nature accordingly. Yeah, I always thought that
there could have been a better way of keeping time to do with the human
biology, the human clock, rather than... There is no such thing as the human clock, but go ahead.
Well, you said the Pope's work schedule, right? So I wondered what is that based on
for what reason? Is it because they wanted to memorialize events?
Well, you can go, if you look at the history of the Julian date, it's an
offshoot of a Roman system, which is an offshoot of a Greek system. Now, a lot of
people blame Rome, as in Roman civil law. It's Rome we're living under and all this
crap. It's not. It's actually Greece. It's still the Greek system. Can you
show me anything, and either take five minutes or take five years, show me
anything that the Romans have that's original, other than the geographic
location? No. Isn't every sort of civilization a copy of
something that was prior to its existence? Like nothing is as original as
as what they seem to be? Not necessarily, but spinoffs and one hatches the other.
But the Roman system is very closely adherent to the Greek system. It's
just in a Roman Latin fashion, or what you might call Western versus
Eastern. You could look at the various aspects of culture as
well. The Romans will be more Western, and the Greek culture will be more Eastern.
If you go to Spain, you'll find more similarities with Rome than you do
with Greece. But if you go to Greece, you'll find more similarities in
Lebanon, which is East, the food and the language. So that's the division of East
and West, sort of in the modern time. But the point here is the learning how to
keep time. And by the way, there's a lot of morons out there talking about time
travel. There's no such thing. What they're actually trying to say, and
because they're so immature they cannot structure any definition, what they're
trying to say, they're going to past and future events. But you're not
traveling, because time is just the recordation of events. You have to
realize that the majority of academia, and what you call science, is based on
science fiction. That's why I implore anyone who wants to, if they want to
donate their bodies after they die, donate it to science fiction. They'll get
more out of it. But the point here is there's so much lack of
definition, and there's such a hypocrisy about not even noticing about what's
going on right in front of them, that these people, for lack of a better
term, want to go out and they think there's something out there, or it's
something they have to find. Well, why don't you take care of the things that
are immediate? So I've heard you say this in the past, that these
people who are purporting time travel or space travel or things like that, they're
pranking you. I've heard you say the word pranking. The majority is a prank.
A prank, if you look it up, is a ludicrous thing. Here's the thing, we feel, when we
bring up certain terms and words, we feel a certain way about them. We think
that we know what they mean, and we'd like them to mean whatever we want them
to mean. But we have no right to actually define the word that we didn't create,
because it was when it was created, right? So this is why I'd like to adhere to
what words mean. The definition of a prank is just a ludicrous trick, and
typically this is the nature of being on this planet. But yeah, a lot
of the time traveler people are the same as the little gray alien people, the
same as the legal people, you
know, the patriots, right? We've got to make our country like it was. What are you
talking about? The reason it's so screwed up is because of how it was back then.
So you want to go back and reset it again? What is it, like changing baby
diapers? You know, the diaper is going to be soiled by the baby, keep
changing it. Is that how you're going to look at your national history?
Like changing baby diapers? You're going to start all over again? Why don't you
grow up so you don't need diapers? But the whole pranking is based on just a
ludicrous trick. For example, the earth is a very violent place. I tell this
to a lot of these morons, and they say, no it's not. So we'll go ahead and turn on
one of your nature channel shows, and within five minutes you'll see one
creature eating another for food or whatever, for territory.
Predators and prey. Right, and most of the pranking that's done in
this society is done in a predacious form by your entitled classes,
your academics, your religious people, your attorneys, you know, your legal
people, not to confuse with law, your academics being scientific, and
your medical as well, your political. And when you take it all the way down, it's
really the parents that started the pranking while you were still in the
crib, in the child's bed. They started pranking you there. So this is the
place of the prank, and typically it's a ludicrous trick, but typically the
pranking gets dangerous where they put people in cages known as prisons, where
they inject people with toxic chemicals. You know that 80% of all medications that
are considered prescription medications are banned and considered illegal and
dangerous after 10 years. So this cycle has been going on since the 50s. So are we
just bandaging in symptom management rather than solutions and cures? Well, yes,
but be careful when you say we. Like, for example, I tend to be objective. If
humanity decides to kill each other off tomorrow or the next five minutes, it's
fine with me. If humanity wants to just take windy walks and love each other
and make a perfect society in the next five minutes, it's fine with me too. I
have to be objective. Have you ever watched a sports game? The guy with the
black and white stripes, can he pick up the ball and score
for a team? Isn't he there just to observe the game? He's supposed to be
refereeing. Yeah, people that are objective. Someone said
once publicly, oh the Greek, he thinks he's smarter than everyone else. I said
no, I don't. I'm just less stupid than you. So there's a difference there. So the
point here is when you get objectivity in such a situation, you see, if you
believe that things are not the way that we're discussing, you will never, you
know, your belief is not based on anything pragmatic or practical. It's
just this belief that is unfounded or baseless. Once you believe in something,
it doesn't matter what it is, whether it's the money credit system, the legal
system, religious system, whatever, start looking at what it's based on and you
will find it's based on nothing. You're being pranked. Whether it's Islam,
Buddhism, Hinduism, or Christianity, you are being pranked. There's no religion on
the planet that does anything at all that's in any of the texts that they
allegedly subscribe to in context at all. You know, you can actually start a
religion based on a chocolate chip cookie recipe. Well, they did start the
Spaghetti Monster religion and it was a parody and it took off. It actually took
off and it's supposed to be a bonafide religion, even though the
creators and the people follow it know that it's a parody. There's a lot
of criticism on Christianity, Islam, Judaism, where it comes from and these
people that are criticizing it, if you actually look at what they're
bringing up as findings, they're incorrect also. There's people
that have websites, written books on it. There are people that discuss these various
religions and they're incorrect also. So I don't know where to send people other
than if you're going to, you know, what makes them incorrect as anyone can see?
This is not an opinion, it's the truth. If you look up anything, regardless of the
subject matter, what was it based on in time? You know, first in time is first in
line. The oldest thing, investigate it. Don't read what someone else wrote about
it. Yes, it does take a lot of work to do it and you'll see that what
you're being told about it is just simply not true. I call it a lot of Chinese whispers.
Sorry for interacting there, Greg. For me it's like Chinese whispers. It's, you know, I read
something and it's just a little bit different from where it was originated
from and that is a little bit different from where that originated from and I
find it difficult to make an opinion and even be objective or subjective on a
certain topic because I have no clue where it started from. And to research,
because it's the internet, to verify its source is kind of difficult for me to
master, so I've given up. There's going to be a movement where those that have
given up or feel like they want to give up before they even start, let's say,
there's going to be a coming world trend in the near future where you're not
going to feel like you're doing it alone. There's going to be a
collective effort on this, so it's alright. Okay, and you did say the
waiting room. What is it that humanity or, as an individual myself,
needs to do right now? If we can't find the information we're looking for, what
is pertinent? What do we need to do right now that's right in front of our
faces? Like you said, the answer's not out there. Everyone's looking for an
answer out there far away from themselves. Well, the problem is, yeah, the
problem is very simple. Start being simple about things, you know, like
little children, you know, when you mention something and say, why? And then
you say, why? And they keep saying, why, why, why, why, why, why, why? You know,
you don't have to do that in a juvenile fashion. Just simply look at what
something is based on, and the thing is, be very careful with your movements. If
you're going to give anyone advice coming to this planet, let's just
preface this. Could it be that perhaps before you visit this planet, let's say
you're going through the galaxy in your mothership, and they send down a crew,
they give you a description of the planet, and then they want you to spend a
few days and come back and confirm what, you know, the report is. And before they
send you down to this planet, they tell you, don't talk to anyone here, because
anything you say is just going to confuse them. Unless you're within their
culture, speaking whatever rubbish they've decided to speak about. You know,
and here's the thing. Some people say, what's crawled up the Greeks' butt? Why
does he sound so pessimistic or hateful or whatever? I'm actually being
optimistic. You don't want to hear, and I'm really padding this and actually
putting a big buffer and a cushion on what I'm saying, because the reality is
too harsh for most people to comprehend, even at this point, because they're
censored. But here's the thing. The advice is, set yourself apart from it. In
other words, are you paying attention? You know, there's an old saying that said
that, you know, about discerning things of the mind or things of the spirit. It was
said once, and the people that asked, when will certain times come, and they
were called hypocrites, because they can discern when it's going to rain, you know,
they see the cloud, or they can discern when it's going to be warm, because the
wind is warm from a certain direction, but they can't discern these other
things. That's correct. They cannot discern time. But, you know, let's
look at it, what the advice is. You know, how can you advise people that anything
you say is just going to confuse them? I even had someone in public on a round
table on a radio on late nights once say, Greek, when you speak, I need
babblefish. I don't understand what you're saying. You see, so that's just
living proof of the censorship. Now, here's the point. The point is, look
around you. A thousand years ago, when structures were built, they were built to
last a thousand years. Some of the skyscrapers in these metropolises that
were built a hundred years ago are still very robust and standing. Right now,
public works and skyscrapers and things like that that are built are built to
last less than 20 years. The other thing is, I was conveying on what they call the
road the other day, and I saw a subdivision of houses going up, and they
were made out of compressed sawdust. They're not made to last. They're not
made to last. Yeah, there's no reason for it, because everyone sort of, like you
might want to say, subconsciously, meaning it's in the conscious, they can discuss
it, but they cannot. They don't understand the source of the feeling. We can just
come out and say, you've got roughly 15 years left, and there's a deniability,
15 years left of man's rule, as things are, meaning the pranking and the
ridiculousness. But here's the point. The point is that you still have a lot of
people that are in this self-medicated mind state. You could see them start off
a conversation. Well, no one knows what's coming in the future, right? You know,
like they're looking for approval, right? Yeah. You see, no one knows about this,
right? Oh yeah, I agree with you. It's like the one that's on the back and goes,
yeah, you're right, you're right. Yeah, you're right. And meanwhile, when these morons are
speaking, you know, one will be speaking, and the other one's like, oh,
when is he going to shut up so I can say what I want to say? So where's the unity?
It's just super superficial. It's paper-thin ridiculousness that humans
across the board are engaged in. And this is not just the Western world, this is
the Eastern world as well. And the Northern world, and the Southern world. Yeah, it's
across, it's the human, what you might want to call consciousness, what they're
aware of. Fortunately for them, before the many of the changes start coming, like I
said, this seven-year period that we're in right now will be ending roughly in
the spring of 2018 on the Pope's work schedule. There's going to be more of a
collective approach to things. Like earlier, you mentioned like, you know,
these, maybe I'm paraphrasing here, that it seems monumental and lack of trust to
research things online, especially, you know, big subjects and things. But there
is going to be a collective that is going to make it more sane and more
practical in the next couple of years. What I mean by collective, it's going to be
done just by the regular, you know, the bus drivers, the street sweepers, the
nurses, the plumbers, the carpenters, not these academic morons, you know, or these
entitled classes, you know, like the people that, you know, are up in, what do
they call them, white... Ivory Towers. Yes, Ivory Towers, yes. Not those idiots. A lot
of them are going to actually be falling more into insignificance. You could
actually read this very simply by looking at the alternative movements,
like you have an alternative media, an alternative medicine, alternative energy,
right? You've heard of these things, right? Yes. There's a purpose for this.
And no one is reading this. Now, within these movements of alternativeness, all
you see is false hope and idiocracy, meaning idiocy, because they're still
bringing the same mindset, because they don't realize that they're being
censored until the time is right, but these things are put in place. It's kind
of like someone who, you know, has one car, but builds a... and one garage, but
builds a two-car garage, and when he's doing that, when he's doing that, he
hasn't gotten the other car yet, but you see? Yep, yep. So it's fine to do
that. I'd rather build the extra garage before I get the car, than get the car
and then build the garage, right? So what they're doing, alternative media,
alternative medicine, alternative food, alternative thinking, alternative this,
what they're doing is, it's the shell that it's being put in place, but what
it's being filled with is the same rubbish. You can hear it. You go to
alternative media, 99% of it is just an echo of what the medium, the
mainstream garbage, or academic garbage, and you can tell that it's
still rubbish, because a lot of these alternative media places, the hosts
bring on guests, and they're so proud that this person has a degree in
something. The very thing that we're trying to escape from, because the
degree is censored education, isn't it? Mm-hmm, absolutely, and it's, yeah, see
the people don't understand that the university system that's in place was
started around the time of ancient Greece, and it was created as a buffer
zone, to make sure that if those that were in power, if just a common
person came up with something that was unusual, unique, or beneficial, they could
control it by sicking the academics on them. Yeah. Oh, you can't listen to him, he
doesn't have a degree like we do, or you can't, you know, and the people don't
realize it, and by the way, if you go to an etymological dictionary, because a
dictionary just tells you how words are pronounced, etymology tells you what
words mean, or the root meaning, look up the word academic, and if you look it up,
or paraphrase, what it means is basically theoretical, impractical, and never
leading to a conclusion. That's why debate, that's why they always like
debating and arguing, they're just a bunch of morons, and here's the thing,
anyone that has more than an eighth grade education in any system, private or
public, in any country of the world, has pretty much done enough irreparable
damage that they're probably never going to recover in their lifetime fully, you
see, this is how vile and vicious the mind has been attacked by main, by the
mainstream school academic systems, and this goes across, it doesn't matter
whether, which country, or whether it's public or private, this is part of the
censorship. Yeah. At this point, I'm embarrassed to have discussions with
people that are proud of having more than an eighth grade education. It's
embarrassing, it's just, I'm embarrassed for them, and you can't, but you know,
here's the thing, they have the support of the population, right? Right. That's why I
am embarrassed for them, because the whole situation is just in the shit, if
we could say that. So you're saying that you're embarrassed because
they're supported by other morons, supposedly, like... Well, it's embarrassed
because, let's say, you know, a ship just landed and they said we're from Beta
Reticuli, let's, we're here to meet you people, who the hell are you going to
introduce them to? Yeah, that's a hard question. I've always made the
joke that the ships would land in the North Koreans and, you know, the, these
visitors judge humanity based on the North Korean society. That would be a
fail for the Western world. Well, it's a metaphor, not that I, you know, I'm not
into the UFO stuff, but I like using that metaphor, because that's what people are
referring to these days, that's their new god, right? But the thing is, you know,
let's say, you know, that we want to, we just landed here, you know, we're, this is
our welcoming, where's your welcoming team? You know, who are you going to
introduce them to? I mean, could you imagine someone came here and they said,
well, what, what, how do you keep time here? And they submit, they start talking
about stuff between January, December, and Monday through Friday.
Ridiculousness and, or, you know, or this wind-up toy they call the clock. Is this how
you reckon time on the planet? You're kidding me. So what would be the best way
to keep time or to record memory? Well, lawfully. Well, anything you do, whether, yeah, whether it's
religious or time or food or education, has to be lawful. Okay, can you define
lawful then? Yeah, very simple. There is no deniability in lawfulness, and lawfulness
also goes based on the way things work prior to your existence, you see? Like, for
example, if you pick up a lawful book on geometry, it'll always say that a
triangle has three sides, and a square has four sides, and a pentagon has five
sides. But if you pick up a book on geometry and it says a pentagram's got
ten sides, a triangle's got six sides, and a square's got two sides, well, that's not
lawful. Right. Because now you're not communicating, you see, now, you know, now
we, it doesn't, it's not based on the definition of those things. So, like,
lawful money, right? You've heard of law, you have legal money. Now, legal just is
whatever you agree to. Lawful, it's based on the natural system. Like, lawful
timekeeping. Like, see, right now, with timekeeping, if you remember anyone who's
old enough, before the electronic convention, it's on these electronic
devices automatically, seemingly, you had to go at the end of the year and get a
calendar from a card shop or somewhere, they gave them away for free at banks
and hardware stores. Yeah. So, you knew what day it was next year, you usually
got it a month or two before the year ended, right? They print them up, right?
That's not lawful, because you have, you're dependent on something that is an
artificial construct and it's baseless. That was created by something that came
after your existence. So, it's legal then. Well, it's legal, definitely. Now,
you can't, there are no days on that calendar, there are dates. There's a
difference. There are dates. Now, here's the point. For thousands of years, people
settled their debt with the new moon, which is the full moon. They even reversed
that on you. That's why today you still get a monthly bill. Yep. Don't you? They
try to settle many of the utility debts and bank loans and things, alleged loans
and things like that, on a monthly basis. Yeah. The other thing that people
don't realize is the day starts at high noon, not at sundown, like some
ridiculous Babylonian convention or all these other things. And we can get into
how they got sundown in certain religions and the new moon being the dark
moon and with specificity, but the day starts at high noon. That's why if you
remember before the electronic convention with banking, if you made a
deposit at the alleged bank after noon, it was counted as the next day.
Right. I'm not sure. Do you remember? Yeah, I remember. It was prior to the
electronic conventions. So, yeah, and it's been memorialized, but people don't,
you see, they are so, at this point, modern. And by the way, any ancient
society, right before they fell or lost prominence in their writings,
considered themselves to be modern. So, another hint. But that's just the human
condition, isn't it? I mean, all societies, all civilizations, when they're
there, regardless of where they are, they're always going to consider
themselves as modern and up-to-date because, you know, while I was going to
say they love themselves to a degree. Let's think about this. This is kind of
a saturated discussion. Let's wrap. I want to maybe wrap it up here in a
minute. And I want to just present something that I've been presenting for
over a decade with the most vile resistance from everyone and anyone you
can imagine. And this is what it is. You have to understand that there is a
central point that things emanate from in many conditions, whether it's social or
personal. We can call it HQ. I call it headquarters, right? You've heard of
headquarters. How many times have you heard, like, certain agencies, you know,
we have to find out what's going on at HQ, right? What do they say? All right.
So, what is the HQ for the body? It's you. You are HQ. You are the headquarters
of yourself, of how you define yourself. And it's both physical and non-physical.
The three things that we define ourselves with is the physical body, the soul,
and the spirit. Now, the physical body is the carne, you know, the material
aspect that's basically a biological machine. Let's skip over that for a little
bit because discussing how the body really works, because the way people are
discussing how the body works with blood pressure and viruses and disease and
food is so ridiculous that they're so deceived about their own body that,
you know, if you're deceived about how your own body works, let's put it this
way. If headquarters is full of deception, what is going to emanate out of
headquarters? Deception. Yeah. And how many times have you heard something like,
oh, that doesn't resonate with me. I don't like that. Now, if you were raised
in deception and lies, that's what you resonate with. Think about it. The truth
is dissonant to you. You won't like it. So we can get into what I call the
container. Now, this is what all of your spiritualists, some of these people
have radio programs, write books, and they have thousands of idiots flocking
to them for guidance, and they don't know anything. There's a saying in Texas
that most of your spiritual guides, by the way, whether religious, alternative,
your tarot readers, your hermeticists, your seers, your psychics, they're idiots.
All of them. Not some of them. All of them. In Texas, there's a saying that
says that they couldn't even pour piss out of a boot, even if there was
instructions on the heel. This is how piss poor they are. And the reason why
I'm saying this is this. Go ask one of these morons what defined the spirit
and the soul. And I'm not saying this because I'm just being, let's say
bitter about this, because I've been going through this for 10 years now,
and there's no polite way to actually refer to these morons that are actually
everyone is going to. Now, I say everyone, meaning, please don't come to me,
or people like me, because I'm not looking for a following or anyone to
flock around. But the point is, ask them what the soul and the spirit is,
and they'll either tell you, well, no one really knows, or it's the same
thing. We're talking about your highly learned, most esteemed. You want to go
to the Vatican and ask the guy with the funny fish hat. He cannot define it.
You want to go to the highest rabbinical, or the highest Islamic, or the highest
Hindu or Buddhist. They cannot define it. Your common people cannot define it.
All of these other people telling you what spirituality cannot define. It's
ridiculous. We're going to define it right now, and it's very simple.
If you, let's do it using the English language, and you'll find this in every
language, but let's use the English language because the convention of the
sciences and spirituality in English in the Western world is based on the Greek
system. And I'm going to show you how this is a very simple proof.
If you look at what we call the soul, that is simply the breath.
Okay. It's meaning you inhale and you exhale. It's the ability to move air so
you sustain the body with life by this pulsing action we call breathing. So the
way you check if someone is dead, the first thing you do is you check to see
if they're what? They're breathing, right? And then you look for a pulse. And
you, and within that range, usually if you're breathing, you typically, right,
you have a pulse. So the point is, if you look at the Greek convention, the
pnuma, p-n-u, pnuma in Greek is the meaning for the soul, the breath. Now
that's why in English you still use the, this was structured very nicely, let's
say, years ago. Whenever you see the p-n-u prefix, it has something to do with
air, like pneumatic, pneumonia. It all has to do with the movement of air. For
example, soul is interchangeable, like your soul is interchangeable with an
elephant, a tiger, a bird, or a dog. In other words, you can breathe into their
mouths and they can breathe what you're breathing, you see? That's all it is.
Now that we, okay, so... So is that the life giver in the material world, the
soul, the animator? Well, yes, it's a part of the animation. Now the spirit, let's
go back to the Greek convention. You'll find this in the Arabic, Hebrew, and also
the other Eastern cultures, Asian cultures, and languages to match what I'm
saying, if you do a little bit of research. The spirit now is intangible, and that's
the mind. In Greek it's the psyche, the p-s-y prefix. So whenever you see the
p-s-y, like psychic, psychology, psychotic, psychopath, or the p-s-y means the mind
or the spirit. That's completely intangible. Now the essence that we are
right now, we say we meaning humanity, is that the spirit has to be animated
through the body and the soul. When the soul, or the breath, stops and the body
goes away, the spirit is no longer animated. Now we can get into the realm
of the spiritual realm and how these things work. We can do that for the next
show. For the next show, perhaps, but most people think that they are
reincarnated, or they can travel astrally, and they could do all this other stuff.
We'll explain how that works. By the way, folks, you will not make friends with
this kind of discussion. You're on planet Earth. Here's the thing. It's best to
know what's going on and objectify it than perhaps not knowing what's going on
and making up porcupines or Chinese whispers to define things around you.
The way that I would describe it is that if you're going to go over a cliff and
you're blindfolded, I would rather take the blindfold off and have an opportunity
to do something about it than just go over without actually seeing where
you're going, if you know what I mean. You try to flap your arms like a bird, you're
still going to hit the ground, and that's what they're doing right now. They're
flapping their arms thinking that some new science or new political leader or
new religion or something is going to help them. But here's the point. The
point is, we'll probably get into more specifics. Let's see what kind of
feedback we get from this kind of sonic thing, also. We'll get into more
specifics about the headquarters, which is how the body really works, and that
you, without the Hippocratic, no pun intended, but the hypocrisy of the
academia. And we'll also get into, we'll maybe leave the soul alone, because that
is so simple to define. It's a pulsing action of air movement through the
lungs. And we'll get into what the spirit is and the mind in the spiritual
world and how it really works and what it is. And this is not stuff we're making
up or what we believe or what the Greeks' opinion on it is, because if you
want to roll with that, there's plenty of other places to go to be delusioned
with. The whole thing is to just actually discuss things that people can access on
their own, simply, with a childlike mind, but not in a juvenile state, with a
mature state, you see. The problem now is humanity lacks maturity. You see, you
can have someone walk in with gray hair and a doctorate degree, and I could prove
to you in less than 30 seconds that this person stopped developing at around nine
years old. They all have a juvenile mentality. When I say now all, when I say
this planet is full of idiots and morons and the academics don't know anything
and the entitled classes are pranking everyone, this is a wholesale statement
that applies to 99.9999% of your population. There are a few people left
on this planet right now, very few, that are not subject to this and can see the
things that we're discussing. Can I just be a devil's advocate? Wouldn't that be a
subjective comment to say? I mean, because you're saying 99.9%, but there
could be maybe people who aren't indoctrinated. It could be 98%. Right. Well, here's the
thing. Now I'm speaking according to this, the wrap-up of
this axial period that we're living in. In the near future, you will have the
illusion that people are coming around to things that are more real, and we'll
discuss why it's an illusion as well. It's not a matter about being better or
worse. It's just a matter of is. The better or worse is a judgments call.
We need to define the thing first. The thing that's going on is that the
people are deaf, dumb, and blind, meaning they can't see, they can't hear, and
they're dumb because what they're saying is just noise. How many times have you heard
a conversation or been at a party or a social event and spoken to people for two hours and
someone said, what did you talk about? You're like, I don't know. It was just rubbish.
How many times have you can say that very often? I mean, just turn on anything, whether it's
a university lecture, alternative media, or mainstream. It's just rubbish.
Well, I find it's the same information as I would have heard a year ago. It's just regurgitation
and just with a few different things changed. Like I was listening to a radio yesterday,
and it was just the same thing. If people want to learn something new, I would hope
that the information would be different to as it was last year, but if I'm hearing the
same things, I'm not learning anything. Well, think about it this way for a moment.
I've been saying the same thing constantly for 10 years. Now, the reason why I say the
same thing is because I'm saying the same thing. You need to go and see that it's based
on something. What is it based on? Maybe what they are saying, whether it's the same thing
or different, is baseless. There's no foundation for it.
There's no foundation. Now, how many times have you heard of an impending financial collapse
that never happened or an impending virus? There's no such thing as a virus. That's
a medical prank. You can define it basically. You still hear idiots talking about viruses
and all this other stuff. How many times have you heard of financial disasters, impending
doom that never happens? Because it's baseless. All of their stuff is baseless. Killer comets.
All of these things are baseless. Extinction-level events. It's the modern thing
to say, but it's baseless. There's nothing to justify.
I don't mind the repetition because I run into people sometimes I haven't seen in five
years. We pull off to the side and we have a conversation for 20 minutes or 15 minutes
because I tend to be long-winded and wordy sometimes. They'll say, hey, Greek, you're
saying the same stuff you said 10 years ago. I'm like, what, am I supposed to change?
Let's use the conventional education system, let's say from kindergarten to twelfth grade.
If you don't get anything in second grade, do they move you to third? You have to do
it over, don't you? Whether it's second, third, fourth, or fifth. If you haven't gotten
anything, you have to keep at it until you get it and then move on. Even your video game
scenarios are like that. If you can't complete level one, they don't bump you up to level
two, do they? No, you stop progressing until you get past
that level you're on. Level one is, are you aware of what these
things are based on? Well, Greek, I didn't know that, but you know what? I don't want
to know and I don't care. That's the world view.
Is that really the mentality of most people? They don't care?
Oh, yeah. Apathy. So here's the thing. I'm not with you guys. In other words, I'm here
to be objective. Whether humanity does well or does poorly, and I know where it's going,
the thing is that when things are irrelevant to the objectivity that I try to provide. Otherwise,
if I start giving personal opinions and what I like personally to hear or what resonates
with me, then I'm going to have to join one of these idiotic groups or one of these sectors
of culture. So I try to keep that stuff out of my life. I try to be objective and pursue
things that are wonderful and pleasant. If you don't know what something is based on,
it's going to bite you eventually, right? Or you're going to find that you have nothing
to stand on. So this is where society is. But here's the thing, and just a word of caution
to people if they don't hear anything from us again, is coming in the next decade, you're
going to be pretty much poised to have a perfect society. The better things get, the worse
they actually are going to be. Not necessarily from a pessimistic point of view, but you're
being set up. Just like right before a scam is pulled on someone, everything is shown
to be really rosy and wonderful.
And that incites a person to persevere and continue, and that's when the blindfold's
removed and you see it for what it really is, and it's like, oh shit, we've been tricked.
At that point, the thing about this is even more ironic, is humanity will never realize
it's being tricked, because even when the trick is exposed, they're just going to make
an excuse for it. And we can give a lot of specifics on this, but let's just say we're
priming the well or the pump for maybe some other sonic events. And with that said, thanks
Rodrigo.
No worries, Greg. I appreciate the time you've taken to have a discussion. We're going to
put this up on YouTube and maybe even have a website set up for it. But in the next few
discussions I really want to expand on law, or lawful, as well as the blindfold that's
been put over us, what the pranking really is, and continue from there. But thank you
so much for your time, it's been a good hour, and we will have further sonic events.