100% listener-supported radio, and now we return you to your host.
Yes, it is hour two.
If you're just joining us on Studio A, welcome.
This is Revolution Radio, freedomslips.com.
This is Ground Control, and I'm Major Tom with my co-host and producer to the show, Keith AZ.
Tonight, we've got the Greek. You're just in time to hear us talking about more.
What we talked about last hour was actually something I didn't know.
It was something I learned about the civil laws.
We got neuralized. You got neuralized.
I'm actually still reeling from that.
You're normal.
I don't recognize myself anymore.
I know. So maybe the Greek is saying the truth.
All right, so maybe, big maybe.
I'm going to drop another image here.
Did you get the image, guys?
I dropped an image of the intestines.
I'm going to drop another image in there.
You could pick up those and drop them in the chat if you like.
Keith, would you describe the second image I dropped, or Tom?
I'll tell the audience.
It's a steel-belted radial profile.
The reason why I dropped that in, is it not?
Did you guys get the second image?
No, I see it.
You see all the layers on it?
What do tires do?
Don't they keep the exterior pressure different from the interior pressure?
Even though it could be a vacuum, it could be a positive pressure.
Doesn't the ambient environment appear to be a vacuum to the pressure inside of a car tire?
You see what I mean?
Yeah, because it's higher pressure.
But nonetheless, regardless of which side there's the pressure, look at all the layers.
It doesn't look like anything will get through that, does it?
No.
I want you to go to the one of the intestines.
Does it look like anything is ever going to get absorbed through that?
Or is that built robustly enough to hold a vacuum?
The intestinal wall?
No, it looks like it could hold a vacuum.
Oh, yeah.
It's about as robust as that tire.
Obviously not as robust.
Yeah.
Nothing goes through there.
Nothing gets absorbed.
Where's the absorption?
Don't these quackademics or medical technicians tell you,
Oh, that food, these vitamins absorb very well.
If you had absorption in the intestine, you would die of sepsis in three days.
You know what sepsis is when you have a hole in the intestine, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Or an infection because you've lost vacuum.
Now, let me just go back to the legal.
Now, you know how we brought up the legal stuff earlier?
Sure.
Now, I brought up some points of representative samples of many, many codes.
I could show you various aspects of American law.
Does what you see on television or even here, even on court TV
or what comes out of attorneys' mouths about the law
even resemble what I just showed you on the codes?
Not at all, right?
No.
It's 180 degrees opposite.
Now, the same thing with the medical stuff.
That's why the biggest farce I say is medical school
because these idiots are taking anatomy,
and they don't even recognize it.
It's right in front of them.
How can anything get absorbed or go through that?
It's the same with the skin.
Do a search on the rectangle, you know what I mean by the stupid rectangle,
the internet, of a profile of the skin.
And I'm not talking about the gore and stuff where there's actually a cadaver
but a drawing of it, which is pretty accurate in most cases.
You'll see the skin also has all these layers.
Nothing goes through there.
It's basically a tunnel from the mouth through the anus.
Everything passes through by, and you get energy from the food via induction.
Here, let me give you another fraudulent thing, a farce or prank.
Calories.
Oh, man, that food's got a lot of calories.
That's like saying, what temperature is that water?
Oh, it's three feet.
What?
That's the wrong scale, dude.
You know what a calorie is?
It's a definition of raising one cubic centimeter or gram of water
one degree Celsius, a thermal measurement.
Yeah, it's a measurement of energy.
Right, and the weight in order to determine what calories are,
you take the specimen and you carbonize it.
In other words, you burn it until you get all the energy out of it, right?
Right, right.
Okay, so now let's say a banana is like 70 calories, and you eat it,
and it passes through the intestines, passes through the body,
and it comes out as fecal matter.
Can you take that fecal matter and burn it?
Yes.
So it's still giving off.
So how many calories did you absorb?
Now, hold on.
There might be someone who is pooping charcoal briquettes, right?
And then calories would apply to them, wouldn't it?
Do you see what a farce this is?
In Latin, farce means prank, by the way.
This is going on.
Have you ever heard of things that you're told by entitled classes
or authorities or television?
I'm not saying authorities are bad.
I'm not anti-authority.
Actually, I don't think there is enough authority of the right kind.
Yeah.
I mean, and I'm going to get into that later if we have enough time.
But what I'm trying to say is you're being misled.
How many times have you seen something on TV
or in the stupid rectangle alternative independent media
that is following along everything else, right?
Now, do a little research.
I'm not going to get into the medical stuff because it's very – you can get elaborate.
It's simple.
Now, simple doesn't mean easy, but it is simple.
It's what do you see.
Have you heard of the – this is a metaphor, but actually it's a very applicable one.
Have you heard of the story of the emperor has no clothes
where the young child says he's basically naked?
Right.
But everyone else, all the trained idiots said, no, no, no, he's a wonderful fabric.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Yeah.
You see, this is what's going on with everyone right now.
And what's interesting about bringing up the medical stuff, maybe not last,
but sort of last on the technical side is because now you're going through a seasonal change
and people think that there's a contagion known as the flu or the cold.
And I'm suggesting that when you change seasons, you should change the way you eat
because if you live in a cold climate and you eat food that's grown in the tropics,
that food that's grown in the tropics is going to change your body chemistry to being in the tropics.
But your body is in the cold.
Your body is in the tropics.
You have thinner blood and a different metabolic rate.
But if you're in the wintertime and you're eating bananas and orange and sugar during the holidays,
which is tropical, in the snow and the cold,
your body is going to change to a tropical metabolism and you're going to get sick.
Very few things are actually contagious.
And by the way, let me ask you guys something.
When it comes to contagions and if it's measured in the blood, like what they call a virus,
which I'm going to get into also briefly, how does it get through the vacuum?
Now we're getting into sci-fi reality, which is the real reality.
That's why when I die, I'm donating this body to science fiction.
So you're suggesting that it's inducted.
It's inducted.
The body actually creates it.
So if you have a frequency or a signal that tells the body not to create that,
you don't have it show up in the blood, whether it's a venom or what they call a bacteria or whatever.
Now the thing about viruses is a scam, a big scam, because anyone –
I'm not going to start dropping links.
You could do this on your own.
I'm not a virus denier or whatever.
I'm just saying it's a farce.
It's a scam.
In other words, if someone puts a thumbtack on the seat and you sit on it and it gets you in the buttock.
Yeah, it punctures you.
I'm not a denier that that happens.
Yes, you are, but I'm telling you it's a prank.
Okay.
If you look up virology, it is a branch of toxicology, and toxicology has to do with liver function.
What they're calling viruses, by the way, they're telling you –
you will never see a picture of a virus, even on an electron microscope.
It's all artist renderings, like black holes.
There's no such thing.
By the way, if anyone in independent media alternative mainstream talks about black holes,
that is the mark of a moron,
which is common and normal because remember the Kevlar underwear everyone wears on this planet?
It's a mathematical model, the same with a virus.
They'll tell you that it's so small you can't even see it.
It's so small it's not there.
What they're calling viruses is mitochondria broken up from the cell,
very robust internal cell tissue like the battery of a cell does not break up and process through the liver.
It gets dumped back into the blood.
They're calling that a virus.
Go look up at what polio and all these other things are.
Polio, they had a lot of –
before the sanitation and the raw sewage was separated from the storm sewage,
you'd have storm sewage and raw sewage mixed in the streets.
You had a lot of flies everywhere, a lot of mosquitoes.
So they're spraying DDT everywhere in the 30s and 40s and 50s until they banned it.
They started realizing all these bugs spraying, the children were crippled.
Oh, it's a bug.
They stopped and there were 10 doctors or seven doctors that spoke on the floor of Congress.
They said, these are neurotoxins.
We need to ban them because people are paralyzed.
But then the medical community says, oh, it's a bacteria.
We have a vaccine for it.
We'll make it go away.
People are retarded.
So basically you could look up everything that I've said but it won't quite bother,
the little flashy neuralyzer thing.
We're going to make sure we flash it before we turn off.
So anyway, so you have people discussing all of these things as if they're real.
Have you ever heard of things being discussed as if they're real and you know they're not,
but you just can't quite put your finger on it?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Well, here you go.
We can go on and on and on.
You could spend the rest of your life just backtracking and covering all the crap that people think is important
and showing that, yes, the subject matter is valid.
But what you think about it is not.
But it's not directly a lie.
It's just a prank.
There's a difference between a – see, a lot of pranks can be harmful.
Right?
Don't you think they are?
Being pranked by an attorney can be harmful, being pranked by a doctor.
People talk about, oh, there's shootings that happen.
People die.
Yeah, but there's a million people that die through medical negligence every year.
And I'm not talking about they made a mistake.
I'm talking about if you just show even a non-medical technician, they're like, oh, this is obviously wrong.
Yeah.
That's 3,000 people a day, Americans, being killed by doctors every day.
Where's the outrage?
3,000 a day.
A day.
So if you want to do an event that shows more than 3,000 being killed in a day, well, maybe it's worth looking at.
Because you're having 3,000 people being killed a day, every day, in and out.
That's how many – a million a year.
That's 10 million every 10 years.
And not a peep about it.
Right?
Not a peep.
I'm not speaking out against them.
You do need medical technicians.
You do need people that know the law.
But I'm telling you, the people in position now don't.
They've got a lot of stories to tell you.
I don't want you to – look, I'm embarrassed to even be human.
I'm even embarrassed to say these things.
I'm even – look, I have to go take a shower after I finish speaking to you guys.
That's how I feel, unclean about this stuff.
But no one else is saying it.
What's wrong with you people?
So I'm going to take a little pause there.
And we can probably change the direction of the subject.
But we can keep going on with the body.
Or I think we'll leave the law stuff behind.
Because, you know, before we leave the law stuff in the background, you know where law comes from?
It comes from your god.
Now it doesn't matter if you believe in one or not.
I'm not saying – I'm not qualifying it that way.
Right?
You know what I mean by a god.
Like, for example, little children, their parents are their god.
You know?
Mommy and daddy.
I mean they could, you know.
See?
And then later on you start looking at other things.
You know, you want to call them ETs.
That's fine.
Because they are.
You know?
They're not here.
They're not overt.
You ever heard of somebody walking through a wall?
Yeah.
Well, you want to call it an angel, an ET, or a demon or whatever?
Well, they walk through a wall.
And they'll swear on a stack of Bibles, which you shouldn't do anyway.
That happened.
You've got to listen to people.
Here's another thing about this type of society.
You know that evidence means nothing?
Your word means nothing.
Years ago it meant a lot.
Your word means nothing now.
How many times have you heard of testimony just being brushed to the side?
It doesn't matter.
The official story says this.
That's what it is.
How many times have you heard that?
Whether it's a small, even a traffic ticket, or even in a family, or a public event.
Your word and evidence means nothing.
So what if the 200,000 tons of skyscraper fell in freefall speed and turned to dust?
So what?
You don't need to know anything about that.
Right?
So anyway, I'm not a proponent for any of this stuff.
Because you're never going to find out the truth of any of these matters.
Because you don't.
I mean, look.
Look what's going on.
I mean, this is just a small representative sample.
Hey, you know what we didn't discuss?
What's that?
This is a keystone thing that I always like to bring up.
Do you ever notice when you celebrate or observe a certain day of the year,
birthday, anniversary, whatever, that every year it's a different day of the week?
Yeah.
Except for one day, and I'll talk about that a little bit.
That's because that calendar that you're using, the Gregorian calendar,
which is based on the Julian calendar.
The only difference is when New Year's and a couple other things were set.
It is not a timepiece.
It's a work schedule for papal subjects, the subjects of the Pope.
You know that almost every country, if not every country in the world,
is using that schedule?
It's a prank.
It's a prank, by the way.
Like right now, I think you're about a week off from lawful time.
And you can go to any university of astronomy.
Within the first two years, they have something called astronomical timekeeping.
And they'll tell you the day starts at solar noon.
You can only keep time with the stars and the moon and the sky, by the way.
The scientists do.
And the moon rules the month.
I can drop a link in that if you want.
You can read it.
This is a university.
But they get neuralized somehow.
I guess when you're in the academic factory,
I guess the conveyor belt is moving too fast to remember that little fact.
So, you know, like here's this.
It has nothing to do with what religion you practice,
because that's when I hear I'm a practitioner of a religion,
I hear you're into minor demonology.
That's the truth.
I could prove it, just like we've shown these other things.
But demonology just means malevolent, not benevolent, right?
Let me ask you this.
Is a real surly-looking used car salesman your friend?
Sure, acts like one.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, sure.
The stereotypical used car salesman is your best buddy, right?
Once he finds out that you don't have enough money or you don't want to buy the car,
he really shows who he is, doesn't he?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, this is exactly what's going on with all this stuff.
Even people's own family members are like that, which is your family, by the way.
Everyone says, oh, no, yeah, there's a lot of evil people in the world,
but none of my friends and none of my family.
I find everybody saying that.
So then where are all the evil people in the world that you guys are talking about?
No, it couldn't be your friends or your family, too.
No way.
Of course not.
You weren't pranked by them.
Santa Claus.
Anyway, it's your birthday, right?
Anyway, this is one of the things I like to bring up, the markers of the morons.
We know when they say emphatically what day it is, and they don't even know what day it is.
You ever notice that septem is a prefix for seven?
Octo is a prefix for eight?
For eight, right.
Noem is a prefix for nine?
December is ten.
Yeah, yeah.
So you get four chances of multiple-choice question-and-answer.
And you're always wrong.
You're always wrong, all of you, statistically.
Now, there's a few that are maybe not, but you don't know.
You're going to see them.
You know who they are.
You always want to stick on the statistical side.
It's safe when you're dealing with the moron mentality.
Because if someone asks you, go count all the grains of sand on the beach, and if you
come back with a number and they want to argue it, you're like, oh, damn, I couldn't make
you count it again.
Just say statistically it's around 400 trillion whatever.
It's fine.
So when I say everyone, I mean statistically, meaning 99.9999999 percent of the people don't
know what's going on.
Sir?
I can't say everyone doesn't know what's going on, because that wouldn't be correct.
Because I haven't met everyone.
I'm not interested in meeting everyone.
Because I'm just telling you what – they got Kevlar underwear, dude.
That's their main industry here.
You get it?
Maybe if you missed the first part, you didn't get it.
But first hour, right?
So it goes on and on.
Do you know I have a list of over a thousand anomalous things like this that should be
in Ripley's Believe It or Not book, but it's right in front of everyone and no one
is noticing?
Over a thousand items like this?
I don't know.
I sound like an ass to most people.
I sound like condescending to most people.
No, no, no.
Not at all.
Actually, I'm still astonished by what you related in the first hour, showing us that
law.
These all were repealed in 1987.
Yeah, 84.
To go in effect in three years, which would put them in effect of October or so of 87,
correct?
Yeah.
I always say that people fear change or people don't like what they don't grasp or understand.
I guess as you said, do your homework.
Look into it.
I believe that the younger kids have a term for that.
I don't understand it, but they call it getting woke.
Stay woke.
Look into it.
Be up to date on what you're wondering about or curious about.
Do the homework.
You got to be careful again.
Let me just make a suggestion.
These younger goats or kids, they're still into the fashion craze, so they're going to
tell you, go get the daisy pattern polyester bell bottoms, not the staphydyl bell bottoms.
They still don't know that they're going to be looking at this later and saying what a
ridiculous thing it is.
You're in the credits right now.
You know how societies have ages and epochs, right?
If you look in the solar system, you look how barren the surface of all the other planets
are and the Earth is this beautiful blue marble, right?
Okay.
What is the reason for that?
Just like, for example, the Earth sticks out like a sore thumb compared to the rest of
the planets.
Just like when you look at a natural scene, whether it's forest or desert, and when you
see man builds a little city, it sticks out like a sore thumb, doesn't it?
You could see it on what they call the Earth maps.
Yeah, you can see it from outer space.
Yeah.
There's a reason why the Earth looks like that.
I'm going to get into more of that in the future.
It's right in front of you.
Forget about the academics.
I mean, it's just a joke.
Just to end up with the academic stuff, maybe we'll get into more stuff.
I run into a lot of professionals, and the reason why I speak poorly of doctors and lawyers
and other priests, rabbis, is not because I read something on the Internet or heard something.
It's because I know these people.
I know many of them interact with them, and they're all the same to some degree.
But the interesting thing is when you walk up to an academic, a professor of tenure or
whatever, or someone who has a degree and they're proud of it and they laud it over
social rank, have a conversation with them.
I'll show you how clueless and mindless they are.
Say to them, you know, pretty much anyone who's got more than an eighth grade formal
education has done irreparable damage to their mind, haven't they?
And all the professors say, yeah, that's true.
But these professors have double that.
Yeah, they've got doctorates.
Yeah, they don't even realize what they're doing.
I mean, it's, you know, the higher you go, the lower.
I mean, this is just a wacky, wacky, wacky thing.
So now most people, one thing I've noticed is the plausibility.
Oh, the Greek says the colleges are bad, or the body's under a vacuum.
Ha, ha, ha.
Isn't that ridiculous?
And the majority of people say, yeah, it is ridiculous.
Ha, ha, ha.
Got any more fart jokes?
You know, this is what I call, you know what a dummy load is?
Sure.
It's like, you know, you've heard of the metaphor of running on a hamster
wheel or a treadmill.
All this stuff is that.
But unfortunately, it's worth speaking about because people get harmed and
killed by the medical system and the legal system and the religious system.
Yeah.
Right?
Now, if it was just a simple prank, like let's say, you know, you got blood
pressure, chemotherapy, and vaccines at the gag store, you know, where they sell
the whoopee cushions and the rubber chickens and the fake dog poo.
That's okay.
That's the proper perspective, isn't it?
Because it's a gag.
It's a prank.
Or, you know, you go to a court and the court and the attorney and the judge
and the black dress is in the gag store next to the whoopee cushion and the
rubber chicken.
It's fine because it's, you know, it's a gag, right?
It's a prank.
But no.
When it's done, it's turned into a monster and it's harming and killing
people on a daily basis.
Now, if no one is giving the specifics, it's not like, oh, well, they're evil,
they're corrupt.
No, that's not good enough.
No.
You have to show how anyone can see how simple it is.
You know?
And no one is doing it, unfortunately.
And I don't want to do it.
But, you know, you sit back for like a year, five years, ten years, 15 years,
and still no one?
It's like, ugh, now I'm culpable.
I better say something.
You know?
If you know something that might prevent harm or help someone, even indirectly,
and you don't say anything, eh, that's not good.
You've got to say it.
No, you're culpable.
Right.
Yeah, you've got to say it.
Now, whether they want to do it, understand it or whatever, you could say,
hey, I said it, you guys are on your own.
Hey, the deck is going to break tomorrow, I see the hole, oh,
we don't believe you.
Oh, okay.
Now, here's the thing about reality is, you know, this is the human system.
And any time you preach doom and gloom, it's going to sound about right.
Everyone wants to hear that, right?
I mean, that's the way it goes.
That's not what I'm doing, folks.
But you are in the credits part of your society, meaning the movie ended.
You're in the credits.
You know, when you're going to shoot a two-hour film,
do you get exactly two hours worth of film
or do you get two hours and ten minutes to give credits?
Credits started a long time ago, around 1998.
You're in the credits.
And what's interesting about the credits is that things are out of order,
and you get to see things that you didn't see on the main movie, don't you?
That's why you start hearing about all these different corruptions and scandals
and things emerging that you'd never heard before.
And also, it's in your face, but you don't care.
I mean, don't you see, like, there's an in your face, but you don't care?
Yeah, we're corrupt.
What are you going to do about it, right?
That is their attitude.
Yeah, this is, whether it's medical, legal, religious, political,
it doesn't matter because you're in the credits, dude.
You know, when I was growing up, let's say in the 60s and 70s,
I remember hearing captains of industry, leaders of countries
talk about multi-generational plans.
You know, now captains of industry and leaders of the people only speak
when it's reactionary, when someone forces them to say something
about something that just went down.
You ever notice that?
There's no future talk anymore.
And you're not going to get no hotel on the moon and space packs
and all that bullshit they gave you in the world.
Yeah, jet packs.
Yeah, you're not going to get any of that, no, no.
You're going to get stupid rectangle and a lot more of it.
Well, actually, I do have a different view on that.
We've discussed it before.
I really do think we're on a transition.
Oh, you are, and I've discussed it with you.
By the mid-2020s, you're going to be in an almost perfect society,
very, very hopeful.
And it's not going to be propagandized.
It's going to be actual.
Yeah.
World peace.
You're going to be soothed with actual.
You know what I mean by a propagandized society?
Like, let's say Stalinist Russia is, oh, you're in a perfect society.
And meanwhile, there's 3,000 people that need deep snow to get toilet paper.
No, no, no.
That's propaganda.
I'm talking about you're going to get distribution of wealth, a level of liberty,
all this other stuff that you consider perfect society right before the kill shots come on.
Why?
Because the last thing you want is to say, well, we were having problems in society,
and you came in and stopped the way we were doing things.
That's not fair.
We never had a chance.
It doesn't work that way.
You're going to have a perfect society.
That's why in ancient texts you hear about the great deception.
The moment you're told that you have 1,000 year reign on this earth of peace,
that you've got less than three and a half years before 90% of the people are gone.
And this time in the next decade is going to start.
What is the mechanism?
I mean do you – I've never – I don't think I've ever asked you this before.
I mean is it going to be the gods coming back?
Yes.
Is it going to be – yes.
The gods.
The gods are a society.
You know how you look at nature and you have a variety of species and plants?
We are like a mock-up of creation on that.
Their society is even more elaborate than ours.
They have more species and more varieties and more beings than we do.
Trillions.
Trillions of trillions of trillions.
We're like a little example to be formed.
And within that godlike society, the Elohim – by the way,
anyone who talks about God in a singular sense is a moron.
There's no such thing.
It's a plurality of them.
And within that plurality, they have a hierarchy system just like on earth.
You've got the street sweeper at the bottom and then you've got the king up top
and the god above that.
And that's how they are.
They have a god as well.
So what's interesting is this is a fact and the truth.
Most people can't hear it, that the earth has been controlled, guided,
and steered by malevolent entities for many thousands of years.
Now in order to pass something malevolent, you have to present it as something good.
Don't you?
Otherwise it won't pass.
All of your educational systems, your governmental systems, your religions,
all of them, not some of them, are all underneath this malevolent system.
You have to put on a cloak, a robe if you will, and tell us that they have authority.
No, they do have authority because if I could cut your head off
and have 100 people to support me in doing that and put it on TV
and everyone will applaud, I have authority.
There's a difference.
That comes with force.
Might is right.
And I want to get into something before we conclude.
This is a hybrid analogy.
I want you to look up the First Amendment.
Anyone can bring that up, and I want you to read it.
I want to show you something you've never seen before.
That's the right of free speech, isn't it?
Oh yeah, just whatever.
No, I'll search it.
Now before we do that, I'm going to read that.
I'm going to show you something that you've never seen before.
I'm going to show you how censored and moronic people are.
I'm going to put up this word or.
I want you to look up the definition of the word or, O-R.
Anyone can read it.
It means either or or instead of.
It means one thing or another, right, one thing instead of another.
So you can have five things with or, or, or, and you have to pick one of them.
Or you want a ham sandwich or a tuna fish sandwich or a turkey sandwich.
Or when you go to a Chinese restaurant, here's lo mein or fried rice, chicken or beef or vegetable, right?
Not all of them, right?
But sometimes they have the house special, which they throw all of them.
But you see what I mean by the word or?
I want you to read the First Amendment.
Just bring it up.
Anyone can bring it up.
Yeah, I've got it.
It's actually about religion.
Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion or prohibiting.
Slow down, slow down.
Establishment of religion or.
Or prohibiting the free exercise thereof.
Or.
Or abridging the freedom of speech or of the press.
Or the right of people peaceably to assemble and to position the government for redress of grievances.
All right.
So you're ordering fried rice and it's either beef or chicken or vegetable.
So which one of those?
Let me ask you.
This is a con, by the way.
No, I see what you're saying.
So it's either Congress shall make no law respecting establishment of religion or.
Or.
Or prohibiting the free exercise thereof.
You've got to pick one of the two.
Or abridging the freedom of speech.
So now you've got to pick freedom of speech, religion or free exercise.
Or of the press.
It doesn't mean you can have them all.
Or the right of the people.
It doesn't say and.
It doesn't say Congress shall make no law respecting the establishment of religion and prohibiting
the free exercise thereof and abridging the freedom of speech and the press.
And it's or.
So you have to pick one of those laundry lists and one of those things and to petition the
redress of grievances.
So people are going and saying the First Amendment says we've got freedom of speech and religion
and freedom of press.
No, you don't.
No.
You got to pick one.
Pick one idiot.
That's why.
Is the government respecting any of those cries?
No.
Should they?
Why?
Because according to law, they don't have to.
It's right in front of you, people.
Now, how many people have read the First Amendment and brought up what I just brought up?
Zero.
Publicly.
I know there's some Supreme Court justice that's laughing their ass off because, you
know, when you become a high level judge, they whisk you away and give you private training
on what words mean.
Yeah.
I don't know if you know that.
I'm just basically saying it.
There's actually a couple of YouTube videos that have leaked out on training federal judges.
I don't know if they're still up there.
And basically, it's amazing.
Listen, most people won't understand it, but it's very basic.
It's all contract.
What you say.
It's exam.
That's why they say anything you say can and will be used against you.
Can.
It doesn't say can or will be used against you.
What's wrong with you people?
Whenever I hear this free speech and freedom of the press, I'm like, no, no, it doesn't
say that.
And it says, yes, it does.
It says, or it says, what's the difference, Greek?
OK, I'm going to go put some Kevlar underwear on because that's what you guys do, right?
You see the level.
Tom, are you with us?
So you're quiet.
Yeah.
No, I am listening.
I had pulled up the or part and I didn't know if you wanted that read out.
But yeah, I am with you.
It's not and.
So if I give you a list of 10 things and there's or between them, you have to pick one.
That's right.
And so do you see it?
You guys have been conned with the cons.
Who's the first president of the United States of America?
John Hansen.
The first American revolution was when George Washington was signed in on Wall Street as
president.
He had one tooth in his mouth, a left bicuspid.
He was sworn in by the Freemasons.
And he says, boy, are we going to have a fun time?
Because Lafayette says he's going to come back and take the whole country, you know,
the British?
Yeah.
And they did.
Second or the third American revolution was at the end of the Napoleonic War, which is
1812 or the 1814.
Right.
A war of 1812 was a Napoleonic War.
The next American revolution was what they call civil wars.
Not a civil war.
It was a war between the states.
That's right.
The next American revolution was in 1933 with FDR turned it into a democracy.
I mean, there's no reason discussing this with anybody.
I mean, you want to discuss this with somebody, not anybody, because they're going to get
neuralized.
So, anyway, that's what I feel better about saying these things momentarily, because I
know they've been said.
I don't recommend anyone act on these things unless you're extremely prudent and wise.
So, you know, here's I'll bring this up to you guys.
I know this is public, but I'll say it anyway.
I tell most people that as so far, no one's ever rebutted this.
You're ready.
I'll tell you guys this.
Go ahead.
No one's ever rebutted this in over 12 years.
No one ever has come back to Greek.
That's not true.
They say quiet and quiet is acquiescence and tacit agreement.
Right.
I said that, hey, everybody you've ever known, everyone you know, and everyone you're going
to know is a freaking moron.
And everyone has been quiet.
I'll rebut it.
Go ahead.
It's fine.
I think I'm somewhat smart.
No, no, no.
I'm not saying you.
Or I can say you.
You said everyone.
Everyone you know.
Everyone I know.
Yeah.
I'm speaking to you individually now, not as a group.
OK.
I mean, I'm not talking to the guy next to you.
I'm talking about you.
I consider some of the people.
Why are you going to let him talk to me like that?
You see, what happens now is the fart jokes come out.
I know some quite smart people.
I know.
Well, there's a difference between appearing to be smart and being smart.
And the word smart means to poke.
So there's many levels to this.
Now, I'm not saying this in an emphatic way that you need to react, but be better to think
about it's a rhetorical statement.
Well, I didn't want to be acquiescent.
Well, that's good.
You see, but I preempted you.
So but I'm trying to show you how these things work and think about it maybe later.
Or they don't work.
Maybe things are meant for them not to work.
So anyway, there you go with enough stuff.
Now, in terms of the religions, which you didn't bring up, you know, there's not a religion
on the planet bar none that does anything or knows anything in the text that they allege
to subscribe to.
Now, one thing that you might realize or not is that academia that controls what's the
written record, what's been memorialized.
Most of academia are like self-professed atheists, but yet they have earmarked the past 2,000
years as the Christian era on this planet.
So regardless of the other religions, this is known historically as the Christian era.
Proof of that is you could look this up.
This is academic.
A proof of that is that everyone's on the Pope's work schedule, meaning the Gregorian
calendar, and there's many proofs to that.
Time and all that stuff.
Actually, if you can usurp time over people, you've got them on everything else, don't
you?
Think about it.
There is no such thing as time, by the way.
There are events, and the way you record and memorialize events is with something called
time.
You see it in the Olympics all the time.
They have that really fast stopwatch.
You know, it's the run.
It's how fast they're doing the run or the swim.
The stopwatch is irrelevant.
It's only relevant to memorialize the event.
Otherwise, they've got to keep doing it in perpetuity.
Then they get kind of tired.
So people say, when you ask these people, there's no such thing as time.
Why?
And they can't answer.
Oh, I don't know, man.
I've got a fart joke.
Okay.
So anyway, you're in the Christian era.
Now, Christians are the easiest to harp on because they have no law, basically.
They tell you the law has been done away with.
They're supposed to be biblical, right?
And if you look at – most people know about Christianity, even Christians themselves, by
what's put out in what they call the churches or what's put out in Hollywood.
Now, if you look at all those stories, and you mention Adam and Eve and the snake and
the apple and Noah's Ark or the Christ and all this stuff, all that imagery and all
that stuff is not in the text that they allege to subscribe to at all, as they think it
is.
Now, I'm not saying, well, yeah, we know Greek.
It's a metaphor.
It never really happened.
No, no, no.
Whether it's literal or metaphorical, none of that stuff even resembles because no one
reads it.
And first of all, you couldn't read it because it has never been translated outside of the
languages of preservation anyway.
A version – you know, look up the word version etymologically.
Towards the end of the definition, it means to destroy something.
That's why you have the King James destroying it.
You have the New International destroying it.
You have the – you see?
Now, the same thing works with the Muhammadism, Islam.
No, I never met anyone that practices Islam that knows anything in the Koran.
Now, they might know something out of context just like they'll pull a verse out.
But I've got a recipe book here and this recipe here for the turkey says preheat oven
to 350.
So does the chocolate chips and the roast beef and the cake.
Preheat oven to 350, doesn't it?
So if I just start saying preheat to 350, I got it all.
Do you have it?
No.
Very different things going on every time you preheat the oven to 350.
You can't take things out of context.
I was telling someone earlier I travel around with a Bible, a Book of Mormon and a Koran
because I tend to get into these conversations publicly.
And so I'll have a discussion about this publicly and so that's not in the Koran.
Oh, you know what?
You got five minutes?
I happen to have a copy.
Yeah, and there it is.
Yeah.
And they'll say, well, you know what?
Actually, the Christians all have – I'll tell you, they're all – you know what the
hive mentality is like the Borg in Star Trek?
Sure.
The Christians have this demon behind them and they have the deniable one.
What they will do is if you press them on what they're doing – I don't do this anymore
by the way, but I'm just going to enlighten the audience and they'll see it in their
own lives if they decide to study these things.
What all the Christians, the hive that they plugged into is if you press them on their
traditions, being contrary, listed on the abominable things, the absolute prohibitive
things to do in the Bible, they immediately start to discredit the text.
Well, who wrote that anyway?
I don't need that to believe.
They all say that.
When I say all, I mean 99.999% of the time they all say that.
Or they say that everyone does it this way.
That's the way I'm going to do it.
They hide behind the crowd.
Gustave Le Bal in the crowd, right?
I'll talk a little bit about Gustave Le Bal if you remind me.
The other thing that they do, well, they pretty much do all that kind of hive mentality.
Now the Muslims, they have another hive, another demon that they plug into, the Borg.
Even if you show it to them, they say, well, this Koran is not the one that I have.
The one you have is not right.
This is not the right one.
Or, no, it doesn't really mean that because the Koran was written to be simple and what
you're telling me I don't understand.
So it can't be.
That's not the right Koran.
That's not the right copy.
No good.
And bringing this up because if you are able to back up what I'm saying, go have discussions
with the various faiths of the world, and they all seem to say the same thing as if
they're attached.
You know what I mean by hide, like the Borg?
It's like a Wi-Fi that attaches them.
They're all saying the same thing.
It's very unnerving to see that how poorly – in other words, the control, what I call
about the cosmic censorship, the malevolent spirit controlling humanity.
Once you start becoming objective, you will see it's overt in your face, kind of like
if you have a Wi-Fi router or something in a room and it's blinking, it's working,
the LED.
It's just like that.
When you see people and you're objective, you're like, oh, this guy is a doctor or
this guy is a Christian or this guy is whatever.
Oh, yeah.
I got his number, man.
Watch.
You could bet with someone.
I'm going to say this and he's going to say that.
No way, Greek.
There's no way he's going to say that.
How do you know?
I said, watch.
They're so easy and it's not a parlor trick.
It just shows how pathetic the quality and the character of humanity has been downbred.
It's a breeding program that you're subject to.
I'll give you an example.
You know what a chihuahua is, right?
Of course.
Okay.
That's a product of domestication.
Yeah.
How long do you think that would last in the forest?
Do you think it would come back in a week and it will be there?
Probably not.
Yeah.
Okay.
So how long do you think humanity will last in the real world outside of the things that
I'm saying right now?
No.
Not at all.
That's why you're being set up and you're very well controlled and very well contained.
Right?
And it's on a high – it's like the Wi-Fi.
You're all tuned into various hives.
These are various – these – when I said all the religions are part of demonology,
like you're giving an example again of Christianity.
You notice like there's Eastern Orthodox Christianity.
They have a certain liturgy, iconography, language and all that, right?
Belief system.
Sure.
And you have Roman Catholic.
They have a different liturgy, different iconography.
Then you have like Mexican Catholic.
And then you have German Lutheran Christian.
And then you have Mormon Christian.
Yeah.
Russian Orthodox.
Russian Orthodox, which is Eastern Orthodox.
And you notice all these Christianity is severely big differences in doctrine and the way they
appear because those are the same post-flood pagan religions exactly from that geographical
location going on the same way they've been going on for thousands of years.
They just called it Christianity now.
Just like a department store.
It's no longer Woolworth.
Now it's whatever, whatever.
It's the same racks, the same clothes, the same people, different uniform.
The same with Islam.
You got all these various forms of Islam.
You hear of Sunnis, Wahhabis, this, that and the other.
Those are all geographically based.
The same pagan ancient gods.
The Yazidis.
They worship a peacock.
Oh, man.
Then you have the Samaritans.
The Samaritans, by the way, were most of your David Copperfields and Houdinis came out of.
You know what I mean by David Copperfields and Houdinis?
You're magicians.
Yeah, magicians.
Sure.
Simon Magus.
Have you ever heard of Gnosticism or Catholic universality, the Catholic Church?
That's Simon Magus, the Samaritan.
He came out with that stuff.
So ask a Gnostic what day it is.
Actually, he'll want to get into a flat earth argument.
I'm serious.
I mean these people are easy.
They're so simple.
I mean it's gone to the point where it's – I'll give you an example.
You ever watch folklore, even Star Wars or whatever?
When you're a sage or a wise man or whatever, do they find them in the middle of town or do they have to go out in the desert and the mountain to get them, right?
They have to go up on a mountain and do a cave.
Yeah, or somewhere.
Bottom of the ocean somewhere.
He doesn't want to be – I mean …
Yeah, they're not in the city.
Yeah, they're not.
But actually what's interesting, a lot of the quote-unquote biblical prophets were put in the middle of the city to prove to them that they had spiritual protection or a literal force field.
And then let me just fast forward and bump around.
We already started with the end, right, which was don't bother, set yourself apart.
Remember the first thing I started saying?
Let's start with the end.
I'm not going to change.
Now, I think I've supplied enough bricks to show you where the structure is going.
And it can't stand obviously because all the things, the little fragments and aspects that I've explained and shown to you and hopefully you put them in the chat and they're gone out there.
Or hopefully we've given enough information that whoever is listening to this later on down the – whatever out of a can can reference them again.
But what I'm saying is eventually to say that you think society is going to get better because you do X, Y, Z or 100, it ain't going to happen.
You can definitely make your life better.
So there are plenty of people that have survived a war zone.
This is a mental spiritual war zone.
In other words, it is not a war of ballistics where you have metal being projected at you, bombs and high-speed chemistry.
It is an intangible one like the Wi-Fi or the radio.
It's of the mind.
Yeah, spiritual war.
Yeah, spiritual which means mind.
And have you ever – if you grew old enough to remember running and some older people say, I grew up during the war.
It was terrible.
We had to eat shoe leather.
We didn't get rationed.
We had no food but we made it.
It was terrible.
Well, most of humanity when they're brought back is going to say, we lived on the earth during this time period.
You're going to be like, OK.
Well, you don't have to pat yourself on the back.
I'll pat you on the back because that was one hell of a nasty time to be on this planet.
But I didn't realize it until it was way later.
You don't want to be realized.
So by the way, just bouncing things around, it's not good to harp on the Christians because they're the majority and they're very sensitive.
It's just really bad.
And by the way, any of the religions, the Buddhists – Buddhism is funny too.
If you look at the writings and the studies of Buddhism, that was about living – how to live a life with integrity and increasing your level of integrity in everything that you do.
It's not about sitting in a lotus position and meditating, clearing your head because you can't clear your head in a lotus because your head starts racing or saying, I want to ride Corvette or something.
You know what I mean?
Sure.
It's easy to make fun of these people because it's just gotten to the point where if you don't, no one will, so you might as well.
But to get to the point, there is no point with that.
It's just a distraction.
It's an entertainment thing.
They take it seriously.
They kill themselves over it.
It's fine because you don't want to stop.
If someone is fixing on going to war, you don't want to try to stop them because then they're going to get on you.
Yeah, they're going to roll over you.
Yeah.
So get out of the way and let them do what they got to do and just hope that it doesn't affect your food chain.
That's one thing I wanted to get into, one of the simple ways just to bounce off the religion thing.
This concept of food, I kind of briefly brought it up, the importance of eating seasonally, how it changes body chemistry, which is totally disregarded by the quackademics.
A doctor, they'll tell you, oh, you need vitamin C. The vitamin C craze, I'm glad that went away, at least for now.
There was a craze about that four or five years ago.
I remember vitamin C. You got the young children in knee-deep snow in the northeast and vitamin C comes from oranges.
Drink oranges.
What happens to the body?
It adjusts to Florida climate, Arizona climate.
No, you get sick.
Vitamin C doesn't work and there's no such thing as a vitamin anyway.
That's another thing.
The concept of vitamins was started by a guy called Rudolf Hoschka in the 30s.
He said, well, food has some kind of vitality and different foods have different kinds of vitality and different properties.
You know, like some foods prevent scurvy.
If you don't have them, you get scurvy, right?
Some foods do this.
So he wanted to find what vitality was in food and he made extracts and he called them the vitalities of foods.
And later on they called them industry of vitamins.
But he published in his works that these extracts are only good for three days.
Let me ask you, when you go buy vitamins, do you think it was extracted three days ago or was it sitting on the shelf for a week or a month or a year?
The latter, of course.
Yeah, it's worthless.
That's why these people that know about vitamins say, oh, Americans have the most expensive urine in the world.
This is a joke.
No, I totally understand because they pass through you without doing you any good at all, right?
Well, because they've expired.
In other words, they take large doses.
In other words, you'd have to take over 100 times the amount when it's vital.
So why not just – see, you know they tell you there's vitamins in vitamin C and oranges?
No one knows what's in an orange.
Now, if you take the orange and you squash it, kill it, kill it, man.
Take the juice, put it in a centrifuge, and then put it under a Bunsen burner until it gets into a powder.
And then you measure ascorbic acid.
See?
There's vitamin C in an orange.
No.
After you kill it, dry it, and burn it, yeah, you've changed it.
You ever hear of transmutation?
Alchemy?
Yeah.
Go talk to people at 3M.
What sort of mineral?
Yeah, you've transformed it into acid now.
What if you put it in a mass spectrometer?
Well, let's see what happens if you do that.
You know the accuracy of those things is really skeptical too, you know.
I had never heard that.
I thought those were the half-million-dollar mass spectrometer is supposed to be able to measure things right down to the atoms.
They measure elements, yeah.
Yeah.
If there is such thing as an atom, that's another thing Walt Disney got on everybody.
Oh, the electron and the proton.
You know, these things are not to be argued.
They're to be known.
Like you want to know that they're going to put a thumbtack on everyone's chair on this planet.
Don't you want to know that?
You know?
Well, certainly.
Because Kevlar underwear is expensive.
Just don't sit down.
It's very simple.
I mean, look, Tom got neuralyzed.
He doesn't even take the neuralyzer out yet.
Anyway, what do you got to say about that, Tom?
Well, you know, I do want to say we're coming up to the end of the second hour.
And we have first-time listeners that may not have been able to catch your name.
This is the Greek that we have on.
Where would you point any first-time listeners?
Uncommon Radio.
Thank you.
Uncommon Radio is the way to get in touch with me.
And I'm going to be showing – I have a radio stream also, which is – it's Uncommon Radio.
I'll be posting links to that.
I'll be doing regular events more in depth.
But Uncommon Radio, you just do a search in any browser.
The first site that comes up, Uncommon Radio.
And the email is UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com.
That's a numeric one.
There's an email link there also.
All of this information is not – what I'm trying to provide is a level of discernment, Tom.
Have you ever heard of people say, don't judge, don't be judgmental?
I agree with that only because people lack proper discernment to make good judgment.
But you have to be judgmental.
If you drive a car and you see a red octagon, do you hit the gas or do you stop?
Use judgment.
You see the red octagon that says STOP on it?
That's using judgment all the time.
If you don't use judgment all the time, you're probably not going to make it home if you leave the house.
What's that big object coming toward me?
It's a bus.
Oh, I guess I didn't judge.
I should have stood on the sidewalk.
But when I hear most people say, don't be judgmental, I agree because you lack the discernment for it.
So that's what's lacking is a discernment.
The subject matter is irrelevant.
So that's what I would say for first-time listeners.
And if you're a first-time listener and you're young, I really feel kind of bad if you're young because you're supposed to look up to the elders for wisdom.
And they've all been turned into – that's why they stick them in nursing homes and they slap diapers and inject them with drugs because they're not doing their job.
You ever wonder about that?
Anyway, so I just wanted to say back on that thought, Tom, about where do they go for what?
Where do they go for reading material?
Besides the radio station, where would you point someone to the literature or the US.gov website for the –
None of that.
None of that because then you're presuming people know how to read.
We just brought up the First Amendment, which has been read by hundreds of millions of people and no one has ever brought up the point I just brought up, how useless it is legally.
It's discernment.
OK.
Well, I wish for everybody to be able to possess that skill.
You acquire it.
When you go to the gym the first day, ever been to a gym, you see all these people pumping iron, whatever.
You get in there on the bench press with 50 pounds and you're sore the next day.
You're like, this is hopeless.
And I'm telling you it's not.
You go again.
You give yourself a break.
You go three days a week and in a month, you'll be impressed at where you are.
And in six months, even more.
And in three years, you'll be like the rest of them.
So like your bodily muscles.
Yeah, just like the – this is not open a can or pop it in the microwave.
Sometimes I'll talk to people and say, I've got to get a coffee.
And they come back ten seconds later.
I'm like, how the hell did you get a coffee in ten seconds?
It's a minimum of 15 minutes or eight minutes, minimum.
If you have a $1,200 barista machine, you could probably do it in five minutes or three minutes.
How did you do it?
Well, microwave, of course.
This is not out of the can.
This is – I don't have any do-it-yourself packets.
People say to me all the time, Greek, you've got to write a book.
Yeah, I could put all this stuff in a book or a little pamphlet or a newsletter, everything we did tonight, two hours.
It would be quite helpful for most.
But if I do that, I'm presuming people know how to read, don't I?
Yeah.
And I'm telling you they don't.
There's a difference.
You know what functionally literate is.
You can read it, but you don't know what it means.
Right now I want you to go to Etymology, Tom.
Put in Etymology on the search.
Let me know.
The first site is Etymonline.
Let me know when you're on the site.
There will be a little search box at the top.
Let's see if I'm spelling it right.
E-T-Y.
Yep, that was it.
Go to the site and you see a search box.
It's got a burgundy, ivory color.
You see it?
In the search box, I want you to put in the word N-I-C-E, nice.
Like you're a nice guy.
Have a nice day.
This is a nice show where everybody wants to be nice.
Be nice.
I want you to hit enter and read the definition of the word nice for me, would you?
Foolish.
Stupid.
Senseless.
Careless.
Clumsy.
Weak.
Poor.
Needy.
Simple.
Stupid.
Silly.
Foolish.
From Latin, fastidious.
I hope this was not a nice show.
Tom, are you a nice guy now?
No.
I hope not.
Yeah.
Oh, I don't need that Bible.
Who wrote that anyway?
Merry Christmas.
Happy Birthday.
We've gone into what birthdays cannibals and dolls have in common.
Hey, do you know what day it is today?
No, you don't.
You don't know what day it is.
You know the date.
You don't know the day.
It's around the 16th day of the 8th month.
It's your birthday.
Merry Christmas.
That's what's important.
Anyway.
Wacky, isn't it?
Welcome to planet Earth.
You know why you don't see the back of the moon?
It's black, they say.
Well, there's a big billboard.
Caution.
You're entering Earth zone.
Planet full of morons.
You don't think so?
Okay.
I've just given you enough evidence that you could presume that in a thought experiment
and see that it's somewhat true.
I would like to believe that it is true.
I really want it to be true.
But anyway, I'm just.
Yeah.
So, you know, do you remember the analogy I gave about the Kevlar underwear?
Right.
We're going to this planet where they have a tradition where everybody puts a thumbtack
on the seat.
That's why manufacturing of Kevlar underwear is the largest industry on this planet.
Now, doesn't that sound stupid?
You want to start examining the industries of this planet, the religions of this planet,
what the academics say, all this stuff.
Isn't that stupid?
Yes.
And you're part of a breeding program.
But fortunately, you don't have a lot of time left.
And unfortunately, you don't have a lot of time left because it's going to get a lot
very uncomfortable.
But for good reason.
Later on, you're going to say, wow.
Yeah.
That's wow.
That is the music at the end of the show.
It's been good.
Thank you so much, Greek, for neurotizing me.
Neuralizing.
I added it to you.
Keep an eye out for the meteor shower coming up this weekend, guys.
And stay safe.
Get woke.
And listen to Revolution Radio.
Keith, are we ready to say goodnight?
Goodnight, everybody.