I want to get right to our guest.
We have the Greek joining us again.
How are you doing this evening, sir?
Oh, greetings.
I'm still on this rock with everyone else, so that's a moot question.
I'm just joking.
No.
No, doing well.
Thanks for having me, Keith.
Is it Tom?
Major Tom also?
Yes, Tom.
Okay, great.
Yeah, greetings.
So we have about two hours of shaking everyone around a little bit, maybe, or just putting
everyone to sleep.
The choice is yours, guys.
So let's go.
Turbulence is good.
Well, you know me.
I like to shake things up.
I want to stimulate people, and that's why I very much enjoy having you on.
You know, you have a very unique perspective and information that you don't get anywhere
else really.
Yeah, that's good and bad at the same time.
I know.
It is.
Yeah, it is.
And the thing is, well, you know, I don't want you to believe anything I say.
Check up on it, first of all.
Second of all, you know, you could talk about a lot of things, but, you know, why bother
if no one understands what you're saying?
The reason why I bring that up is, you know, let's just say it this way.
I was out today.
I was at, you know, a British vernacular at the shops, let's say, right.
And I just looked around and I wouldn't say I was afraid for my life, but I was definitely
afraid for their lives, the way they people act.
And I'm not saying this was, you know, I was in the ghetto or anything or in a war zone.
I was just in a, you know, American Southwest, you know, various places just dealing with
the public.
And it and I wouldn't say I was in absolute horror, but I was in just looking around
and saying, wow, if this is humanity, I don't want to be a part of it.
You see what I mean?
So and it's not that I'm agoraphobic or antisocial or anything.
I wish thing.
I like good things.
I like things of quality.
I like pleasant conversation.
I like pleasant things.
Right.
And I find what are the norms.
What's just what would you say understood or accepted is is unacceptable in most cases,
if you know what I mean.
Right.
No, I absolutely do.
Yeah.
So for many years, for about a decade and a half, I've been studying full time on what
the hell is going on.
I mean, I could say that again, like, what the hell is going on?
Right.
And I don't mean from the perspective that most people are used to hearing questions
about society or even personality or anything like that, because that again, like you said,
maybe I have a unique perspective.
Maybe I don't.
But I would say that what I've summed up to this point by looking at things objectively
is that humanity is under what I call a very heavy dose of cosmic censorship, in other
words, being censored.
What I would say about that, and, you know, I keep I'm very redundant and I've been speaking
on the Internet for almost 10 years now and I've been redundant.
And there's a reason for it is if he begs repetition, because nothing has changed.
I'm not expecting it to change.
But what I mean by cosmic censorship is, you know, people are censored on a worldwide scale
in general.
And what I mean by censorship in this case with people is they really can't see sometimes
what's five feet in front of them or up in the sky or a concept.
Right.
You know, like what words mean or just a concept in law, a concept regarding the human body,
a concept regarding history, ancient writs.
You know, how many times have you heard people wanting to argue with you?
Right.
They want to they want to when they hear something that they haven't heard before, say, I want
to debate you.
Right.
You hear that all the time.
Or you hear what is your opinion of that or what is your truth?
I mean, you know, all that irrelevant stuff, because you can't really get stuff done or
built based on those things that I just mentioned.
So just to lead into another train of thought, people are very easily impressed if you haven't
imagined that or seen it.
I'm telling you, they are right.
And they have been impressed by industry.
They've been impressed by, you know, edifices.
You know, if someone builds a very tall building, that makes them a very great person, I guess,
you know, because they know how to mold metal and glass and brick and or whatever, you know,
or they know how to shoot projectiles out of a barrel, you know, make some powerful.
They're very easy to impress, you see.
So so I've been looking at things objectively and and then I've noticed that the only solution
or advice I would give to anyone is to set yourself apart from what's going on.
Right.
And then there's a whole other list of maxims we can get into that I've discovered, which
we might or may not.
So no, that is that.
Go ahead, Thomas.
I was just going to say two hours flies by.
So wherever you want to start, oh, at the end, of course, everything's backwards.
You know, I tell people, if you take anything and just turn it upside down, anything, just
turn it upside down.
And guess what?
Now it's right side up.
So the end of the matter is that there's, you know, each one is hearing or interacting,
you know, I call it the stupid rectangle, you know, the Internet, you know, give you
an idea.
Recently, I told someone, you know, you're getting that information from the stupid rectangle
when he was holding one of these tablets, says, what's that?
And I said, well, put it down and walk away.
And he says, oh, man, I see what you're saying.
It's a rectangle and it's stupid.
Right. So everyone is sort of interacting right now on the rectangle.
Right. So from that point of view, the end of the moral of the story is you're not changing
anything other than yourself and you're not going to change yourself into something like
in a fairy tale. The best you can do is set yourself apart.
And what I mean by that is, let's say I said to you guys, hey, listen, you might need some
extra cash or something.
You're like, yeah, well, how about I pay you ten thousand bucks a day to work in the
sewer? You're like ten thousand bucks a day.
Should I'll do it. But are you just because it's ten grand a day or does that mean you're
going to skinny dip and drink the water or are you going to put on a full on hazmat suit?
You see, no, I would take the latter.
Yeah, exactly. I mean, can you could you be so happy that you'd want to skinny dip in that
crap and no way.
The same with working on power lines.
Are you going to just go and grab it with a tank top sweats and flip of flip flops or
are you going to put on the proper gear?
So the proper gear for operating in this society.
And when I say this society, I'm not just talking about the American one.
I'm talking about any country you're in is to set yourself apart from them.
And the way you do that is very simple, because if you don't know how to set yourself
apart and it seems like a new idea.
Right. Because that's something new.
I never I don't know what even how to begin.
Well, if it's something that is so new, the only way to find the best new ideas is by
looking at really old books.
So if you want a new idea, look at an old book.
So. So what that goes back to objectivity.
Now, that's the end.
Now, to to maybe show what that is built on, meaning is the end means like it's the
top. Right. That's the cap.
Let's go down towards the foundation of these things.
You know, there's an interesting thing.
Have you heard people say, we're so modern, we're so great because we're modern.
What's interesting, if you do a little historical research within, let's say, the
common vernacular of the ancient Greeks, the ancient Romans, the ancient Babylonians
or any of these ancient societies.
Do you know that right before their societies fell into disarray, they called
themselves modern in their in their contemporary writings?
No, I was not aware of that.
Yeah, it's interesting when you research it.
Now, I'm not talking about like going to school and redoing a history class.
I'm not going to tell you anything because the schools are simply just factories.
They're basically you go to an assembly line like a factory and they put stuff you're
on a conveyor belt or, you know, one that you're sitting at a desk and they're
plugging you with stuff.
And if you don't repeat back to them what they want to hear, they don't you don't
pass. You spend more time there.
Then they give you some very expensive toilet paper called a diploma.
And now you now you have a social rank that you can go out and lot over people.
How many times have you said have you heard her people say, well, we have doctor so
and so. Oh, wow.
Oh, you know.
So it's like it's quite the opposite.
Right. In many aspects.
What I'm saying, what things are built on is that you've heard of fashion, right?
It's quite fashionable to be a certain way or think a certain way.
Fashion is not just food.
I mean, not just clothing.
It's also food. It's also the way things are considered.
Right. Yeah. And ideas as well.
Yeah. The things, you know, being in this, of course, is fashionably late at a party,
you know, and of course, hopefully it's a party you want to go to.
But essentially these fashions that are viewed in high regard later on tend to fall
into low regard. Like, for example, if you're old enough and you know someone old
enough and they take out an old photo album from the late 60s or 70s and you see
these big wide lapels and polyester bed bell bottoms and these terrible colors and
patterns that didn't match.
Well, and they're like ashamed of it.
Right. It's like, oh, that's so gaudy looking, you know.
But at the time they thought it was a good idea, didn't they?
Right. All that fashion.
So so this is what I see.
And well, anyone can see it.
All right. Now, I just want to bounce around.
When you bring up concepts like this, I found out that people kind of go mute and
they listen. It's a very contemplative thing.
But on the other hand, I recommend that when you go down a path like this, where you
try to objectify, basically a good technician is also very good at being objective.
Right. Someone who you hire to troubleshoot something should be objective.
But basically, when you go down this path, people tend to be quiet.
And the other thing about it is I noticed that you remember that movie Men in Black,
the little red flashy thing, the neuralyzer?
Yeah, sure. It's funny how they'll sit around and listen to you, whether it's five
minutes or five hours. And then as soon as you stop and walk away, it's like they
forget everything you've said goes back to the cosmic censorship.
I don't you know, you really don't need a neuralyzer.
They have one built in.
And it's really interesting how that works.
So just to go back to the fashion, besides the fashion and the entitled classes, you
know how we brought up how things are, you know, if you want an old idea and then
leading to the academia and how basically the social rank and you get it through a
factory, right, known as academia.
What's interesting is that that academic factory has produced what I call the entitled
classes, the knowledge bearers, knowledge givers, like the word doctor means teacher.
And here's some advice.
I do give advice. Don't let anyone ever laud a kind of title like that over you.
It's a it's very belittling to the human spirit also, by the way.
So what I tend to do is just watch it at a distance and see how it plays out.
And it's very sad because it's based that social rank stuff.
I'm not saying that because if someone holds a position of power, they should be
belittled. Right.
But I'm just saying how I see it being used, typically these academic social ranks,
especially. Do I have a bone to pick with the academics?
You could say so.
But I also have a bone to pick with the religious society entitled classes.
You know, the legal society, they're entitled classes, the medical society.
And why is it personal?
No, because if they're so great, how well are they serving the society?
Well, look at the the entitled legal classes, you know, the attorneys, the attorneys
generals, the judges, law enforcement and all that.
The more of them you get and the better they get, the more people are being put in
prison and losing their property.
And if the medical society and their entitled classes are doing so well, how come the
more of them and the better that they get, the more cancer and the sicker people are,
you see.
And how come is it because, you know, there's so much information.
I mean, you go to the religious, which is a whole other discussion.
How come you do a little bit of study and see that every major religion on the world
is practicing demonology?
Straight up, right.
What I mean by demonology means lower level entities, which we could get into that
also.
So there's many levels to that.
And I also want to give some examples tonight.
Maybe I have some things that I could drop in the Skype chat box and either one of you
two men there could read it, go to the link, can read it, because when I read the reference,
it doesn't seem to have the same effect as someone else reads it.
I don't know.
You and I, Keith, could read a reference.
But when you read it, it seems to have 70 percent more punch on the audience for some
reason.
You know, I don't know why that works.
No, certainly I'd be happy to do that.
I can also post it in the chat room.
Sure, sure.
I'll drop it in there.
And, you know, it's not a matter of...
See, here's the thing.
Anyone that says we have to do this to make the world a better place is a complete fool,
moron, idiot to be avoided.
Because typically most people say that and they're on that level.
They don't see what's going on because they can't measure the times.
You know, it's like if you see the Titanic is sinking, if you're saying we're going to
try to save this ship, you're an idiot.
You should be looking for a life vest, a jacket or a roll top desk.
And I'm not saying this because there's that kind of urgency in society, you see.
But I'm just using that as a metaphor, you see.
But what you can say is I'm going to try to save myself or make myself better.
Just like the old adage, when an airplane is in distress, a modern airplane, they tell
you to put on your own oxygen mask first before you try to put on someone else's.
You've heard of that, right?
Of course, yeah.
Yeah.
So you get yourself in order first, which is not happening because of many of the things
that I mentioned.
People are looking up to the entitled classes, whether it's legal society, religious society,
medical society, all these.
What I mean by entitled ones, you know, they tend to be better off than everyone else, you
know, because of that rank and and also the the fashions that people go through and also
just the absolute lack of objectivity.
Combine that with cosmic censorship.
Should I go on?
Yes.
Do you see how simple it's not this simple TV thing like, oh, the current administration
is influenced by the Russians.
If we get rid of that, we'll be fine.
No, sorry.
You know, if we all eat brown rice and go vegetarian, we're going to be fine.
No, that's not going to fix it either.
Right.
Oh, if we just get free energy, that's going to be.
No, that's not going to do it either.
It's all you have to do all of it or none of it, you see.
Or in other words, if you don't do all of it, you're going most of the way and then
it just falls short and nothing takes place.
Right.
So it's kind of like a machine with many cogs.
If one little tiny thing goes wrong, the whole thing stops working.
So you have to address the entire thing holistically.
And since that will not happen, it will not happen in this terminal society.
You can doesn't mean you cannot apply those principles to your own life, you see.
And I'm not trying to prop up myself or even give sound like a help self guru.
Forget about that nonsense.
You know, there's a lot of that stuff going on, too, which is ridiculous the way it's
being done based on its own quality.
But what I'm saying is that, you know, for example, people in the emergency services,
one of the attributes that you must have in order to be employed there is you must be
able to maintain objectivity, calmness and coolness in the most agitated and critical
situations.
Right.
So if you're a paramedic and you go and you see someone who's, you know, front half of
their bodies in the front seat in the back half of the bodies in the back seat, you can't
get too squeamish and cry about it.
You have to be objective to that.
You see, so there's a level of how you're going to perform within your own sphere.
But the main the main gripe that anyone can hold, you know, let's say, for example, it's
not even a gripe.
Let's just say it's just so poor that it's in it.
It's so obvious and.
It's not being discussed, it makes it even worse, you see, because it's not being discussed
is that if you take the perspective as if you're on a starship and we just landed on
Earth, you know, when you see a lot of these sci fi programs and you notice before they
send the scout party down, they give them a little briefing of what the planet is like.
You see what I'm saying?
So when they go down as a scout party and they come back up to the starship to report,
they have to be objective.
Yeah.
And they have a context.
Yes, they might.
They can't say, well, Captain, you know, I went to an ice cream shop and I really like
strawberry.
You know, it doesn't work that way.
You have to give a general context again.
And what is really going on there that, you know, in few words you can explain.
Unfortunately, when you're dealing with the inhabitants of this planet, you can't
use very few words because, well, if you had, let's say, for example, if I go up to the
starship, I'm just going to say, listen, this is a planet fully full of morons.
There might be a few hundred you might want to take off.
Otherwise, aim all the plasma weapons to the surface, put these bastards out of their misery.
Right.
That would be the best recommendation.
But that's not what I'm saying should be done.
I'm just saying that would be the enthrallment that one would feel if they actually visited
here.
You see, this is how bad it's gotten.
But it's going to get worse because it's going to get better.
Duh.
What did you just say?
Okay.
To make a long story even longer, I want to work a little bit on the entitled classes.
And, you know, a lot of times like Greek, you don't give a lot of references or something.
I want to give a couple of things tonight that anyone can reference.
Okay.
And let's pick you want to pick the religious society, the legal society or the medical
society.
Which one do you guys want to go first?
Let's go with the legal.
Okay, go ahead.
Go with the legal societies.
Okay.
I gave I gave the illusion of choice.
I gave the illusion of choice.
Yeah.
You see, I'm trying to play.
I'm trying to show you what's going on here as well.
So, you know, how many times have you heard, for example, of an attorney?
Right.
Yeah.
You got all legal.
You got to get an attorney.
Right.
And all this stuff.
Do you know, like when you go down to the court system and you look at all these guys
and all that, and they call themselves administrators, you know, it's the administrative,
whatever, you know, court or, you know, they're supposed to be administrative, supposedly.
Right.
And they're called administrators.
But really, they're judicial.
There's a there's an interesting thing going on there that the most of the things that
people get involved with, like a traffic ticket or being sued, they go right to a judicial
court, don't they?
With a judge, you know, it's judicial justice, which no one gets still have, you know, has
been talking about for a decade.
No one has realized yet that justice is the statue of a woman.
It's the revived ancient goddess religion.
And this is not a stupid metaphor like other people make.
You know, this is the truth.
If you research it, you see those are all administrative things, a judicial, the only
judicial matter that I'll give you an example of a judicial matter would be like a neighbor's
dog jumps the fence, bites your leg.
And you go to the neighbor and you say, your dog bit my leg.
You know, you have to compensate me.
He says, screw you, slams the door in your face.
That's a judicial matter.
Traffic tickets, foreclosures, most lawsuits, all that stuff is all administrative.
Right.
So you're all being taken for a big ride, notice, but it's better to be taken for that
ride than a ride in the back of a cop car and put in jail.
So people say, I'll just I don't want to study that Greek.
But anyway, here, what I'm going to do is, as I'm speaking, I'm trying to walk and chew
gum, right?
I'm going to drop in the Skype text.
You could read it.
Here's a link to the laws.
There's something called laws, right?
I'm being facetious here.
Go click on that.
Either one of you.
It's 28 U.S.C. Section 607.
And you know how they say they're practicing law?
You know, these administrators, they're practicing law and you go to jail because if you don't
have a license, you can't.
There is no license to practice law.
But anyway, go ahead, click on that link and which is the law itself.
And anyone can reference this.
It's 28 U.S.C. Section 607.
It's called practice of law prohibited.
I'm going to mute out for about 30 seconds.
It's only 12 words.
You could read it and talk about it.
I'll be right back.
OK, an officer or employee of the administrative office shall not engage directly or indirectly
in the practice of law in any court of the United States.
L.I.I. has no control over and does not endorse any external.
OK, that's just anyway.
There it is.
Do you want me to read it again?
Yeah, go ahead.
An officer or employee of the administrative office shall not engage directly or indirectly
in the practice of law in any court of the United States.
So that this this again goes to what you're contrary.
Yeah.
In other words, no attorney knows this.
If you go to the attorney general's office or any court building says this is an administrative
office of the attorney or the court.
Yes, it is.
But the law says that they can't be doing what they're doing.
Just like an example.
When a cop gives you a ticket, that's not a judicial matter, even though it says there
you agree to go to the court.
That's a contract that you're going to go to the court.
Right.
That's a that's an administrative matter.
He's an administrator.
He's supposed to get administrative hearing.
And what's interesting, when you look at the laws, especially the codes that were written
under the National Safety Highway Act, which it says anyone that receives federal funding
has to go under these federal traffic laws.
Now, do you know of any cities or municipalities in the US that don't get more than twenty
five dollars of federal funding?
No, they all do.
Right.
So that so that do you know that in order to cite a citation like a fine or levy a fine
or a penalty for a motor vehicle or anything like that, that citation, a ticket has to
be signed by the director of the Department of Transportation.
Did you know that?
I did not.
Yeah, no one does.
And the police don't know it either.
And you have to have DOT certification.
How many police sheriffs, Department of Public Safety people that are DOT certified?
None.
The only ones I found out are excuse me, are the ones that operate the scales for weighing
trucks and things like that.
Yeah, right.
So yeah, so I mean, I don't want to be too pedantic, but that's an interesting one.
I'm going to give you another one.
We've discussed Title 12, Section 411 before, haven't we?
Which is you could put in Title 12, Section 401 or I could.
Remind me of what that is.
I don't I don't remember.
Federal Federal Reserve notes are you can't use them.
Only Federal Reserve agents can use them.
No, it's authorized or they just say Title 12, Section 411 says Federal Reserve notes
are only to be used by Federal Reserve banks and Federal Reserve agents.
And no other use is authorized.
Right.
But then it tells you if you have them, what to do with them.
How many people are in jail over tax issues and all that stuff, arguing the tax code?
Wrong argument.
I'm not.
Now, by the way, we weren't bringing up here.
Anybody could look up.
And you know, there's not an attorney that knows this.
How do I know that for sure?
Because if you have a good hearted attorney, let's say, which I don't think exists.
But if you have an attorney that learns these basic codes and applies them, they will be
disbarred.
And they'll end up being a used car salesman.
And that's not a joke, by the way.
I know I've heard of several attorneys that have been disbarred and they all end up being
car salesmen.
That's a phenomenon.
They don't know each other either.
It's an interesting thing.
But USC, do you want me to drop in?
I'll produce USC 12 USC 12 section.
I'm going to do a bunch of stuff tonight like this.
Um, because you look at it and you're like, how come no one knows about this stuff?
And it's in the law because you're lawless, right?
You get it.
You ever heard of an ancient writ that said the society will be lawless, whether it's
whoever's law, you're just don't know it.
So if you're lawless, let me ask you, you know, you've heard of something called a game,
you know, in order to play the game, if you walk into a game, it was a card game, football
game, baseball game, any kind of game.
And there's trouble in the game or there's something critical going on or there's mayhem
or whatever.
You know why?
It's because they're not following the rules of the game, are they?
Right.
Yeah.
And it's important that when you're in a game that you follow the rules.
So if you have attorneys that say they know the law and they don't know any of the law,
what's going on?
Yeah, there's 12 USC 411 and that one is a good attorney catcher, by the way, because
it says Federal Reserve notes.
It's Title 12 Section 12 U.S. Code 411 issuance to reserve banks.
Right.
There's an interesting catcher there in the middle.
It's you want me to read it, Keith?
I'll read it real fast.
Sure, sure.
I can, if you'd rather.
No, go ahead.
Yeah, but I'm going to ask you to stop to show you how they've set this up to be fatal
for most people.
Go ahead.
Read it.
Federal Reserve notes to be issued at the discretion of the board of governors of the
Federal Reserve system for the purpose of making advances to Federal Reserve banks through
the Federal Reserve agents and here and after set forth and for no other purpose are authorized.
Yes.
Now, do you need now?
What does for no other purpose or authorized mean?
Do I need to hire someone for 150 an hour to tell me what that means?
No.
Okay.
And what are Federal Reserve notes?
Those green things, right?
Yep.
That's our public currency.
Yeah.
Privately issued.
Can you interpret that away?
No, it doesn't require that.
I think I think the letter and the and the intent behind that is clear, isn't it?
Yeah.
Okay, continue.
Okay.
The said notes shall be obligations of the United States and other public dues.
They shall be redeemed in lawful money on demand at the Treasury Department of the United States
in the city of Washington, District of Columbia, or at any Federal Reserve bank.
Right.
But actually, you bumped up a part and says all banks and for all taxes, customs and other
public dues.
Right.
Now, we see an attorney will say he says here you could use it for taxes, customs and public
dues.
Right.
But not you.
The Federal Reserve agent can use it for taxes, customs and public dues.
You see how they it's easy to get caught up in wrapped around the axle on that.
Right.
So that's why it's very interesting.
If you, you know, basically something called competent record keeping, you know, if you
get a piece of cash, you should have serial numbers on them.
You ever notice that?
Yep.
Yeah, you're supposed to make a log of all those notes and all those serial numbers.
And now they have phones.
You could just a picture of it.
And, you know, you those part of your earnings, but it's not your income.
You know, you can have if you if you make a demand for lawful money, that's not income.
That's all earnings.
And you're never going to get anything for it, are you?
Now, the the idiot merchant doesn't know it.
So he's going to accept it for product.
He's giving you all this product for fiat currency.
Right.
That's not the point.
The point is, like, for example, you know, I had one hundred twenty thousand in earnings
last year and I redeemed it all in lawful money.
How much income did I have?
Zero.
Right.
Very simple.
So there's no reason to argue any codes or anything.
I'm going to give you another one here.
This one is a little deeper, because when I drop the you'll see it's a big link when
this one is less even less known than any attorney, even though no attorney knows the
other ones, by the way, I'm going to drop this one in.
This is a public law, which is usually a revision to a law, you know, you know.
So here, click on that.
And that that one is a little more elaborate.
When you click on it, it doesn't it opens in the middle of the page around Title 21.
And that's how I send it out there.
Right.
You got to scroll to the top.
And the reason I bring it up and opens to Title 21, if you notice, that's just food
and drugs.
Right.
Let me know when you got it.
Well, I've got I opened the page U.S.
Government Publishing Office.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yes, it is.
And if at the top and what does it say next to U.S.
Government Public Office, what does it say?
Publishing Office.
What does it say next to keeping America informed?
Thank you.
But that doesn't mean the attorneys or the courts or the police.
So why?
Because if you scroll down to Title 21, that is everything that has to do with food and
drugs, which has to do with narcotics, possession, trafficking, all that stuff.
Right.
Okay.
So what is it?
Why did I it has all the various titles, right?
Right.
Now, if you scroll to the top, it's the 18 U.S.C.
4201 repealed.
Okay.
And I'm going to explain this.
Publication 98-473, Title 2, Subsection 218A5, October 12th, 1984, 98 Stat 2027.
Right.
Okay.
Now, if you study that and you could read more on that, what that basically saying is
criminalization of all these other things below has been repealed.
So all these things that were because it says right there, if you go to contained within
Title 18 crimes and criminal procedure, you see that when you scroll down underneath U.S.
Code, you see under metadata.
Title 18 crimes and criminal procedure.
Yeah.
Part three, prisons and prisoners.
Okay.
So basically it has to do with criminal offenses.
So if you look at Title 21, which has to do with narcotics, drugs, and all that stuff
as being criminal offenses, all that's been repealed as being criminal.
It's only civil now.
Huh.
So how many people are in jail for a joint or trafficking 40 pounds of pot or 100 pounds
tons of cocaine?
How many people are in jail for all that stuff?
Narcotics, trafficking, possession, intent to sell.
How many?
That's under criminal charges.
How many people?
You say a million, 2 million, 3 million, maybe more.
Probably something like that worldwide.
It's probably.
Yeah.
Well, in the U.S. it's been decriminalized and it's only civil.
In order for it to be civil, that means that if an agent or somebody catches you with 100
pounds of kilos of cocaine, well, it's not criminal, but it's civil.
So he has to make, he has to go and sue you for having that personally.
You know, you heard like O.J. Simpson went through a criminal trial, but he lost the
civil trial, you know?
Right.
There was no jail time on the civil.
He just went after his money.
Yeah.
So who in their right mind is going to go, I mean, if somebody just says, hey, this guy's
got 100 tons of cocaine, uh, that's a civil lawsuit.
I got to sue him for having that.
Well, I don't know on what grounds, you know, you're going to sue me for that.
So what is going, how many attorneys know this?
Actually, there's some that do.
It's been decriminalized.
Now, the way, if you read, if you study this statute, it was actually this public law.
It was put together in 1984, but it was to take effect in three years, which, so in 1987
and after it was all decriminalized, right?
I'm just giving you a little filling in and you have the link there.
You could throw it in.
It's basically public law, uh, public law 98-473.
So anyway, do you see what happens when ignorant, you know, how much misery can be brought upon
a society when they're ignorant?
Well, it's incredible.
Uh, so, uh, what you're proving, proving a point here.
I'm not what I'm saying.
I'm what I'm showing you.
And when the irony, by the way, I just cut you off is the U S government publishing office,
keeping America informed.
How many Americans are informed about what I just showed you?
I wasn't.
Yeah.
Would you say a handful?
Only.
Yeah.
I, I know, uh, there's less than a hundred people.
Uh, that know about this.
Maybe I wouldn't say I'd know, but I wouldn't say there's more than a thousand people that
know this.
And by the way, they're quite successful legally with it.
If you know it, attorneys don't know this.
No way.
And if you're an attorney, you try to say, I'm representing the client for narcotics
possession.
I'm going to use this.
He's going to lose his bar license.
He's going to say, do I lose my bar license or get this guy off?
Uh, this guy goes to jail.
Yeah.
He's going to keep his license.
He's going to lie about it.
So do you see what's going on here?
And I can go on and on.
I have a roughly, let me see, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, too many
to count.
I'd say about 58 codes on a piece of paper here that I could keep dropping links in that
are all like, just contrary to what you think.
So the reason why people are going into jail for smoking a joint or transferring 200 tons
of cocaine or whatever is because when you go with a man on the street and you say, Hey,
this guy got caught with, you know, a truck full of pot.
Oh, he should go to jail.
He should go to jail.
Yeah.
Not because it's in the law and all, everyone is like, all the, you know, the judges, prosecutors
are like, Oh yeah, yeah.
We'll put him in jail.
No, he doesn't know.
Nobody else knows.
No, but you know, fine.
Let's do it.
Even his own family says, well, he did the crime.
He should do the time.
Right.
How many times you heard that from your typical human moron, right?
Too many.
Yeah.
So I'm giving the proofs here and this is not, I mean, whether you want to see it or
believe it or know it is irrelevant to me.
I'm just saying, Hey, you know, just go look at it.
You know, pretty simple.
And basically it applies to decriminalization of all these titles down below.
You could look at title one, general positions, the Congress, the president, domestic security,
aliens and nationality, illegal alien and illegal is basically a sick bird, isn't it?
Illegal and illegal.
Yeah.
So, I mean, this is kind of funny.
This is a, you know, how I was talking about cosmic censorship.
Do you ever hear, you know, what pranking is pranking?
You know, when you pull a prank, certainly you're all being pranked.
And you know, when the pranking started, when you were in the crib, your parents pranked
you to favor here, tooth fairy, Santa Claus.
You ever hear that stuff?
You ever hear of a go to college.
So you get a good job.
Yeah.
Your pranks.
Okay.
Pay your taxes.
You go to jail.
Well, if they're your taxes, you better pay them.
So, I mean, the level of pranking here.
Okay.
We're on the mothership, on the starship.
And before we go down to this planet, guys, all right, Keith and Tom, I want to let you
know that the biggest industry on this planet, okay, is Kevlar underwear.
Why Greek?
Say why Greek?
Because they have a tradition of before they sit down, they put a thumbtack on the chair.
That's part of their culture and tradition.
So they, so Kevlar underwear is the largest industry because it doesn't hurt so much when
you have Kevlar under, anyway, do you get the metaphor?
Because we're being pranked.
Yeah.
So what they do instead of, instead of stop putting the, instead of stop putting the thumbtacks
on the chair.
They put on Kevlar underwear.
So they could keep pranking.
Right.
Do you, I mean, I'm not going to, I'm just going to stop with these codes because I think
they're heavy hitters.
One shows that, you know, there's these people that say they're only ones who could practice
law.
The law says they can't.
I want to show you what everybody has in their pocket.
They're not supposed to be using it.
And I want to show you what you think is illegal or criminal actually isn't by law.
Right.
I think those are three, three good, let's say general representative samples.
I could keep going.
We could spend the next eight hours, not hour and a half.
I'm just showing you how no laws that no attorney knows.
And it would be, it should be in Ripley's believe it or not.
Shouldn't it?
Right.
I did have one question on the civil, on the civil court laws.
Do these transfer over or are they applicable to the federal system or is it just different?
No.
Well, I'll give you another code.
You put it in, look up 28 USC, which is 28 U.S.
Code 1738 530 B.
Right.
Or, and then look at the, or look at 77.1 CFR, which is another section codes of federal
regulations.
And it says that all federal courts and U.S.
attorneys have to use state law.
Because we're going to, you're not going to pull someone out of a federal district.
You're going to pull them out of one of the 50 states usually.
But, but, but the thing is, these things are not criminal in order for them to be civil.
It's just suing someone because they didn't make right on a contract.
You see?
Yeah.
I mean, you know, I'm just threatening to sue you for libel or whatever.
There's no, I mean, it's civil, not criminal.
There is no, anyway, there's, there's a higher power at work here.
It's a preemptive neuralyzer.
Instead of neuralyzing them after the fact, I think they're neuralyzed before the fact.
You see, this is the cosmic censorship that I'm talking about.
And by the way, I've been around, let's say, let's say, give you a hypothetical example.
I have about 50 or 70 codes that should be in Ripley's, believe it or not.
And I've done this with attorneys and they're all amazed.
And the minute I stopped talking to them, they forgot everything I said.
Like they can't, they couldn't say, well, I don't know.
You said something about something about being criminal.
I don't know.
It's like, holy crap.
What the hell is wrong with you people?
You know, this is planet earth.
Like, for example, have you ever been in a parking lot somewhere and heard someone say,
hey, look, you know, it's supposed to be a clear sky tonight.
You know, look at all the tic-tac-toe clouds.
Look at all that.
You ever notice that those planes are spraying something?
Oh no, those are clouds, man.
No, but you notice that's plain, that's just regular contrail.
Yeah, but it, you know, when you have steam coming out of your teapot in the morning,
it doesn't like fog up the whole kitchen white and last till three in the afternoon, does it?
Okay.
So you see those planes are kind of playing tic-tac-toe.
Oops, where's that plane going?
It's going to Mexico, man.
Oh, but he's making a U-turn and coming back.
He's going to Mexico.
Oh, that's just planes, man.
I don't, I don't, I don't see what you're trying to say, man.
Right.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, it's right up above their heads and they don't see it.
So now you're going to show them laws and they're going to get it?
No way.
You ain't got a chance.
You keep going.
I mean, what would be interesting here is to make a treatise or a paper with all these
different codes and just put them out and see what people think.
Right.
I think it'll keep a lot of people from suffering miseries that are unnecessary.
So you see, this was probably the more pedantic stuff.
But, you know, I think most crowds these days tend to consider themselves savvy when they
can get into things legal or lawful.
Years ago, it wasn't fashionable.
I think it's more fashionable now to have some comprehension of these things.
You know, that's why I brought them up.
I think these three were just a general representative sample of what's going on.
And by the way, there aren't any attorneys that know any of these, by the way, codes,
because if they did, they wouldn't be attorneys.
They would be selling cars.
So just we can get into the medical system.
You want to do medical, religious?
Let's do a little medical.
Medical, I'm not going to get pedantic because it's not like a code that we can read like
that.
But you know what the biggest farce, one of the biggest pranks in society is?
Is medical school.
Why?
Now, Greek, should we not go to school?
I mean, I have civil engineering degree.
I learned a lot.
I agree.
Yeah, but not everybody has a bridge to build, do they?
Right.
Or, you know, Greek, what are you talking about?
I went to aviation school.
I learned a lot about avionics systems and structures and all that.
Yeah, but not everybody is going to be building airplanes.
But guess what?
Why is medical school a farce or a prank?
Because everybody does have a body, don't they?
Until they're not one of the bodies anymore.
You ever notice that?
You ever notice that anyone you've ever talked to has a body that's usually alive?
Unless you're into a necro or whatever.
You ever notice that, guys?
That everyone you ever interact with has a body?
Of course.
Well, no, actually, actually, that's not true.
I do interact with beings that don't have a physical body.
But that's another story.
Anyway, go ahead.
It is, but we'll go on to that when we get into the religious texts and how far off they
are from, you know, how little knowledge they have of things.
Yeah, from actual reality.
Okay.
Yeah, the reality of it.
But, you know, why it's a farce is, don't you think that if everybody has something,
they should know a little bit more than what they see on TV about it?
You get it?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, even people that drive a car as a ritual, you know what I mean, as a ritual,
they don't know.
They just open the door, put the key, turn the wheel, push a pedal, and they know they
get to the store.
It's a ritual.
They know if they perform this ritual, every time they get into this machine, they know
they'll get somewhere with it, right?
It's a ritual.
They don't know much.
But even then, they know if it stops moving or it's really bumpy, it means you have a
flat tire usually, and that has to be changed, and they usually are aware of something about
that, right?
Yeah, and putting gas in it and having the right papers in case you're stopped.
And that's about the level that people know about their body.
But you can do without a car, but you can't do without your body being in good shape.
So you have these technicians.
I call them medical technicians.
And by the way, one of the things I want to mention is I have a map.
It's easier now with the computers and the internet, because you could map out any city
where there's a medical office, a doctor's office, or a hospital, and they put the little
dots on the map, you know, on the stupid rectangle.
And I have that mapped out on a GPS when I travel around.
And I have those earplugs, the little sponge ones that you compact and put them in your
ear, or tissue paper.
And I know when I'm getting around town or even traveling, at least a block or two before
I pass a medical office or a hospital, I have to pull over and plug the ears.
And the reason why I do that is because if I don't plug the ears, if I drive by without
plugging the ears, the quacking is so loud my ears are ringing for about two days afterwards.
Anyway, that's an old school joke.
No, I know, because quackery is being performed there.
Yeah, and it's so loud.
It's deafening.
It makes my ears ring for two days or three days after.
I don't want, I don't like that.
So anyway, it's a joke.
Just, you know, I have sometimes discussions with people and they say, I went to Dr. Greek
and I'm not sure about what he says.
And maybe, you know, I say, well, okay, hold on, hold on.
I don't, when, when you went in there and you, you got diagnosed because, you know,
they're an industry and they have two products.
One of the products is diagnosis and the other product is treatment.
Those are the two products they sell.
Right.
We can get into banking.
We didn't get into banks, don't deal anything with money.
Those are products, financial products they offer.
Right.
All the time because there is no money.
I think we just showed that.
So anyway, I said, listen, before you told me, give me his opinion, right?
I want to know when, when you sat down and he did his diagnosis thing, did he strap anything
on your arm and tell you anything about pressure?
He says, oh yeah, he took my blood pressure.
I said, I don't want to know anything.
He says after that, that's total quackery.
You think anything good is going to come from that?
I mean, unless it's the obvious, you know, unless you have like a big laceration, you're
bleeding and it's funny.
You tell, you know, a nurse or a hospital person, you're bringing in someone who has a broken
leg and the minute you present, they're like, oh, he has a broken leg.
Well, I told you that.
You're like, wow.
Okay.
You know, I mean, this is like idiocracy, right?
Yeah.
So, you know, I wanted you to show me where the blood pressure is in the body.
You can't, what you have to do is get a sphigometer, which is a cuff and, and apply
pressure on one of the limbs, stop the flow of blood that it moves normally, restrict
it, right?
So you can check the, you know, stalic and precostalic and stupid stalic stuff going on
in between, right?
And anyone that's ever played around with a garden hose knows that even the smallest,
finest thing that's under pressure will create, you know, a spurting of fluids, right?
Yeah.
And I want to know, um, when you put your feet and hands in water, do they puff up like
a frog or do they shrivel up?
Right.
When your skin membrane softens, doesn't it shrivel up?
Yeah, it shrivels up.
Right.
Yeah.
And I'm not talking about a guy coming out of the shower or anything.
I'm talking about the fingers and the toes, right?
I like to be lascivious sometimes.
So what I mean here is if you take a slab of meat with some bone on it, throw it in
a Ziploc bag or use the brand name again, plastic bag, pull a vacuum on it.
Does that bag expand or does it shrivel up around that slab of meat with the bone in
it?
Well, of course it shrivels up, yes.
Yeah.
So maybe we have a slight vacuum in the body.
That's why when you stand up and you have a solid skeleton made of minerals and fibers
and all this other liquid and plumbing going on, does all the liquid suddenly crash to
your feet and swell up?
Or is it all held together neatly in a package because you're under a slight vacuum condition?
Right?
Yeah.
No, that analogy actually made sense to me.
I've heard you talk about this before and I never quite got it until you use that specific
analogy.
Yeah.
Here, I'm going to do something for you right now.
I'm going to go to the stupid rectangle.
This is very rare.
Usually when I speak publicly, I'm out in the garden and now I'm in the office.
I'm in front of several monitors and it's quite interesting.
I used to be accused of, oh, this guy, this Greek, he's just reading.
He's really fast on Google.
He doesn't know any of this.
He just does quick searches.
I was like, okay, that's fine.
That's the perception I get.
That's all right.
I'm not trying to say that I'm smarter because the aspect is, are you objective enough?
But people say, Greek, you're so smart.
And you know what I say?
I'm just less stupid than you.
Big difference.
Speaking of which, there's the break.
We'll be right back.
We've got another hour to go.
We'll be back in about five minutes.