Most guys freeze, that's your cerebral cortex looking for an answer it doesn't have.
See, even your brain knows you're screwed.
Your blood is filled with adrenaline right now, whether you know it or not.
Your heart's beating fast.
It's giving a little harder to breathe.
The neurobiological system is telling you to run, but you need to sit awake to move.
Fear is not real.
The only place that fear can exist is in our thoughts of the future.
It is a product of our imagination, causing us to fear things that do not at present and may not ever exist.
That is mere insanity.
Do not misunderstand me.
Danger is very real, but fear is a choice.
We are all telling ourselves a story.
You're listening to Revolution Radio at freedomslips.com.
100% listener-supported radio.
Reporting the danger, unafraid, right here, where information never sleeps.
Revolution Radio.
The opinions expressed on this radio station, its programs, and its website by the hosts, guests, and call-in listeners or chatters are solely the opinions of the original source who expressed them.
They do not necessarily represent the opinions of Revolution Radio and freedomslips.com, its staff, or affiliates.
You're listening to Revolution Radio, freedomslips.com.
100% listener-supported radio.
And now we return you to your host.
Good evening, good evening.
This is Revolution Radio at freedomslips.com.
The number one listener-supported talk radio network in the known universe.
And thank you all for your support.
Mike Ringley, our station owner, has made it very easy to support the network.
So please go to the support tab on freedomslips.com.
It's right on the front page.
And there's any number of ways you can support the station.
Anything from $1 donation all the way up to all kinds of wonderful gifts.
For instance, $100 for a seed pack with 35,000 different seeds of 53 varieties.
So anyway, tonight you're listening to Keith A. Zee Live.
I want to do a couple of quick station notes.
I'm going to be filling in for Barbara DeLong tomorrow night.
And I will be filling in for Monique Lasson on Wednesday evening.
And then, of course, Thursday evening I'll have Ground Control.
So tonight I have changed the format.
This used to be an open roundtable.
And I've changed it to Keith A. Zee Live because I just wanted to do a little bit more focused work.
And tonight we have a guest who many of you will be familiar with.
A very, very interesting fellow.
And without no further ado, welcome to the show, The Greek.
Greetings, Keith.
Thanks.
Are we sure we want to call this a show?
I usually call them sonic events.
I looked up what the word show means, and it doesn't seem to ring in many's favor, let's just say.
Etymologically, do you want me to just tell you what it means?
Sure.
It's performance and deception.
And deception?
Yes, yes.
But nonetheless, we're here.
Thanks for inviting me.
And we kicked around some topics because, you know, here's the thing.
If anyone's ever listened to me speak, I have the perspective of just visiting, taking notes.
In other words, I'm trying to be objective.
And when one tries to be objective, you will be shocked to see that the most secreted, occulted truths about anything are within arm's reach and right in front of you.
It's just no one sees them.
So nonetheless, bringing up some topics that you might have brought up, you said we could pretty much discuss anything.
Do you want to kind of lead things around, or what do you think?
Well, I always defer to my guests.
So, you know, I feel you know your subject material better than I do.
So I'm very happy with anywhere you'd like to go.
Oh, well, the subject material basically I've been gauging in since about nine is observing surface-dwelling earth inhabitants because they're very peculiar.
Meaning, I'm going to just go into why people are so peculiar, in a sense.
Certainly.
Because they rarely do what they say and say what they do.
They rarely know the definitions of things, and they rarely know why they do things.
And they have this very interesting order of, because everyone else is doing it, it's fine.
To give you an example, you know, I was looking for some natural bug spray, you know, instead of spraying like DDT derivatives on people.
So I went into what they call a health food store, and the lady, you know, I inquired about natural bug spray.
And the lady behind the counter said, well, I can't really recommend one, but this is the one that everyone buys.
And I said, well, that's the one that I don't want.
Right.
Now, think about that for a moment, because all you hear on the propaganda, advertising, all that, this is the best-selling one, right?
So that means, oh, it's the best-selling one.
I should get it, too.
Or this is the best TV station, or this is the best radio station, right?
Or this is the, oh, that's the one you want to scrutinize, right?
Because, why?
It's planet Earth.
Now, if we're on Alpha Centauri or somewhere else, things might be a little bit more altruistic and be actually true, you see?
So the subject matter is, let me give you another example.
Subject matter is open, but it's not.
You know, I was, I've done various sonic events, and if you want to contact me, it's uncommonradio.com, by the way.
And someone once called in and said, well, so what should we do?
So I said, great.
I'm glad you asked that question.
You know, we as a large altruistic question, you know, like what's the meaning of life kind of thing, right?
I said, great.
I'm glad you asked that question.
It's really simple.
You've got to pursue the best quality of food, clothing, and shelter that you can afford or want to afford.
And also, you have to learn on what the spirit, the soul, and the body is, meaning your mind, your breath, your metabolism, and your body.
And if you pursue that all your life, you'll be fine.
And I said, well, that's kind of shallow, don't you think?
I said, well, listen, if you pursue the best quality of all those things and learning about those other three things that make you up,
you will learn what there is or what can be learned about everything else in between.
Right?
So that's the subject matter.
Yeah, you give yourself, if you have the quality of life, you give yourself the opportunity to pursue those other interests.
Well, the thing is, they're not interests as they stand.
People don't even acknowledge that there's anything to be pursued in those fields other than meeting the basic requirements.
Like what I mean by that is like, oh, my stomach's growling, man.
Keith, what should I do?
Well, you might say, well, when was the last time you ate something?
Oh, I haven't eaten since yesterday.
And you're like, well, Greek, maybe you should eat something.
Oh, man, you know, Keith, you're smart.
You're so smart.
That's a good idea.
Do you see the level of what's going on?
Here, let's just fast forward, because I've threatened to do a private project and all that, and I've held off since I stopped speaking publicly.
Because, I mean, hey, look, you want to gauge a situation.
You know, like when you have toast, you look in, is it brown yet?
You know, if you're looking at things, are they ready yet?
You know, is it ready to go to the next level?
Right?
You know, it's not quite done yet.
Yeah, so, but it's also not ready to go to the next level.
But the interesting thing, Keith, is one of the things that I wanted to do is get together, maybe we can go over it a little bit,
is get together like a manual, let's say, so to speak, but a loose manual, not necessarily to be followed,
because whenever you discuss anything being followed, have you ever heard of someone called Gustav Le Bon?
L-E-B-O-N.
No, I don't think so.
Well, he wrote two books, very interesting, around the late 1800s.
One of them was on the FBI seizure list, which right away is like, you've got to get that one, right?
And that was about metamorphosis of materials, and he just proved that radioactivity is not in the material, and vice versa.
I mean, it basically tells you how to take aluminum and make it radioactive in your kitchen.
And that's definitely not what you want people to understand, because that's another whole thing.
When we say the word radioactivity or virus, people run the scare.
They don't understand what that means, right?
And the other book that he wrote was called The Crowd, and he tried to objectify why crowds form.
I'm not endorsing him, but I'm just giving it as a guide that someone can look into.
Basically, what he came up with with all this research and a few hundred pages was the crowd mentality, right?
When you have a crowd, a multitude of people, you have what's called also a mentality that follows that crowd.
Now, that mentality is, let's say, birthed or started by a leader.
Now, it doesn't matter what field it is. It could be scientific, religious, cultural, social, right?
What that leader portrays or puts forth to the people is a concept, but in order for the people to comprehend it,
it has to be so simplified, and sometimes oversimplified, that the cause no longer represents its original meaning.
And when you get it to that point, then you have a crowd following, right?
So, you see what I mean by the, you know, that doesn't sound good, does it?
But, you know, you have crowds.
So, the Gustave Le Bon thing.
So, what I wanted to do, again, going back to the manual, kind of like the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy thing,
but for the Earth, because we do have manuals in ancient writs, you know?
Basically, you've heard of, like, writings of wisdom in ancient writings and things like that.
And people leave those things, supposedly gaining a little more knowledge of the ages and what mankind is about
from just the perspective of a 70- or 80-year lifespan, let's say, right?
Well, certainly the Bible would be one, wouldn't it?
Yeah, the problem with any biblical discussion, though, is that you don't really have it.
You have versions.
Sure.
Yeah, it was what people, if you want to go into that little bit tangent, and I want to go back to it also.
Let me just say, and I'll challenge anyone on this, and I have been for over a decade and a half.
You know, there's not one religion on the planet, I'll say it slowly.
There is not one religion on the planet, bar none, that knows or does anything that's in the text that they allege to subscribe to.
Not one.
Now, to the laity or the layman or the passerby, it appears that way, that they do.
But appearances can be deceitful, right?
Now, if you forward into modern history, the first millennium, if you were caught with anything of the ancient writ,
which was preserved in Hebrew or Greek or known as the scriptures,
the Catholic Church, which is a Greek term for universal, which was a power base,
it was a break-off of the finished Greek empire, let's say,
if they found the public laity dealing with laity or anyone dealing with that,
you were probably dealt very harshly initially and then subsequently put to death.
So there was a little bit of outrage on that.
So they said, well, let's just get these guys to sum up something in English real quick,
make it a public work and put it out there with this regent.
He wasn't even a king, King James.
They called him a king, though, because anyone that goes to work in that palace every day must be the king, right?
So he was really a regent.
And he figured he might as well put this out, make it popular to drive a wedge between the monarchy and the people
because the people had already deified the king.
So at least if they had access to this loosely translated, mostly hypothecated version of the scriptures,
the people then would at least focus on some other deific subject, you see.
But you don't have the Bible.
I mean, what you have is in any translation, and no one is discussing this.
By the way, this is part of the manual.
Whenever you hear people bring up biblical stuff, the cliches,
they're all out of context and untrue, and the way they're using them is out of context.
Well, I mean, is trying to rebuild a car engine with kitchen utensils out of context?
I would say so.
Well, you could pry the dust cap off with a butter knife.
You get done to a certain point.
That's why there's no clear cut.
But again, here's the other thing.
If you were, let's say, Christian and you studied the Bible,
you would see that everything Christians do is in the abominations category, like the don't-dos,
and what they tell you it's about you won't find in there, and there is no way you will call yourself a Christian.
You mean like the Ten Commandments?
Oh, that's an interesting point. You want to get into that for a minute?
Yeah, I'd love to.
I still haven't met anyone that knows any of the Ten Commandments written on stone.
Listen to it carefully.
I still have not met anyone that knows any of the Ten Commandments that are written on stone.
What the people recite were never written on stone.
Those were oral commands that were given when they were gathered at Mount Sinai after they left Egypt.
Go read it.
It's funny, right?
And when you read the ones that were written on stone, because remember, he went up to get the ones on stone.
Yeah, right, Moses.
You know what the first commandment is, the ones that were written on stone?
You could look it up, Exodus 34. It's pretty easy. Anyone can do it.
I actually had a biblical...
They're all idiots, by the way, the ones that are studied in this.
They have to be, otherwise they won't give them a degree.
But I had this one biblical scholar studying several degrees in it and all that.
And I showed that to him, and it's right there in black and white, black ink on white paper.
And he says, oh, those can't be...
And it says this is what was written on the stone, right?
And he says, oh, that can't be it because it doesn't sound like the other ones.
That's right.
But the first commandment is do not go into covenant with the pagan or the heathen.
In other words, do not go into contract with the heathen or the pagan.
Yeah, yeah.
There's no do not steal, do not murder, do not cover your neighbor's wife.
Those were commands that were given, let's say, when they came out of Egypt,
they gathered at Mount Sinai, and they were all told to go up the mountain.
And they were like, no way, no way, Moses.
Hell no, you go, we stay here.
And Moses says, okay, no shoes, no shirt, no service, right?
He knows what he said, anyone touches the mountain dies.
And if you hold on...
Now, this has nothing to do with whether you believe it or not.
This has to do with what you've got to reference, right?
So anyway, like the same thing, if you're a Muslim and you study the Koran,
there's no way you'll call yourself Muslim.
I mean, there's no way, unless you're evil or ignorant.
I mean, the same with the Buddhists, the same with the Jews.
Any religion.
Yeah, I think you said that on a show you were on with me a year or so ago.
The best way to cure somebody of their religion is to actually read the text.
Right, the same with doctors, the same with attorneys.
Like, you know, the attorneys, none of them know any law, and this is a fact.
They have the appearance of knowing law, like they'll shout out a code.
Just like, go back to the biblical stuff,
you hear people that are so devout Christians,
and they yell out a verse like Matthew 25, 26, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I'm like, wait, slow down.
It sounded like two old beef patties, special sauce, cheese, and a sesame seed bun.
What are you talking about? Right?
Like, attorneys don't know any law at all.
They have the appearance of it, and this is a proof of it.
It sounds dogmatic, but it's true.
If you're an attorney and you study law, as it should be,
and you show up in court, try to practice it, you will be disbarred.
And I've actually run into a few that have, and that's not the phenomenal part.
You know what the phenomenal part is?
Is that the three of them that I know of, they live in different parts of the country,
but they all ended up as car salesmen, independent of each other.
I said, what an interesting phenomenon.
But anyway, that's the thing.
And the same with doctors.
Here's the interesting part.
You're probably going to get another virus scare coming here in the near future.
And I remember once there was a radio thing, and I was going to call,
and they said, no, no, no, you can't talk about it because you're not a doctor, right?
But here's the thing.
When you say doctor, that is a social rank.
Because you could be a doctor of medicine, a doctor of engineering, a doctor of philosophy, right?
It's a Ph.D., right?
Of many subjects.
You get a doctorate in a particular quacademic discipline.
That's a misnomer.
They show he's a doctor.
Everyone presumes medical doctor.
They're not really that.
They really should be called medical technicians.
Think about it.
Now, they don't know how the human body works, but they're working on it.
They don't know.
I'll give you an example.
Like, I'm known to have health discussions.
And sometimes someone will call up and say, I went to the doctor, right?
And he said, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I said, well, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Before you tell me what this guy told you, when he first diagnosed you,
did he strap anything on your arm?
He says, yeah, I took my blood pressure.
He says, I don't want to know anything he has to say.
That's total quackery.
Like, if you ever hear of something called blood pressure,
that only exists when they put a cuff on your arm to block the flow of blood.
That's the same thing as having a colored chart from pink to purple on a wall,
and they tie a string around your finger for two minutes.
And there has to be a medical clock, because a regular clock doesn't really,
it's not good enough, right?
And then when your finger turns a certain color, they hold it up to the chart
and it says, oh, you've got stupiditis level A over here.
See? Anyway.
Right, right.
Yeah, and the thing is also, you're going to have,
and part of the manual is I go over these facts.
They sound dogmatic to people, and this is like how to discern traveling.
I'll give you an example.
A few years ago, people used to, I don't know,
they used to check with the State Department before they went to a company.
I always say that company, country,
to see if there were any warnings from the State Department.
They do that, travel warnings and such, and they tell you why.
Yeah, you might not want to go here because of terrorism or something.
Yeah, yeah.
People used to, not anymore.
I mean, they still kind of do it, but whatever.
So it's kind of like that.
Before you travel somewhere, and of course, but here's the thing.
This is not for the everyday person because, you see, people, humans,
surface-dwelling earth inhabitants,
are very heavily invested in emotional responses.
Not their emotions, but their response from emotions.
Like, for example, if you, let's say you're out in the public,
and they're playing tic-tac-toe with jet airplanes in the sky, right?
I mean, literally, tic-tac-toe.
Yeah, no, I know, I know.
I've seen them write letters, too, a lot, or big Xs and things like that.
Yeah, so if you point that out to, you know,
you could always pick the common lady when you're out in a parking lot.
You could see their eyes look like plastic.
They have no internal, like they're dim, you know.
And you say, hey, look at that sky over there.
You know, you're about as old enough to remember that, you know,
growing up, the skies didn't look like that.
Oh, that's just a jet airplane.
I don't know what that is.
Well, do you know it's possible they're spraying that deliberately?
No, I don't think so.
But you'll notice when you start to give them the newer suggestion,
if you look at them very closely, it usually lasts for a few milliseconds.
You can catch anything more than five milliseconds, right?
Sure.
Most people can.
They have this twitch.
It usually happens around the eyebrow, side of the face,
sometimes near the lip and the chin.
And that means that that person is heavily censored cosmically.
Like, no, don't even bother, at least right now.
You could put a gun to their head, they're still going to deny it, right?
Sure.
And it's not because they're emotional.
It's because they're attached to this little emotional impulse that they get.
Just like when, you know, a couple discusses something in private,
and then when they're in public, the other person does it,
and they kind of give them a quick poke to remind them, you know.
Sure.
You have this in turn.
Most people have it internally.
So what I'm trying to say here is this manual doesn't apply to that.
It applies to people who, you know, I call it the stupid rectangle, right,
the computer and the devices.
You know, and I once brought this up to someone.
I said, what do you mean by that?
He had an iPad or something.
I said, put that thing down and walk away and look at it from a distance.
He's like, oh, shit, I see what you're saying.
Okay, so.
So if you do like media, any media, alternative mainstream,
whether it's visual or radio or study or even in school.
Yeah, or print.
Or print.
This is like a list you could look up to see that you're being pranked.
It's propaganda.
It's misinformation, right, and I have an entire list.
It could grow into the thousand items,
but maybe we'll go over a few of them tonight and anyone could look this up.
But the thing is when you hear this, if you get that little bit of an emotional twitch,
don't even bother looking it up.
It's maybe a couple of years from now you might want to revisit it.
But that's like a little guide because it helps a lot of people.
This way you live a life with efficiency.
I'll give you a quick one.
Whenever you hear like a biblical reference,
someone trying to use something out of the Bible,
if they don't preface by saying, well, this is a biblical reference,
but yet we do not have a translation yet.
If they don't preface that way, forget it.
It's going to be erroneous.
And I can give a couple of examples.
The Christians like to do that.
Now, I'm not against Christians.
I'm not against Muslims or anything.
I'm just against stupidity and evil and ignorance and all that stuff
because we're better than that, right?
Now, people are so emotionally attached to these things.
The funny thing is they say, well, I'm a real Christian.
I'm like, wait a second.
Oh, boy.
They don't understand anything, but they're best left alone.
Here's the other thing.
I was going to get into the biblical.
The other thing is you hear a lot of Gutton's messages,
not so much recently, about Satanism.
Now, people like to make stuff up.
When you hear someone saying Satanist or whatever,
that is a very loose term.
Now, if you want to get specific about usually what that discussion leads to,
it leads to a specific group of people in the category of priests, wizards, warlocks
that know how to evoke and invoke ancient balls or ancient deities
from ancient Egypt, Babylon, and other places to do bad things.
Alistair Crowley would be an example, wouldn't he?
Yeah, sure.
The Kino guy and there's a whole bunch of people in Mexico that do it for drug dealers.
They evoke a female entity.
She's a goddess of death.
They do it in Asia.
The Yakuza have one.
They all have it.
But that is not Satan.
Satan, if you look at all the ancient texts,
is a grand character that the entire man's civilization has been given over to.
So all of the mainstream religions are Satanic.
All of the mainstream institutions, governments, bodies of knowledge,
the mainstream is Satanic.
So that's another thing to watch out for.
Whenever you hear someone saying Satanic, it's not accurate.
But fortunately, the conversation doesn't end there.
They get more in depth of what they're specifically.
But you're going back and forth, like, well, why are they using that term?
They're reviving an ancient lord.
So in essence, Islam, Judaism, Buddhism, Christianity, that's all.
Satan controls all of that.
So what they call Satanism are like the rogue coyotes,
like the intelligence agencies.
You have the head of the CIA, then you have the rogue little offices
that do whatever they want.
It's kind of like that.
But you're not going to make friends discussing it.
So that's on the list, too.
All the various religious points have some biblical cliches, for example, in there, too.
Have you ever heard of the JES character that they put in front of everyone?
They set that up very carefully.
So if you use the letter J, you don't know what you're talking about.
The next thing would be Christopher Columbus used GPS, right,
and he had a speedboat.
It's so inaccurate.
But the point is all the iconography that's put in front of you
by the circus, which is church, and all that is false.
It was all invented 400 or 500 A.D.
and the actual concept of Christianity started with Simon Magus, who was a magician.
He was like a David Copperfield with the budget of Bill Gates or so,
or Vladimir Putin.
Very influential, and he had very many groups.
And what era? He was 400 A.D.?
No, no, that was first century A.D.,
but by 400 A.D. it became a government project with Constantine.
I see.
Yeah, and then by 800 it started forming into the modern church that you see,
which is the circus.
Now, before that, the circus or the church didn't use the architecture
that you're familiar with today.
The architecture that you're familiar with today, let me just say it this way,
if you got someone from a time machine from 2,000 years ago
into a modern western neighborhood and you're walking down the street,
he would stop and say,
Oh, wow, man, I didn't know you had a sex temple in your neighborhood,
and guess what building he would be pointing at?
A church.
Right.
So that has nothing to do with the, you know.
So all of these things, and also you have this guy with long hair
nailed to a Roman cross wearing a diaper, right?
That's not in there either.
You know, they put the shroud of Turin in front of you.
You don't need scientific.
You could just look at that for three seconds and tell it's a fake.
How do you do that?
Well, he had long hair.
That was unlawful.
The long hair.
That's your first catch.
You know, here's interesting, even people, and people,
no matter how educated they are,
and by the way, just bounce around a little bit,
if you didn't get your college degree by 1908,
you really don't have one.
You might as well have just gotten in the Cracker Jack box.
1908, so think about it.
It's a joke.
It's a prank, guys.
What changed then?
A new prank?
Yeah, that was pre-World War I.
That was when they were getting ready.
They had just finished the Central Bank experiment.
You know, the Federal Reserve was 1913.
Right.
But they had just finished a 20-year experiment in Canada
by putting that system in people.
You know, that real quiet country to the north?
They had just finished experimenting on those idiots for 20 years,
and they said, okay, we're ready for the Americans now.
Okay.
Yeah, but to give you an example,
even if you don't know the Bible,
this is, I'll show you the level of fraud.
It's also easier to fool a billion people than one, right?
Because if you fool one person, the other, you know,
999 million will say, hey, what are you doing?
But if you fool a billion and one person sees it,
well, he doesn't have a chance.
But here's, even if you don't know the biblical text
and just watch the stupid movies they make about it,
what they tell you in church,
that when the Christ was arrested,
notice I didn't say G-E-S-U-S, right?
He was brought to the various orders.
He was arrested by the Judean religious authorities,
brought to the Judean king who was under occupation,
who then submitted him to Pontius Pilate,
who was the governor-prefect of Judea at the time.
And the scene that happens there is Pontius Pilate
produces a small lather, and he washes his hands publicly.
And he says, I have no interest in hurting this man,
or this man is innocent of what you accused, you know,
bringing him to me for.
And that signal, by the way, that he washes his hands
means that he knows the Mosaic law.
Because in Mosaic law, according to the ceremony of the red heifer,
you know, the elders had to wash their hands
to show they had nothing to do with the murder
that had taken place, right?
I see.
And also, what you have to realize, even today,
if you're going to be an ambassador or a governor
on an occupied country, you get a little bit of training.
Like these army officers, before they send them to Afghanistan or Iraq,
they get some training about the culture there
before they're sent over.
But Pontius Pilate happened to have a knack,
and he was trained in Judean studies from a young man.
And of course they hide a lot of the stuff about Pontius Pilate
because they just have to keep him as a figure for whatever.
But what's interesting, if you read in the book of Matthew and Luke,
this has nothing to do with whether you believe in it or not.
This is, are we accessing information that's been memorialized?
And the answer is no, no one is.
And why? Because it's right in front of you.
Anyone can.
Even if you stayed at a cheap hotel, you could open the nightstand
and there's one right there you could check into, right?
You know what I'm talking about? The Gideon Bible, right?
Yeah. Yeah, it's everywhere. That's why no one knows it.
But, you know, Pontius Pilate said,
I'm returning him back to use your law.
And in another book he says, I know you have a law.
I'm making an exception.
Now let me ask you, what law do the Judeans use?
Roman civil law or do they use the law of Moses?
I don't know.
Well, they're Judeans, they're not Romans.
Okay.
So they use Judean law, which is Old Testament, let's say,
what's called, there's no Old Testament anyway, that's what it's referred to.
Well, what is the capital punishment in Old Testament Mosaic law?
Stoning.
I see.
Not crucifixion.
No, here's the thing, and it's quite obvious,
but if you've gotten to that far down,
because there is no Old or New Testament, it's one continuous book.
And you know how they tell you there's 66 books?
There's 49 books.
Like they split, divided some books so they could get 66.
That's why you have like 1 and 2 Peter, 1 and 2 Chronicles,
1 and 2 Kings, you ever notice that?
You have 1 and 2 books.
So they divided that around the time of King James and a syllable before
so they could end up with that number that they like, 66, right?
But there are really 49 books.
But anyway, in the Old Testament, this is a high crime.
You'd be nailed to a tree.
So we know it's an almond tree that he was nailed to,
because we're not that stupid.
There's over 30 hints to the almond tree about something happening, important.
And we know that the people passed from the third to the ninth hour.
For six hours they passed by.
And there's three men nailed to one tree.
He was front and center. He died first.
The men on the back had to have their femoral arteries cut,
because breaking their legs, you could survive for weeks with a broken leg, right?
Right.
And also it says that anything that hangs on a tree is accursed and to be burned.
So that's why they had to rush and take his body and put it in a grave,
and not only did they roll a big stone over it,
don't you remember in the cartoons they show the Roman guard guarding the body at the tomb, right?
So why?
The Romans had to guard it because the Judeans wanted to take it.
And do what with it?
Burn it, I guess.
Yeah, but it doesn't say that clearly in the New Testament, because, duh, you know.
It's like, if you're taking calculus, if you're further down in your math studies,
you're calculus, and you can't figure it out,
and you tell people you don't know how to do basic multiplication,
well, you're in the wrong.
See, that's why in the Christian tradition they tell you the law is done away with.
It doesn't say it anywhere in Scripture.
They just say don't look there.
The same, like, if you study radioactive materials, the same thing.
Like, don't go near it.
Well, why not?
Oh, it's dangerous.
No, it doesn't show it.
Well, it is.
Get away.
Or anything, the human body.
Well, okay, you can't talk about the human body.
Where'd you get your medical degree?
All these blocks, these emotional, psychological blocks, right?
But, you know, how all this, let me just, a little bit more of the Bible.
There's two things that connect to it very well.
If you go to any major Christian website, they'll tell you no one knows when he was born, the Christ.
And remember, when you say Jesus Christ, there's like 15 of them.
That's not biblical, right?
You've got a black one, a white one, one from Mexico, one from Italy, one from Greece.
You've got, you know, one, if you don't believe in him, you go to hell.
The other one, you can do anything you want, everything's been forgiven.
I mean, I'm so confused.
But biblically, you know, there's an astronomical alignment when he was born.
Virgo, 12 stars, the moon over her chest, sun at her feet, moon at her feet, sun over her chest, right?
That's an astronomical alignment that happened 3 BC, the month of September, the day of 11.
That's why they had that big birthday party for him in 2001 in New York.
September 11th.
Yeah.
You can look this up yourself.
It's in the scripture.
Put in, do a search.
Give me the astronomical alignment when the Christ was born.
It's down to the minute.
It was around 6.40 PM.
And they're all telling you, we don't know when he was born.
We do it December 25th.
M-I-C-K-E-Y-M-O-U-S-E.
It's your birthday!
Talking about, you know, level of stupidity here.
The other interesting thing about that is, I mean, well, there's so much.
Well, the other interesting thing is, if you talk about anything biblical,
whether it's the Garden of Eden, Adam and Eve, Abraham, any of the prophets,
any of the events, Sodom and Gomorrah, the flood, there is no, let me see,
no with a capital O accurate discussion whether it's online, in university,
or in people's homes going on right now.
Do you know why?
Because they're not getting their information from the text.
Go look up any biblical curriculum in universities.
Show me where it says they're going to study scripture.
They don't.
They'll say traditions of the Old Testament.
As a matter of fact, pastors and ministers, on their seasons off,
they do this continual education, and you get a curriculum on it,
and there's like anywhere between 5 to 17 items.
Do you know that none of the items include reading the Bible?
I did not know that.
Well, just like when you're a doctor, when you do anatomy,
and you actually get hands-on, what are you working on?
What hands-on anatomy?
A corpse.
Yes.
So maybe that's really good for working with corpses.
So when you look at the medical profession, you really have, I don't know,
like 3.5 million morticians running around pretending to be medical technicians,
strapping cuffs on your arm, telling you you have blood pressure and viruses.
Anyone, I dare anyone to look up virology.
Virology is a branch of toxicology,
and toxicology is the study of liver function.
Come on, folks.
Look, you know, Keith, when I travel around anywhere,
I have those earplugs, you know, the real soft ones that you squeeze,
and they expand in the ear.
They get really good form-fitting.
Sure.
They're usually orange or yellow.
Yeah.
They're like foam.
Yeah, they're like foam, right.
I keep those around, and I have a very good map of where doctor's offices
and medical clinics and hospitals are.
And when I know I'm approaching, let's say, a regular doctor's office
or a medical clinic or a hospital,
I have to stop and put those foam earplugs in really well,
because if I don't, when I drive by, the quacking is so loud,
my ears ring for about three days.
Now, what are they doing?
A lot of people say they're very helpful.
Yeah, they're helpful, because they're practicing accumulated knowledge
of almost 3,000 years of battlefield medicine, and not even that well.
They don't understand the lymphatic system or anything like that.
I mean, I'll tell you a story.
This is true.
There's a pun on this.
I know this doctor lady.
She teaches doctors, by the way, right?
So, I mean, what does that make her even better, right?
And nurses and things like that.
Well, one day, you know what a Faustner bit is?
It's a really big, flat drill bit.
They use them to make holes in telephone poles.
They're really sharp and nasty, right?
And I was holding a piece of plastic in the hand with a strong 18-volt cordless drill,
and it slipped, and the Faustner bit, about an inch diameter,
went into the palm of the hand while the drill was turning.
This is razor sharp.
To your hand?
To my own hand, yeah.
Oh, geez.
Imagine four razor blades mounted on a quarter-inch shaft rotating at 800 RPM, okay?
No fun.
And I looked at it, and I was like, oh, that doesn't look good.
And, yeah, that's fascia tissue, and that means that's the bone right there.
Well, I quickly wrapped it very, very tight, lots of paper towels, lots of electrical tape,
to the point where the fingertips turned blue after a few minutes.
So then I very gently loosened it until I got circulation back, and I repeated that for about a day.
So I kind of ruined my day because I kept keeping my hand as tight as possible.
Now, after about three or four days, it looked like I basically scratched myself with an X-Acto knife,
and about another three days after that, it looked just like a pink scratch on the hand.
None of the tissue, all of it went back together.
Now, I'm paraphrasing here, but I've had other people report similar things.
Now, that very same day that that happened, this doctor person that I know that teaches doctors
had a pruning accident, gardening,
and they had an incision that was half the size and half the severity of mine,
and they went to the hospital and they got 16 stitches.
And when we met a week later, she still had the stitches in her finger,
and I showed her the hand, and she says,
it basically looks like you have another palm line, and that's it.
So the level of severity was incredible.
And I've also helped, I should say, people with the concept of understanding the lymphatic system.
So they don't know what they're doing.
And, you know, 80% of what they diagnose is misdiagnosis anyway.
Oh, sure.
But what they're doing is they're accommodating society.
Now, we talked about religion, which has an entitled class, the priesthood,
and the medical society has a priesthood.
We're not talking about the garbage technicians, right?
Because even the highest guy that's in the garbage collection industry
is not regarded as the lowest doctor, you see.
Sure.
But, you know, if that whole thing went away, it would stink so bad.
You see, people's priorities are out of whack, you know what I mean?
The reason why people are living longer, quote-unquote, is because of sanitation,
not direct intervention.
Yeah, right.
It's quite the opposite.
You know, there's all these hypocrites in the military and wherever else.
They say, look at all these soldiers dying and people dying here and there or whatever.
Like, are you joking?
There's almost 4,000 people every day dying by deliberate negligence in the U.S. by medicine.
Alone?
Alone.
That's over 1.2 million.
That's 10 million a year.
And you guys aren't doing anything about it.
You know, it's like even with my weather work.
Like, aren't you going to stop that hurricane in Texas?
And I'm like, hell no.
That should be fire and brimstone.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to touch that.
It should be fire and brimstone.
So anyway, and then it should move like the elections, the voting.
They should go from town to town to town.
Anyway, that's not my wish.
I'm just saying that's what it should be.
It's a big difference.
So there's another level to all of this.
Now, whenever so obviously when you get your next health scare that the NIA, all these people are laughing about.
By the way, you know, the CDC is another branch of the military, you know, Center for Disease Control.
It was started in 1946.
They have a general.
And it was started for military purposes.
It's a company.
So you have the Army, Air Force, Navy, Marines and the CDC.
Anyway, go look it up.
No one talks about it.
But the next time they start pranking you guys and you probably on this station and others are going to talk about a virus, you know.
And it's like, just turn it off when you hear that kind of talk.
There's no such thing.
There's an interesting German doctor.
He studied virology for 20 years.
This is enough is enough.
This is all fraud.
I've never seen one.
There's only a bunch of acids and peptides.
You tell me to test.
There's nothing in there.
This is all mitochondrial tissue.
You guys are a fraud.
And he obviously, you know, he went from, you know, doing, you know, socialized medicine doctor doesn't make as much as a neurosurgeon, let's say, here.
But he was probably flipping burgers.
But he, you know, he has a little bit of honor.
But, you know, all the other millions don't.
And I have a lot of discussions.
I'm not in as much anymore.
I've been in the past with doctors.
And in private, they'll all say what I'm doing is suspect.
Everything.
I don't know what I'm doing.
But, you know, I'm doing it.
All of them.
Just like people in the religious fields.
They'll say, well, Greek, you know, I'm not denying what you're saying is not true.
I haven't looked at it.
Oh, really?
You've been a priest for 30 years.
You haven't looked at it.
Okay, good.
Or a rabbi, you know, says, yeah, I'm not saying what you're saying is not right.
But if I do what you're saying, I have to get a real job.
That's what they say.
I mean, in private.
It's amazing what people say in private, you know, in quotes.
Yeah.
Right?
And it gets quite interesting.
You know, there's many aspects.
There's a scientific side also, by the way.
We could probably get into maybe after the break if there is a break.
But maybe beat up the social-cultural aspect.
So whenever you hear these biblical clichs, you know, and by the way, you know, a lot of people consult on me with the Bible.
Because I give a proper interpretation, you know, and there's no such thing as your interpretation.
Because then it's your version.
An interpretation is like if you go to the United Nations with an ambassador and a translator, that translator is interpreting what you're saying.
He's not giving a version of it.
Right.
The man on the street will give a version.
The reporter will give his version, let's say.
Yeah.
But there is possible to get a proper interpretation.
But it's not allowed.
Because how dare you?
How dare you?
Right?
So it's like the philosophers.
Whenever the philosophers ponder a question, if you just say, well, the answer to that is this.
They're like, how dare you?
If we had the answers, then I'd be out of a job.
Yeah.
But it is possible to properly interpret what's called the scriptures.
But you're not going to do it out of King James, King Jimmy, I call it.
You're not going to do it in any English or Chinese or Spanish version.
And you're not going to learn going to the circus.
Now, what does it tie into?
You don't even know how to keep time.
Do you know that thing you call the Gregorian calendar, the Pope's work schedule?
I call it in jest.
Half in jest, all in earnest.
Because it really is the Pope's work schedule.
Like, you ever celebrate an anniversary or a day every year?
It's a different day of the week every year?
Sure.
All of them.
Yeah.
And if you try to look at an explanation of how contorted and convoluted, they can't explain it.
But actually, there is research you could do on the Gregorian calendar.
You could look it up on the Julian calendar date category under the Naval Observatory in Greenwich website.
And it says that we just count days.
Months and weeks are arbitrary.
Yeah.
And for solar and astronomical purposes, the day starts at high noon.
But for the people, it's civil midnight.
That's like how they defined oats in old dictionaries.
Oats, what we feed horses in England, but the staple of the people in Scotland.
So, basically, you don't even know what day it is, and no one cares.
Very few do.
And it's very important to know what day it is, measurably and lawfully.
Here's the other thing.
No one discusses lawfulness.
If you're ever tuning around, that old tuning comes from the old quartz radio, right?
Anyway, looking around the Internet, no matter how much people try to give insight on any subject or commentary on the subject,
do you ever notice the word lawful never comes up?
Lawful just means that you could reference based on something.
You could look it up.
So, basically, your timekeeping is very important.
Why?
Well, you guys can organize and communicate.
I'm going to meet you at Starbucks tomorrow at 3 p.m., Keith, the 28th of August, 2017 at Starbucks.
We use that for communication purposes.
It works.
But guess what?
The elephants, the roaches, the dolphins, the zebras, the grass, the rivers, the sky, the planet doesn't go on that.
So, if you're a fisherman chasing a school of fish around, maybe you'll learn more from a school of fish.
That school of fish will be there exactly the same time next year on using the day starting at noon.
The first day of the month is with the moon and so on.
So, for example, today is around the 23rd day of the 6th month or the 6th moon.
So, you've got another 7 or 8 days before you get a new moon in the 7th month, which is a pretty good month, by the way.
The 7th month is the end of the year, basically.
It's also when you mark the year.
Anyway.
Why is it a good month?
Well, because it's fall.
It's in-gathering.
It's fall harvest.
And the autumnal equinox.
Well, equinox doesn't mean what you think either.
Equinox means equally, means equal or to measure.
And nox means night.
Right?
So, that means you're going to be doing a measurement in the middle of the night.
And that equinox really traditionally is not so, but technically means the sun and the moon pass the same ecliptic that day.
You know, the same path in the sky.
They switch places.
Right?
And we have the same amount of daylight as darkness, right?
No.
No?
I thought it meant equal.
I thought that was when you had 12 hours of light and dark.
That's what they tell the people.
No.
But equally means to measure and nox means night.
So, if it was equal day and night, it wouldn't be called equinox.
It would be called equidiemnox.
Because it's a Latin term.
It's like the word nice, you know.
If you look at what it means and how people are using it.
But look, you know, all this stuff, you know, it's actually positive.
The reason I'm saying so is because they're accommodating the people very well.
You know, I've talked about cosmic censorship.
I'm kind of like all over the place here.
But I think this is the kind of, it's late enough and back in the east coast at least.
I'm in the southwest like you are.
I would suggest that no one knows how to keep time, so you can't navigate.
Now, you know, I make a lot of biblical references.
But you'll never hear me suggest anyone read the Bible, right?
Whether it's in the King James or in the original language.
Why?
Or any of the ancient texts.
You know why you never hear me encouraging people to do that?
No.
Because you ain't going to understand a dang thing in it.
Even if you tried.
Why?
Because you've got to get your act together.
What day is it?
You know, there is no Pope's work schedule in the biblical text.
And actually they put it in there.
They put in Easter Sunday and Good Friday.
And you've got to laugh, you know.
It's ridiculous.
They kept time, you know, the months had numbers, the days had numbers.
And the month started with the moon and the day starts at high noon.
So it's a lunar calendar, I guess.
No, it's not a lunar calendar.
It's a lunar solar calendar as well as constellational.
Okay.
Because lunar movements are not linear and solar movements are not linear.
But when you put the two together, they're symmetrical.
Just like a jigsaw puzzle.
If you look at a jigsaw puzzle, you know, the pieces are not linear and they're not straight.
But when you snap them all together, you see another, the image that forms is linear and cohesive.
Right?
Right.
It's kind of like a cam in the car.
You know how the cam, they're lobed?
You know, all the lobes on the cam, they don't, you know, if you rolled it on the sidewalk, it would go up and down, right?
Right.
But when on a bearing and it's affected on by each individual piston, it's a perfectly circular motion.
Yeah, it's this non-linear, cyclical, how many times have you heard it's not linear?
Right.
In many things, right?
There's a slight, it's curvilinear, I should say, if you're going to use the term linear.
But that's okay.
This stuff that I've been discussing for over a decade and a half is not, is the trailer or the precursor for the next society.
It's kind of like, you know, when you go to the summertime in the movies, they show you a little two-minute skit for what the next summer's movie is or something.
Sure.
That's all, that's what I just dedicated a decade and a half to as humans.
There's no sense in really getting down and creating a place where you can impart this technically and usefully unless it's very narrow, consulting, private, whatever, things.
You don't, you know, I did some sonic events in the past where I just come out and discuss these things, but it's like, I'm not accommodating the audience, you know.
An example would be, let's say you're well-versed in astrophysics, right?
And there's some interesting things to discuss in discoveries.
And you get a room of 500 eight-year-olds, and you speak for an hour on these wonderful discoveries in cosmology, and they're all quiet.
And then you say, anybody got any questions?
And they all raise their hands, and you're like, yeah, great, they were listening.
And they're like, what's the question?
And they all say in one voice, you got any candy?
Right?
This is humanity at this point.
Because they don't know how to discern, you see.
They don't know how to discern, and they won't right now because they're being censored, rightfully so.
Let's go back to the, let's see, what they call the biblical text for an example.
They had a lifespan of almost 1,000 years and were interacting with spiritual beings on a daily basis, or not too difficult to.
And they had to be wiped out with a flood.
And even after that, when their lifespans were shorted, they were still interacting with angelic beings, and they tried to build a tower that would make them like gods.
And they had to be confused.
And it goes on and on and on.
So the gods are like, yeah, you know, I think we need to give them access to the information but make it unpopular so no one can say they never had the information.
And so they could go about their little petri dish for the given amount of time until they go to the next level.
Otherwise it's just too disturbing.
They want to jump, you know, they want to jump around, you know, and get off.
And they're hungry for knowledge once they understand they can gain from it.
So what the gods did was they gave the oracles, their high-level oracle stuff, to a group of people that everyone will hate socially, religiously, and culturally.
You get it?
And they held it in their writings.
And so if anyone wanted to go and look at it, they were like, oh, that's Jewish.
I don't want that.
Or, oh, that's Greek.
I don't know that.
So the gods operate on a level of IQ of two million.
So you're not going to outsmart them, but you're going to have to see their plan.
And it's not difficult.
I always give the bear analogy, Keith.
Like, you know, if you say, do you know what a bear is, you say, yeah.
And most people say, yeah, I know what a bear is.
But you really don't.
Well, we know enough about a bear that we can communicate that we do.
You see?
There's a big difference.
The only way you'll really know what a bear is is if you sit down with him for a day or two.
Talk to him.
See what's on his mind.
Right?
And until that happens, you really don't.
But we know enough about bears.
Like, we don't know exactly, you know, about the gods directly, let's say.
But we know enough about them.
And what we know is that they're creators.
And when they create, they create in really large numbers.
Whether it's cells in a body, stars in the sky.
Right?
Grains of sand.
We know that their characteristic is when they create things, they're into big numbers.
Get it?
Yeah.
So that's why you see 7 billion people.
That's why you see all this.
It's not because you're special.
It's just because you're being created by beings that happen to indulge in very large amounts.
Well, we've got an estimated 400 billion stars in our own galaxy and at least that many other galaxies.
Right.
That's visible.
And every year they say we're only seeing like maybe single digits of what's out there.
Right.
10% tops.
So the gods are into big.
And that's different.
The space is like a movie theater.
You know, you could actually, you know, sit down in a movie theater and watch a space movie.
And the visual perspective goes to infinity, let's say.
But once the lights come on and the screen goes up, you know, the reality.
Now it's time to, you know.
So that's how you're kind of seeing a projected thing going on out there as well.
Wait until people find out that there's no light in space.
All of it appears in our atmosphere, right?
So that's why no one's coming back and talking.
I actually have a screenshot from the alleged space station where they said,
now this is a sunrise seen from outer space.
And it's pointing right at the camera and there's no sun.
But the part of the disk that intersected the thickness of the Earth's atmosphere lit up only.
Right.
Because you keep staring right at the sun, it's totally black.
Only where it comes through the atmosphere is it visible.
It'll still burn your eye out.
That's why they use diffraction mediums on all the windows.
That's why you see the guys with the gold visors so they can see the sun.
But you don't see any stars or sun because it's longitudinal.
Well, they say the same thing about the photographs from the moon landings.
Well, there's photographs from the moon landings and then there's photographs from the moon landings
and then there's photographs from the moon landings.
Which one are you talking about?
You know what I mean?
There's the ones that they show to everyone which are patently ridiculous, like 9-11 stuff, right?
Sure.
Like the airplanes going into the buildings and all that.
That's patently ridiculous.
Then there's the ones that are taken from outer space on the moon.
And then there's the real photos that have been taken on the moon,
which are not on the Internet, by the way, or in public.
And let me just preface.
The American Southwest is a great place for lots of spooks to retire, if you know what I mean.
So I was wondering why the hell I'm living in the high desert.
And over the years, I'm like, you've got some really interesting people living down here.
Anyway, read between the lines.
So, yeah, there's photos that are on the moon.
But that's not the point.
The point is whenever they're not having a good time, they always make you focus over there, right?
Right.
The 50s, it was like, oh, yeah, we've done screwed up so bad.
Everybody focused on outer space.
In the 90s, oh, we're screwing up, so everybody focused over there in the Middle East,
which is another thing I discuss all the time.
Yeah, they've always got something to distract us, right?
Well, anyway, well, it doesn't take much because, you know, you're most mature.
You're the wisest people that I've run into that are propped up, you know, publicly.
They have like a 9- or 11-year-old mentality.
Your average university professor operates on a third-grade level.
And you could prove this pretty easily.
I mean, I probably won't do it on this show, but I will do it.
Do you mean emotionally?
Emotionally and academically as well, yes.
Yeah, okay.
Academically as well.
Now, they're trained.
This is the thing that people fall for, which is ledger domain, which is a magician.
They're trained to speak a certain way, string words together a certain way.
It makes them sound smart.
There's a big difference between someone being smart, which means to poke around, and not being so smart.
But there's not a big difference between someone who was taught to sound smart versus someone who's not, right?
Sure.
You know, thieves do this all the time.
They're like, just look like you work here.
You know, it's like, I'm so nervous.
I'm not going to go in and steal.
I'm like, just act, just pretend that you live there, you know, or work there.
You know, you'll relax about it, you know.
But they don't know.
I mean, there's  remember I mentioned earlier that you're under a cosmic censorship.
In other words, it's the 800-pound gorilla in the room that you don't see.
And you're being censored.
But the thing is, once you know you're being censored, you could look a little further, try a little harder.
There's a discipline where it's kind of like the oasis thing, you know, where if you want something so much, it appears as an oasis in the desert.
Sure.
But when you actually do find water in the desert, it still looks like an oasis, doesn't it?
Yeah.
I mean, the mirage, I should say.
Mirage.
So if you're going to look through the veil and look through the things.
Now, what makes it so difficult is the effect of the emotional impulses on people.
But, you know, it starts  everyone's blaming the public fool system and all this other stuff.
It's really their parents.
And not to blame, but they started pranking the children in the crib, or what's called  crib is where you put animals.
But, you know, as they were in swaddling cloth, they told you about Santa Claus, the tooth fairy, go to church, go to college, all that, right?
You know, all the little lies.
And they never apologized for it, did they?
No.
They gave you dolls to play with and birthday cakes.
The birthday  maybe we'll get into what cannibals' birthdays and dolls have in common.
Is there going to be a break?
Yeah, we got about maybe two minutes, maybe 90 seconds, something like that.
Hmm.
Yeah, we'll get into a little bit more of the scientific stuff because we brought up free energy and why nothing's free.
And consider that the F-R-E-E, it might be an acronym that actually stands for revenue emanated elsewhere.
But, anyway, or from energy emanated elsewhere.
That's all it is.
And maybe we'll get into a little bit about that.
But the whole idea of bringing up all these points, we focus a little bit more on the biblical stuff and a little bit of the medical stuff.
Because people are still wandering around.
They're on a weekly focus or daily focus.
You ever notice how they get their panties in the water or worked up into a platter over a news story this week?
And you're like, what about this?
Well, that was last week.
Shut up.
I don't care.
So, you know, it's  yeah.
So you want to avoid all that and live a life of efficiency.
You ever hear of these guys called preppers?
You know how they used to get angry a few years ago?
If you didn't prep, they'd shoot you if you came asking them for stuff.
And now you ask them what?
Oh, that was last year.
How efficient is that to go out and spend 500 bucks on rice and beans that you're never going to eat anyway?
Not efficient.
There isn't going to be any disaster as such because there's a Middle East Union that's coming on the scene.
And all the countries are going to prop it up and support it.
And how are they going to do it if they're in catastrophic cataclysm, right?
But that's okay.
Little boys and girls, they like playing around and making up stuff.
And they like the emotional feel.
I just tell people, don't get caught up in that emotional stuff, man.
You know, just touch yourself, you know, if you're looking for impulse, you know.
Why do you have to get all worked up into what these other morons are talking about?
So have a good meal.
Go take a walk.
Turn off the stupid rectangle.
Live a life of efficiency.
And with that, we'll be right back, everybody.
Got a short break.
Listen to Revolution Radio at freedomslips.com.
We'll be right back after this message.
Looking for a nightcap to fill your listening needs?
Come join us on Spaced Out Radio with me, Dave Scott, right here on Revolution Radio.
Monday through Friday for three hours a night, starting at 9 p.m. Pacific, midnight Eastern.
We will take you down the supernatural path.
From E.T. contact to the paranormal, and all of the spiritual, cryptid, and conspiracy stories in between.
You can find us right here on Revolution Radio, at spacedoutradio.com,
on Twitter, at Spaced Out Radio, and on Facebook, at Spaced Out Radio Show.
Spaced Out Radio, it's a night of talk and interaction.
Are you experienced?
Most guys freeze.
That's your cerebral cortex looking for an answer it doesn't have.
See? Even your brain knows you're screwed.
Your blood is filling with adrenaline right now, whether you know it or not.
Your heart's beating fast.
It's getting a little harder to breathe.
Your neurobiological system is telling you to run, but your knees are too weak to move.
Fear is not real.
The only place that fear can exist is in our thoughts of the future.
It is a product of our imagination, causing us to fear things that do not at present and may not ever exist.
That is near insanity.
And do not misunderstand me.
Danger is very real, but fear is a choice.
We are all telling ourselves a story.
If you're listening to Revolution Radio at freedomslips.com, 100% listener-supported radio.
Reporting the danger, unafraid, right here, where information never sleeps.
Revolution Radio.
The opinions expressed on this radio station, its programs, and its website by the hosts, guests, and call-in listeners, or chatters, are solely the opinions of the original source who expressed them.
They do not necessarily represent the opinions of Revolution Radio and freedomslips.com, its staff, or affiliates.
If you're listening to Revolution Radio, freedomslips.com, 100% listener-supported radio.
And now we return you to your host.
Welcome back. Welcome back, everybody.
This is Revolution Radio at freedomslips.com, the number one listener-supported talk radio network in the known universe.
And this is Keith A. Zee. This show is Keith A. Zee Live.
We have the Greek with us tonight.
And, Greek, you're stirring up a lot of comments in the chat room.
I briefly looked at it.
I have another chat on the Just Greek Speak Chitango that I'm looking at as well.
And also I'm fetching some coffee and some smokes.
And I figured on maybe continuing on a few more points instead of asking what's in chat or answering if there is any questions.
That's what I was going to ask you.
I said you're on such a roll.
You know, go ahead and keep going.
I just wanted to mention that.
Well, there's a few salient points that I made describing this society in the past year.
And I want to just cover those because if anyone's going to leave, leave with this.
Because let's just say we're traveling around in our starship and we land here.
And we have to come back.
We spend three days here.
And we have to go back and report what the general inhabitants are obsessed with or interested in or whatever.
Right?
Right.
And one simple way to understand this society, I would write in a report.
If you understand what cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common, you will comprehend this society.
And also they're obsessed with human sacrifice, directly and indirectly.
Now, you know what a parody is or an effigy.
It's not the thing itself, but it's actually something with intent pertaining to it.
Right?
Sure.
Okay.
So the cannibals, birthdays, and dolls, and that's going to tie into the human sacrifice,
which there's no one explaining this or describing it this way at all.
And it's just shocking because it's like, let's go back to the numbers game.
You know, just because there's seven and a half billion people, you know,
it doesn't mean that they're all, you know, or even a large quantity or small quantity are available to explain it.
So if you can, you might as well.
Right?
Right.
So what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
In the ancient world, which pretty much started in the Mesopotamian region, let's say,
or let's just focus on that because that's influenced this more,
they spoke the Chaldean Hebrew tongue.
Right?
Just like Latin is all the romance languages.
And what they had a certain offshoot groups that would, let's say, worship what's called the balls,
which were basically lords, which most people refer to Satanism these days, the minor deities.
Right?
And the priests in that language were known as the Qahans.
And the Qahans would convince the people if they wanted prosperity,
they had to bring a child and have it sacrificed on their altar.
And they all took a piece of the flesh and the blood and they partook in eating it.
Because it was like, well, I'll get into it later why.
Now, that's where you get Qahanbalism.
Literally, that word means priest of the Lord, cannibalism.
Today, you have priests of the Lord everywhere.
So various lords and all that.
So now when the family went back, obviously, there was a child missing.
So the altar boys made an effigy of a child with, say, a doll.
And they said, well, give this, and this will replace physically the position of that child.
Right?
Right.
So now you know the history of dolls.
And if you ask people, well, I didn't do that.
I got one.
I enjoyed playing with dolls.
My mom, you know.
That doesn't matter.
Just look at the history of it.
Right?
There are several groups throughout history that have made a point about this.
But, of course, they shut up and sit down, you know.
Right?
So that's the history of that.
And, actually, that's a pretty big industry.
You have factories making these things still, don't they?
Right, dolls?
Okay.
Now, what happened was some of the people actually had wanted better quality of life
and drove these guys out of town.
And the ones that stayed back says, okay, let's not really just do it in public anymore.
Let's just make a parody, bake a loaf of sweet bread, put lights in it,
put the child in a high chair with a pointy hat like we wear,
and have them blow out the lights, which signifies blowing out the light.
And everyone eats the sweet bread, represents the body.
And I looked at that.
It took a few months.
I was like, wait a second.
That's the birthday cake celebration.
Right.
And, also, to show that the event worked, you brought a present for the child
to show that the wish of prosperity.
That's why they make a wish of prosperity.
So, when you hear, whether it's mainstream, alternative, print, writing family,
whatever, birthday celebrations, these people are not, quote, unquote, enlightened.
Let me just say this again.
Enlightened.
They are in the dark.
And we'll talk a little bit about darkness, also, because it's not what you think.
There's visible darkness, and then there's darkness, spiritual darkness.
Now, why did the people involved instill today with these old, ancient groups
of parody human sacrifice?
Now, remember that question, because I'm going to give you another metaphor.
Let's go back to the biblical text.
You know how all these morons say there's a different God in the Old Testament
than in the New Testament?
You've heard that a lot.
Yeah, I've heard that.
Well, no one's read it, obviously.
It's not.
Like, the Israelites in the Old Testament, it was a wrathful God.
They were told he would kill everyone, right?
Remember?
Even the animals, you know, the Canaanites.
Well, the reason why is, if you look at history and look at the Scripture,
is because they indulged in this openly and many other things.
Like, for example, let's say you and I keep going to Time Machine,
ancient Canaan, and other places like that.
And we go back, and we're, you know, taking a windy walk.
You know, you don't have to hold my hand or anything, but, you know,
we're going on Canaanite village, you know, whatever.
And, by the way, when you were friendly, male or whatever,
you'd hold hands in certain countries, by the way.
If we're having a discussion in many other countries,
to show that we would hold hands.
So this is, you know, not a homeopathic thing, you know.
Just like in England, everybody kisses each other,
like the bus driver will kiss you, you know, in England.
Not anymore, but, you know, at least in the 70s or something.
So anyway, we're walking down in a Canaanite village,
and we see this one shop, and you're like,
Greek, what's this shop that's got all these animals tied down?
Like, oh, you know, everybody's out here doing commerce.
They might want to get off, you know, sexually.
So they got a donkey tied down, a sheep tied down.
They got all this stuff. They got children tied down, you see.
This is a shop. You pay for that, right?
Openly. This is open now, right?
And then you go to another shop, and, you know,
you got shoes or whatever, fruits or whatever.
Another shop there, you see these little dirty children,
physically dirty, not well kept in cages.
And you're like, well, what's that, you know?
Well, you hear those bells ringing down the street, you know.
You're like, yeah, well, let's go there.
So you see this statue of a bronze statue seated.
This wouldn't happen all the time, but it was certain times often,
quite more often than not.
They would stoke this statue red hot,
and people would make a wish of prosperity,
and the hearth would be in the belly, usually, or underneath it.
So it had a large belly, and it was bright red.
And they would place the child in the lap and sear it alive.
And you didn't want to use your child, so you bought one of these children.
Because people would sell their children, you know,
because they were poor, let's say.
There were plenty of them available.
And they would sear the child.
And also because when, let's say you're trying to negotiate on buying, you know,
a hat or some gloves or some sandals,
and you hear a child screaming, that's not good.
So they ring bells to drown out the screams.
So that's why today in open markets, like known as malls,
they have this fat red character, and they put a child in his lap,
and they ask him a wish of prosperity, and they have jingle bells.
So now you know the history of that.
So it doesn't matter.
When you bring this up, the birthday cake, the Christmas,
all the holidays people do that are based on these things,
they say, oh, well, we do that to celebrate.
We like to live a joyous life.
Get out of here.
This is, do you see what I mean?
Yeah.
Yeah, so that's the darkness we'll get into.
Okay, so now you know a few more things.
I mean, it's very common.
You'll see it.
So if you want to judge a society, meaning, you know,
the judge is like, you know, I like, you know,
let's say I want to buy a car, and they have all these,
I want a red car.
Well, the guy's like, buy this one.
Well, I don't want this one.
It's green.
I want a red car.
Well, aren't you making a judgment call?
It could be that light, you know, judgment, you know,
or it could be more severe judging.
You know, you should always judge, right?
So now you know that if you start hearing about these holidays
and celebrations, not everything else they do in their lives,
would you say, is worthless or evil,
but now you're getting into a level where
if the people that do these things have anything of value,
now you're getting into the level of eating undigested corn
out of their poop.
You get it?
It's like if you saw some poop with undigested corn,
Keith, that's perfectly good poop.
Have at it.
I mean, perfectly good corn.
Why don't you eat it?
Oh, no, man, it's in the poop,
but it's perfectly good corn, isn't it?
You see?
So that's the whole thing here,
and I call that, if you want to describe humans in general,
they're coprophagia.
Anyone who wants to look up what that word means?
C-O-P-R-O-P-H-A-G-I-A.
Coprophagia.
Anyway.
Okay, so why all the human sacrifice?
Are you still there?
Yeah, yeah.
It got really quiet.
No, I was just listening.
So not everyone who celebrates these things is totally worthless
because they might be good at something.
You might want to listen to that,
but you also have to keep in the back of your mind,
this is how they judged their joy,
with human sacrifice.
And you're not going to avoid it.
It doesn't matter what country you're in,
you're going to find this kind of stuff, right?
This is, at large, the human condition at this point.
That's why when you read the biblical texts
and other ancient texts,
the gods, when they speak about men,
do they speak about men very well or not so well?
Not so well, right?
Right.
Yeah, it's very easy.
Now, why all of the obsession with human sacrifice?
And I'm the only one saying this.
This is from years of study.
And coming across it, not pursuing it,
but just coming across it constantly
with these ancient rites and rituals,
they always come up.
What's interesting is that you're living at a point now
where you have instant communication
with these little electronic devices and all that,
and it's very novel compared to other times in history, right?
Because of that.
Well, what's novel that hasn't come across through history today,
but other civilizations in the past,
is they were more openly contact in the spiritual world.
They were far more acknowledging the gods
and on all of the various levels of the gods,
from the chief deity down to the lower demons and imps and stuff, right?
Sure.
They were more aware of it, right?
Okay, what's interesting is that most of the lower-level entities
that were dealing with mankind
had pretty much surmised the purpose of mankind
and said, well, everything has a level of importance, doesn't it, right?
Like in the automobile, for example,
it would be steering wheel, windshield wipers, and brakes, right?
If you don't have those things,
you can't operate it safely.
Now, with humans, you look at the agricultural metaphor.
When you are farming and you produce crops,
whether it's for sustenance or market or whatever,
what's very important is that you maintain a cache
or a warehouse of seeds for next year.
Because if you don't, well, you farm for one year and you're finished, right?
Sure.
Now, let's put aside that you're going to buy them, buy the seeds,
because even if you're going to buy them,
who you're buying them from had to have done that.
So either way, seeds have to be saved to preserve the species, right?
So the people were convinced that the most important organs in the body
were the ones that allowed for propagations of the species,
which were the genitalia, male and female.
Follow me?
Yeah, absolutely.
What that leads to, now, have you ever heard of phallic symbols?
You know, a lot of symbology,
whether it's in sigil form in print or in architecture,
that's symbology of human genitalia, both male and female.
Haven't you heard of that?
They're all over the place, even the Vatican.
Exactly. That's where this comes from.
It's the lower-level entity interaction stuff, just like now Wi-Fi.
It was the Wi-Fi of their day.
You knew that if you saw those symbols,
those people were spiritually in tune with the lower levels, let's say.
You get it?
Yeah.
This has not been explained.
I'm just shocked how this is.
But I just said your professor is on a third-grade level.
By the way, when you hear about someone touting about any kind of college degree,
just right away you're eating corn out of somebody's.
But anyway, because in 1908, unless they're, what, 136 years old?
Anyway.
So at this point, you see the genitalia.
Now, let's go back to the agricultural metaphor.
The fruit is where the seed is in,
so the seed and the fruit are like the best products, let's say.
What is the product of the genitalia?
It's the baby.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, when you're going to make an offering
to one of these little imps and demons that they call their lords or their gods,
you've heard of making an offering to a god.
You bring your best of your best, right?
So that's why they brought the children to be sacrificed,
because they brought the fruits of their most important organs.
So now you know the deep, deep, deep, deep core underlying history of human sacrifice.
And the people that are doing it don't know why they're doing it, believe it or not.
I'm not defending them or being apologetic,
because there are also a lot of invocations, actually, that require that, that I've heard.
So there is no discussion at all on the stupid rectangle
and how simple it is.
We just broke it down in less than five minutes, right?
I view 9-11 as a ritual sacrifice.
Yeah, but 9-11 is also, you're not getting,
there is someone out there that's got some good information,
and I'll give you a video, it's on YouTube, I'll show you, everything's obvious,
where I could show you a YouTube that was done,
it's a declassified film, it's on YouTube,
where 60,000 tons of steel are turned into dust in less than eight seconds.
Yep.
And it's not, this was 1960s, and I'll show you the video and how it was done,
and you'll be like, oh, that's how they did it.
Now, let me just give a little bit on this.
Now, if people say, well, you can't talk about 9-11 unless you're a structural engineer,
you can't talk about viruses unless you're a doctor,
you can't talk about the Bible unless you're a priest,
and I assure you, none of them know anything about the field that they're supposed to be in,
just enough to get away with working in industry.
This is a fact. I'll drop a link, you can do it later.
I have a fact sheet that's accumulation from before the towers were built
up until the 1980s of all that was required to build them.
They were the strongest buildings ever built.
They had to use special steel made, Mitsubishi and someone else in Japan,
special heat treated, three to five inches thick.
Yeah.
And they would not give the building permit unless they had an emergency demolition scheme.
And it's very simple how some, because the people are so ignorant about how things work,
they used a very crude device. It wasn't explosions, it was one explosion.
Now, here's the interesting thing.
You ever notice when the towers came down,
the building that allegedly got hit with the plane second was taken down first?
Right.
The reason they did that is because the controls were in building seven,
and if they took down the first building first, it could have damaged the...
Building seven?
No, it could have damaged the delivery tunnel, and they wouldn't have been able to take the second building.
Because the controls were in building seven.
It was a nuclear device, basically, 150 kiloton, one in each one.
What people don't know is that when you say nuclear,
people think atmospheric, like what they're shown.
There's no knowledge about what happens when it goes underground.
They're very safe for two weeks.
That's why, if you remember the oil spill in the Gulf,
they said, why don't we just put a nuke down there, and it'll seal it off.
People don't know what radiation...
By the way, with radiation, there's no radioactivity in that material.
The radioactivity appears, because it's such a large isotope,
that it reflects the dielectric field in the environment.
It's a reflector, like plutonium, uranium, and all that.
They're very dense materials. That's what makes them radioactive.
All that radioactivity is coming from your environment.
Tesla proved that, and many people proved that.
You just put it in a hole underground, with a Geiger counter strapped to it,
and record it, and the radioactivity goes away.
As you bring it up to the surface, the radioactivity increases.
That's why, if you bring it in space, it's extremely radioactive.
Anyway, it's all false.
The reason why they tell you it's so dangerous, which it is.
It's ionization.
If you lock someone in a room...
Do you ever see those big UV lamps they use to sanitize sewer water?
No.
They're big 200-watt UV lamps.
If you go in front of those for about five minutes,
you won't get rentogens and millisieverts,
exactly the way you do from that material,
because it's coming out of electrical elements.
You will get leukemia.
You'll be ionized from UV.
Anyway, the reason why they're telling you this stuff is dangerous like that
is to protect their inventory.
At $100,000 a gram,
do you imagine what kind of security apparatus
the bankers had to put in place to protect the material?
But if you tell everyone it's going to kill them,
they all run out of the room.
It's a little late for that now.
For other things, they would have done that with everything else too.
They would have said, studying books will kill you.
But they don't have to.
They have the stupid rectangle to replace it.
But anyway, there's your human sacrifice and various other things
jumping around 9-11 and all that.
By the way, I'll throw another spoiler in.
All that thing about Russia,
the reason why they're having all that talk about Russia
is because you ever heard of the Kursk submarine?
One went down in 2000.
It had 21 granite missiles aboard.
Granite missiles were known as shipwreck missiles.
Nothing in NATO can stop them.
And they had a characteristic.
Once they were shot, a kilometer before they reached the target,
they hover above the waterline.
And they move at Mach 2.5, which is a bullet speed.
And they're armor-piercing.
So the guys that absconded those missiles
and shot it into the Pentagon,
you have these idiots saying it was a tomahawk.
Tomahawk's got a fiberglass nose.
Yeah, it wouldn't penetrate.
A Fisher-Price hammer could damage a tomahawk,
not even a real hammer.
Yeah, it wouldn't penetrate.
So what happened, the Justice Department and all the government,
they want to pin that on the Russians.
And Putin is like, no, that came out of the Ukraine,
but the Ukraine never had P-700.
So Putin is playing the shell game with the Americans,
and they stuck it on Victor Boot,
giving those charges are not enough,
because that's a pretty big charge.
So Putin's giving the Americans a runaround
on where the missiles came from,
because he was in control of that, by the way.
Blamed it on the Ukraine,
which the Ukraine suffered a whole bunch from.
No one sees this stuff.
This is like James Bond type stuff.
I'm telling people, look, the Ukraine's going to be in trouble because of this,
because Putin blamed it on the Ukraine.
And what happened?
And I said, this Russian thing in the news is not going to go away
until they settle the missing P-700s,
and Putin's not caving in.
And guess what you hear?
They'll blame anything on the Russians.
Look, we're out of ketchup at McDonald's.
It's the Russians' fault.
Right?
So the reason I'm saying this stuff
is because, again, I'd like to put a manual together.
When you start listening to people discussing 9-11,
all the way to, I call it,
who shot Roger Rabbit,
the JFK assassination.
All this stuff is what I call dummy load.
Dummy load is an electrical term,
but even if you don't know it, it just makes sense.
Dummy load, you're being loaded with dumb stuff.
Who shot Roger Rabbit?
The thing about the JFK,
I worked with someone who was an expert on studying that,
and I said, look, you're never going to find out
who shot JFK because they used the right people.
And if you found out who did it,
they didn't use the right people, did they?
But because they used the right people,
you're never going to find out.
The closest you're going to get is to speak to someone
who is a trained sniper,
trained in taking a successful headshot.
In sniper school, I shouldn't discuss this,
but to be a sniper, to take a headshot,
you get one chance at it.
Because if you graze the ear or go close by,
the subject moves.
So what do you know about very high-precision,
high-level sniper marksmanship
that's designed to do the headshot deal?
And nobody's going down that route.
Just like with 9-11, no one's going down the route.
Who was in the TV stations
planting all those fake videos of planes
going into buildings, number one?
And people don't understand,
those buildings were under the auspices
of the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey.
It's their own jurisdiction.
It's like a little mini-sovereignty,
and there's no discussion about them.
They have full control over this.
There's no discussion about the Granite Missile.
What makes the Granite Missile scary
is their 500 kiloton thermonuclear.
Now, obviously, the guys who launched it
out from sea that came into the Pentagon
didn't have the arming codes, obviously.
How do I know they didn't have the arming codes?
Because it didn't blow up.
Yeah, Washington, D.C. is still there.
It was a nuclear event.
Now, the only place you're going to see,
if you go to El Mundo,
which is the New York Times of South America,
on September 12th, they say
three atomic blasts in New York.
It was accurate.
But most people can't fathom that,
because there was an idiot, she wrote,
well, I shouldn't identify him,
but they write about those energy weapons
and all this stuff, and it can't be atomic
because it would be a blast, you'd see it.
You're talking about Judy Wood?
I'm not talking about anyone.
I don't want to use anybody's name.
They're all idiots.
When I say idiot or moron,
you're guilty until proven innocent.
Remember the Gustav Le Bon mentality?
You have someone come out with a topic,
they have some kind of credentials,
and the subject has to be so stupefied
in order for people to follow it,
whether it's religious, scientific, medical.
All this stuff is very simple to look at.
It's not easy, but simple doesn't mean easy, does it?
Yeah, sure.
So, anyway, we were talking about
various things about understanding the planet.
I hope just to go back to
what do cannibals' birthdays and dolls have in common,
and also why the Gainic symbols
and the phallic symbols
and the human sacrifice.
It's about time there's some,
I wouldn't say discussion, because I'm more like
talking at instead of talking with,
but that's okay, at least we're divulging.
Now, let me give another example about darkness.
Even if you haven't read it, you might have heard it.
They discuss about, be careful,
all the ancient writs, the workers of darkness.
It's not necessarily...
How are you going to work in the dark?
You need something to see.
Obviously they're not discussing
visible darkness and visible light.
There's a feeling.
Dark meaning something not good, usually.
You're trying to grow mushrooms or something,
which are not lawful to eat.
So, anyway, you see, in the ancient days,
man garnered all of his supplies for construction
and clothing and all that from things
that were grown in the light.
Animal skins, plant fibers, surface minerals.
They didn't go into deep tunnels like they do,
blasting those minerals,
gardening on the surface, exposed to the light.
Their inks were from plants, their food and all that.
Their day started at high noon,
their year, which was the brightest time of the day.
Their year started in the springtime,
which was when the brightness came back.
Their full moon was the new moon,
which is full of light.
Okay, now, if you look at the current society,
they get most of their materials from petrochemicals,
which is black, which is dark,
and it comes from, formed in the darkness.
Is there anything anyone can say
that's listening right now,
that within arm's reach cannot touch,
and I'm going to say not to touch,
but not touch something that is not affected
by petrochemicals?
Almost impossible.
Everything around you is garnered from the dark,
from that respect of the petrochemical influence.
Look at, what is your new moon?
Is it a full moon or is it a dark moon?
It's a dark moon.
When is your new year?
In the darkest day of the darkest season, right?
Right.
When does your day start?
At midnight, the darkest time?
So now you know, beware of the workers of darkness
or the society at large.
And you're going to find out who shot Roger Rabbit,
or 9-11, or even, you know,
you go to these quacks that put a,
strap a cuff on your arm and tell you
you've got pressure in the body?
Look, just to bounce back to these idiots,
when you put your feet,
by the way, they have websites and YouTubes
that tell you nobody knows why this happens,
so I'm going to tell you I'm not nobody,
because I'm going to tell you how it happens.
When you put your feet and your hands in water
for a while, don't they shrivel up?
Yeah.
You ever notice that if you're under pressure,
if you take a slab of meat with some bone,
put it in the bag and put pressure in the bag,
doesn't the bag expand?
Yeah.
Now, if you take a slab of meat with some bone in it
and put it in a bag and draw a vacuum on it,
doesn't that bag kind of shrivel up around the meat?
Yeah.
Well, duh, because your body is under
a slight vacuum condition.
That's why when you cut yourself,
it takes a while for the blood to come out.
Even the femoral artery,
which is like a garden hose,
when it's severed, you've got to count
three, two, one, and then it starts shooting
across the room.
Anyone that's worked around a garden hose,
you'll walk by and you feel like this little mist.
You can't even see it if there's the slightest hole in it.
Yeah.
Yeah?
So where, you know, the heart pumps the blood.
Oh, really?
So what pumps the heart?
I mean, this is ridiculous.
There is no pressure under a vacuum.
Here's the other idiotic thing that they'll tell you.
You absorb things.
Take this, you absorb it.
Right now, I dare anyone to go into images
and anatomical images anywhere
and look at the intestines.
You're going to see no less than three or four
hydrophobic impervious layers.
How the hell does anything get absorbed through that?
It's like a multi-ply steel radial tire.
Now, if anything got absorbed through the intestines,
you would die of sepsis.
Nothing gets absorbed in the body.
It's all done through induction.
You know, science fiction shows you this
with food replicators.
They can't come out and tell you how the body works.
You cannot know how the body works
because if you know how the body works,
now you know how headquarters operates.
And if you're not under deception with headquarters,
how are you going to believe deception?
You ever heard of resonance?
You ever wonder why there's so much deception
and lying in the world?
Because people, what?
They resonate with it.
If you want to resonate with people,
you better give them some deception
because they're deceived about their own...
They're a meat popsicle.
I mean, they're walking an incredible aspect of creation
and they think they're meat popsicles.
I really like that saying.
If you want to resonate with somebody,
you better give them some deception.
Because the truth is dissonant.
Right.
I've been on, publicly speaking,
what they call Ashtar or Easter.
I said, that whole thing never happened that way.
And the person listening,
you know what their response was?
But a lot of people were crucified back then.
They're like, oh boy.
Or you've got to just walk away.
It's the same with blood pressure.
But a lot of people get blood pressure checked.
I'm like, oh boy.
Oh boy.
Just walk away.
I tell people, don't argue with them.
Because remember, they've been pranked in the...
They were pranked as little babies like you were.
Your parents pranked the hell out of you.
Completely pranked you.
And they never apologized for it.
So, if you don't start realizing objectively
what's going on here,
you will probably resonate with, you know,
what we just mentioned.
Happy birthday.
It's your birthday.
Right.
Merry Christmas.
I don't care.
I'm having a good time.
Yeah.
You know, if you go to...
People say you just need love.
What are you talking about love?
If you went to the National Pedophile Convention,
heaven forbid,
don't you think you're going to find a lot of love there?
There's a lot of love
at the National Pedophile Convention, isn't there?
I wouldn't call it love.
Well, if you asked them, they would profess.
I know.
They would.
Yeah.
We also get into, you know,
the attorneys, you know, by the way,
are, you know, another joke on humanity
and all the priesthood and the medical community.
All of them are.
Your engineering community is a joke on humanity as well.
Telling you about how things work and all that.
You bring it up and they're like,
well, I don't believe that.
Whatever.
But the interesting aspect of any of this
is that there is an underlying thing
that people regretfully don't acknowledge.
Even the atheists.
You ever heard the word goodbye?
That means God be with ye.
Right?
So if you're an atheist, say goodbye.
He's actually telling you God be with ye.
Look it up.
That's what it means.
Right?
So your law comes from your God, your deity.
And I didn't say God.
I said your God.
Anybody says do you believe in God, walk away.
That's a stupid question.
Which one?
What are you talking about?
God.
There's many.
And there's a chief deity.
Right?
So walk away.
But anyway, your law comes from your God.
Just like when you're a very tiny baby,
your parents take that position
because you have no concept of a higher deity at that point.
So you're being pranked by your gods, right?
So that's why you have prankster gods now.
So anyway, what's interesting about that
is that every country has a matron or a patron deity.
And the Western world has adopted,
if you look at a lot of ancient writs
about the goddess religion.
Right?
And I'll give a short little plug-in for that.
Not that all goddesses are bad,
but this one happens to be malevolent.
She works with the chief deity and others.
I mean, the chief deity of this earth.
Right?
Which is a malevolent one.
And remember, when I say malevolent,
if you're going to counterfeit a $100 bill,
you don't use a crayon and a napkin.
You have to get the right paper and printing paper.
You have to make it look really close
to what people imagine is good or right.
Yeah.
So, yeah, that's why they, you know,
like rat poison is delicious, isn't it?
Right?
So, happy birthday.
Anyway, so, Merry Christmas.
Yeah.
So, the whole thing about this goddess religion,
which is interesting,
it's personified through justice.
The blindfolded woman,
everyone's always asking for it,
and I'm like...
Yeah, with the scales.
Yeah, I got to do the double hand-faced palm.
I'm like, oh boy, where do you start?
These people, there's, you know, the sacrifice.
Now, the teachings of the ancient goddess religion,
I was looking at this for years,
I said, I got to break this down
in like a minute or two.
So, this is how you break down the goddess religion.
It's very simple.
Her teaching,
it's a false teaching, by the way,
teaches that mankind was in a godlike state,
which was hermaphroditic or asexual,
and the way that human society will become godlike again
is by promoting male with male union
and promoting female with female union.
The males become effeminate and sterile.
The females maintain their fertility
and procreate without the men
to produce hermaphroditic or asexual beings.
And this goddess religion
was put into full force in the 1890s
through the New Age movement.
That's why you look at the legal society,
the religious society,
the judicial society,
all work together,
like in vitro fertilization,
genetic manipulation,
what do they call it?
Rights for the sodomites.
What do they call that?
LGBT.
All that stuff.
None of that stuff
is what people think it is at all.
And it's also promoted through the chemical,
the physical aspect.
You know, when a male child is being developed,
it has most testosterone in the first 16 weeks.
And if you give that child formula,
which is based on soy,
which is mostly phthalates and estrogen,
of course it's confused.
And right now there are chemicals
used in certain cleaning facilities,
those clean rooms or whatever,
I've forgotten the industry.
They're okay to dump in the river
because they're sort of benign,
but they form a compound in the river
with the nitrogen in the air
that turn the fish into female fish.
All the fish become female.
Wow.
Right?
Overnight, almost.
Also in plastic bottles,
the BPHA or whatever it is?
Yeah, they're called phthalates.
P-T-H-A.
P is silent.
So all these people that are duped into
this new sexual revolution are dupes,
so they don't know anything
about the history of it,
just like the people with the dolls and the cakes
and the Santa Claus.
Now, the thing is about these people,
when I see them grouping
the majority of humanity together,
is that they seem benign.
But if you expose them to this,
they go blank and they carry on.
But don't force this,
because they get violent.
And before they get violent,
if they do get violent on you,
you deserved it,
because they always give you a sign
that they're going to get violent,
like a snake that rattles its tail.
Right.
They always tell you,
if you say it again,
I'm going to screw it.
You can see the anger on their faces.
So if you get messed up
by one of these morons on the planet,
it's your fault.
You've got to know
when to just avoid them.
And what you would like to do,
obviously,
is find people without forming a group.
Because remember,
if you're going to form a group,
it's going to have to be dumb.
Otherwise, you get no group.
So, anyway,
read Gustave Le Bon on this.
I think we gave some tidbits
that you're not going to hear anywhere else,
unless you listen to Greek-speak.
But you can reference for yourself.
Actually, in most cases,
I get a lot of people say,
I don't see this on the Internet.
I'm like, oh, man.
You know, there are some universities,
by the way,
I hate to use them as a reference,
but when they get their students
in the semester,
they get a note under the door,
and it says,
yeah, welcome to the university.
And when you start doing your studying,
you'll discover not everything
we're teaching you is on the Internet.
They actually give this little handout.
I don't know if they do anymore.
Because all these students
try to go online
and try to study their field,
and they don't find stuff.
Yeah.
So, you know,
the Internet is subject to input.
If no one inputs it,
now it's machines, too, also.
Let's say,
but if it's not inputted,
it's not up there, right?
Well, it's also subject to filtering.
Well, now it's,
yeah, obviously,
there's the dummy load in the news
is that the major search engines
are going to start sequestering,
censoring, filtering, and eliminating
what they don't find
to be politically correct.
Well, they've been doing that already, though.
Now, let's just talk
about political correctness.
Because if you were
in a certain part of Europe
in the 1930s,
if you were registered
or professed to be Jewish,
it was politically correct
to have that person registered,
probably wear a yellow star,
and eventually thrown into a camp.
That was politically correct.
If you didn't do that,
you were not politically correct.
In the American South
about 50 years ago,
if you didn't tell a black person
to go to the back of the bus,
that was not politically correct.
Right.
So be careful
what's politically correct.
Now, that's why I stood up once
and I discussed this,
and I said,
that's why you've got to use the terms
niggers, spics, white trash,
and all that liberally,
just to shock people.
You know?
Anyway.
Yeah, I said that.
So what?
So being politically correct
and motivated,
that's why the whole movement,
with the sexual movement now,
with all these rights
and all that stuff,
it has nothing to do...
Oh, by the way,
I went into the whole thing
in private on a second hour once
with someone.
Tattoos.
You ever notice everybody
getting tattoos?
I was out in public today.
I didn't see one person
except a 75-year-old,
80-year-old person
in a wheelchair
where the only one
didn't have a tattoo.
Do you know,
back in 2003,
I was telling everyone
who was going to get tattoos,
I sent emails out,
I said,
that's not going to happen
because tattoos are what bikers get
and people in the Navy
and people that hang out in bars
only get tattoos.
I said, no, watch.
The ancient writ states
that eventually
a very strict,
very, very strict version
of the biblical law
will be put in place
in the future.
And in the biblical law,
anyone that,
it prohibits marking of the skin
and you couldn't take part
in society if you were
and you were put outside the camp.
But if the entire world
is under this law,
where is outside the camp?
Do you think they're going to
build a Hilton for you
on the moon?
Nope.
I'm not rolling it out.
Yeah, okay.
So when they declare this
on a grand level,
you could scrub that shit off
all you want.
That ain't coming off.
Yeah.
And there is no police.
Your own family is going
to turn you in.
So when you read about
one third of the people
being taken out
by the other two thirds,
you're like,
oh yeah,
check these guys out.
And I tell people,
if you got a small one, man,
go get it removed.
And there's a couple of people
with some wisdom
like, yeah, Greek, you know,
I didn't want to believe
what you said,
but I meditated on it
and I studied it
and it's like, yep,
I got that tattoo off.
So, I mean,
you're being set up.
The gods are setting you up.
You know, the gods
will not throw the kill shots
on this planet
unless they do it lawfully, right?
That's why if you read
in scripture,
you know, the Christ
was without sin,
but while he was being executed,
in order to be killed lawfully,
he had to take on the sins
of every man, woman,
and child that ever lived.
Wow.
Right?
To be lawful.
So people are going to,
you know, here's,
let me give a little
cliche here.
Do you remember
the woman of adultery
where they were going to
stone her as a story
and the Christ said,
he who is without sin
throw the first stone?
Right.
All these Christian morons
are like,
oh, he's so merciful
and all that.
No.
He was using the law
because in the law
it states that
you cannot witness
against someone
unless you have your,
you know,
if you have outstanding
parking tickets, right?
You can't be a witness.
In other words,
those people
had outstanding transgressions
that they didn't atone for
at the temple.
Right.
So they couldn't
throw the stone.
And also he was
writing something
on the ground
which, you know,
in order for someone
to prove if there was
no witness,
the bitter waters,
you know,
from the dust
on the ground,
you know.
But if, let's say,
for example,
those things
were taken care of,
he'd be stoning the bitch.
Right.
People don't,
they make up this stuff.
It's like they think
there's some other religion
coming out of this.
And I saw there was
a thing about the Gnostics
on there.
Forget about Gnosticism.
That's a sect
from Simon Magus.
Now, I'm not going to say
forget about it
because that's telling
someone what to do.
Gnosticism would be
like the 9-11 commission
about what happened
on 9-11.
Or the Warren report
for the JFK assassination.
Yeah, there's nothing
in there.
I mean, it's just,
Simon Magus was,
you know,
you ever see
commercialism sometime
to the point
where it's just like
overdone
and it's like
only the dumbest
need apply
to this stuff?
Like Black Friday
or whatever, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
That's Gnosticism.
And there's a big,
trust me,
there's a big group
behind them
and they get pretty vile
if you talk to them
that way.
But that's just the quick way.
Now, you can reason
with them to a certain point,
but that certain point
ends very quickly
because all they have to do
is tell them to go back
and read what they're reading.
And this was spread out
and fortunately
and unfortunately
a lot of these movements,
just like inventors,
you know,
like you'll invent
things in one place
and someone else
in another part of the world
doing the same thing.
Right?
And you don't know
about each other.
It happens all the time.
And then they meet up
eventually and they form
a little group.
That's what you see
going on with all religions.
I mean, look at Mormonism.
Or they sue each other.
Yeah, or whatever.
I mean, look,
all these religions.
Yeah, go ahead
with Mormonism.
I don't want to,
but I'm going to make
a reference.
I'm going to go look.
South Park did something
about that.
Yeah.
Do you remember it?
No, I haven't seen...
Only the dumbest
need apply.
I mean, at that point
you're irre...
Humanity at large
is unrehabilitatable
at this point,
by the way.
So picking on the Mormons
or the Christians
or Gnostics
or a particular group
like doctors or professors
is useless at this point.
You see?
It's not efficient.
No, it's not
because the entire group
is...
except for a small...
Now, when the gods
administer their kill shots,
by the way,
you have about
another decade and a half.
And I'm not asking
anyone to believe this,
but just file this away
for later.
Because here's the thing.
Let me give you an example.
Keith,
you got a mailbox,
let's say,
and I just put
a million bucks in it
and it's 20 miles away
for you to get it.
And on your way
you crash your car,
you find out your dog dies,
you lose all your clothes,
but you're not unhappy
because you know
when you get that million bucks
you'll be able to replace
all that stuff, right?
Sure.
But you're going to get there
and find there's no
million dollars there,
so now you're really screwed.
But you're emotionally
bypassed all the other
bad stuff because
you were focusing
on that one thing.
Starting in the next
seven years,
humanity is going to
go under world peace
and you're going to
have an international
leadership that is
going to bring up
all this stuff,
saying you're going to
have a thousand years
of world peace
and a wonderful society.
And when the stuff
starts to go south,
people are going to
be like,
oh, it doesn't matter,
we had a billion die
last night,
oh, we're on this
wonderful society,
we'll just clean up,
we'll be fine.
All these things
will be happening,
wiping them out,
and they're going to
get the million
dollars in the
post office,
it doesn't matter.
So in other words,
you know this is
coming when you
start to see a
perfect society being
propagandized and
actualized,
you're getting
closer to the time
where you're going
to see,
if you think people
are insane now,
oh boy.
So there's no
prepping and all
this stuff,
there isn't going
to be no calamity
in the United States
or anywhere else.
You have little
disasters here and there.
They blew up three
nuclear devices
underground in New
York City and the
whole world was
watching and no one
really said anything,
come on.
They get away with
that.
Look at all the
false flag stuff.
It's the same people
in Barcelona,
Sandy Hook,
all these people.
And they're getting
away with it.
They're not really
getting away with it,
they're accommodating
the people.
People love that
stuff.
And also,
they're accommodating
themselves.
They're very efficient.
But in the future,
this is the
interesting thing,
the marking of
this,
we're speaking now,
is this is the
last,
this is the
last bit
of this
seven-year period.
You're going into
another seven-year
period.
The last hurrah?
Well, no,
you have four
seven-year periods,
two just finished,
you have two more
to go.
Which is interesting
because now you're
past the center,
you know,
halftime in football?
Right, right, right.
Yeah, you're at
halftime right now
in the credits.
So it's interesting
and don't even
talk about
details in public
because you're going
to lose people,
you know,
and not because
you can't talk about it
is because you can't
talk about it the way
they're used to hearing
things in this
little Miss Daisy,
you know,
two plus two equals
four.
There's a lot of
background that has
to be given.
You know,
like we gave on
The Cannibals,
birthdays and dolls,
what justice,
the goddess religion
is,
you know,
what tech,
what things mean.
You can't just give
this one hour
sitcom,
whatever,
you know,
one hour show,
55 minutes in,
the world's still
going to be destroyed
and they save it
in the last three minutes
and the credits come in.
No, it's not like that
reality, you know.
But anyway,
we have only a few
minutes left
and one of the
things you wrote
is essentially
free energy,
right?
Let's just talk about
that because that's
another thing to show
you how ridiculous
this society is.
And I don't endorse
the people I'm going
to mention
because
I wouldn't say
they're breakfast
cereal types,
you know what
breakfast cereal is
made of,
fruits,
nuts and flakes,
right?
But borderline,
there is no free
energy.
What they're actually
using,
it doesn't go against
the laws of physics
because these are
idiots,
by the way,
like Santa,
it's your birthday,
right,
when you go to
physics school,
you know?
But you ever
heard of photon?
You know that
term was created
by an occult
psychologist?
No.
Yeah,
look it up.
The Big Bang
was started
by a Catholic
priest.
Oh,
here's another
dummy load.
Whenever you
hear anyone
bringing up
Einstein has
done anything
good,
that's just
you're eating
corn out of
somebody's poop.
You hear that
all the time
on places.
Oh,
Einstein is,
oh,
Einstein,
there's nothing
you've ever used
or done or
heard of that's
useful that Einstein
came up with.
Einstein is like
Oswald and
Osama bin Laden.
He was someone
that was put in
society to mark
an axial period,
a change of
thought.
But anyway,
go back to
free energy.
Basically,
what I'm going
to say,
if anyone,
it's been around
since the 60's,
it's right in
your face,
not really right
in your face,
but it was on
the Johnny Carson
show,
that's enough.
His name is
Joseph Newman,
the energy
machine of
Joseph Newman.
He was really
wonderful.
He said,
look,
they tell you
when you
move a
copper wire
through a
magnet,
the electricity
goes at
the speed
of light.
Now,
I'm an old
country boy
and I know
if I move
that magnet
slow over
the wire
and all of
a sudden
electricity
is moving
at the speed
of light,
there's no way
that could
happen.
If you're
moving the
wire slow
and all of
a sudden
electricity
goes at
the speed
of light,
how can
that happen?
Everybody
knows that.
If everything's
slow,
how can
this thing
go fast?
You could
use,
let's say,
the analogy
of a
high-speed
chemistry,
the powder
charge going
off in a
gun,
but that's
high-speed
chemistry now.
It's not
electricity
flow.
So he
started putting
stuff together
and he
basically
developed a
feedback loop
using mechanical
commutators.
You know,
when you
rotate a
magnet in
a coil,
it creates
a current
through the
coil?
Sure.
But as the
current builds up,
it creates
resistance on
the magnet,
doesn't it?
Right.
So what you
do is you
switch it
when it
gets to a
certain point
so it
reverses and
pushes the
magnet and
then returns
back and
gets it
rotating again.
And also
you have a
coil on
the magnet
that does
that.
Very simple.
It's just
like a
water wheel.
How many
years did
people live
by the
river before
they decided
to put a
water wheel
in it?
Right.
Probably not
very long or
maybe very
long.
But on the
other hand,
if you just
wanted to put
a water wheel
in a river,
you think you
can do it or
it's best to
get in the
Yellow Pages
or whatever and
call someone
who's expert
at it for
a second,
right?
So if
anyone wants
to look at
the energy
machine of
Joseph Newman,
there's plenty
of stuff out
there.
There was
recently in
Idaho about
three months
ago a
demonstration
of not
one,
not two,
not three,
but about
five or
six of
these devices
in real
time.
They all
work and
anyone could
poke around
on the
internet.
Now this
whole thing
with this
free energy
stuff,
it's best
that it's
not done
on a
little
benchtop
unit,
tabletop
unit.
It's always
the bigger
you build
it, the
more momentum
it develops
just like a
water wheel.
You'll
hire the
efficiency.
And the
efficiency goes
up, yes,
only because
of the
investment.
You can
still make
a very
small one
very efficient
but you
gotta get
really tiny
little wires
because you're
looking at
sometimes two
miles worth
of copper
wire.
You heard
me right,
that's
11,000
feet of
wire or
100,000
inches of
wire.
You could
go to your
local
electronics
shop right
now and
tell them
I need
two miles
of 22
gauge wire.
They're
going to
just stand
there looking
at you
like,
uh,
we don't
have that.
I'd love
to see that
spool.
Yeah,
exactly.
And also,
right,
here's the
thing.
If you
could put
the spec
to a
supplier and
get it in
a spool,
he did
all the
winding for
you.
Think about
it.
You just
said it.
It's
not
free.
It's
not
free.
It's
not
free.
It's
national debt that is all put out by little back room toilet water weak chin
legal types that you'll never find out about and they're laughing their asses
off at all the public on the internet soaking up coprophy yeah coprophy if
anyone looked up that term COPRO PHA GIA anyway that means shit eater by the way
copro means feces and foggy means to eat so so what happens is could you imagine
by the way Volkswagen had explicitly said sign and drive remember the
commercial few years ago I saw it I don't watch TV but I was doing an oil
change once and I was in the waiting rooms at sign and drive so these guys
are telling you the truth they just said all you need to sign your name drive out
with a car well anyway that's your free energy rant and you're not going to get
it because you're rotten to the core as a society that doesn't mean that
everyone is rotten to the core but if you said this the entire society is
rotten to the core statistically 99.999% that's pretty accurate you see it
doesn't mean you have to be now here's the other thing to watch out for you
ever hear someone says we have to do this to make the world a better place
they're screwed you just screwed yourself when you said that not when
you're doing that when you said it you see if you're going to do things do them
but don't say you're doing it to make the world a better place why because all
of the malevolent spiritual entities don't want to see the world a better
place and when you voice it you they become your enemy right right but now
you're at a point where all the benevolent gods are also coming down
for the kill shot so now they're your enemy that's why anyone in history from
Tesla on up I assure you who says we're going to do this to make the world a
better place ends up sleeping on park benches or homeless or killed or worse
think about it everyone now there's very few exceptions so there's less so I'm not
saying this to make a world a better place but if anyone has the wisdom to
understand what I'm saying or not because I'm saying it because what is
being said you will see how you could make your life better and more
sensible and efficient in this world is a big difference you're not going to
make the world better because it's ready to be taken out not by humans here's the
thing you know when human agents try to fight other human agents they try to
weaken the opposition before they attack right when the gods go after a
civilization they prop up and make that civilization at their height and then
they come in with one arm behind their back and take them out so when you see
this society on the planet at large going up to its pinnacle and by the mid
2020s and everyone buys into it that's the time when you're like hey could I
borrow you know that rice and can I borrow that Jeep and can I borrow yeah
we're doing great you can have whatever you want that's when you do your prepping
when everything's doing well not when everyone else has to prep look I look at
this the dummy load that they put on alternative media and mainstream or
mostly alternative how many times was the United States supposed to collapse
since the last three years at least a dozen times right sure yeah I think
what's collapsed is sensibility rationale and vision you ever heard in
ancient times I said for lack of vision the people perish yeah there's no vision
I assure you let me just say it again no with a capital O on no one at all
right now zero whether it's some old fart walking around talking about how
he's been doing this for 50 years or some other old idiot talking about how
he gets information off the internet or some young jerk-off saying that he
channels whatever or there is no vision zero nothing nada you people are
pathetic when it comes to visionary future events and you must know the
future must if you walk into a room and see someone with a cookbook out and they
got flour eggs and the oven preheated they know the future they know in 45
minutes there will be chocolate chips coming out of that oven you don't see
anything you must know the future you have these idiots that you listen to all
of them not not a one I and here's the thing this is not a rant this is the
truth there is no one speaking anything that makes any sense when it comes to
vision in the future at all none it's pathetic it makes me you know it
actually disarms me Keith I don't want that's why I haven't done this the other
project I don't want to be the only one you know it's like kind of like you know
the terrorism they put on children when the you know it's a hard class you're in
the fourth grade or whatever the teacher picks on you to answer and you like you
know the answer but you nervous you know cuz you've never spoken before right
right yeah I don't want to do that and look here's the other interesting part
there are other people that know what should be said yeah but they're not
speaking and they're not going to because they're far more disgusted by
humanity than I am you see so you don't anyway that's then that's how it goes
and there is no vision at all and there shouldn't be because why because this is
a cosmic setup you're being set up by beings that have IQs of 2 million and
plus so and and you're a little puny the the idiots that you look up to for
information that's what they are at best actually they're better words to use but
I'm not there they go into the medical realm then you have nothing right now
and you won't but you know here's the good thing keep that might sound like the
Greeks ranting and being pejorative or whatever right this when this cycle
ends not by the spring that's coming up what you call 2018 and the fall you're
gonna see a lot of people emerging saying that we need to go back and find
out what white what things are based on starting from ancient times till now and
coinciding with that next few years you're gonna have a lot of ancient
discoveries that are gonna start bringing people's attention so there you
go thanks for having me man hey thank you very much this is the Greek
everybody say your website real quick again uncommon radio check it out very
interesting very informative thank you so much three all right be well see ya
everybody