Welcome to Uncommon Sense here on American Freedom Radio.
I am Seth Michael and I'm joined by the Greek. Welcome, Greek.
Thank you, Seth. Greetings, everyone. And you can find us also at www.uncommonradio.com.
I think I got it right. And that's an easy way also to go and follow the links for listening
for archives and such. But yes, we are on American Freedom Radio, which is a
listener funded allegedly site. It would be good if some listeners did help fund it.
And you know how to do that if you can, if you will, if you do go to the homepage,
you will be instructed somehow electronically to do that. So yeah, with that out of the way,
greetings, everyone again. And yes, I just wanted to bring up, I think we brought up before we
started up perhaps to be talking a little bit about food again, just slightly. It's been
quite a role on that. I think it's been successful on the feedback, especially people
having success performing the suggestions. And the reason I wanted to just do a little
bit of food talk was recently someone suggested that they were happy to find a part of their
percolator, meaning coffee percolator. And one of the replies I made, that's a perfect way to ruin
good coffee. So perhaps we'd be discussing a little bit about how to make a simple good coffee.
And I know you have a place in your desires to have such a thing, Seth, as well.
Oh, yeah, certainly.
And there's so many ways, but the easiest thing, folks, is don't kill it with over brewing and
the water temperature being too hot. The hotter the water temperature, the shorter the contact
with the coffee. Would you say that's the simplest suggestion for always having a good cup or good pot?
Yeah, absolutely. And you can find, you know, inexpensive or relatively inexpensive machines
that will actually do those two things. They don't get too hot. They heat things up to the
proper temperature, things like that. Yeah.
Yeah. So in other words, folks, the lower the temperature of the water,
the more dwell time over the grounds and the grounds can be coarse or fine. Again, it gets
technical. Absolutely. You can make really good coffee without a machine at all, just with a
jar with an airtight lid, you know, without without any heat.
But because it takes more time to get more time.
Exactly. So the hotter the water, the less the time. That's why the espressos work so quickly.
Because they're very high in temperature now. Unfortunately, still, what I found is the average
coffee maker slash whatever electric plug in the wall, convenient, typical Western world or American,
I should say, doesn't mind the water temperature that much. I find that they run the water
through an aluminum coil that brings it to a boiling point, if not beyond, and then dwells
on the filter cone and such. And you end up ruining good coffee that way.
Now, mind you, many commercial pre ground coffees are blended with chicory and
other things or whatever, let's just say, and to make it more forgiving. But if you have some good
coffee and you do grind it yourself, and if you want to go to the next level, roast it yourself,
the hotter the water, the less dwell time. And I would say that would also go with tea.
Now, teas get very complex, because some teas can be as expensive as silver.
Believe it or not, I was in a major city a while back on the East Coast, and there was a tea
purveyor. And it was like walking into an armory. They had to buzz you into the door to get into the
shop and then buzz you in to look at the teas with security guards. I found out they had teas
there that were more than 20 bucks an ounce, if not even higher than that, maybe three, four times
that. So that gets into a whole other subject. But making a proper cup of tea depends on what you're
brewing as a tea as well, whether it's a leaf, if it's a cured leaf, if it's fermented, if it's a
root-based tea. But again, consider the water temperature and what is suggested for the particular
thing you're trying to brew. But essentially, again, to making a good cup of coffee, or as we say,
the higher the water temperature, the less dwell time. So cowboy coffee still works,
but just make it really, really quick. Anything else on that coffee venture stuff? I know we could
spend not just one show, but two shows based on the amount of time you and I have spent in private
discussing making coffee. Yeah, coffee is easily relatable. I bet there are 20 people out there
listening. Yes. It's one of those things that if you know how to say coffee, you can say it in just
about 150 languages, by the way. Yeah. Right. Cafe. Yeah. Cup fee in Korean, right? They throw
in Vietnamese, it'll be cup fee. But still, if you say anything that resembles a C, a vowel, an F,
and a vowel, you got it anywhere in the world. Absolutely. What would you say? I drink just
regular black tea, but I don't know that we've ever... Yeah, that's a dried... You know,
it's interesting that the green tea and the black tea are typically very similar. It's the same leaf,
let's say, or similar. And one is air dried through time that makes it black, but when it's
dried with heat, it retains its green color. You would think the opposite, right? Intuitively. I
was amazed to find that out. Because typically when we apply heat to something, it browns it,
right? You throw some toast in the fire or near heat or anything that you... That golden brown,
we refer to heating. But we found out most leaf teas that are heated to be dried retain their
green color. So the black teas would be, I guess, yeah, the same. Most of the teas are...
There's black tea, like you say, that's the typical tea. And then there are many varieties,
which are blends like an Earl Grey and things like that, right? But most of the teas that people do
order or make are of that variety. So again, hotter the water, the less dwell time. I'm not
a big fan of leaving what they call these convenient items called tea bags, you know,
and things in pots. Typically in many Asian cultures, the tea leaves are bulk fitted or
placed into a kettle and they sink to the bottom, but they use a very small amount.
So I don't want to maybe get into the teas too much because we might have some
acquaintances in the UK that are really going to get upset if we start talking about how to make tea.
So kind of a joke there. But speaking of that, there's always comments, you know,
I'm being political, correct, Seth? I'll just kind of bounce around a little bit.
And someone in the chat put something about no feminism or blending or something. I thought that
was interesting. And then the Greek side came up, you know, I said, oh, yes, Greece, where the men
are men, the women look like men and the sheep are scared. But there's something now that's going
on, which is interesting, this tyranny of the political or politico about being politically
correct. Of course, it's for the non-discerning, you know, the crowd mentality. You know, they
latch on to it has to be something super simple. And whenever something is brought up that is no
longer politically correct, they look at it as if it's a law or, you know, religious connotation.
You know, that's not politically correct, you know, but that's the crowd. And we keep bringing
up Gustave Le Bon's The Crowd, and I'm not promoting the book. But many people have said
they've gone out and gotten it. And good for you, at least you'll be able to rationalize what's going
on around you. But this thing about political correctness now, you know, things like, Seth,
I think we might have brought it up once, maybe we'll do it for the audience. Have you heard of
Winston Churchill's? I believe it's Winston Churchill's version of heaven and hell in
Europe. We discussed that ever, I think might have brought up in passing, but perhaps in passing,
but yeah, that's that wouldn't be politically correct anymore. But it's so true based on the
cultural inclination, you know, each culture is inclined to perform things a certain way,
right? Traditions, things like that, right? Training, education, right? Culture, right?
Well, it's just interesting to bring it up, just because this is not things like this will never
be discussed anymore, at least in the in the mindset right now. But okay, so heaven in Europe,
all right, would be where the British are the police, the French are the cooks,
the Germans are the mechanics, the Italians are the lovers, and the Swiss are the bankers.
Hell in Europe would be if the British were the cooks, the French were the mechanics,
the Germans were the police, the Italians were the bankers, and the Swiss were the lovers.
So I thought I'd bring this up, because it also reflects a different mindset, which now would tend
to be radically uncommon, I would say, you know, racial jokes, feminist jokes, things like that,
that people that grew up in the 40s, 50s, 60s, and 70s or so were pretty much,
how would you say, immersed in, have now gone away, not that they're good.
I'm not saying that they are good to do those types of dwell on those types of comments. But
it's interesting how the instead of addressing what was said as being right or wrong or lawful,
now things are addressed as being political or unpolitically correct. So I just find that to be
very obtuse and common, so. Absolutely. It seems that,
yeah, everyone is concerned with offending others. Yeah, well, here's the thing, you know,
once I've said that if you took the current events and put it in a time capsule, went back in time
50 years, everyone would stop at what they're doing. I mean, everyone and well, let's say
statistically, and most of everyone would say, we have to stop what we're doing. So these things
don't happen. Right. And you want to call it the frog being boiled in the pot, the gradual,
yeah, it's possible. But that is another discussion, in a sense, because if you are
living lawfully and adhere to a set of laws that the frog being boiled in the pot doesn't work.
Right. So if you live by certain covenants or rules that you consider lawful, which come from
your God, by the way, and by the way, if anyone tells you that any God has done away with rules
that they had, they're lying. And you fall in for the crowd mentality. And you shouldn't be
listening to this show because it's just going to make your life well. Well, you may or may not make
your life miserable, but you will be very confused. And you probably won't understand anything that's
being said. But anyway, I don't know why I give these little caveats. But the if you are have a
set of rules that you live by that that frog in the pot being boiled, that gradual change doesn't
affect you, by the way, because you have what's called discernment. Right. And that's one of the
things I said, we wanted to do a recap on the perhaps the previous sonic experience, I kind of
glanced over it, we didn't really prepare anything for this show regarding that. But there's a
handful of items which, you know, can be discussed. And I think going into more depth, which we'll
give more in the future. But to bring up the first episode of the last sonic experience that I did,
was a general overview of many, many, many topics to kind of lay the groundwork and the foundation
of what Greek speak is about. And by the way, someone, I want to thank them maybe anonymously,
like she'll just mentioned their name, Robin, she assembled something called,
I think it's called just Greek speak, blogspot. So it's not Greek speak, that's something else,
but just Greek speak blogspot.com or something. So we'll find a link and post it, maybe someone
will that's something that's coming together. It's just things put together of interest about
Greek speak. But I think the when one especially pursues lawfulness, which you will not find in
the world today, by the way, it almost seems to be a private and personal endeavor. Would you say
that would be fairly accurate, Seth, to pursue lawfulness as a private personal endeavor?
There's no group or any place to subscribe to that is contemporary, I would say?
Yeah, absolutely. I can't say that absolutely, I suppose. None that I have seen.
Yeah, that's evident. Yeah, that's evident that we could say, here, here's a place to go.
And also, by the way, folks, and not to brag or be arrogant, but the reason Seth and I get together
and do these conversations is because we're saying things that just kind of need to be said. I mean,
but no one else is talking. I mean, all the stuff you hear out there is, well,
to get into it, you know what it is, you might have heard it. But the reason of coming together
and doing Uncommon Sense is shaking your head and two face palm moment kind of thing,
where imagine the metaphor would be the question of the day or the week or the year is how many
fingers do we have on our hands, let's say? And you're like, dude, all you got to do is
look at it right in front of you and count, right? And they're still asking that question.
So the things we're discussing is just as clear as that, you know, we're not
trying to overlay any personal experiences or some kind of,
well, you know what I'm talking about how people are always introduced as being this or that.
We're always wanting to go back to what is very, very, very basic. If you ever hear us discussing
things that you have to go more than five feet from where you are to discover it's not us,
we've been taken by the pod people. So whatever. The likelihood of us having an expert guest is
relatively low. Yes. Now, could it be that the definition of an expert
is someone who is always learning more and more about less and less? So anyway,
and of course, they're also very academic. And if you would like to know what we mean by that,
it's what the word means etymologically. So you can look that up. We have a lot of fun with that
as well, because, you know, we also like to bring up the level of hypocrisy. There's a thing about,
you know, people can choose, right? Their desires and their wills and their
personal preferences. And the hypocrisy involved in that is just astounding where, you know,
when they hire a carpenter to have a door installed, they want it to fit, or when they
go to buy shoes or something, they want it to fit. But when it comes to what words mean
and what things mean and where things come from, they don't want to know because it doesn't matter
if it fits. You see, well, okay, but in that
light analogy, if you go and look at the information purveyors, whether it's
mainstream or alternative, not some of them, but all of them, again, because if there was anyone
out there discussing what needed or should be discussed, we wouldn't be here. It is this part
of the country. It's mid-afternoon on what they call the pagan weekend, which, by the way, I
believe I'm reckoning around the 16th or 17th of the fourth month now lawfully. We could be doing
other things, but I don't know if this is a responsibility to mankind in any way or just
maybe saying it to clear one's own conscious. Nothing is being said out there that is of
relevance to what can be. And using the construction site as a metaphor, you see a carpenter that's
kind of bewildered and upset and you ask him, what's going on? And he says, well, I've cut this
board three times and it's still too short. Well, you know, maybe you should stop cutting it, right?
Now, what's going on is now some people say it's a distraction. It's fear-based stuff or this. I
think it's just really ignorance, but they're just accommodating, you know. Anyway,
the whole thing about distraction also, this has come up in several, let's say,
discussions in the past week, Seth. You know, people say, well, these are all distractions.
That's irrelevant. The reason is because if you're on the proper course,
distractions can be enabled, but you're still on that course. Like, for example, if you're an
airplane or a ship is going across the Atlantic Ocean, a storm might be categorized as a
distraction. So you go kind of around the storm, which, you know, and then you get back on course
to your destination. So people have brought up this past week in discussions that it's the
distractions that people have. And I had to disagree. And it took them a few minutes to
kind of land the thought on it because they're so used to hearing that, right?
If you know where you're going and you have a course of lawfulness, for example, or rules
and things that you know that you, or good references, the distractions are not relevant
because you correct the course, you see. And, you know, I've also discussed the concept, you know,
there's a lot of excuses. You know, one is just people are distracted. Well, no,
they don't have any course. They don't have any path. You know, the distractions come. So let
that sink in, folks. It's not the distractions. It's the lack of lawfulness. The other thing I
wanted to bring up is people I've heard often is, oh, it's fear. It's fear, man, fear. And they
want to give some personal fear experience. And that's irrelevant. Now, when you hear someone
saying, oh, it's all fear based, well, you have to define what's going on there. Now, fear is
being disabling. Yes, it can be if you lack skill in a matter. And if you are weak minded or weak
spirited, you are susceptible to general all types of fears. Like, I don't like to bring up
FDR, or Uncle Franklin, Roosevelt's horrible leader type thing. But nonetheless,
he said there is nothing to fear, but fear itself. So whenever you hear someone saying
people are distracted, and it's fear based, and that's the cause of their ills, you're speaking
to someone who is not thinking properly or clearly themselves. Again, I think I gave the example of
the distraction. If you are on a set course, expect the distractions you're on course. That
is not an excuse for why things are so off, not the distractions at all. The other thing would be
fear based, forget it. You know, for example, with fear, I keep giving the example, if you don't know
how to operate a dishrag or a mop, you're indefinitely afraid of a glass of milk spilling
over. Now if the milk spills over, you're terrified. But if someone in the room or near the presence of
that spilled milk knows how to operate a dishrag or a floor mop, you're going to say, it's okay, man,
you got it. Don't be afraid. So all of these things that are being discussed, I find to be
well, stupid, can we say that? How would you spell it? S-T-O-O-P-I-D. But anyway,
no one is paying attention. When I say no one, I mean statistically, and everyone has somehow
fallen statistically for these easy catchphrase, you know, out of the can expressions to make
excuses for the unaware. Boy, oh boy, I'll take a pause there for a moment. So if any,
any comments, if you're still there, or didn't know we were going to go down this direction,
but nonetheless. Yeah. You know, food, water, shelter, food, water, shelter, other people,
good food, you'll be more comfortable, you know, good, good drink, good water. You'll be healthier
and, you know, good company, you'll feel healthier. So those three things, those are
important. The rest of it is details. And yeah, well, well, also the details are important if
there's precision and accuracy and good source. You know, here's an example. You know, we've been
asked very often to do a show about water, which we will, but I think bringing it up a little bit
to set the stage here. Someone wrote in chat, I asked my buddy's 14 year old brainiac daughter
to explain the clouds and water being heavy to see her reaction. She will research it. I'm sure
you're not going to find it. Sorry. What's out in the, well, you, well, it's not going to be that,
that easy to discover. You see, no one is paying attention. And they, and what's got,
what's been gotten away with regarding that lack of discernment is astounding. And it's
socially at the point of no return, obviously. I mean, well, I should say that obviously, but
humanity at now is way, way past. In other words, if you made, humanity would have to make 100
steps in the opposite direction that they're, that they have been going just to get to zero.
Right. So they're not going to do that because they're still pursuing the wrong direction. But
the reason I brought this up is because, you know, if there's any water in the clouds, you know,
you know, millions of tons of water are dropped as in the form of rain over a city.
And is there any water where it wears like a cloud of sponge rings out, you know, is it,
is it like, you know, thousands of tanker ships, tanker loads of water up there,
you know, sorry, guys. Yeah, yeah. So anyway, I brought this up because yeah, she could research
it all she wants. And she'll just be spinning around what she needs to do, by the way,
is stand in the next time there is a storm stand in an area that's covered and observe what's
going on. And you will see the water being formed instantly under the clouds. I mean,
at a distance, you know, you will see it as it as you see it coming near you, but clear the mind.
The internet is subject to human input. That's all I have to say. Have you met
your average human lately? Anyway, so I don't know what's average. Yeah, you know,
why don't we look that up? Let's, let's give the people a little bit of a proclamation on
some etymology today. What do you think? Oh, I like words. Well, communication. Yeah.
You know, you know, can you please cut that board at 12 inches? Or I'd like a size 10 shoe,
you know, or I'd like, you know, a turkey sandwich. Right? Specifics, right?
Not broadcasting on UStream today, for anyone who is interested. Okay.
Could put in a pinch. Or Yeah, okay. It was inoperable this afternoon, for whatever reason.
Yes. Well, what's being said? Regardless, someone I mean, I think if we weren't being
heard, stop the signal. That's right. Can't stop the signal. Actually, we Yes, we do. I think we
mentioned and threatened to say that this sonic project is also limited. I believe this might
be the 11th episode, we might have about seven more to go. I'd like to keep it around the 18
number. And then we'll we might continue. Or we might just say this is enough for now. Let's do
another sonic project. I think things should be limited. This, this roteness about, you know,
going up and picking up the paper because you know, it's going to be there every day or a lot
of the shows that you see in mainstream and alternative just constantly being there just
finding out stuff to fill the talk about it. You know, folks, listen, you may you may not be like
that smart, right? But you know, when you tune in to stuff in media, it's filler. Yeah,
it's filler, they have to show up, they have a schedule. And they're just filling in the space.
So yeah, this is not what we're here for. So yeah, average, late 15th century,
financial loss incurred through damage to goods in transit. From French every which is damage to
ship and Italian every word from 12th century Mediterranean maritime trade. Compare Spanish
averia. Other Germanic forms also are from Romantic languages, which is of uncertain origin,
sometimes traced to Arabic. I don't I don't speak any Arabic. Our our area, our area, damaged
merchandise, meaning shifted to equal sharing of such lost by interested parties, transferred sense
of statement of a medial estimate is first recorded in 1735. So several hundred years after
it's first recorded, the mathematical extension is from 1755.
Wow, okay, so I don't know how we're gonna save that one. But I'll tell you,
I once saw a high school diploma from the 1700s or 1800s. And well, it wasn't called high school,
it was some kind of other training, but young person. And it said this, this vessel has been
launched, referring to the person. So I don't know. Yeah, so let's, let's, let's put that in
perspective. And now let's not cut that board too many times. Yeah, damaged merchandise.
That's Yeah, but that's also been used to refer to people. By the way, folks, we speak like regular
people do. You wouldn't believe how many times I've spoken to people who are public. And, you
know, in the background, you know, it's like, Oh, yeah, people are dumb, we have to dumb it down,
whatever, whatever, whatever, whatever. I'm like, screw that. You know, if they're dumb,
they have to know they're dumb, because maybe they'll do something about it. You know how people
say, for example, you know, yeah, people are dumb down, but it's never them, or never someone they
know, or love, right? Sorry, guys, you're on this planet. Bad shape. Nonetheless. But thanks,
Seth. Thanks for doing that. I think it was a pretty good expose. You know, it'd be interesting
to go through the entire etymological dictionary. I know. And find out the what are the most common
words that people use and see if the common usage or common definition is in stark contrast
to what it really means. Like, you know, the word nice, for example, right? Or now it's average,
and things like that. Or apology is another one I found people are confused.
Yeah, yeah. I once was on a call about someone made a biblical term was clearly erroneous,
like they mostly are. And I stated, I'm going to I'm going to defend and apologize what I just
for what I just said. And they were like, why would you defend and apologize? Well, I said,
well, it's just like saying I'm going to defend it. I'm going to defend it. And it went really
quiet when I put in the definition of apology. So it's interesting. Yeah. I mean, as people think
of saying you're sorry, or whatever. And that's just an expression of that's an abbreviated form
another form of the word sorrow. Yeah. Yeah. Right. Versus happy. Yeah. Yeah.
I find it to be very interesting, but maybe a quick glossary of rudimentary sifting through
of what maybe 50 words that are commonly used that would be in stark contrast to their common usage to
their meant definitions, let's say, I think that would be an interesting little thing, you know,
kind of like what the police, you know, the police are called, by the way, law enforcement, right?
They don't know any laws at all, by the way, that's pretty easy to discern, especially if you're
working law enforcement, you just sit back, take a deep breath, you heard what I just told you about
yourself. But anyway, if you meet anyone in law enforcement, they, they basically it's crowd
control. It's all the training they do. Policy enforcement. Yeah, yeah. But even officers,
police officers, the only extent of law they have, they have this little vest pocket thing,
it's like a couple of inches long by a couple of inches wide. And it's got all the regular
statutes and codes, you know, a couple of them, maybe a couple of dozen. And it's funny, you know,
how they, they go through it, you know, when they write up a ticket, you know, they cite it,
and then that's all they know. It's just like, you know, you can actually have a machine replace them,
which they did try, by the way, with the cameras, right, the red light speeding cameras,
was an attempt to show that how police or enforcement law enforcement can replace by
machines. And it would be done more efficiently, by the way, because it doesn't matter. But
nonetheless, this is this goes for most people, by the way, and in their quote, unquote jobs,
it is not difficult to replace them with machines. And the reason why I'm saying this is
when machines do things, well, it's something that's produced by a machine, it's usually
a lifeless meaning soulless, right? It doesn't breathe. It doesn't have anything flowing through
its veins. And usually the quality of the product that produces doesn't jive as well as something
that is made by a machine that has a soul which breathes and has blood flowing, flowing through
its veins. And for example, the ancients had machines, and they found out that the products
that were produced, did were not of quality. So they went back to training, or, you know,
maintain the training of people to make things right. But right now, the way people are making
things are of so low, such low quality that you might as well just replace them with machines,
because the quality would not be discerned. That's why I brought up the law enforcement,
they don't know any law, just just pick them out of a hat, for example, because I recently saw one,
had someone on the side of the road, and they pull out this little tiny vest pocket thing.
And they're like, paging through the three pages to write down some kind of a code. And I'm like,
you really don't know any laws, do you? No, they work for the attorney tickets are multiple choice
even. Yes, I have a number of them listed that they can just tick off. I've run the machines that I
operate. And when I'm at work, they can be considered to have a soul. A lot of them are
actually have a pneumatic element to them. One for one purpose. Yeah, that's a pseudo soul.
In other words, if you turn off the soul for a return off the pneumatics for a given amount of
time, it can be reanimated though, right? It doesn't, it doesn't. The machine will alarm out
and stop operating if you turn that, that part of them off. Okay, and then you can turn it on
and bring them back up. Interesting. And there's no decomposition when you turn off the pneumatics?
No, but there is, there's a change a lot of them have to warm up, like will not,
they operate different at the varying temperatures. And once everything becomes regular and
regular, relatively static, things will run smoother for longer periods of time and things
like that. I do a lot of repetitious steel cutting and just general metal cutting.
So what's interesting, even though you're immersed with the machines, you still are there to create
or bring or impart a discernment to the product. Even though machines might do 90% of it, it's
you are discerning whether the product, yeah, the quality of the product.
And the machines have to be maintained as well.
So, yeah. Yeah.
But yeah, it's just, I figured I would offer that up as an exception to the rule.
The definition of the soul, by the way, is pneumatic, P-N-E-U, whenever you see that
prefix is the soul. And, you know, I do, let's just give a little secret. There's,
I have people in Skype contacts and such that send contact requests over time. And these are
people that discuss things publicly and they're known as spiritual, you know, whatever, air quotes.
And I sometimes chide them by telling them to tune into the show and, you know, the uncommon sense.
And when we define soul and spirit, you know, these people supposedly that are guiding the
rest of the people on these, quote unquote, spiritual journeys are, they kind of freak out,
you know, because what we're doing is making accessible these definitions, which they
unwillingly, unwittingly as well, prefer to not be defined, right? Because then no one would
listen to what they're saying, which is garbage anyway. But nonetheless, we bring up the concept
of the education system, you know, kindergarten through 12th grade is 12,000 hours of education,
a little bit more than that, actually. And I have some people try to argue with me,
and they say, well, it's really around 9,000 or 10 and a half thousand, you know, because they
don't want to admit such a vast, astronomically high number of hours. I don't know if it's
astronomical, I'll be billions, but it's wasted on the individual, right? Because anyway, out of
those 12 years in school, how much time do they spend discussing things that you might find of
interest or in need while you're an adult or leave there, like, for example, instruction on how the
law or the legal system works? Zero. Or how about some medical practices, battlefield medicine,
you know, someone's going to fall, someone's going to get cut on what you know, on
you know, some some kind of unwanted physical condition might arise. Right? By the way,
when I say that the medical society is just what they're good at, is they've accumulated
3000 years of battlefield medicine, anything that's outside of dressing a wound or, you know,
some kind of what they call emergency medicine is useless, folks. And this is not a harsh
criticism. It's a mild one. How much out of 12,000 hours of education do they spend a day,
a week or a month even on how to perform basic battlefield medicine, or emergency medicine? None.
Right? So very little, I guess I attended public school for some of the educational process there.
And there, I learned some basic emergency first aid training, actually, in junior junior high,
a little bit in high school. So, you know, between the ages of, say, 12 and 15, I had some
was it comprehensive? Or was it was it something that you could use or do something you remember?
Was it practical? Very basic, like rescue breathing, cardiopulmonary resuscitation,
things like that. But, you know, what they what they call the Heimlich, things like that,
we were actually shown I don't know if that's, you know, how regular that is better. But that
was actually something useful. And I remember those classes very well, even so. Right,
practical stuff, right. In other words, they spend even 10 minutes in public school telling
you that everything legal is a presumption. No, no. So you're being pranked. In other words,
society has set up the pranksters. In other words, with the imbeciles on this planet,
have been pranked, and they don't know it. And the pranks go on, and go on and go on. So
part of what we're discussing, perhaps is, let's, let's pay attention a little bit,
and see, you know, what's interesting, you know, 12,000 hours of education is not maybe something
that's in the room with you right now, but something most people might have experienced.
And it's sad to say, you know, that much time was wasted, not wasted, but it was to put you
in a certain direction. So you'll never realize what, you know, conditioning, essentially,
that's, that's one way of summing it up. That's the end result is, yes. Yes. And the thing is,
you know, I bring up the concept of parents, which is touchy for many people,
because, you know, the subculture of what they call kids, right? It's a subculture, right? And
literally, it's it's beyond a subculture, because a kid is not even an offspring of a man or a
woman. At least I hope not. If it was, it would be in a freak show. If you know what I mean. But
kid is a baby goat. So from from the parental aspect, the parents are still insisting that
because I went through it, you have to go through it, meaning to the child. So we're talking about
a pretty sick bunch of people. I don't. Yeah. Yeah, you don't. But the majority do.
No, there's actually I have quite the opposite approach to that.
Yeah, but I do. But you wouldn't believe how much I hear about that.
Yeah, no, I can I can relate to it. I mean, I'm I know other people.
Yeah, they're like, well, because see, so so this is where you have this self perpetuating,
self consuming thing. This is where I say, you know, humanity is unrehabilitatible as a whole
at this point. So speaking of being unrehabilitatible, anybody even watching the
what's going on in the Middle East, it's kind of quiet. It's been quiet. But there's a lot going on.
You know, when we just discuss geopolitics, we tend to err towards what's coming because yes,
you should know the future. Not only can you know the future, but it's can be mandatory if
you're concerned about things. Right. For example, if you're baking a cake or washing a car or
anything that relies on results, you need to know the future or what you're looking for.
So, by the way, we've also mentioned, I think, more than once, Seth, that what people should
be looking for geopolitically is a Middle East Union being formed. Well, unlike the EU, but
nonetheless, a union or focus on that part of the world starting in the next decade in a big way.
And what's interesting about it being quiet, there is a lot of stuff going on there right now
regarding the Assyrians, not Syrians, Assyrians. So nonetheless, if anyone wants to do a little
bit of research on Assyrians in the past month or so, it's going to be pretty interesting,
especially what's going on in Iraq. Now, when I say Assyrians, what you should be looking at
are the geographic areas of what's presently known as the country of Iraq, what's presently known as
the country of Turkey and what's presently known as the country of Syria. Yes, we've discussed this
years ago and now they've been in the news quite often, but regardless of them being in the news,
watch those three geographic areas because amongst the three areas, Iraq, Syria and Turkey,
there will be a new emergence in the northern part of Iraq, taking some land from Syria and Turkey
as well to form what could be called the new Assyria or a land for the Assyrian people. It's
A-S-S-Y-R-I-A-N, not Syrian. Most people have never even heard of that,
but that is something to look for. What you're also going to be looking for
is focused on that part of the world but not limited to is the general mindset of the population
returning to things of the gods. Yes, plural. If anyone tells you they believe in God,
they don't know what they're talking about because there's no such thing. Yes, there's no such thing
as God. The term God... If asked for clarification, they might know what they're talking about. It's
just a poor way of saying it, I suppose. Yeah, it's a plural term. So, yeah.
Actually, we use it often. Sometimes we say God, right? But like you said, for clarification,
absolutely, there are gods. There are many, many, many, and there's a hierarchy there.
And it's an entire society, albeit, let's say, how would you say, unfamiliar to most?
I would say it's resembling ours, but very significantly different.
Yes. And as a matter of fact, this is a loose mirror image of that. So, that one came first,
right? Which is interesting. Yeah. So, the interesting thing, the reason I say they don't
know what they're talking about is because when you do press people that are, quote, unquote,
faithful, which is what we kind of titled the last broadcast is Beware of the Faithful,
is they don't want to even look at it. Right? It gets very scary. And it should be,
because this is a society or a reality that is formative. And formative things tend to be
scary. Yes, they are formative, meaning they come before and are providing source,
are the source. So, there's going to be an interest in discussion in those things,
albeit, it'll still be inaccurate, but there will be a focus on that.
And it also will show how invalid and ridiculous the current world religions are. And that's
another discussion which has been done many, many, many times, if you hear
the Greek and Seth discussing things. But yeah, so that is another thing to look at.
And another thing to look at is there will be a loss, obviously, what goes part and parcel with
these other two things is a loss of confidence in the entitled classes, your professionals or
experts, as we so-called defined. And I loosely said an expert might be someone who is learning
more and more about less and less. But if you actually look to see what they're learning less
and less about, or more and more about, that is, again, baseless. So, they have a lot of problems.
And I mean, entitled classes, people in the medical society, legal society, education society,
scientific society, we mentioned something, for example, people that consider themselves
scientists or praise the virtues of science, I first tell them that I don't think that current
affairs or the current state of science would withstand or can withstand its own scientific
methodology. Right? The same with the legal society, legal society will not be able to
withstand its own legal precepts if they were applied to them. The same with the education
society and the same with the medical society. If you apply the precepts that they allegedly
profess, or profane in this case, right? Professing to be a scientist would simply be
professing to know. So, it's not something I'd ever call myself. Generally, a musician, I guess.
Most of the people I tend to run into are more on the, I guess, what would be considered a creative
side of things. I don't find myself running into many people that refer to themselves as scientists.
Every once in a while, I'll run into a professor of some sort or another.
Yeah, and to profess is to speak on something. But yeah, when we say these terms, they link
directly to these subcultures or societies within society, right?
Absolutely.
You know, we won't actually, we're not going to point out, let's say, attorneys or judges or
police, when we speak about the legal society, because they are a small part of it. There is a
large fraction, I should say, of the regular society that supports them directly. You know,
if you ever walk into where these legal societies set up shops,
most of the people there are just common folk going to work doing something. Yeah. Yeah. So,
they're a part of that society. The same with the medical society, the same with the education
society. There's a lot of non-educationists or education type people that work in those societies
as well. I mean, all the way down to the janitor. Actually, you might learn more speaking to the
janitor. But nonetheless, there is going to be what you should expect in the future is less of
a focus on these so-called specialists and experts, simply because people are going to inquire
a little bit more on what they're doing. And they will find that what they're doing is a prank.
They're just pranksters. So, in general, not emphatically, absolutely, yes, that's all they do.
They give the appearance of what they advertise to be doing, whether it's the legal society,
the medical society, the educational society, what have you, religious society. They give
that appearance. But if you start looking at what they're doing, it's not based on anything.
So, well, at least it's a profane version or a profane aspect of what they're supposed to be.
Is it a widespread hidden cult of like Loki or Coyote?
It's prankster gods.
Oh, yeah. Oh, absolutely. They're prevalent.
They claim justice. That's the one most prevalently claimed in one of its varying forms.
That's cruelty. Yeah, that's the revival of the goddess religion, which is a very cruel
religion. And it's anti-gender. It's anti-male and anti-female. It wants to go after the...
She's very upset, by the way, the goddess religions. That's what I've gotten out of
from studying it for a decade or so. Very upset at the ultimate manifestation of a
spirit through material. And what's one of the emails we've gotten, by the way,
is what is the purpose of all this? And it's very simple. It is the highest form of creation
is for the gods to have had a spirit animated through material. We call it living things.
It's very simple. And again, it's been going on for a while. And one of the emails was...
I appreciate the emails, but when the people bring up stuff like
certain societies and pieces of pottery that have been dated 80,000 or 20,000 years ago,
get wrapped around the axle. None of that stuff is accurate. And I'm not going to discuss timing
and how old things are. But when you look at the actual manifestation of a spirit or a mind
through material with a soul that breathes, living things that are living, that is the highest form
of creation from the gods. And just go study what's been written about the gods, and you'll
see how they value it. But don't be distracted, let's say, about big numbers, just because it's
been going on for a long time and such. But the goddess religion wants to kind of break that up,
and it promotes the disengagement of polarity, opposite forces, opposite sexes,
to continue this manifestation. She's very upset about something, we don't know exactly what.
There's some inclination, maybe some hints here and there that were given, but not much. But the
purpose of the goddess religion is to basically put a stop to creation as it is semi-automatically
automated through conception, let's say. I guess conception would be a semi-automatic process,
like pollination of seeds, animals mating, people mating. I guess I call it kind of a
semi-automatic process. The purpose of the goddess religion is to disrupt that.
And that's what you see going on in politics right now with a lot of the agendas being put on. It has
nothing to do with people's rights. They don't care about your rights. No one cares about anyone's
rights. And there's all this talk about it, and it's just absurd. So they feel good when they say
they care about rights, but what the hell are rights anyway? What does that have to do with law?
So what I've discovered from looking at older law, let's say conventions, is that
when you're working with laws, you're working in harmony with the environment. But when
that harmony is transgressed, let's say, or the law is transgressed, or something goes wrong,
now you go under rights, right? Because now you have to be removed somehow and sequestered
somehow, because you're not functioning properly, and you go under rights now.
So people are asking for rights. I'm asking like, what did you do wrong that you have to function
under rights? In other words, rights are superseded by law, folks. But I know this is really out of
place and out of time almost to discuss this now, but I think it needs to be said.
Yeah, it's not being said anywhere else, so certainly.
Yeah, and we've gotten several suggestions. I don't know if you have that. Oh, hey,
Greg, you need to listen to this guy. He's saying stuff like you are, and I listen to it,
and it's not even close. And I'm like, oh, man. And it's not the joy of thinking that we don't
have to do a public speaking or what they call a show. And now I can go and go fishing or do other
things. It's not about that. It's just what's so sorry about that is when people refer other
things that are similar, is that how far off it is, it makes me realize that they're not listening
at all to what's being said anyway. You see, that's the tough part. But nonetheless, I know
that there's from communication through emails and electronic conventions, there's definitely a good
four or five people out on the planet right now that appreciate what's being done here.
They've recently learned how to make really good rice.
Yes, yes, and we might have about another five or 10 that are listening, and I think that's enough.
And we're going to go, this is, I guess, the first hour and we're going to go for a short break,
folks. And we will see you back in a few minutes. Greetings and welcome back to Uncommon Sense
with the Greek and Seth Michael on American Freedom Radio. And folks, American Freedom Radio
is listener supported, or was or should be. And go ahead and do the right thing, folks.
And if you will, they could use it. But nonetheless, this is Uncommon Sense with
the Greek and Seth Michael. So on the break, we said, I asked Seth what we're going to perhaps
title this. And he said, let's call it Coffee and Tea. And I think it's sort of appropriate.
Coffee Talk, perhaps, Tea Talk, or things like that.
Yeah, absolutely. We could talk about time a little bit and then call it Coffee Time.
Yeah, yeah. Now, the thing is, well, unlike the weather, you know, there was a saying, you know,
everyone's talking about the weather. When is someone going to do something about it? You really
can't do much about time other than record it. You see, time is just the recordation of events.
The funniest thing is when I hear this time travel, you know, what they actually, I believe,
are trying to say is traveling to past and future events. But time is just the recordation of events.
And I think that good records are proper. And they should be lawful. And the only lawful timekeeping
that I've ever been made aware of or have found is that the sun rules the day, the moon rules the
month. And the years get a little more complicated. But nonetheless, they still are planetary motions.
And because they're very accurate, like I stated earlier, today appears to be roughly the 17th of
the fourth month. Here, it might be the 16th and other parts. But most likely it is around that
time of the middle of the fourth month. Yes, I know it might sound strange. What are you smoking,
Greek? What are you drinking? Well, no, it's about being lawful. Now, I think we brought up and this
is one of the mainstays of any discussion of that might be called uncommon is here it comes. You're
ready. The calendar, the Gregorian calendar, also known affectionately as the Pope's work schedule
is not a timepiece. You can't keep time with it. Sorry. Maybe I'm not, but I should be. I didn't
make it up. But it is a work schedule for you guessed it, the papal subjects, period. That's
the truth. And yes, there are, there is truth of the matter. And there are still are people out there
in Basilica enough to think that they have their own truth, or this is your truth, or whatever
truth. That's very imbecilic, but it's very typical. The truth of the matter is the Gregorian calendar,
no matter how much they try to spice it, splice it or dice it into making any sense does not.
There's no such thing as a leap year. There's no such thing as what they are
purveying on everyone. But as Seth has said in the past, it works, doesn't it? If you're subject to
something, and that's the thing that you're subject to works for you, hey, who am I to get
in the way of your pursuit of happiness? It works better for some than others.
Well, it's not lawful. Like for example, today is what they call June 4 2016. Well, last year,
it's what they call a Saturday. Last year, let's just be one to be accurate. A little more of the
safe someone's listening. Let's go to June of we said it's June 4. So June of 2015. The fourth
was what they call a Thursday or a Thursday. Okay. You're ready. Let's go to what they call
2017. And June 4 is what they call a Sunday. So let me ask you, folks. Is June 4, a Thursday,
a Saturday or a Sunday? Or guess what? It's arbitrary. Right? But just like the money
being fiat. I don't care if it's fiat or as long as I go to the store and get something for it.
Right? This is your average human. I don't care if it's based on anything. Not I got the weekend
off. I don't care. Yep. That's why you're unrehabilitated. Anyway, time. I think we
just set the precept. But what's going on with that? It's people have no concept of how to
record it lawfully. What else can we say about it? It has interesting etymology.
Time does. All right. Let's give it to us, man. Old English for a limited space of time.
From Proto-Germanic. A source also of Old Norse time or proper time. Swedish an hour
from Proto-Indo-European. D-I-M-O-N. A suffix form of root da, which is to cut up or divide.
And then commends that you see the etymology of the word tide as well, because it's it relates
Old English. Point or portion of time. Due time. Period. Season. Feast day. Canicle hour.
From Proto-Germanic. The division of time. Also of Old Saxon tid. Dutch tid. Old High German zit.
German zeit for time. From Proto-Indo-European. D-T. Division or division of time. Suffix form
of the root. Same as time. So hold on for a second. So it's just various ways of saying it.
To divide and cut up. Okay. To divide and cut up. Gotcha. Yeah.
Okay. So. Yeah. So divide and cut up. But nothing about recordation of events.
Hmm. Interesting. Close enough. Yeah. Divide and cut up. The source also of Sanskrit dhati,
which is cuts and divides. So yeah, just.
Yeah. And by the way, by the way, when you brought up the Sanskrit or the Hindu culture
and all that, the peak of their culture was around 500 BC. So if you, all these morons out there
talking about, you know, it's 40,000 BC or it's the oldest writing and all this, it's,
yeah, it's just moronic, which is common, by the way. Yeah. I could hear stuff like that. So
do your research, folks. But nonetheless, Seth, would you say, I mean, how else would we talk
about time other than are you doing it lawfully or not? And, and then at that point, maybe bringing
up the contrast, the aspect of the Pope's work schedule is fine. But again, it brings up a lot
of questions when people are publicly making comments about the quote unquote, system or
systems on the earth, and they're professing malicious intent towards the Vatican and
you ask them what day it is and what they very quickly respond with is something on the Pope's
work schedule, which indirectly has them admit that they are papal subjects on one end,
but on the other end, they're bad mouthing the Pope. Yeah, the work schedule works just,
just as, you know, as a schedule for work. That's why we reference it as being such so often. It's,
you know, it works for a schedule, I guess, of mundane things, like building.
Well, it's interesting, as far as recording the celestial movement and things like that,
which is what has been used to, you know, record time, as long as the concept has been with us.
Let's go back to work for a second before you go on. Hold on. I'm gonna step on you for a minute.
Most of the ancient world had in lawful timekeeping to take the seventh day off.
So that has to do with work as well. So you're going to end up with having your day off,
roughly being on every quarter of the moon, where you would judge that or discern that time
as such. So lawful timekeeping is also being used for when to work and when to not work.
But and you're actually you're going to be doing it with the natural rhythm.
Think about that for a moment. You and I have discussed what they call the seventh day lawfully.
Mm hmm. It doesn't apply to this society. Nothing lawful applies to this society. They want rights.
Anyway, what do you say? You know, I mean, there's no you know, it seems like there's no one.
Here's the point is just digress for a second. Having a discussion about population of what
they call the United States of America or America. And, you know, how we bring up, you know,
and other things, but I'll tie it in with something else here in a minute.
So no one lives here anymore. They're all residents.
What's a resident? You know, temporary. I'm not saying that anyone's permanent.
It's kind of like if the future of mankind depends on his children, there is no future
because all the children have been turned into goats with what they say. But yeah,
the work schedule is also can be lawful. The seventh day. Typically, there's something called
the circadian rhythm, which is now just discussed on the 24 hour clock, you know, meaning light and
dark. But it was also there's studies inclusive on the moon phases, and it clearly showed that
metabolisms of living things tend to subside in different rhythms or different levels with each
moon phase. So that would be the seventh day of the week, which almost every culture has that
in it. So it can be. What's interesting is it can be also used on the lawful side.
So I stepped on you there. Do you have any more thoughts on the time aspect?
Kind of like on a roll? I wanted to just interject that before we lost the moment.
Another, you know, easily it's another easily access point of reference
that, you know, everyone has available to them. Anyone can walk. Well,
anyone most can walk out and, you know, see the moon and the stars and the sun and see that
the numbers associated with it are they don't it doesn't figure it doesn't work out.
They come out accurately. Right. And when it comes around the next time of year, it's the same day.
Not like the nonsense we just showed with this June, what they call June 4th,
Thursday, Saturday or Sunday. But no one's set up that way. But, you know, like,
there's there's old writings. Someone certainly referred to as prophetic that speak towards
times, you know, being manipulated and changed if they could be. And we've what we're witnessing
is sort of like a parody of of that happening, like a pseudo change of time, things like that,
because it's Tuesday because we say it's Tuesday. Right. Right. It's an apathy. It's a removal.
You know, it's just like, you know, the concept of a holiday is an appointed time or celebration.
And most people don't care. This is there was a I want to pull up, maybe do a brief audio.
There's a guy named Mark Dice. OK. And and he and it's very often that he'll show
going in public and asking your typical American something and how stupid they sound.
And when I show this to people like, well, that's edited out. It's only showing
the worst ones. You know, he could have interviewed a thousand people,
only two said something stupid. He'll play the stupid stuff. Right.
And I'm telling you, that's a good optimistic view, but it's quite the opposite.
There was a celebration on the those that have died in the military recently. Right. I think
they call it Memorial Day. And everyone that I spoke to, which was all of like three people
on that day outside of the normal, you know, just people chatting in public, they didn't care
about anything. I have a day off. That's all I care about. Right. How many times have you heard
that? So why is it a national? In other words, you're living in a society. Again, it's the
hypocrisy. If you say something about what it's based on, say, well, that's our system,
that's our society, that's how we do things. I don't care. But and if you bring up something
that is supposed to be of significance, oh, it doesn't matter. It's just a day off.
Okay. The purpose of a holiday or a feast day or an appointed day is something of importance.
So on one hand, the inhabitants of a certain area that incorporate traditions and cultures and
systems will vehemently defend on one hand, and on the other hand, totally wipe the floor
and throw away and trash the things that are supposedly held to be honorable and significant.
And I brought up the recent holiday. All of their holidays are like that, by the way.
They're, I think the American God wears a red suit. The one that they tell people on their
white beard and the children sit on his lap. He's the highest. He's the highest God, I think,
in the winter, isn't he? Santa Claus is their patron deity. And it might sound funny, you know,
everyone I heard once on a call say, well, as Christians, we're not so bad. We just lie to
our children. Someone said in public, right? Okay. Anyway, yeah. Morons, right? But that's normal.
You know, a moron is a compliment, by the way. If you're on this planet, take it as a compliment.
But yeah, even then, their highest God, I think, is Santa Claus. And even then,
I don't care. It's a day off. Or man, that day really stresses me out.
Aren't you honoring your God on that day? Anyway, it's kind of crazy.
Lots of bowing down to trees on that holiday.
Hmm. I like the Odin story there where he flew through the sky, was pulled by staghorn creatures,
and he knew what everyone did. And the way you worship Odin is by bowing down to a tree. That's
why trees are made of Odin. And Woden's Day, that's why they have their Bible studies on Woden's Day.
Every Woden's Day in the Bible Belt and the buckle of the Bible Belt. And it's Woden's Day.
Yeah, Odin. Yeah. Talk about... Anyway. Yeah, really, really bad shape.
But not as bad as it's going to be. So let's see if we could find Mark Dice Memorial Day.
This is... Is it Mark Dice? Let's see. Mark Dice. I'm unfamiliar.
He's a fellow that goes out in the public and it's called Memorial Day Morons. Americans
clueless about holiday and reason for it. Mark Dice. Here we go. Let's see if we can get something
going. What is Memorial Day? What started Memorial Day? What's the purpose of Memorial Day?
Do I have to do this? Yep. As an American, you have to do this. See? There you go. I don't think
so as an American. Okay. It's Memorial Day weekend. We sort of celebrate the repeal of
Don't Ask, Don't Tell that was preventing the gays from serving in the military.
What are you going to be doing to celebrate this weekend? I'm just visiting. So, you know,
I'm just going to enjoy this ocean and have a few drinks. That's about it. And appreciate the
inclusiveness of the LGBT community. I will. I love the LGBT community. Of course. For sure.
For Memorial Day. For sure. Awesome. I'm all about it. I'm all about it. Just getting people's
opinions. Yeah, of course. What is the purpose of Memorial Day? No clue. That's my answer. No
clue. No clue? Okay. For the soldiers. It's a memorial for the soldiers that fought in the wars.
For the ones who died. Yeah. Slap him upside the head. He got it. What is Memorial Day for?
For military. I'm pretty sure. What specifically? I can tell you. If I sat down and kind of...
What gets to you next? Is it Conan? No. I know it's military. I know I should know more about
it, but I don't right now. So I need to sit down and think about it. You definitely do. Yeah.
Okay, Zombie. Memorial Day weekend. It doesn't feel like it, but it will. Yeah. And we're just
kind of commemorating the freeing of the slaves and the end of the Civil War. Just checking to
get people's comments on what you're going to be doing this weekend. Just doing some drinking and
having fun. That's about it. That's all that matters, right? Yeah. Just enjoy yourself.
Okay. Thank you, Zombie. Memorial Day weekend, the time when we celebrate the signing of the
Declaration of Independence. Yes, yes. What are you going to be doing? Well, we were drinking,
but we just got an open container ticket, so... Well, okay. So water. Party on. All right.
Thank you. NASA has a big celebration every Memorial Day to commemorate Neil Armstrong,
the first man on the moon. Government's decided to cancel that Memorial Day celebration this year
at NASA. Is that the wisest thing to do? Or should we be commemorating Neil Armstrong
this Memorial Day? I think we've been commemorating him for long enough, so
we should save some money right now. Save some money this Memorial Day? Yeah. Maybe next year.
Maybe next year. Bring it back. Bring back the NASA celebration. Yeah. Okay. All right. Just
give people's opinions. All right. Thank you. Take it easy. Comments on... Anyway, get the point.
Yes. Yeah. This is common. This is not Memorial Day. This is everything that's going on. I don't
care if the money isn't based on anything, as long as I get something from the store.
Right. Now, there are beings that do care, and there is right and wrong, folks. And obviously,
it has escaped most people. And this is going to be one of the things that you will be looking for
in the future. It returned to, well, semi-sane approach. I would say that using that word
accurately. Semi-sane approach to acknowledging things that are right and wrong, acknowledging
the gods, acknowledging law form. And when I say the gods, not just some regular pantheon that you
might be familiar with as some form of mythology, but the actual true hierarchy that exists.
That's kind of scary to talk about publicly, by the way, as well, Seth.
Greek, how do you know about this hierarchy? Okay. That's an interesting point.
Well, I can imagine someone out there, because it's been brought up a couple of times over the
last hour and 15 minutes here. And I can imagine someone who's hearing it brought up for the first
time going, well, is this guy prescient? Is he psychic? Is he a seer? Right. Yeah. So...
Where's this idea, this concept, this information coming from?
To be clear upon examining anything, there's always a path that one goes down to examine it.
Unless it's like an instant download and you got it, right? There's an imparting of information or
being exposed to information that you might discern. And when you go down that path, there's
let's say a road, you get to a point where there's a fork in the road. Let's say the left hand says
this information is unvalidatable, not important, or it's irrelevant. And you should put it down.
The right hand or the right path of the road is that it is validatable, it's a good report,
and it should be looked into. So we can do this with any piece of information.
So when I went down and looked down this road to see what the ancients had written about the
spiritual world and the gods, I examined both sides. Is it bunk, left hand, or is it validatable?
And is it true? And fortunately, or unfortunately, it was true. In other words, it is a good report.
In other words, what I'm trying to say is if you have a discussion like this with a typical
modern contemporary person, the first thing that comes up in their mind is, oh, we're so modern.
They were primitive. They made stuff up. They were stupid. Right? Okay, so when we look at
what's been memorialized, is it a good report or not? And you will find some very good reports.
The only problem is now there is a level of discernment that is difficult to attain because
there is a level of awareness, or let's say education, that's required to look at these.
Let's say reports is very distant and removed from the current mindset. Right? Here's an example.
This, so how do you know? Well, if you, well, go back just to finish one thing up. The example I
wanted to give was just the time. You will not find the Gregorian work schedule in any of these
ancient texts. Right? And they still discuss, I've heard arguments, oh, Jesus was crucified on a
Thursday, or Sunday. It's like, oh, boy, you guys are, you need some help. You know, there's,
you know, what's the next thing? You know, they, Columbus sailed the ocean blue with GPS and an
iPhone. You know, out of place, out of time. So the problem here is that there are spiritual or
psychological need, need one say, hurdles or attachments that need to be abandoned or overcome
before one looks at this stuff. And when you find it, you will find that the report is good.
In other words, how, the question to ask there, Seth, perhaps, is how do you know
a good report is a good report? Or is it propaganda, or misinformation or disinformation?
That would be the more important question. Because then they would do service to going beyond
studying what the ancients wrote about the gods. And what's interesting about what the
ancients wrote about the gods, and many of them, it does state there's a cutoff period,
that there is no contact. It doesn't mean they're gone and not looking.
Kind of like when grandma baked a cake, don't open the oven, right? So the question here is
discernment. But you're not going to get discernment, when people are exposed to the
fact that the money is unlawful in fiat. And they're so I don't care, get something from the
store or what they believe that they should make their society better. Right? You hear a lot of
people that are patriotic or religious or concerned, we need to make society better.
Right? And then you bring up, you know, their society aspects of their society,
and how apathetic they are to it. So on one hand, they want to, we got to make the world a better
place. And on the in the same breath, I don't care what that means. I just got the day off. I don't
care. See, and that's, that's something very important as well. So how are you going to get
discernment? How is an individual that is based in that mindset, going to approach something and know
if it's a good report or not? And the answer is very quick, very swift and very sure they're not.
So how else can you respond? Judgment is bad.
The reason I'm speaking, right, we're not supposed to judge. Well, the reason I'm speaking to you
right now, same thing, right? Well, the reason I'm speaking to you right now here is because of a lot
of judgment. I was out in what they called an engine driven wagon, and I saw a red octagon that
allegedly had written stop on it. A couple of judgment calls, there are quite a few actually
I stopped, I looked left, I looked right, I looked again. And I kept making judgment calls.
And that's what I attribute to being here alive to do this show with you right now.
Yes, any sense? Yeah, knowing to, you know, halt at one of those red octagons. That's good. That's
good practical knowledge. Good judgment call there. Yeah. As in German meaning stop. Yeah.
There's a difference between, you know, judgment and condemnation. I don't recommend much
condemnation. But, you know, judgment is can come down to, you know, this works, or this doesn't
work, or that's correct. And this is incorrect. That's right. This is wrong, etc, etc, etc.
That's all judgment. And I believe that I say, I believe that saying that humanity is
unrehabilitatible and the things that they set their hope and faith in right now is a judgment
call. It is a very good judgment call. It is actually a very wise judgment call to see the
things that are put on society by themselves, by the way, right? There's no draconian
dictatorship that is pressing people to not inquire. Let's use that term inquiry. Look a
I don't have time. Right? Have you heard that before? Now, the case in that is when you're
the reality of it is you're born and you die and all you have is time in between.
Now, what they might mean by that is either I'm not managing the time enough to fit that in,
I can't see how it could be managed. Or I don't want to put any time into it. But saying that
you don't have time is another one of these moronic expressions. Right? So again, no matter
how you look at the current state of affairs, and again, the paramount one would be, let's say,
on the American society, is there right now in sort of a frenzy about an election,
which has nothing to do with them, by the way, unless you're an elector.
And maybe we'll recap that really quick voters vote electors elect folks. So if you're being
told to vote, you're being told to basically do nothing. Well, what they're doing is collecting
your signature. And that is monetized or as money. You don't know that in you probably will
never know that most people that no matter how simply you explain the money system, they kind
of give you the deer in the headlights look, you know, or the look of a look of a baby seal right
before it gets clubbed. You ever see the look of that face? There's a reason they pick up birth
certificates in an armored vehicle. Anything you could sign a bubblegum wrapper and a banker
will jump out of his limousine to pick it up and use it where most people would just view it as
garbage. So the interesting part here is that going back to the American aspect, there's a lot
of Americans in this movement, sort of alternative and mainstream to make the country better.
But if you start looking at the pieces that make up their culture, their traditions,
their economy, their daily lives, all you hear, I don't care. It doesn't matter.
And that's all you hear. Now, if you go to the, the Gustav LeBaron's crowd mentality, where the
idea has to be oversimplified for the crowd, the imbeciles of the crowd to accept it. That's what
they're following. Oh, we've got to make America great again. Or we need to get rid of Federal
Reserve. Yeah. Or we need better health care. Or, yeah, these are all oversimplified, dumb ideas
or dumbed down for the imbeciles. If you start to examine the subject matter, and not even a great
deal of minutiae specifics, but the general subject matter that is overtly and plainly
given that anyone can access, the typical moron will say, Oh, I don't care. I got a day off.
Oh, it doesn't matter. I go to the store and get what I want with it. Oh, everybody's got an
opinion. Or Oh, that's your opinion. Right? So if you do good science, and you look at the average
American, by the way, we'll just pick on that group. It's not even picking, it's just being
objective. They tend to have a general feeling to improve things or make things better, as a general
statement. And if you look at what they're discussing, as to be made better, the ideas are
so oversimplified and removed from their true character. And if you start looking and bringing
up the true character of these things, whether it's the economic system, the medical system,
legal system, their religious system, their patron gods, there's absolute resentment in
discussing it, or bewilderment. And it's, it's, it's bewildering to see. I mean, what the interesting
thing is, is, there's the only way to write to explain it is a lot of the terms that are brought
up is that it seems like they're censored cosmically. Right? Because these things are very
easy to explain. So there's a censorship that's not worldly. The other thing is they tend to be in a
in a waiting room status. Like they're always waiting for something to happen. Right? Like,
they don't understand how money works. They don't understand how this works, or they don't
understand how that works, but it doesn't matter. It'll sort itself out. You see, so that's why I
bring up the point that there's also the waiting room, it's as if they're in a waiting room, you
know, to be followed into the office to be anesthetized, so they could pull that tooth,
because if you don't numb that numb them out, you can't do the extraction, they'll be jumping all
over the chair, you know, and writhing and screaming. So there's an aspect of something
being discussed as the dumbing down. That period ended a long time ago. You're in the numbing down
is another way to expect it. Now they do speak, these imbeciles do have mouths that move and make
sounds. But it doesn't mean that they're not numb. So it's interesting. And I like to use the word
moron and imbecile. It's used very commonly, by the way, in Le Bon's writings and other people's
writings. No one is saying this publicly, because I guess no one's going to subscribe to their
website or watch their YouTubes. But that's not what we're here for. So nonetheless, what say you,
Jeff? Yeah, it's, you know, there's, I don't know, just commentary on the current state of,
I don't know what's being broadcast as being important, you know, with the
politics and whatnot. It's just, I kind of see myself as an outsider from all of that.
Yeah. And because and kind of taking that view on it, even if you don't consider yourself to be
like trying to take and look at all of that from the outside. Really, it's all garbage. I mean,
it's some people get very invested in it, you know, and think of it as a way for or a method for
bettering their lives or bettering the lives of others. It's a dummy look. Yeah, it's yeah,
it's a treadmill. It's a photograph on the wall you're running towards.
They feel better, like people have seen small little apartments in the cities, let's say,
and people feel like they're in good shape. And it's a little tiny place,
you could barely walk around and they have a treadmill and they use it to stay in shape.
And they put out this energy to, right, so they have they've been told that they have to dedicate
a certain amount of energy to it. And it's all put out into a treadmill, you know, a hamster wheel.
Yeah. And there's also a lot of people or enough people discussing
avarice or acrimony or things that are not positive against those that are in power.
And I'll tell you right now, thank the heavens that those that are complaining about those that
are in power are not in power. If that makes any sense. Yeah. Yeah. So, right. It's just Yeah,
it's just an interesting observation. So the whole the whole, the true nature of it is to set
yourself apart from it, right? If you're not sure, set yourself apart. If you get more surety by
looking at it and seeing that it's just dumb, for the dumb by the dumb. That's another reason to
set yourself apart from it. And also, there's a quality aspect, if the quality is so low, like,
for example, I think it was Henny Youngman said, I looked high and low for you, couldn't find you,
but I guess I didn't look low enough. When I look at what's being put out there by the mainstream
and alternative, both is a such low quality, that it cannot be entertained. If you know what I mean,
or considered because the quality of the information and the way it's presented,
and all that, as being what it is, as something that can be entertained, meaning to look at, I
guess, is unpalatable completely, at this point. So the only thing to do is set yourself apart. Now
be aware of it. It's not bad to tune in to see what's being discussed. You have to kind of want
to laugh. Otherwise, if you're living near a fire, it's good to keep an eye on it. You know? Yeah,
exactly. Yeah. But fortunately, knowing what's coming down the line,
there is no doom and gloom on a global level, as people think, at least next.
You can watch how they still spin their wheels in their uncertainty. The thing to
to what's interesting to observe, socially, mainstream and alternative, is the level of
uncertainty that they profess. And that on one hand, and on the other hand, they profess to be
information. Think about that for a moment. We've got good information. And on the other hand,
if you listen to what they're saying, nobody knows. If you listen to most of the broadcasts,
mainstream or alternative, oh yeah, we've got the goods. And when you listen to the content,
it's all maybe, what if, don't know, no one knows, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
in that context. They're like, wait a second, am I going insane? Because I thought I was getting
information. And all I hear is too many maybes. And I don't know. I mean, am I going crazy? Oh,
no. These people are crazy. Get it? It's okay. If you kind of sometimes get the feeling,
like there's too much insanity. That's not just a feeling. That's a pretty good objectifying of
reality right now. Insanity meaning not well. Unhealth. Yeah. Yes. Sanity. Sanitation. Saneness.
Good things. Yeah. I have been, by the way, applying a little bit more access to the mainstream.
It's actually quite a relief because, you know, I've been trying to,
if years ago fell in, oh, the internet's great, you know, alternative, you know,
there's no censorship, right? They don't need censorship. Right? But anyway, going back to the,
looking at what the mainstream has put out, at least it's better packaged. Right? They got high
production value, better polish. I mean, it's obviously dumb as could be, because they have to
that's guess what? You know, they have to accommodate their audience, but they are also
pretty much, you can go to any mainstream venue and start off with a question regarding the subject
that's being presented. And guess what? After the presentation is done, you're still wondering
what the hell is that question? Yeah, absolutely. Have you ever seen the movie?
Oh, now the title slips my, is a Mike judge movie.
Is it evolution? No, Idiocracy. Have you ever seen the movie Idiocracy?
Yes, that is a documentary. Yes. Okay. Yep. You've seen it. Certainly. Okay.
It's just when I mainstream television, what, you know, little I access or whatever,
what little I see is just every day, every day, it's closer and closer to being
nearly identical to what was presented in, in Idiocracy. So it's an entertaining movie,
frightening if you're watching it with open eyes, I suppose. But yeah, I would, I would suggest that
part of society, if not a good fraction of it is already deeply involved as such. Very much so.
And there's another fraction that is kind of neutral that can go either way. And then there's
a small, such a small group that can observe it as being that way. I think that's what I consider to
be an accurate explanation of the film Idiocracy. But the majority, I'd say 90% of the people are
in it right now. And they don't know it because it's a slight variation of it. It's not exactly
the same. And then a small group is kind of neutral, they could easily go either way.
Then there's such a small group that it's not even a group, a very small spattering that can
see that, you know. And you know where you illustrate that, by the way, the Idiocracy
is not by the common guy on the street, go to the legal society. And I mean, like, you know,
the universities, the Ivy Leagues, go to the medical society, you know, the universities,
again, and, and where they practice. Right, go to the scientists. And that's where you'll see it
the most, the Idiocracy. And don't be distracted by the terminology and the shop talk that they use.
The actual individuals in there are not. Well, you guessed it, right? I don't have to say it.
So it's pretty interesting. Someone wrote, you don't have to turn on the telly, just go any big
box store or mall scary. Well, where did those people come from? To go to the stores? Or did
they walk through a wormhole from another dimension? You know, they're living right
around. Where did they learn to behave in the manner in which they're behaving?
It's, it's the, it's the self consuming thing. The parents, I've said parents typically hate
their children. Now, what I mean by that's a strong statement that really rubs a lot of people
the wrong way. You know, the concept of watching a video with audio, right? Watch a family,
a typical American family, a videotape of their day. I'm not saying such a thing is available
without sound. Okay. And don't listen to what they're saying, watch what they're doing,
and how they treat each other, the body language, and all that. And if you tell me those are people
that love each other, you're not paying attention. Just watch them. It's interesting. Watch what they
do. Don't listen to what they say. If that makes any sense. It shouldn't make sense. Well, it should
make sense. But if it makes sense to you, you're going to be in a world of hurt, because you will
end up being an observer. I think we mentioned on the last get together, we're looking at spiritual
quality or mind quality. Ever notice some people that say my, my, my, I, I, I, my, my, my, my, yeah,
yeah, there's a level of, could it be that people that are more spiritually evolved to
say down the line or more aware of what's going on, speak more in the third person?
You know, I recently was possible. Yeah, it certainly is possible to watch. That's, that's
when I, when I say, when I brought up the point, watch what they do, not what they say. When you
pay attention to that, folks, you ever if you know anyone? Well, actually, I'm only addressing four
or five people here, by the way. If you around people that you're like, something like quality
issue with this person, you know, maybe like an idiocracy level kind of guy here, listen to what
they're saying. My car, my tire, my hand, my kid, my hair, my house, my attorney, my doctor, my
country. Yep, listen to that. And you're going to see a lot of my, my, my is Oh, my. Yeah. Yeah.
It's very interesting observation. So I'm just putting this out there publicly. And just for the
four people, the rest of the people coming across this thing and say, what the hell is this guy
talking about? doesn't make no sense. You know, my favorite is listening to discussion. Man,
I got busted. I had to go to my court case. The judge gave me five years. But I only did three
years. I'm so happy. This is the level of mentality going on. Well, it's your court case.
Guess what? You just took you got to pay the bill. All these things. You know, whenever you say my,
or I, you're taking liability. That's why when you tune in to the new idiot box, which is the
internet, they're always putting it on you. Click here to get my Yahoo, my Yahoo account, click here
to get your account. Really? They know that they're dragging you in. That if they get you to
say it's my my mine, or because it's yours, yours, yours, guess what? You get the bill.
Even though there's no evidence that any of this yours, legally or lawfully. But yet, that's what
comes out of your mouth. And now you're taking liability. So the pranksters keep going on
with clean hands. So you're being pranked. And you know, eventually, Seth, you know,
what happens is when we have these conversations, especially well, I don't put the
onus on you, when the Greek is really pushing these topics. You know, we've lost everyone,
pretty much. Most people are like, I don't like what he's saying. I find it offensive.
I don't agree. That's my favorite one. Oh, I think you're being generous. I'd say that happens
after about, you know, 3045 seconds of broadcasting. Yes. My favorite one, though, is the concordant
mentality. I don't agree. That makes it untrue. Two plus two equals four. We're not doing this
to be agreed with. Are we? No, never look for approval, folks. You'll always get in trouble
doing that. Looking for approval. But there's this other thing that I hear often, because
someone doesn't agree with a fact or something being said, it makes it untrue. Interesting.
That's your typical earthling surface dwelling earth inhabitant, folks.
You know, I think sometimes that the purpose of getting together and doing this publicly
like this is not for the people on this planet. You ever get that feeling? Anyway,
I don't know what you can do for these inhabitants anymore. There are plenty of observers out there.
There are. You're not going to meet too many of them, though. They're very rare. They're
spread out like salt. You know, like when you put salt on a plate, you want to get just one grain
in every bite. If you put a big lump in the middle of the plate and you put that in the mouth,
you spit it out. So they have to be spread out very, very thin. So nonetheless, it's
interesting. I think these things being said are beneficial to some. The responses we've been
getting are, I would say, atypical, meaning they're all very positive, but typical based on the subject
matter that we've discussed or brought up. And again, just to bring come around to a semi home
place here. There's a lot of talk about requesting doing a show on water. How do you think we should
do that, Seth? Because one part I mean, the shows are typically divided in first hour, second hour.
I'd say the first hour, water as it relates directly to, you know, to health,
you know, as far as, you know, drinking good water. And then the second half to how
much of, you know, much of this world operates. Yeah. Other than just, you know, taking it into
oneself. The reason I'm asking this publicly is perhaps to get some more feedback on how the
water show should go, because there's actually quite a bit that can be discussed about it. And
like you said, how it affects health might be one of the last things, actually. I might want to turn
that upside down on you. Okay. And I might want to discuss just what, how do we perceive water,
what it is. We don't really know, but we know what it's not. We know it's not H2O, right?
And things like that. And most people wonder, what did he just say? Yeah, well, if water is H2O
in the periodic table of elements is accurate. Why does a bucket of water weigh more than a
bucket of air? It shouldn't. And don't say because one's a liquid and one's a gas. It's irrelevant
we're talking about one molecule. So think about that for a minute. But basically what water is,
how it wants to perform in this environment, what keeps it in its best highest quality state,
and then perhaps applying it to health. In other words, what happens to the health of a being
when low quality materials and things are imparted to it versus high quality
is imparted to that being, right? Would be the simplest way to discern that aspect.
Again, I'm just going to suggest here, one of the emails that we've gotten was basically,
what is the importance of a, well, the comment was, I said sarcastically, water, you know,
well, I stated water should be at 39 degrees or four degrees Celsius in the dark in an
ovoid shaped container. That's why when people go to purchase water at the shops, it's always in a
clear container at room temperature with a flat bottom container, right, sarcastically. But what
was meant by a flat bottom, flat bottom meaning it is not ovoid. And that is, again, something
that mankind has been led into sort of turning material substances into geometric forms that are
not conducive for life. If you look at any time there is stagnant water in a natural condition,
it always takes on an ovoid shape in an organic body, whether it's the eye, the testicle,
the ovum, the kidney shape, or the organ shape, the egg of a body, many of the plants
have all ovoid shape, ovoid meaning circular, global, but one end is slightly more tapered
than the other of all kinds of shapes, you know, seeds, that's ovoid. Now the ancients had them for
us. And of course, they were primitive and stupid. That's why they couldn't make pots that stood up
on their own, right? They had a point at the bottom. So people would say, look how primitive
and stupid they are. They couldn't even make a pot that stands up on its own. They had a point
on the bottom and they had laid them in sandboxes because they knew the quality of whatever was put
into it was always kept up high and cool. So, and by the way, a lot of the things that we're
going to discuss will catch on to most people's ear, will be sweet in their mouth, but bitter in
their stomach, meaning, okay, Greek said, keeping water cool and in the dark raises its quality.
I've gotten you wouldn't know how many messages that say, that's true, it works every time.
But when it comes to seeking out a non-flat bottom or ovoid shape container,
you will know what I mean by the idea is sweet in your mouth and bitter in your stomach,
right? So the simplest way to do it, we've done on travel, long trips, we had to store some water
for a week once in the cool. And the typical top of the bottle was tapered, you know, where the neck
and the cap is, right? You know, it's not flat. And the bottom is flat. In other words, where the
cap on the container goes is typically more rounded and less flat than the bottom. What we
did is we made sure that all of the caps and the lids were tight. And we placed them upside down
in the cooler. Yes, they didn't want to stand up, just like the H&M 4s don't want to stand up
on their own. So you have to take some precaution, right? And we kind of neatly stack them on their
sides first and, you know, put some filler and towels and whatever bits in there to hold them
and then held them upside down in storage for a week. And believe it or not, the ones that were
in that shape or laying down or in that condition, the water tasted more vital and more energetic
than the ones were vertical with the normal flat bottom. So that is the easiest way. Now,
let's just sweeten the thing up a little bit. If you're seeking an amphora shaped,
non-flat bottom container, you will have a difficult time in this society because you're
so modern and advanced and knowledgeable. So just turn it upside down if it's got a lid on it,
folks. And we will probably consider doing the water soon and it will be very good.
Thanks again, everyone. And here's the music and
a little coffee and tea time with Seth and the Greeks. See you guys again soon.