Greetings once again and welcome to Uncommon Sense with The Greek and Seth Michael.
And you're listening to us on American Freedom Radio.
At AmericanFreedomRadio.com there is also a chat if you would like to participate in.
And perhaps there might be a Ustream going on as well.
You will find that at www.uncommonradio.com.
That would be the site that we probably would also call for use of contacting The Greek
and Seth for this current sonic project.
And yes, this is a sonic project that we bring to you, we meaning The Greek and Seth,
perhaps to discuss things that are uncommon which tend to be obvious in many cases.
You might notice we don't like to be pedantic or academic
or basically discuss things that are not attainable.
I think the easiest way to consider what we're saying is maybe the last thing that's left
for man to discover is the obvious, right?
What do you think, Seth?
I would agree.
And just for confirmation, we are broadcasting on Ustream as well.
Excellent.
Great.
Thank you.
So, Seth, what do you think about one of the things that we like to bring up are things
that are lawful or based on something or founded on something that are tangible versus this
fictional self-consuming lie that everyone seems to be engaged in.
When I say everyone, and I don't want to be dark about it, I mean pretty much everyone.
There's only a small handful of people on the planet that are left that are really willing
to pay attention to what's right in front of them and discuss it in a rational manner.
You know, the discussions that we like to bring forward are pretty much something
that is not really out of necessity but maybe a personal one
because they're not being said anywhere else or by anyone.
And I think they can be known and can be discussed to help perhaps, well, not necessarily help,
but necessarily maybe sonically present what can be presented that maybe should be presented
from an objective point of view, you know?
Yeah, absolutely.
The subject matter is certainly discussed in other forums and other venues.
But as far as how it is discussed, it's very uncommon.
And yeah, whether it's helpful or not is, I suppose, that can be argued one way or the other.
But that depends a lot upon your perspective, so.
Right.
And the thing is I found that there's a lot of discussions still going on about making the
world a better place or helping people.
People really don't want that.
And I'm not saying this from a point of view that I tend to want to deliver
because it's what I think.
It's because what can be observed.
There's a couple of sayings that say, you know, I want you to do well,
but I don't want you to do better than I'm doing, right, kind of thing.
That's what people think, you know?
Or in public speaking, I've seen when someone is doing a presentation,
if you look at the eyes of the audience, they're like,
when is this guy going to shut up and sit down so I can take the microphone
so people can hear what I have to say?
And what I've noticed, there's an old philosophical saying that said that a fool
has to say something, but the wise have something to say.
I get the feeling very often looking at media, all media, that people are coming on and showing
up and presenting shows or presenting projects, whether it's mainstream or alternative,
and it's filler.
Basically, they have to say something.
But basically, what they're saying is unfounded.
And you hear a lot of discussion on conspiracy theories, certain researches,
whether it's all the way from history, assassinations, all the way to 9-11,
going all the way to various forms of science and new aginess.
And I try to look up a lot of the stuff that's being brought up or seeing what it's based on.
And I just gotta.
And there's a lot of work being put in perhaps to present these things.
And there's an old saying that says perhaps a workman is worth his due or worth his wages.
But in this case, I think a parrot is worth a cracker because all I see is parroting.
You've heard one, you've heard them all in a way.
And it's very, very common in that way that it's just junk out there.
That's why we like to call it the dummy load,
which is like basically spending your time running on a treadmill.
Yes, the meter, the pedometer or odometer or whatever on the treadmill says you ran three miles.
But I'm telling you that you got dummy loaded.
You didn't go anywhere.
And that's exactly what's happening in all media right now.
And I mean all media with a capital L.
And yeah, so this is just one of the reasons why we tend to show up for this sonic project.
And all things come to an end.
Yes, this is a limited sonic project.
In other words, the title of Uncommon Sense will not be around forever and ever and ever
as people like to think or say, you know, that show's still around.
Well, you know, this is a limited sonic venture.
And one of the limitations is perhaps a numeric one.
I think this might be the ninth time we're coming together.
Who knows how many more we're going to do.
But I was kind of having some private discussions with the administrative side, you know, people who,
well, let's say people as in people, one that likes to help out behind the scenes.
And perhaps maybe rehashing a lot of the things that were brought
up on the last sonic project that was done on AFR.
And going over them, maybe filling in a little bit more information.
And one of the things which leads us to today's discussion, perhaps, Seth,
was there was discussion in the last sonic project of perhaps doing something
in quotes called a cooking show or food preparation or food or nutrition and things like that.
And there was a good reply.
And I kind of mentioned it briefly.
I don't know if you remember or the folks at AFR at the end
of the last program I mentioned I want to do something regarding food.
And interestingly enough, two days ago on Common Sense Radio, we got an email regarding that.
So what a better way to kind of underpin the thought, you know.
So might want to talk about something that might let the listener feel and actually
in practice have some more skill after the next hour and 50 minutes or so.
Because again, very often the dummy load doesn't leave you with a lot of anything to take away with.
You know, a lot of people listen to internet radio and mainstream radio
because it's background or they get emotionally excited.
Today we're going to try to do something that will perhaps leave the listener
with actually a little more skill.
Now if you're terrified of what's called cooking or not interested,
obviously you might clearly mark this as saying, well, I'm not interested in this subject matter.
But nonetheless, even if you're not interested, you might find it interesting.
Let's just suggest that.
So what do you think about that, Seth?
Are you ready to go on something like that?
You and I in private have shared various things about food preparation and food in general.
And what would you say up until now?
I mean, in private discussion, I think it might be worth bringing some
of it publicly is what I'm suggesting.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
Good food, good drink, good company.
If nothing else, those are certainly what I try to achieve personally.
Those are words of wisdom, folks, by the way.
Good food, good drink, good company.
Those things are important.
You want to survive?
Good food, good drink.
I was thinking about this the other day.
You know, being on alternative media, those of you that do listen to it often
or even occasionally are liable to hear, you know, survivalists.
There's a word for them.
What are the preppers?
They call them preppers.
And that's fine if that's what you want to do.
That's I mean, it's it's vanity, just like just about everything else is.
But at the same time, some of the things that come up a lot when in the concept
of that is, you know, food, clothing, shelter.
And I like to add people into those as far as necessities and honestly, clothing
and shelter, you combine into one because clothing is shelter.
But so it's food.
And if you consider, you know, water, good water as part of that.
So you've got food, shelter and people.
That's that's what's necessary to survive comfortably.
And the scary part about that, Seth, is some of when you say people, the thought,
even though albeit being dark, is that if you don't understand certain forms of meat,
you could be fed people and actually enjoy it and would not know that you were.
But anyway, that's what we'll get into that discussion, how scary that is.
And I want to also give a true account that someone who had a restaurant, what they had done
regarding that and how they got away with it.
And I took it to the next level for them and they didn't like it.
But it's the truth. So, yeah.
So what do you think?
I think getting into the food thing is really a big subject because we can discuss food prep
without actually discussing any direct food prep at all.
In other words, procedures or recipes, because there's an entire mindset that could be laid
down or considered just approaching the subject.
And maybe you want to get into the mindset a little bit, which would be, you know, there's
quality, there's types of food based on seasonality, which directly affect what's called
health and well-being or being able to adapt in one's to one's environment.
There's also, I guess, a level of in order to practice the art of cooking, there's a level
of equipment that might be required, right, to some extent.
And also discuss, you know, cooking versus non-cooking and all these other things.
These are just the mindsets.
And maybe just covering the first thing, which is perhaps, you know, people say you are
what you eat. I would suggest you are what you ate.
Right. So from that point of view, the suggestion and beyond suggestion, the
reality, the objective reality would be is if you were dropped here from a starship on
this planet, left for three days to take notes, you'd realize that there is a seasonality
on this planet that bears a different yield from the land, even from the animal crop,
let's say. All right.
Like a lot of the newborns are born in the spring on the animals and things like that.
So that bears on seasonality.
In other words, food is seasonal, like certain things grow at certain times of year based
on temperature and positioning and things like that.
And the suggestion and more than a suggestion that has been made is that could it be that
the from even just think about it from a biochemical or chemistry perspective, that what
you eat adjusts the body chemistry.
Right. And that holds true because if it didn't, people wouldn't take drugs.
Think about it for a moment.
Right. So what brings to mind the let your food be your medicine and your medicine, be your
food, which is not biblical, by the way, but it is a pretty good saying and it does rhyme
almost. Right.
Right. Interesting thing about biblical stuff, by the way, people, that's the book that
everyone loves to hate.
And yeah, I was just going to say that to me it brings to mind just the helpfulness of
food. And if you are in need of medicine, chances are you're just not eating.
Well, some properly right now, could it be again just that we've been kind of this
should almost be mentioned every time as a credo or get a T-shirt or hat.
Could it be that if you live in a warm climate and you eat food from a cold climate that
the food will adjust your body to the climate that it was grown in or harvested from?
I would suggest, yes.
And could it be if you lived in a cold climate or cold season, if you ate food that was
grown in the tropics, it would adjust your body to the tropics and you'd be pretty
miserable again, I would suggest.
Yes. Now, the interesting thing about this, Seth, I was having a discussion.
I've never I've never been met with any resistance on this concept, but I would like to
say that nine out of 10 people who try this find it to be successful.
Why not out of 10? Well, it's really 10 out of 10.
Well, why did I say nine out of 10?
Because there's one individual that I did run into and I did ask him how the eating
seasonally or eating cross latitude worked for him.
And he says, well, that doesn't work.
It didn't work for me. And I'm like, well, what did you do?
What did you change that you discovered it didn't work?
Your answer to the individual was, I didn't do any of it.
Yet they said it didn't work.
So this is a reaction that is super rational, of course, you know.
So I would say at that point, when you scratch that particular experience or comment or
feedback out, it's 10 out of 10, which is pretty good batting average.
So to continue with that thought just a little bit more, it's also a cross latitude
thing. There's an interesting thing that goes on that, you know, we've given many
examples where, let's say you're living in the northeast of the States here and you're
knee deep in snow and you have what's called a common cold and you are told that
vitamin C will help that.
The first thing you think about or remember is that you're also told that oranges have
vitamin C. You start drinking orange juice, which has grown in a warmer climate out of
season. And typically people do not get better because that orange will adjust your
body chemistry to the southern latitudes and vice versa.
I can I can personally attest to that.
That's when all growing up, you know, I was encouraged to start getting a head cold,
start feeling under the weather.
You need that vitamin C and get that vitamin C from that orange juice.
And so I would start getting stuffed up or whatever, you know, mucusy, I'll say.
And then I'd be like, oh, I'm starting to get sick.
My throat's a little bit irritated.
I'm going to I'm going to drink.
I'm going to go get a jug of orange juice, you know, the fresher, the better.
And I'm going to drink as much of it as I can stand.
And without fail, it would it would constantly make it worse.
I would become whatever symptoms I was I had at the time would just be
exasperated. And in a conversation with you and me, it's probably been nearly three
years ago. You suggested that was probably a bad plan that I'm paraphrasing.
Yeah, I stopped doing that and started concentrating more on just constantly
drinking, you know, as decent a quality of water as I can attain currently, which
right now is basically just out of the tap and then chilled.
I'm not not poured over ice, but actually kept chilled in the refrigerator in
glass. I'm fond of drinking out of glass, actually.
But it yeah, it's I've stopped.
I'm getting ahead of myself.
But yeah, the orange juice I can personally attest to.
If you're living in the States in the winter, don't don't drink orange juice.
Well, yeah, the thing is, you've got to realize that everything's based on
commerce. You could even look at the days that people acknowledge and celebrate.
They're all it's the god of commerce, let's say.
So, you know, it's a very powerful god, by the way, this particular one that forces
this notion that things have to be done for the sake of commerce.
So, you know, but the water is another thing.
And but, you know, just just to go it's actually another it's the same thing, really
water quality, which ties in with a lot of questions as regarding overall health.
You know, the mismanagement, mishandling and mistransporting of water is actually
one of the causes of the major ills and ailments in society.
Yes, it is. And that's a that's I think we should do a discussion on water alone
because there is no rational discussion on water on the Internet right now at all.
We could dedicate an entire an entire two hours or an entire season of broadcast to
water. I've very, very easily.
That's why I said, well, I'm kind of getting ahead of myself because I ran you off of
the. Oh, that's fine.
Yeah, the tropical and all that.
It also works inverse if you're living in a hot climate, let's say in the American
Southwest and during the summer and you enjoy salmon or tuna, which is typically
harvested from a cold climate, you will not be able to cool down.
You see that will adjust.
You know, that's why the concept of people have heard of the people that live up in
the very northern regions of the Earth tend to eat very fatty foods.
Right. People know that, you know, there's a high consumption of fat and animal
product will thicken the blood, let's say colloquially, and, you know, high consumption
of other things that grown in the tropics thin out the blood.
And so these are very simple, basic concepts which are discussed by no one.
When I mean no one statistically, I have never heard anyone discussing them, especially
on alternative media. Now, I have someone in the background that did tell me that there
is a particular quote unquote doctor that did suggest that.
And kudos to them.
Of course, there are people that know about this.
There's a concept known as macrobiotics, but that is really so centered on the Asian
aspect of doing things, again, kind of dogmatic that they also suggest eating locally
and somewhat seasonally.
So there is this notion and this was done consistently, by the way, before this
international commerce was imposed.
So, again, you know, we spend quite a bit of time discussing something that we always
discuss only because it's very, very, very, let's say, critical in comprehending you
are what you ate.
So I think the next thing that you mentioned, we can dedicate quite a bit of time just
discussing water.
And here's the thing.
This is what is not being discussed that is critical, folks, is that water likes to be
kept cool and in the dark to have a higher quality.
If you want to raise the quality of any water, cool it down and keep it out of light.
That's why all of the majority of the waters that you buy are in clear containers and at
room temperature. Right.
The opposite. Yeah.
And you have morons with a capital R discussing.
These are water discussions on alternative media and some mainstream.
And they never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever bring those two
simple points of raising the quality of water up.
They'll tell you all these fanciful stories about their experiences and what water is.
And I'm telling you, it is idiotic to the core.
All of them, not some of them.
And, you know, here's the thing.
The reason I'm saying this is because if they weren't, we would not be planning on
discussing water, would not be discussing water.
We'd simply break the chain and give you a link to where you could find the
information. But sorry, guys, if you it's not out there, no one is discussing it.
Now, what is out there is the works of Victor Schauberger, VIKTOR, S-C-H-A-U-B-E-R-G-E-R.
He was a naturalist and he did a lot of work.
Don't get wrapped around the axle with the UFOs and all the fancy machines.
Go and understand the concepts that he found out to be relevant.
So with that said about water, keep it cool and keep it in the dark and you will
raise its quality immediately.
Well, meaning overnight at least with because the more duration it has to a certain
point in the coolness and in the dark, the more it will mature to that higher quality
form. Because the other problem, the main problem with water is the way it's being
transported. It's through straight pipes and in square boxes or bottles with flat
bottoms. So that's going to be very difficult to overcome.
But, you know, so so those are the two major points that we kind of always bring up
is sort of something regarding water.
Well, regarding eating seasonally and then the water being something that needs to be
considered and perhaps do a dedicated time to it.
But what about food?
Let's get back to that. Now, we mentioned that there's many aspects to it, but the
general aspects are basically most food needs some preparation before it's consumed.
You know, even people that eat raw food tend to want to wash some of the dirt off, you
know, so there is some preparation there.
By the way, bringing up the concept of raw food, there is a lot of raw food discussion.
There was more, let's say, in the past somewhat.
This is the basic concept of raw food, and this is going to be a tall claim and you
might want to consider it.
Typically, the more active the being, the more raw food can be taken and the less
active, more sedentary the being, the more it should be cooked, let's say.
So if you look at all the wild animals that jump around and move around, tend to eat
raw food, they're fine.
If you're very active, for example, and by the way, just throw this in there.
Yes, raw food does retain more, quote unquote, nutrition and vitality because you're
actually eating something that's alive and transferring that life force to the body.
You know, you can't put a cooked carrot in water and have it continue to grow where a
raw carrot will.
But typically, if you're, again, the animals that eat raw food tend to be very
active. Animals that tend to be in creatures that tend to be less active tend to have
very strong secretions to almost pre-digest the food or dissolve it before they even
ingest it. But if you are, for example, a delivery driver, an athlete, a construction
worker, you get the point.
Even a orchestral conductor, you ever see how they move their arms for two hours?
Very active in that sense.
If you are an active individual, you will probably be quite happy and benefit much more
from raw food than someone who, let's say, has, quote unquote, an office job that is
sedentary or a truck driver who is sedentary.
Or so how you spend the level of activity that you pursue, whether it's high or low
should determine how much heat is applied to the food, because the heat just breaks
the food down and makes it more its constituents more readily available.
Give another example.
When someone isn't feeling well, they lose levity, they lose mobility.
They tend to be horizontal in a restful state.
Stews and soups are recommended, right?
Like chicken soup will make you feel better.
What doesn't have to be chicken soup?
It could be miso soup or vegetable soup.
It tends, you see, even like, you know, grandma suggests if you have a cold, you're not
feeling well, have a soup, right?
Some warm tea, something that has been broken down with heat, you see.
So that is the idea of the raw versus the cooked.
Let's say it's your level of activity.
Now, what happens if you're if you're sedentary?
And I've seen this from being around proponents of raw food and having discussions.
And I brought this up and one guy stood up and said, yes, yes, you know, I work at an
office job and I try the raw food thing and I was constantly gassy and I couldn't go to
the bathroom. And then other times I went to the bathroom too much.
I said, well, yeah, because the body is not properly, let's say, applying enough energy
to the raw food to break it into a state that you can use it.
And I was I was probably told to shut up about it because this was a these were raw food
proponents. They had things to sell.
So DVDs and books and things like that and also raw food.
So they didn't like what I had to say because it actually might have disturbed their
volume. But anyway, of sales.
So again, the commerce thing.
So the food prep just covered their idea of being raw or so there's there's a level
of prep and prior to prep is obtaining the food, you know, like, you know, there's a
talk now about organic versus GMO.
And the first thing I want to say is the body, most natural organisms, men and animal
and even plants are very robust.
They can take quite a bit of punishment and toxicity.
That's why most things still tend to thrive, even with poor quality food.
And yes, GMO foods, genetically modified organisms.
And there's a lot of discussion about GMOs and it's given in a way that I call it can
be called fear based and all fear is is designed to disable those that have weak mind
and have lack skill.
If you have a weak mind or a weak spirit and you lack skill, you are subject to fearful
communications. And I think we've given an analogy with how that works.
You know, if you lack, for example, skill in using a mop or a dish rag and milk falls
over, a glass of milk falls over, you are in terror.
But if you're next to someone who knows how to operate a dish rag or a mop, they'll tell
you it's OK. Don't be afraid.
It's just spilled milk.
We can take care of it.
So right now, it seems that the human culture, lack of a better term, has been sort of
modified itself into a state of a weak minded individuals that lack skill.
So you are subject to fearful, quote unquote, fearful type of communications.
But back to the GMOs regarding that, do a little bit of research.
What they're really doing is very crude.
You know, you guys, you guys know what a gene gun is.
I don't know if you ever heard of a gene gun.
They actually just inject vegetables and plants and fish and things with chemicals that
are attached to heavy metals because the heavy metal acts as a reflector, seeing how the
thing will modify and procreate.
So it's don't be don't be like, oh, mesmerized or these guys are so technically
advanced, man.
They're so like smart to be doing that.
Corn comes to mind anytime anyone brings up GMOs, specifically because currently I
think it's somewhere I'm pulling this out of the dark, but it's somewhere between 80
and 90 percent of the corn that's grown in the US for human consumption is genetically
modified. Probably more of the world.
But it's currently between.
Yeah, it's the difference between, you know, three heads of or three ears of corn per
stock and five years of corn per stock.
But, you know, here's the thing, you know, it's kind of like what came first, the
chicken or the egg, it's the chicken farmer, because when you say chicken, you kind
of get an idea of what a chicken looks like.
But before the chicken farmer, you know, before they were domesticated, there was a
tremendous variety of chicken.
The same with corn. Corn is a type of Bermuda grass, I believe.
Don't hold me to it. That was genetically modified, just like, for example, almost
all of your leafy green vegetables are genetically modified forms of cabbage that
have been begun thousands of years ago by crossing, cross pollinating.
Cross pollination is another way to genetically modify, just like a mule, a horse
and a donkey is a cross pollination.
And they tend to be sterile when you cross pollinate things in a very abrupt way.
But essentially what I wanted to mention, there's a targeted audience out there about
being terrorized about GMOs in the alternative media.
And there's also obviously the terrorism, the bio-terrorism that's being done by the
guys in white lab coats and certain agencies on the people, you know, because the
form of terror is to inflict fear and I guess terror.
So so there's a misunderstanding that there's there's genetically modifying genome,
meaning, you know, the hereditary of something.
There's been grafting of trees and plants for since time immemorial.
There's been cross pollination since time immemorial.
But the reason I brought up the gene gun is they have this really rudimentary thing
now where they actually just sit around all day, thousands of experiments of injecting
various things that are targeted.
Let's say, you know, what's on the plan to modify with various strains.
They call it DNA, but it's really just mitochondria, toxins, dead stuff.
And to see how if they could, through trial and error, get plants and things to change
the way they work.
It's very simple. It's very simple.
Like there's things called phthalates, P-T-H-A-L-A-T-E-S, phthalates.
It's with a P-T-H.
That's a plasticizer that's used in a lot of plastics.
And it's an estrogen mimicker.
So you have, you know, eight, nine year old girls going through menstruation and young
men growing breasts and other problems with organs because there is an abundance of this
estrogen mimicry through phthalates, you know, BPAs also, things like that.
So there's more to genetic modifying, which means to modify the heredity of something
than meets the eye and how it's been purported in the idiotic alternative media.
Yes, I did say that.
So anyway, I wanted to bring that up in the prep because gaining access to your food.
And by the way, another comment on society would be this thing about organic food.
That is the most ridiculous thing I have ever seen from a social perspective, meaning
social tolerance, because what is being said there, not in protest, but just an
observation, is why would a society at large allow their food stock or foodstuff to be
separated as foodstuff that is toxic and other foodstuff that is not, meaning organic?
What kind of a sick bunch of individuals would exist that would allow that to happen to
their foodstuff? We're talking about a sick society here that you would actually allow
your food to be divided as organic and non-organic.
That is a sick group of people, if you ask me, because all food should be organic.
It should not. See, if you're so you've allowed you've allowed people have allowed all
seven billion of you, yes, have allowed your foodstuff to be divided into toxic and
non-toxic. And it's OK.
You know what? Pretty much everything else you've allowed is very toxic to you.
But anyway, that's another subject again.
So why turn every show into a rant, you know?
So the genetic modification aspect is to be considered simply that it is low quality.
And just like anything that is low quality can be damaging, like certain low quality
fuels can damage a certain engine and so on and so forth.
Right. So it's just view it as low quality.
Don't be in terror of it.
The more you study what genetically modified foods are, you will realize the real
reality of what it means to be on this planet with seven billion imbeciles.
Yes, I said it again. So, yes, to move on from that.
Yes. So it's just, yeah, mind boggling what's being allowed.
The food prep. Yeah. So gaining your food.
Let's not really go into part about growing food.
But, you know, when you acquire your food, try to always get the best quality.
Well, duh. You know, there's there's something else that's considered, you know, I want to
talk about, you know, so we're going to leave some notions that will actually people
skilled. We'll talk about certain things, you know, how to prepare certain grains and
veg and meats and things like that.
Let's say if you tend to want to eat meat, let's say.
But always get the best quality that you can.
And there's another thing about the bioterrorism that's put on you by the
establishment is this thing that certain meats have deadly bacteria.
Right. Like you have to cook it to death to get rid of these these buggers, you know,
that are on there. Actually, the buggers are the ones telling you that.
But whenever you hear of meats being tainted with various salmonella and pathogens
and things like that, that's because it is of low quality.
Commercial farms tend to jam animals together and they're standing in food and feces
just like you. If you stood in your own fecal matter while you were eating your dinner
every day, you will be one sick puppy.
Yes, you will. So whenever you hear about warnings of salmonella and this and that on
your meat, for example, on the meat you might want to purchase and consume, that means it
is a very low quality and it is dirty, folks.
Yes, it has nothing to do with this naturally occurring.
It is a condition that is induced based on the way these things, you know, animal
husbandry. They're actually now terrorizing people, telling them that there's deadly
bacteria on veg.
Yes. If you're transporting veg and certain inert gases so they don't go bad and
whatever, whatever.
Yes, things will get kind of dirty.
So learn how to clean stuff, wash things.
Water is your best friend in this.
But again, on the food prep, high quality and look for the highest quality and don't be
a victim of this terrorism, this bioterrorism, mental bioterrorism about GMOs and
things being full of bacteria and such.
Just learn that you must seek the highest quality if you are looking for something
good. That sounds pretty obvious.
Highest quality. What's some easy what's what's what's easy ways to spot high
quality? It's getting harder and harder and harder.
Like, for example, with the veg, it seems like it's almost impossible to know, you
know, whether it was grown properly or or engineered somehow.
The sniff test, the site test is best.
Right. You look at it if it looks good.
And then there's a sniffing test.
Right. And then there's the touching test.
You know, there's a feeling that people have about certain things.
Also, you might want to go by that.
But actually, meeting your average surface-dwelling earth inhabitant lately, I don't
know if they have any proper feelings anymore.
But yeah, it would be if you ever remember some older people growing up when parents
or others, older people used to go and purchase melons or something, they would actually
sniff the melon. Right.
And the one with the most. Right.
Or yeah. So if it smells like a melon, you know, if it doesn't smell like a melon and it
looks like a melon, chances are the flavor won't be there.
And, you know, you won't get what a melon should be giving you.
So either way, another way of looking at quality is, is it in a situation that would
promote decay versus not?
Right. Like things shrink wrapped in plastic.
That's an anaerobic environment, guys.
You know, anaerobic bacteria tend to be nasty and a lot of things are now wrapped in
plastic. I think it was Brave New World.
One of the comments in there was, oh, no, these people are eating food and it doesn't
come out of plastic, you know.
So if you can avoid things that are wrapped in plastic.
Oh, wow. You know, that just, you know, how that's pretty difficult, believe it or not.
These days, there's a lot of things that are added.
I'm not going to be adamant about this, but let's just say when you look at ingredient
lists on foods, that is what's added to the food.
Things can be added to the package that you that don't have to be listed on the
ingredients, by the way, like fungicides and bactericides, by the way, can be added to
the packaging. But because during the mechanical process, it's not added to the food,
it's added to the package.
It does. They don't have to tell you.
Interesting. So looking for things that are not shrink wrapped too much is really one
way to start. I've even seen veg like cucumber shrink wrapped these days.
So, oh, yeah, you can buy individual potatoes and things like that that are shrink
wrapped in plastic.
And it's not that it's plastic, it's that it is in an anaerobic environment.
There's no breathing. Everything breathes, you know.
And typically, you know, a lot of on the meat side, you'll notice that if you were to
purchase meat, you know, they add blood and things and water even tells you that may
contain up to 10 percent by weight in water.
It's all commercial again.
If you do, let's say, get something that's wrapped in plastic, which is probably going
to be the the chance, get it out of the plastic as soon as possible and rinse it and
wash it and then store it properly, you know, in a dark, cool place.
Cheese is what immediately comes to mind.
Something that I purchase a lot of that does come wrapped in plastic.
Yes. Get it out of the plant.
You know, there's in high end cheese places, there's a job, let's say a job or a job
within the place.
By the way, no difference in a job and a job.
A job probably has, you know, sick days and workman's compensation where a job doesn't
have sick days or workman's compensation.
But anyway, yeah, it's cheese places.
They have someone called a cheese wrapper every day.
They change the wrapping on the cheeses so the culture does not develop beyond what is
garnered as the flavor of the cheese.
Yes, because cheese is based on its culture, unlike many countries these days.
But so, yeah, so yeah.
So, yeah, that's interesting.
You get it out of the package and do it and also change the packaging and the wrapping.
You know, if you do have veg, there's something used to be called a root cellar.
You could store veg in a cool, dry place, meaning cool that it stays cool.
And dark as well.
You can also practice by having veg in what they call the fridge in water.
If you do buy bunches of parsley or other things like that and you want to keep them
growing, there's nothing wrong with putting them in water, just as you would a vase with
flowers. Right.
Any kind of cutting can be kept alive in water.
So the food prep part is, you know, again, use your discretion.
As long as it's clean and fresh, you will have high quality and, you know, all things
about GMO put aside, study the GMO stuff, folks.
Don't be subject to the terrorism from the alternative in the mainstream regarding GMO.
It's been going on for thousands of years.
It's just that the level of how it's going on now is malicious, just like everything
else. You know, whether it's religious, scientific, judicial, political, religious,
what have you, education, you are surrounded by pranksters.
Yes. One third of the people on this planet are straight up pranksters.
The other third are supporting them being a milli, and the other third are just waiting
to be pranked, you know, or joining the pranksters.
You know, in the next decade or so, I'd say 90 percent of the people are going to be
pranksters. So anyway, you know, this I'm a brief aside, but talking about media and
stuff like this, I've heard that explained on a on a horrible television program in the
last couple of years. But it stuck with me because it was this guy sold a whole bunch
of people. These I don't even remember what it was, but it's something that would have
been easily available from, let's say, the things that are advertised predominantly in
alternative media, alternative broadcasts and things like that.
And he he did this, but he did it on a much larger scale.
And when it became obvious that what he was selling was completely and totally useless,
they were like, I don't why why did you do that?
And he just explains to me like, well, there's there's two kinds of people.
There's doopers and there's doopees.
I'm a dooper and you are doopees.
And so, yeah, it's just a very there are.
Yeah. Or like, let's go down the path for a moment.
We've got to get back to the topic as time is going.
But there's two kinds of people, those who want to be left alone and those who won't
leave them alone. And then there's three kinds of people, those who can count and those
who can't. But anyway, absolutely.
So, yeah, so the food prep is interesting.
Now, let's just jump around a little bit.
You know, I don't have any agenda or notes on this.
I'm just going off that, you know, I'm I'm I'm taking a few notes so that we can
kind of maybe provide a summation at the end.
But, yeah, let's let's bring up on the food prep, too.
There's something called a knife, cuchillo in Spanish, right?
Machete in Greek. So these things tend to separate and make things into smaller pieces.
I have yet to go into anyone's home, what they call a home, let's say, and find a proper
knife. Knives have to be knives, have to be very sharp, folks, because
the sharper they are, the the easier it is to cut and safer it is to cut.
And always try to learn how to keep a sharp knife.
And the idea of having a serrated knife because it doesn't need sharpening will ruin a
cutting board. You'll get all those grooves.
You'll get a fuzzy cutting board.
Right. So if you want to learn about knife skills or good knives, that that would be a
good suggestion. Yeah, knives should make the whole process more pleasant as well.
Yes. Yes. And there and by the way, there are almost no commercial knives available
that have a proper edge on them.
Even if you were to go out and spend a hundred bucks on a kitchen knife, a chef's knife
or a santoku, which is more of like the blunt end, it doesn't have the point on it.
It's a Japanese variety, which means like three cuts, I think, santoku.
None of them really. They seem sharp out of the box, but they don't really have a proper
edge. So you're going to have to on your own learn how to put an edge on a knife.
And this was actually a pastime in many ways in the past because the having sharp
knives was important.
And not anymore. Well, it sort of is.
But you're being marketed things that promote laziness and lack of skill.
So learn how to adopt a good knife and a good cutting board and keep everything clean
and never put a knife in a dishwasher.
That will dull it out. Even if you isolate it for some reason, it's one of these
phenomenal things that water can do when it's done a certain way.
So sharp knives and good cutting boards, you know, kind of went over the general food
prep, you know, there, but not enough perhaps for someone to change what they're
doing. But maybe consider that, you know, food prep is about being high
quality, keeping it clean, getting it out of plastic.
Don't stress the genetically modified stuff too much.
You're robust enough to handle it.
Yes, it is pretty toxic, by the way.
But again, I'm saying you are robust enough to handle it.
You're not going to put anything out in the market that is going to have you drop
dead like a fly immediately.
It'll probably kill you slowly, but so are many other things.
So don't be too stressed about genetically modified stuff, even though it is to be
avoided. So it might sound kind of duplistic to say that, but this is, you know,
welcome to planet Earth, folks.
You do know you're on planet Earth, right?
You know what's going on here.
So the concept of meats having strong bacterias and salmonellas and eggs and
chickens and E. coli and all that stuff is simply because it is garnered from an
unclean source.
So this is the reality that you live in, folks.
But yeah, and the concept also of raw versus cooked.
Yes, there's always more nutrition to be garnered from raw food because it is still
alive. But if you are not very active, you will find yourself perhaps more comfortable
eating foods that are slightly cooked.
So those are like some of the basic things to consider that are not being discussed at
least at least directly.
But we've got about 15 minutes or less for this first segment of the show.
We might want to get into perhaps prepping certain things.
And there are two things that I wanted to discuss the prep of and let's say more on
the vegetarian side, which would be perhaps grains and starches, maybe potatoes and rice
or things like that tend to be something very common, very, let's say, applicable when
you think of food.
Common and inexpensive and relatively easy to acquire.
Yes. And perhaps maybe a simple flatbread concept, but maybe we'll cover the grains
first. What do you think, Seth?
How to make rice, a perfect rice, pretty much, which is fascinating because to me, how
little information is put out there.
But just before getting into it, I've seen something called converted rice, various
modified rices.
So the rice doesn't become a starchy lump and you have individual grains and things
like that. So that shows me that there's a lack of skill out there and on how to
prepare it. And yes, even in the Asian cultures, unless you're getting a good, high
quality sushi preparation, I found that even most of the Asian cultures, which pride
themselves as rice being a staple of their diet, it is this white, tasteless, lumpy,
sticky starch, typically, not always.
So, yeah, this would also we're going to give some suggestions that will even trump most
of the situations that you find in eating out as well.
How to make perfect rice, generally, if you're going to make rice at all.
Why not? So we'll get into it.
One of the simplest ways to approach it is if before you start to prepare the rice, when
I say rice, I mean, typically this would be a stripped grain or a white rice, like a
long or medium grain, a very short grain, which would be a sweet rice or a pearl rice
requires a slightly different preparation.
Something like a whole rice or a brown rice requires just a lot more cooking time.
So this this suggestion will be mostly for your average medium to long grain rice that
is cooked by most people and essentially will describe how to simply cook it and then
variations thereof. So here we go.
We said we, you know, let's we threatened perhaps giving some information about help
people and give them some more skill.
So here we go, guys and gals, before you start cooking your rice, depending on how much
you're going to make, you're going to decide what volume of rice you're going to make.
So you're going to measure out a given measurement of dry rice.
And when you measure out the rice dry, whatever form you measure, the cup or liters or
whatever, note where that measurement is and put it aside and remember how much dry
rice you measured out.
Now, what you're going to do, the first step would be to wash the rice.
What you do is simply either put it in the pot or mostly recommend it is in a strainer
or a colander that is fine enough or is fine enough screen or a hole that the rice won't
fall through. Most people tend to have a like a window screen type mesh strainer.
You know, when I say window screen, meaning that fine or you can just put it in the pot of
the rice. And what you do is you add water and if it's in a pot and dump the water out
without dumping the rice out and do it two or three times.
If you have it in the strainer, you could put the strainer in the pot, fill the pot with
water and dunk it once or twice and then give it a slight rinse.
Now, once you do this basic rinsing of the rice where you remove the water once, twice,
three times, let's say at least twice, you want the rice to sit dry.
In other words, remove as much of the water as possible.
That's why the strainer works best.
Have it strained and let it sit after it has been rinsed in a drying or draining condition
for at least 10 minutes.
Right. Yes, I know how people everyone's got their own way of making rice, but this is
the suggestion. So once you rinse the rice, drain it and let it sit for at least 10
minutes. OK, minimum.
Then what you will do is you now you approach the cooking part.
Typically, you would place the rice back in the pot if it's already in the pot because
you didn't have a strainer and you have it tilted or an angled or drained as much as
possible. Place the pot over some heat and turn the heat on medium.
And start applying, I suggest when you're doing a Western dish to add some kind of fat,
you know, oil, butter, something like that, olive oil, a little bit, a little bit of
sesame oil, perhaps, or butter to the rice itself and maybe some salt to taste.
Less than a pinch, a little bit or more, depending on the salt that you have.
And stir the rice around over the medium heat for about 30 seconds to a minute until you
hear a little bit of a sizzling sound or just, you know, that the water is going up in
temperature. And then what you would do is you would add the volume of rice that you
measured out dry, equal volume in water to that rice, right, and turn the pot up a
little bit until you see the edge of the pot rolling slightly now, meaning a rolling
simmer on the outer edge, not the entire pot of rice, and then apply a cover to it.
Now, I didn't mention that before you started this, you must have a pot that has a
airtight cover or a very firm cover, not a loose cover.
If you don't have one, you can always use another pot over it that would, that the
bottom of the pot would breach the top of the lower pot to form a good seal, right.
And if you don't have even that, you could wrap a towel, a dish towel or a wet dish
towel over something to cover it and weigh it down and make sure that the towel is out
of the way of the fire.
And at that point, you would lower the rice to the lowest possible setting.
If you notice any overboiling at that point, even when it's covered at the lowest
setting, turn off the heat until the overboiling stops, meaning like steam or liquid
coming off the side between the pot and the lid, wait about a minute or two and then turn
it back on low.
And in this case, you might have to stand around while it's cooking.
And I've also been asked, why do I stand around and monitor food while I'm cooking?
And I said, because you're supposed to.
So at this point here, you're going to have the rice cook for at least 10 to 13
minutes. And you're going to have to manage your heat, have it on the lowest heat.
Now, the lowest heat in some of these electric ranges is so low that it's a warm
setting and it will not cook.
So you're going to require a slight simmer for at least half of that 10 to 13 minutes
and you will see some steam.
Now, this is just for your basic rice now.
So again, just to recap, you need a pot with a lid that is sealed pretty well, not a
pressure cooker per se, but a good lid.
You rinse the rice, let it stand for about 10 minutes and then you apply some heat to
the rice in a dry pot with some fat of some sort.
And I say fat, meaning an oil of some sort that you prefer.
Olive oil has a very low boiling point and goes rancid at low heat.
But because this is going to be a very short cook alone with the rice and it's not
just olive oil being cooked, that's a good suggestion.
Or sesame oil is a higher form of heat and maybe some butter, however you want to
taste. And you will be then adding the equal amount of rice, dry rice volume to the
pot in water.
Now, you could substitute the water with a broth or a stock if you want more of a
flavored rice, depending on the dish.
And then you would actually bring it to a rolling simmer where you see a rolling
simmer on the outer edge of the pot.
Put your lid on or you can initially have the lid on if you know what's going on in
there. Somehow with a medium flame, if you see some steam, you can start off with the
lid from the beginning and you cook that rice for 10 to 13 minutes.
And after that 10 or 13 minutes, you turn it off and you let it stand for 10 minutes
or so. Then you would remove the lid and bring a fork to the inside of the pot from
the outer edge of the inside of the pot all the way down to the bottom and gently move
towards the center, lifting some of the rice.
Just to give you an idea, if it's crispy on the bottom, you have too much heat or it's
really soggy, it needs more cooking.
The rest period also allows more cooking to take place and then cover it and let it sit
for another five or 10 minutes.
So this is a very simple way to make perfect rice.
And I'm going to go over it one more time when we return on Uncommon Sense.
And we're going to talk about food prep and cooking today with Seth Michael and the
Greek on AFR.
Greetings and welcome back to Uncommon Sense with the Greek and Seth Michael on
American Freedom Radio.
And by the way, American Freedom Radio is brought to you by American Freedom Radio and
wholly subsidized by them, but actually relying on people's donations.
So they don't do American Freedom Radio for themselves.
They do it for you guys. So you know what to do.
Go to the homepage. You will find a way to apply some gratitude.
And enough said about that, folks.
So let's let's get to it.
Send them something.
And back here with the Greek and Seth, we were just speaking before the break about how
to make perfect rice.
And just to sum it up, because sometimes I can get a little wordy because I'm trying to
think of the process.
And if you've done something for a long time, there are a lot of fine points that
almost can't be conveyed.
And you might end up jumbling the process.
But the process is simple as such to make perfect rice, essentially rinse and strain
the rice. When you first apply water to the rice, let it rinse out and dry out
somehow, you know, whether it's in a strainer or whatever.
After it's rinsed, let it stand not in the water for at least 10 minutes.
And then the dry volume of rice should be accompanied by equal volume of liquid and
cooked for about 10 to 13 minutes in a good seal at low temperature.
And then let it stand for a few minutes and then just fluff it slightly with a fork.
And when you fluff the rice, make sure that whatever utensil you're using goes to the
bottom of the pot, gently lifting it.
Now, if you get to the bottom of the pot and it's hard and crusty, don't lift that and mix
that into the rest of the rice.
At least, you know, the condition of it at the bottom.
There is actually in certain Latin cultures, when they do get that sticky stuff on the
bottom, they remove the fluffy part of the rice on top and add some cooking oil and fry
that and becomes like a dessert.
But nonetheless, the purpose of bringing up rice is how to make perfect rice.
And what inspired that was years ago when I was traveling out in the countryside, somewhat
away from everywhere with some others, I decided to cook some rice and beans out of the
back of a minivan where everyone else wanted to find the nearest gas station to get frozen
pizza and burritos.
And when I mentioned I was making rice, they were amazed and they said, you know how to
make rice? I was like, yes.
And I found out how people are just not privy to how to make perfect rice.
And when I say perfect rice, you will have a starchy grain that has a wonderful flavor.
It is not lumpy like a massive starch.
You will have individual grains of rice and it will actually develop a beautiful sheen, like a
satin sheen to it of some sort.
And it will taste wonderful and you will get the pleasure of enjoying almost a nearly
perfect plate of rice every time.
If you rinse the rice, dry it, let it stand for 10 minutes, cook it for 10 to 13 minutes
under a good seal, fluff it slightly, let it stand again.
And the fluffing also allows you to recognize whether it's underdone.
You can add just a little bit of water with the heat on and cover it again.
So that is the basic rudimentary aspect of cooking rice.
And this would be your medium to long grain rice.
If you're going to do a brown rice that way, I suggest a pressure cooker, actually has
been suggested, or you can let the rice soak in water for at least one hour before you
cook it. And you would have to double your cooking time and increase your water
slightly.
Is that after straining it, do you still strain brown rice?
Well, what you would do is soak it for at least an hour, I would suggest, and then
strain it and let it stand.
And then you would at least double or triple the cooking time depending on your
altitude. And yeah, and a very tight lid.
Now, there's some high end preparations of rice.
There are some rice companies, let's say in Japan, that will not sell rice to you
unless you know how to cook it.
This would be on the restaurant level.
I think there's a fellow named Gido who has the most prestigious sushi shop in the
world. He received Michelin three stars.
He has a very specific reason for making the rice the way he does, because it's a
very special rice.
It's interesting. I had seen a documentary on him and someone said, well, you
actually do very similar things that he does.
And I said, yes, it's very important to understand the grain of the rice also.
That's why I brought up, prefaced, that this procedure of making perfect rice every
time by pre-rinsing it, letting it stand and then cooking it for 10 or 13 minutes
and fluffing it, letting it stand, works best for your medium to long grain or
medium short grain rice.
It's not your specific sushi rices or brown rices or things like that.
Most people will commonly get in the Western world a medium long grain rice, and
this would be the best way to cook it.
There is no mystery behind it, just some skill.
So essentially, again, rinse the rice, let it stand for 10 minutes, not in the
water, drained out somehow and then resume cooking at a low temperature.
But you must bring it to somewhat of a simmer initially.
So, yeah, kind of like, you know, I'm thinking about four different ways of
cooking four different grains here.
And I need to be specific.
This works best for your, you know, what's called a jasmine rice or a typical
medium long grain rice, even a basmati.
Again, rinse it, let it stand out of the water for 10 minutes, strained, apply
some fat oil or salt, add some heat while it's dry in the pan, add your
corresponding equal volume of liquid.
If you're new at this, bring it to a simmer on the outer edge only, not in
the center, and then cover it for 10 minutes to 13 minutes.
If you get an overboil, even on low, just turn it off.
If you have an electric range, don't put it on warm, that will not cook it.
It will have to be on low.
So, that's generally the perfect rice.
The thing to remember is to rinse it and strain it for at least 10 minutes and
then just basically following the rest of the instructions will also yield a good
rice, typically instructions given on packaging.
The only thing is you might want to cut back on liquid.
I think on most packages of rice, they do suggest using a little bit more
water than the volume of rice.
So, because it has been soaked previously or rinsed previously, you can just go to
equal parts liquid to rice.
And this is how you make a perfect rice just about every time or approaching
perfection instead of being shocked by the concept of cooking it or buying
something prefabricated.
So, the other starch I want to discuss is something called potato.
People like cooking potatoes.
I think, Seth, you mentioned they're inexpensive, they're easily available.
They are a nightshade, I believe.
So, in some health circles, they're not recommended, but albeit, there are things
like baked potatoes and mashed potatoes to be enjoyed.
Now, here's an easy way to make mash, folks.
I've seen people try to cook mashed potatoes and they boil the crap out of
potatoes and they leave them in the water.
Guess where all the flavor is?
In the water or they cooked it away.
Now, when you do your potatoes, in order to conserve on heat, peel the potatoes.
And the smaller you cut the potato, the less cooking time.
Right. The easier it is for the heat to get to the center mass of the actual
piece. I have seen people put whole potatoes in a pot and boil them for an hour
and a half and wonder why they're so hard on the inside.
So, what I recommend typically doing when you're making a mashed potato type dish
or potato salad even, you know, you cut, let's say, a starchy potato or russet
type, which are the oblong ones.
Don't use a waxy potato, you know, the smaller round potatoes that are purple or
whatever. The red potatoes or yellow potatoes, those are very waxy.
Those are for different applications.
I'm talking about a starchy russet type or Maine or Idaho, let's say here in the
States. What you do is you peel it, cut it in half a long way, cut it in half a
long way again. So you have four long pieces and then cut those in four pieces.
So you can get roughly 16 pieces out of a whole potato.
Put that in some water and salt.
Just bring the water to cover the potato.
Don't you don't have to create an aquarium.
And you only need about 15 minutes to 20 minutes of simmering at that point.
Strain out the potatoes and make sure that they are barely fork tender, meaning
that if you put the fork through the potato and the potato falls apart, it's
overcooked. What I mean, fork tender is you can put a fork into the potato and it
still has the tiniest bit of firmness possible, a little bit of crunch in the
center. That is OK.
Do not overcook them.
And when you strain the potatoes, return them back to the pot, just strain, not
rinsed, with a low heat for about five to 10 minutes.
And you're going to have to mind this because some low heats are not that low.
Now, in this case, if you had a warm feature on electric range, I recommend
using that for about 10 to 20 minutes.
And don't stir the potatoes.
What you are doing there is a stovetop baking now.
And then when you proceed with your mashed potato, whatever seasoning or fat
you want to add, people add milk and butter and things like that and start
mashing it in the pot.
You will notice that when you open the lid after the potatoes have been strained
and sitting on the stovetop low, you will get this wonderful potato essence,
almost like the smell of a baked potato.
And you have this wonderful potato flavor coming out of the potato that or
emerging that you tend to call very potatoey, let's say, or enjoyable versus
this bland starch that needs a lot of salt and butter and fat.
So you don't want to overcook the potato.
Cutting the potato into smaller pieces, not too small, but if you have very little
energy or heat or time, the smaller, again, the faster it will cook.
Do not overcook it to the point where the potato falls apart.
It should be fork tender.
The fork should just penetrate.
Put it back in the pot for a low heat until you get that wonderful baked potato
smell and then add whatever else you're going to add to mash the potatoes.
And you will have some very delicious mashed potatoes.
It will taste like a baked mashed potato versus the standard just puree starch.
Now, there's a lot of, let's say, mashed potatoes being served up in what's
called America.
And the reason I brought this up is, like Seth mentioned, potatoes are easy to go
get and they're inexpensive.
And this is just one way to make a delicious mashed potato.
Do not overcook.
Now, there's another concept of a baked potato.
I've seen people fire up an entire oven for one or two potatoes.
That is a lot of volume to heat up a space for doing a baked potato.
Now, I know there's microwaving, but I will not even touch the subject of
microwaves. If you use a microwave, maybe you should open the door and put your
head in it. But anyway,
that's another bad thing to say.
But so what? If you're going to do a baked potato, one way to do it is what I
call a stove top.
Go ahead and don't peel the potato.
Just clean it a little bit.
Even if you don't, it's fine.
Put it in a pot that is just about the size that fits the number of potatoes you
want to bake and just bring water up to the top level of the potato and plenty of
salt, more salt than you'd normally use.
Bring it to a simmer and then a rolling boil for about five or ten minutes and
then turn the potatoes over very carefully with a set of tongs and then let it
boil for another five or ten minutes and then remove the potatoes very carefully.
You don't want to break the skin.
Place them back into the pot on a very low temperature.
Now, remember, there's no liquid in the pot, so you can burn a very thin bottom
pot. When I say a pot, it would be something with a heavy bottom and hopefully not
aluminum. If you use aluminum or Teflon or a thin bottom pot, you will probably
fail in all of these suggestions, just like you would fail if you didn't have a
sharp knife getting into and you wanted to get into cooking.
So this does require some prep and some equipment.
But the concept of baking on the stove top can be done, just like making a pizza on
a barbecue can be done.
You don't always have to bake in the oven or even grill on the top.
You can, as long as you have a heat source, if you know how to manage the heat
source, you can achieve the effect, the desired effect ultimately.
But the concept here with the potato is they tend to taste better when they are in a
dry situation when heat is applied.
That's why baked potatoes taste so wonderful.
But you can do a stove top bake by first boiling the potatoes and then just putting
them into the pot on a low temperature for another five or ten minutes and turning
them, because you'll notice the skin will brown where it touches the pot.
So now you can actually achieve a baked potato flavor on a stove top.
That is another way to do that.
And also French fries are a concept.
Yes, fried food is not bad for you if the oil temperature is high enough.
What makes fried food, let's say, unpleasant or unhealthful is when the
temperature is not high enough.
So when you're frying something that has moisture content, if the temperature of
the oil where it's being fried is high enough, there's always an outward movement,
an ejection of steam that keeps the oil from penetrating the food.
If the oil temperature is too low, the reverse happens and you end up with a
greasy piece of food.
So, by the way, the best French fries are when they're cooked three times.
You would actually cook the French fry first by blanching it in hot water, dipping
the French fries in boiling water, letting them stand till they cool down.
And then you would either deep fry them or pan fry them until they, let's say, get
really hot before they turn brown of any or change color, then remove them, let them
cool down. And then the third time cooking, which would be the second fry, is when
you would fry them till they get the color that you desire.
And that's a proper palm frit, by the way.
That's why typically store bought French fries that are frozen that you reheat always
taste better or mostly taste better than single cooked homemade fries because they
tend to be twice cooked.
So that is your two basic starches of, let's say, potatoes and grains.
Now, the other thing I want to address, since we're on the potato grain, let's talk
about veg and that leads into maybe doing pot cooking where you do stews and things
like that. I've been experimenting lately with adding flavor or bringing out the flavor
of veg. And one thing to consider is if you're going to do a stew or a vegetable dish
of any sort, I've lately been getting into roasting root vegetables and then rinsing
them off before I prep them or cook them.
So if I was to incorporate, let's say, carrot or parsnip or turnip or any kind of a
root veg into a dish, I found that actually roasting them in the fire, getting a
carbonized layer on the outside of a carrot, let's say, just to give an example, and
then rinsing that carbonized layer off, just like if you've heard of roasted red
peppers somehow available, rinsing that layer off actually changes the flavor and
changes the consistency of the carrot.
And it actually brings more of a carrot flavor and a sweetness to it that you will not
get with other forms of cooking.
There are certain Asian dishes, especially if anyone's ever had Vietnamese pho or
pronounced pho, but it's spelled P-H-O as in pho.
One of the secret ingredients there, or not so much of a secret, is to actually take
ginger root and roast it in fire until it carbonizes on the outside, slightly rinse it
and smash it and include that into the broth.
It actually changes the flavor of the ginger.
And again, just like I brought up roasted red peppers that are carbonized to some
degree and then rinsed off typically in some European or, let's say, Italian cookery,
that also changes the food.
There's something about roasting that also changes and imparts a different flavor.
So that was the concept of the veg.
Now, again, to go to the concept of the veg, since we brought up starches, potatoes and
maybe just included here just the roasting of veg, most veg, in order to be palatable,
should be cooked.
Now, I'm talking about root veg, tubers, things like that.
Most veg that people consider veg are leafy greens, typically do not need to be cooked,
even though they are done so.
Like if you get spinach as a side dish in a restaurant, it's typically cooked.
Now, or it can be in a salad as well, which has become more popular, certain greens.
But in order to be palatable, like let's say you are growing a garden and you have collard
greens or beet greens or things that are very robust green vegetables, like cabbage, for
example, you can turn them into a slaw.
You know, like cabbage, for example, is a very robust leafy green, very difficult to eat
on its own raw.
So but if it's cut very fine in a Julian fashion, you know, very narrow cut, it's what
you call slaw, let's say.
Right. So other vegetables other than cabbage can be turned into slaws like collard greens,
beet greens and other things like that.
So if you do either grow or purchase root vegetables that do have a leafy green
counterpart, that can be eaten also in the form of a slaw raw.
And remember, when it's raw, you don't need as much of it.
So it's essentially here with veg or actually anything.
Don't cook it to death.
Don't overcook it, meaning can't cook things, but don't overcook things.
That tends to be a problem unless you have someone that is very sedentary or horizontal
and typically then overcooked things tend to help out because they are not moving.
So basically, that was just the interjection.
I think the the crown achievement of perhaps discussing food today might be just how to
make perfect rice. I think we've pretty much explained that already.
So that can I make would you mind if I make a request?
Oh, please go ahead. Bread, flatbread.
That's a good one. Yeah, that's and that's another thing that is we've spoken about
before. It's something that I I enjoy a lot.
And it's also easy to acquire, readily available and fresh.
Yeah, there's nothing like having immediate bread, meaning fresh bread.
And, you know, of course, that's why bread is always discounted or bread products should be
discounted if they're a day old, but not if they come in plastic bags like they do today.
But, yeah, you know, you know that concept, Seth, about day old bread.
You know, what happens when you go to the store and they have this something they call
bread in a loaf and it sits there, I mean, for a week, the price doesn't change.
You ever notice that? Yeah, it takes it takes quite a while for the they do.
They do drop it occasionally.
But I've stopped. They don't do it after I bought bread like that.
So but American American bread or white bread sliced in the loaf.
I mean, if it's put on the shelf today, it's not reduced tomorrow.
But typically the price of baked goods was always reduced the next day.
So what does that tell you? Folks should be fresh.
Now, Seth made the request to bring up the flatbread concept because it's very simple.
You're not looking for leaven of any kind.
I would just weigh out some flour, measure out some flour on a board of some sort.
And you can add a an egg to it or two eggs, depending on the volume, and mix it on the board
and some fat. Again, when I say fat, it would be butter or shortening.
I would not add an oil because that would make it very hard.
More like a pretzel consistency, like a hard piece of cardboard sometimes.
But add butter or shortening of some kind and mix it on the board.
Add some salt, perhaps, or anything else you want to add, sesame seeds or whatever, and make a dough ball.
Also, you're going to be adding a measurement of water of cold water to it very slowly.
You can make a little ring of the flour, by the way, on the board and add your liquids and things to that.
Chop up the butter and just add all those ingredients together and mix it around until you get a dough ball.
Meaning you might have to add a little bit of water at a time.
And if it gets too soft and sticky, you should have some dry flour on the side where you add that again.
You know, you might want to press it flat and fold it and roll it again and then let it sit for about five,
ten minutes or a half hour in the fridge or on the counter somehow.
And then break off pieces and roll it flat and you can put it in a hot pan.
And or in the oven just for a matter of 30 seconds per side, wouldn't you say, Seth?
In less than a minute or two, it can be cooked, right?
Very simple. Yeah, if you're doing it in the oven, you do it at a very high temperature to do it that quickly.
But yeah. Yeah, the easiest way to do the flatbread, by the way, if you're in a kitchen setting,
is to make it a round, thin, flat piece of dough, throw it into a hot pan that's on the stovetop
and then immediately take that pan and bring it down to the broiler section of the oven.
So now it's hot on the bottom and hot on the top.
And 30 seconds to a minute, it'll be done.
You don't have to flip it or you can flip it.
But either way, this is a very simple thing.
Just adding flour, some fat, you know, in the form of butter or shortening of some kind.
And maybe an egg and some water until you get the consistency of a dough and have some flour and water on hand.
So in case it gets too wet, you can temper it back up to being not too sticky and like a dough.
Or if it's too dry, you can add some water.
And they say add water very little.
And the easiest way to do that is, of course, to make a ring that put the flour on the working area and just make a ring in the center.
Would you have any other suggestions?
You have some experience with this.
Now, so how would you tell the listenership how you would do it, let's say, or how you have done it, maybe to add or take away from what you just said?
That's that's I mean, that's pretty much it.
I tend to add, you know, things to it, depending upon what I'm going to use it for, because I use the flatbread for just about anything.
I'll make little pizzas with it.
I'll wrap anything in it.
It's basically, you know, depending upon you can smash it out then as a tortilla and that I mean, then you have tortillas and you can wrap anything in it.
But I'll add like when I'm making bread, I'll add parsley.
If I'm making pizzas, I'll add, you know, some different spices, herbs and spices.
If I'm making something sweet, you know, I'll add a little bit of sugar just but it's very, very useful.
It's and it's quick.
It's easy and it's inexpensive if it's the budget.
Right. And it's super palatable being that it's freshly made.
And it's not we're not talking about leavened bread here, folks, just a flatbread, which tends to be very popular in most cultures.
I was speaking to someone in Australia, by the way, and they said they enjoy burritos.
And I'm like, what did you say?
I said, I enjoy burritos.
And in Australia, you have Mexican food in Australia.
He says, yeah. And I was like, OK, great.
Well, you know, interestingly enough, folks, every culture has some sort of sandwich or where some kind of food,
whether it be a meat, protein, vegetable or starch is wrapped in something, whether it's seaweed in the Japanese or a tortilla or a pita or an American or European sandwich.
Everyone else is the concept of wrapping something to be held by hand.
So what Seth mentioned, it's versatile in that respect.
Thank you for mentioning that, Seth, that it can be used many ways as a wrap or it could be just used as, you know, serving it on the side as well with any meal or making a pizza like.
Yeah. So it's hummus.
Yeah. Yeah.
And yeah, I think.
And it's also I found out what's interesting is that sometimes the flatbread stored overnight or even a couple of days even tastes better the next day or two days.
It just achieves a wonderful flavor.
I think when it goes stale, it tends to get even more complex flavor to a certain degree and you can still warm it.
You know, it makes a good leftover as well.
And it doesn't give you it doesn't leave you with that overstarched feeling or of, let's say, full stomach kind of feeling that you get from a leavened bread.
Right. Notice that.
Yeah. And it's very satisfying.
So the concept of flatbread, it shouldn't be strange because there's a prevalence of flatbreads in Middle Eastern culture and in the Latin culture, let's say.
Well, it just takes less waiting to it's like I said, it's it's immediate.
Yeah. It's very quick.
You don't have to wait.
Right. Yeah, I spent a lot of time working.
So when I'm cooking, I'm I consider how long it's going to take to prepare whatever it is that does come in.
Yeah. Coming to play for me a lot.
So. So perfect rice.
Don't overcook your potatoes and also slightly undercook them and apply some heat in a dry form in the pot.
Don't burn the pot. And making flatbread.
Now, there might be even some YouTube videos on making easy flatbread that I would suggest.
The other two, there may not be suggestions on YouTube, but I know that perhaps from looking and suggesting requests about flatbread,
years ago, I did find some things on what's called YouTube.
But, yeah, getting into making simple flatbreads is just wonderful because it's fresh and it's wonderful.
And again, you're making it yourself.
It doesn't take much of an effort.
And it is actually not much of a cleanup either for the effort.
You know, it's very simple.
So from that respect.
Yeah. And I also wanted I threw in a little bit what might be considered exotic about roasting of vegetables for changing flavor.
So something to think about for those of you that already do apply cooking food.
Now, we talked about grain starches and veg and flatbread.
And one of the emails was regarding health, you know, regarding the C word, A-N-C-E-R and food.
Well, of course, just to go back to, you know, this is this is what kind of underpinned the thought of doing a discussing food is that,
yes, there's a relation to food and being ill.
But I think considering eating seasonally and then, of course, what needs to be considered is there's something called your law.
Your law comes from your God.
Yes. Not talking about traffic law or tax law or things like that.
There are laws for the food that man should eat, just like if you worked in a pet food store, you would give dog food to the dogs,
cat food to the cats and bird food to the birds and fish food to the fish.
But apparently mankind, well, actually living in the Christian era, somehow someone has the pranking idea to tell this group of people or the secular era that there is no law from any God anymore.
And what is the most ridiculous bit of tripe I've ever heard?
But nonetheless, you get your law from your God.
So if you don't have a God and you're getting it from the scientists or the state, that's fine, too.
Then they're your God. And April 1st is your holiday.
So this is another thing to consider.
And if you do consider, again, tying that back into what to eat or such regarding your health and the C word, there's more to it than just food.
It's basically environmental and it's also energetic within the body.
And that is a very touchy subject.
So, but, you know, considering the amount of time you left, you have left as a society a decade and a half or so, it doesn't it could be a long time for some and not so long for others.
You can prevail within a, you know, having a high quality existence if you pursue it.
So nonetheless, Seth, what else do you think in the well, actually, Seth, you know, what's interesting, I'll bring this up, you know, the concept of the biblical text that I'm going to read to you is this.
That everyone loves to hate. No one has ever read, by the way, or seemingly no one has ever looked into it.
But there's something in Leviticus 11 that if anyone were to go there and read that, I believe it's Leviticus 11.
And not only in the biblical text, but any of the holy rites of the world or most cultures indirectly, indirectly promote a vegetarian diet.
Did you know that?
I was aware that the biblical text does.
Yeah. Indirectly, though, and the way it does in the biblical text indirectly is by stating that if you touch the flesh of an animal, you're in an unclean state until noon, you know, where you wash.
Right. For example, and this is repeated in the Book of Haggai, where he goes to some priests and he says, is it not true that if a garment touches flesh, it's unclean?
And they answered, yes.
Now, here's the interesting part. If you're eating a tuna fish sandwich, a turkey sandwich or a roast beef sandwich, are you touching dead flesh?
Yeah, absolutely.
So if you have enough of a rational mind, you will find this in many of the holy rites, ancient texts of the world that is unfit to touch a carcass of an animal.
In other words, you are not in such a good state if you do until you clean yourself up, let's say, or wait a certain period of time and apply water.
Right. So they do indirectly promote, you know, what's interesting, the Hindus about the cows and all that.
What's interesting, I think it's in the Mahabharata and one of the chapters or might be in the Rig Vedas also.
It states in the Hindu text that Brahma, I'm just paraphrasing here, Brahma created everything in seven days and goes on.
And then it also states that if you're ever visited by any of the angels of Brahma, you're to slaughter a calf and offer it to them.
Isn't that interesting? This is in the Hindu culture. Right. In their own writings, by the way.
Isn't that interesting?
So there is a concept of it being indirectly the concept of not even touching the carcass of an animal is being promoted.
So if you're going to have lunch with animal in it, it's the same as touching it.
So anyway, it's kind of indirect, you know, bringing up the there will be discussion on the lawfulness of what was written and delivered to mankind in the past.
And I think we've said we will probably end up discussing this sometime in the future because simply you folks are not ready for it yet.
Meaning you folks, meaning the general group of people on this planet, they balk at it.
You know, they don't want to hear it.
I've personally been attacked both on air and off air about discussing things that once were that are memorialized.
So, yeah, it's not time yet, folks. So why push the issue?
But for anyone who is listening and is interested, yes, all of the ancient texts do promote indirectly a vegetarian form of eating.
So with that said, maybe should we move on to the concept of eating carrion or eating being carnivore or, you know, because carnivores, by the way, in nature, they devour and attack and eat an animal while it's still alive.
In some cases they do store the carcass, but mankind in almost all cases does approach something that has been dead for a while.
I have a question. Maybe before we get into that, what about like eggs?
Yeah, good. Ovo, I call it ovo-lactic, ovo and dairy. I thought about it and kind of avoided it. Why?
Because eggs are the most heat sensitive substance or material or object one can engage into when they're cooking.
As a matter of fact, when I brought up Jiro in Japan, when you work at his restaurant, you must do at least a 10-year apprenticeship before you're allowed to cook any egg product.
Yeah. So actually most people that do do the 10-year apprenticeship, it takes them about 100 tries before they get it the way that it's preferred in that restaurant and they break down crying when they do achieve it.
So think about that for a minute, folks. There is  yeah, eggs are interesting, very, very heat sensitive.
So less heat, the better. Don't overcook the egg. It will get dry and rubbery. And if you put too much heat, you will release moisture.
But here's the point about egg before we might want to touch into, and that's a good part to start because it is an animal, quote-unquote, product.
From an energetic and ethereal point of view, when you eat an egg minus the shell but the interior of the contents, it is pretty much similar energetically to eating an entire chicken, meaning not just eating chicken, an entire chicken where you sit down at a pub and have a roasted or fried chicken.
I'm talking about eating an entire chicken, meaning the beak, the feathers, all the internal organs, the feet and the claws as well.
Where does that fall in relation to, like we were talking about, lawfully touching dead flesh?
Yeah, it is in a sense because here's  that brings up the interesting point of the right to life.
When is a human a human in the embryo and is it a conception or further on? That is an interesting point.
But it is flesh in a sense, is it not? It is just not flesh. It's flesh in a primary state because you can actually see  you put a little window in an egg if it's incubated and you could see how it develops.
But the interesting part from an energetic point of view, it is an entire chicken from an energetic point of view.
So that's interesting. It's also extremely heat sensitive because of the state the quote-unquote proteins and liquids are in.
But essentially what I do suggest about eggs, of course, is always get the best quality you can.
Again, eat few of them because they are extremely potent even though it may not feel as such and be mindful with the heat on them, very mindful.
There are actually some stupendous things you can do with them.
Eggs are incorporated in just about savory and sweet dishes, right? Almost all  most  I shouldn't say all, but many pastries do include the use of eggs.
We just brought up the concept of egg in the flatbread.
You know why the French pastry chef only uses one egg?
No, why does he do that?
Because it's an oeuf.
Oh, okay, gotcha.
Cool.
So, all right.
So, yeah, that's all right.
So the concept of eggs, yeah, that's a good one, yeah.
But that is the pregenitor, I guess, for the early start into considering animal material.
And then milk is the other, you know, dairy.
Cheese, by the way, you know, and other products, dairy products, change the dairy.
That's why some people might have an adverse reaction to drinking certain types of milk but don't to cheese, right?
So when you make a cheese, you've actually changed it.
Obviously, its form, its flavor and all that, and its reaction to the body also changes.
But there's many aspects to that as well.
You know, if you find yourself intolerant, then avoid it.
But the point here is with dairy, think about it.
The purpose of the dairy in animal or even human is to provide nutrition to the early or the young, right, newborn to young offspring, right?
And what's interesting is the potency of the rate of growth and the type of animal is also resembled in the milk.
So, for example, a very simple way to look at it is that it might be less challenging to the body for, let's say, a man or a woman or a human to drink goat's milk or sheep's milk
because the animal tends to be more in relation to the physical size and rate of growth to mankind,
where if you drink cow's milk, that is a much more potent type of dairy.
Some people might think this is an urban myth, but this is just the practical side of it,
is the rate at which a calf grows is disproportionate, you know, at rate than other smaller animals.
So there tends to be a contention about milk in general.
People have an intolerance, and it's basically the cow's milk.
It's basically like rocket fuel, you know, when people drink it,
where something like goat milk or sheep milk would be more benign to the human, let's say.
That's something that has to be considered as well, and it's not discussed that way.
It's kind of discussed across the board that all dairy is just dairy, right?
And this is just the finer point, you know.
But it also, for some reason, milk being a whole product has sort of been banned
because it is such a whole product and complete food, so it's been fractionalized.
So again, just like going into the subject of, you know, people have certain wheat allergies, gluten-free and whatever,
that's the most ridiculous thing that can be said.
What people are finding adverse reactions to with glutens and other things like that
is the quality of the gluten or the quality of the grain that is being provided
and the things that are added to it.
You know, have you heard of like gluten-free diet?
That's ridiculous, you know.
It's the quality that's being offered, again, and not necessarily whether it's organic or not,
but it's actually the strains and the types of grain that are being raised for human,
quote-unquote, consumption have changed.
So these are things to be considered.
But just as we're running out of time here to get into those that do prefer or do consume animal flesh,
and what's interesting about it is, you know, when we, say we meaning in the Western world,
go to eat animal, you know, let's say beef, we say a steak or a rib or whatever, you know,
we call it things like that, but it's actually muscle tissue.
You know, what's interesting, if you go to an Asian restaurant
that is predominantly accommodating Asians, and the menu is in Chinese or Korean or what have you,
and they do give you an English translation for the non-Asian patrons,
a steak will be listed as beef muscle, right?
So it's quite an interesting idea.
So when you're eating the flesh of an animal, let's say,
you're actually eating parts that can be identified.
Is it organ meat?
Is it skin?
Is it muscle?
Is it bone marrow?
Things like that.
Is it, you know, what type of organ?
And this is something that has to be considered as well.
And it seems to have been washed away, just like when young children are asked now,
in what they call the States, where does milk come from?
And they say it comes from the store, you know.
So this is something to be considered.
Now, the suggestions that are made with meat, let's say fish and fowl,
we mentioned earlier that it is almost indirectly recommended to be vegetarian,
but nonetheless most people still do engage in eating of those things.
The problems, the main problems you'll find here,
which are discernible is the level of quality that's offered,
especially with the four-legged animals and the fowl or the poultry,
is the quality is going down and down and down because the profit margins are
trying to be maintained and also maintaining low prices.
So the actual practices in the western world and eastern world now,
especially which is gaining popularity, is what's called commercial farming.
So if you had grown up, for example, 30, 40, or even 20 years ago,
if you have a discernible palate,
you will notice that the quality of what's called meat and fish and fowl is going down.
It's because the conditions that these animals are being raised in,
in terms of husbandry, is getting worse and worse and worse.
And this just happens to be the way things go.
I mean look at what most people,
look at what pretty much everything mankind is doing at this point,
whether it's political, education, judicial, religious or so, scientific.
It's just getting worse qualitatively.
One thing I like to say, which is not necessarily to regress from the subject,
but today is a little bit worse than yesterday,
but not as bad as it's going to be tomorrow.
That is another way of saying the frog being boiled in the pot.
So yes, just putting that aside for a minute,
when you're going to deal with fish, fowl and four-legged animals,
one suggestion that I would make with the four-legged animals,
well typically, just to put it out there, this might sound religious.
If you think it's religious, cover your ears.
But what's fit for mankind to eat if it's four-legged
is to have a clove and hoof and chew the cud.
Yeah, you heard it right.
So most animals that are four-legged may or may not do that.
Like a pig has got a clove and hoof, but it doesn't chew the cud.
A rabbit chews the cud, but it has a paw.
A dog and a cat does neither.
And just to throw in a little joke, I think it was Malcolm X,
they asked him, why don't you eat pork?
And he says, well, pork is half dog, half cat and all rat.
But anyway, that's not true.
But let's just say it's a joke against that.
And I think I brought up the concept earlier of the dangers of people who have a taste for pork.
What danger is that, Greek?
Well, by the way, if you look at mythology when people were turned into pigs,
and I'm not just suggesting or promoting anything here.
Just listen up, folks.
Pig flesh tastes identical to human flesh.
So let me give you a little bit of a story.
I was in Texas a few years ago speaking to an ex-restaurateur,
and they had a veal special.
And they ran out of veal, and one of the chefs suggested,
why don't we just serve the pork instead of veal?
And they did.
And the people ate it as if it was veal.
And then I suggested, well, you could have served human flesh,
and the people would have eaten it also.
And they found that to be ghastly.
And I suggested to them that from testimony that I've seen memorialized through the ages
and even from watching an HBO special on a serial killer who ate his victim,
suggesting that it tastes exactly like pork and calling the reporter a hypocrite.
When he asked them if he ate pork, I am suggesting,
well, not suggesting and not recommending this for or against,
but I am just making a statement here that if you have a taste for pork,
that could easily be substituted with human flesh.
Use your imagination, and you will be quite satisfied.
So anyway, this is not to be conspiratorial, but let's maybe just dwell on it.
The Polynesian Islanders called when they were talking of the cannibals,
they were talking about human flesh.
They referred to it as long pork.
Mm-hmm.
Now, Americans have been promoted, and most Europeans in the past century, that bacon.
By the way, having pork with breakfast and all that,
that started in the 1930s, the promotion of pork as such.
It was kind of like the same time when Skinner and these other guys came in with marketing.
It's like, watch, we could  it's kind of like the thing with P.T. Barnum.
You know how they said a sucker is born every minute?
Well, the rest of it, I think, goes something like this.
A sucker is born every minute,
and you could never lose money by underestimating the intelligence of the American public.
But nonetheless, I've actually read once in an older literary work, a fiction, let's say,
where a man was introducing his son as being nine years old, and he's learning how to eat pork.
I found that to be very unusual, how that was brought into subject matter.
I don't think it was Dickens, but it's just a strange thing.
And, of course, you know what's interesting, by the way?
People that live in the so-called Bible Belt in America love pork.
So I guess the Bible makes a good doorstop for them.
But anyway, that's another  I don't think we need to harp on people that are mentally deficient.
But nonetheless, let's just say be careful, folks.
If you have a taste for pork, you can be easily fooled,
and there are some pranksters in places that can provide you with something that's not pork that you will think is pork.
And let's just let your imagination run wild there for a minute.
Fried green tomatoes. Have you ever seen the movie Fried Green Tomatoes? It's an older one.
No, no. I've heard of it, though. Yeah, about the women in the hair salon or something.
No, no, not really. There's human flesh that's served up and sold as pork in it.
That's why it is applicable there. Yeah.
It's  I don't know. It's an interesting movie.
It's been many years since I've seen it.
The simplest suggestion I would make with meats is very simple.
With any meat, actually, except for the fish, is learn to employ certain spices
and things that were usually and typically reserved in the Western world for pastry.
What does that mean? Well, there are spices called cinnamon.
There are spices called cardamom.
There are spices called anise, like star anise. It gives it that licorice flavor.
Learn to incorporate those in marinades or dry rubs in your what's called beef or lamb
or other, quote-unquote, red meat, and you will be amazed and surprised at the complexity of the flavor.
This is typically used in a lot of Vietnamese culture, by the way,
and also a lot of Middle Eastern culture.
It is not uncommon to add cinnamon to a roast, right?
That's why very often Westerners or, quote-unquote, Americans or Northern Europeans
will go to eat something at a Middle Eastern-type restaurant or certain Asian restaurants
and be amazed at the flavor, and they wonder why they can't make it at home,
simply because they're using a spice profile that is typically reserved for pastry,
such as cinnamon, anise, cardamom, even cumin, and some clove.
Clove is very strong, so use very little.
But nonetheless, learn how to incorporate those when you're cooking red meat.
And the interesting thing about cooking any meat is I've noticed that very often
people take it from a cold climate, like what's called a refrigerator, to the pan or the oven.
Always learn to temper food, especially like when you brought up how to cook egg.
If you can possibly allow the meat before it's cooked to come up to room temperature
before it hits the pan or pot.
Now, of course, people will say, well, Greg, you're promoting foodborne illness
because bacteria grow on it.
Well, if you actually look at the concept of a lot of these spices, they do retard that.
And again, if you are concerned about the food being laden with pathogens like that,
you have gotten a very low-quality piece of meat.
So you can cook it until it's black or eat it raw.
You're still going to have the field or the energy of that pathogen.
But nonetheless, be clean with these things because they are decomposing.
Once the animal dies, it is in a decomposing state.
But the quickest suggestion that can be made, as we're running out of time,
is to start including other spice profiles that would typically be reserved for pastries.
Learn how to use anise, cinnamon, and cumin.
And you might be surprised, either in a dry rub or a marinade of some sort.
And there are various forms of curries that are formed as such.
On the aspect of cooking fish and cooking meat and cooking fowl,
what's interesting about the aspects there are your time periods.
With meat, it's either going to be cooked for a few minutes or at least an hour and a half.
Anything in between there will render the muscle fiber very tough, depending on the cut.
Usually the more expensive cuts of red meat are such because they remain sort of tender
throughout any cooking time period.
But most cuts of red meat that people will purchase should be either cooked for maybe a few minutes or so
or an hour and a half, like a stew, where it breaks the toughness.
The fish, in another perspective, would be something that requires very little time and temperature.
And something like fowl is always best prepared if it's dried.
Very often people cook chickens and turkeys and things like that.
One way to actually create a perfect dish with poultry is to hang it and dry it for a couple of hours before it's cooked,
which is very interesting.
There is a tremendous amount of moisture in bird flesh and skin and such.
Now, if you're getting fowl parts or chicken parts or turkey parts, it's kind of hard to dry it,
but keep it in a strainer.
If you reduce the moisture content of bird flesh, for example, it will cook better and taste better as well.
And you don't get this soggy, steamy kind of stuff going on when you're trying to fry or broil it.
So those are just simple suggestions with preparing animal.
And, of course, you know, fish is also animal flesh.
But there is a concept of having people having, especially more and more, of avoiding animal or eating meat,
but perhaps still engaging in what I call ovolactic, which is egg and milk, and perhaps fish.
That is still animal product, but nonetheless may be a little better than eating the rest.
But the suggestions, again, today, if anyone can walk away with learning how to make perfect rice,
I think we have accomplished quite a feat because I found that rice is a sticking point, no pun intended,
with most people in the Western world and European world, let's say.
And also, I'm going back to rice, not to avoid speaking of meat, but we have about 10 minutes left.
So I'm going to go back to rice.
And I think that the concept of cooking the rice the way we suggested would probably be the central point
of presenting food preparation today, because it really kind of upsets one to go down the aisle
and see that there are processed rice dishes, like converted rice or bags of rice or things like that,
that people buy and consume because lack of skill on creating a perfect rice dish at home
without having something processed like that, so nonetheless.
But yeah, the meat, fish, and fowl concept is, again, the easiest thing to incorporate there.
It would be on the meat side, you know, with, say, beef, lamb, and such,
is learn to incorporate some of the spice profiles, again, like cinnamon, anise, cumin, cardamom,
things like that, and you will have a completely different and more digestible, let's say, dish prepared.
And use your discernment on that.
If you actually mention to someone in the Western world that you'll be using anise and cinnamon
and, let's say, garlic powder and salt to season a steak, they will find that to be crazy sounding.
But if you actually tried it and cooked it, they would be quite rewarded with a wonderfully tasting piece of meat, let's say.
So this is something, again, unusual we wanted to bring up, but to be considered regarding cooking meat.
But, again, just to bring it up once again, if you folks out there are afraid of cooking rice,
and I think today was the central point was learning how to cook perfect rice
would have been the central point of today's discussion on cooking food.
And, again, sort of indirectly discussing the concept of health and food, which was brought up,
simply a way to overcome that is to learn how to eat seasonally,
pretty much understanding that food changes body chemistry.
If you're speaking to a chemical-based materialistic mindset, eating seasonally or cross-latitude,
if you're in a warm place, eat food that comes from a warm place.
And if you're in a cold place, eat food that comes from a cold place.
Don't mix and match because the body will adapt on its input.
So I guess that would be like a simple way to sum up what people can get away with
from listening to what we have to say about food prep or cooking.
And water likes to be cold and stored in a dark place.
Yes, exactly.
That's why when people go to purchase water at the shops, let's say,
it's always in a clear container at room temperature.
Ha ha ha.
It's never cold, and it's always exposed to light, and no one is paying attention.
And to make things worse, you have people seeking out, quote, unquote,
better information, alternative media, and you have all of these morons with a capital R
who want to discuss water, and not a one ever mentions keep it cool and in the dark.
They want to tell you little stories about what they think is going on,
which means absolutely, Jack, you know what.
So, yeah, interesting point.
The water, the freshness, the quality, seek best quality,
and not only quality in your food and food in preparation, but in conversation.
What say you on that, Seth?
Yeah, good conversation.
Absolutely, absolutely.
I know that when this is over, I'm going to go prepare something to eat.
Yes, why not?
Yeah, and also the thing about food, by the way, there are laws and requirements to the body,
and when I say laws, meaning, you know,
anyone who is around pets likes to give the appropriate creature its appropriate food,
but people tend to think they can do anything they want.
So consider that as well, what's fit and proper, folks.
Absolutely.
Thanks for tuning in and listening to the discussion.
We'll be back around this same time next week.
So thank you all for being out there.
Yeah, thanks again, everyone.