Greetings and welcome once again to Uncommon Sense with The Greek and Seth
Michael. You're on American Freedom Radio and it also is being streamed on
Ustream which you can access by going to uncommonradio.com and you will find
your instructions on pretty much how to do that. And welcome everyone again and
hello Seth. Greetings, salutations, how are you doing?
We're doing well, yeah, yeah. Again, so we're here again pretty much again like we
said you could find us on Ustream and we are on American Freedom Radio which
is a internet-based format and it requires your input not only just the
output that you're getting from listening to it through however you're
listening but the folks here or there at American Freedom Radio would appreciate
anything you could send their way and I've said with that but just to pretty
much interject one other thing Seth is on the on the feedback that we've been
getting let's say through emails and other messaging platforms we want to
just thank everyone for not only the extremely let's say positive response
but also the encouragement and also the inquiry about where to donate. Several
people have come forward and say hey I want to donate to you guys we appreciate
that very very much. There is no platform for that to do it to us directly other
than to perhaps support the platform known as American Freedom Radio and you
can donate to them by finding that out by searching their home page. I don't
know how prominent the donate button is but you will find something on there I'm
sure. So with that said I just wanted to bring that forward because it's kind of
like a little bit of something that has been brought up to us about donation so
there you have it. So absolutely in the near future we'll set up a way to take
donations for us directly as well but absolutely support American Freedom
Radio they're making it possible for our audience to get it on that platform so
yeah absolutely as well as you know Ustream we're using the free service
there as well but if we can get some sort of small regular income we can do
the professional Ustream side as well and that will be a lot no ads you know
things like that so that'll be pleasant but yeah that's all in the future so
yeah and it should be done democratically let's say by the by the
people if they want it they'll come up with it but you know you can't really
stop the signal we say perhaps and if we want to call this sonic experience a
signal it will go on you know there's always been talk about the internet
going down it's not going to go down folks because it's been at this level of
achievement or accomplishment to accommodate the population it will not
be taken away but we decided to do a Ustream when AFR was down for a short
time and also to cover that I think it would be interesting get some ham radio
people with some repeaters and perhaps even provide a in print form transcript
slash newsletter just to cover all the bases but I don't think it's necessary
because the internet is here to stay albeit all the ridiculousness that is on
it it is designed and structured to accommodate the population on the planet
meaning in a common way right okay it's sort of having a discussion with
someone recently set about you know the show it was I don't know I don't know if
I really even like calling this a show because I usually implies strictly
entertainment but one of the first things that came up in conversation
Seth was with this individual was that you know the word common it doesn't it
it doesn't mean anything good like yeah I know that's why we kind of like want
to talk about things that are uncommon and I think we kind of brought up maybe
clarifying a little bit of cliches at every show I don't have one to clarify
this week let's say but the last cliche I believe what might have been
clarified was a biblical one which says it's not what goes into someone's mouth
that defiled but what comes out of their mouth that defiles them and the actual
term there's the term being common not defiled so it's yeah being common is not
good so you know with that said yeah any other thoughts before we get into
something that we don't know what we're really going to get into other than
perhaps more thoughts about these things Seth any anything random perhaps okay
Seth all right he's just remains wants to be maybe quiet for the moment but
let's let's maybe get into it now what we're gonna get into this week we don't
really know but the same concepts keep coming up very often by looking and
hearing and seeing what's going on in the world and what's really interesting
if you want to pretty much look at something that it's not really discussed
much is something called mental health I'm kind of defining it as the aspect of
what is mental what is you know the mind and if you've listened to any kind of
Greek speak or with Seth and myself speaking we've always tried to bring
back definitions of things and bringing bringing a center or reference that is
accessible by anyone and the the mental state or the mind is essentially the
spirit so when you hear about things being mental or of the mind they are of
spiritual in nature intangible in a physical sense so from that point of view
in passing you know even though just mentioned don't have much on the agenda
let's say to speak about there's something about mental health it's been
coming up recently in conversation and even even from the perspective of what
is spiritual all the way down to little little things that people take to as
helpers you know like little pills and things like that you know and the in the
materialistic side and one thing that could be considered is what is mental
health you know what is the is it possible to restore it you know what
what's going on with the the aspect of the spirit or the mind and it's it's
very easy to see how it's being guided if you tend to pull back and be a little
more objective and see what's going on with your own faculties give you an
example not to harp on the alternative media but you know it's very interesting
I've kind of retracted from looking at the internet personally too much because
it's just seems to not being let's say put into effect and it's best and
highest use other than a telephone book or a telephone or pretty much looking at
weather or basic things like that even the weather is another subject one day
we'll get into but what's interesting what I noticed about the alternative
media very much is that they should thank the heavens that the mainstream
exists because every time I sort of tune in even albeit five minutes a week here
or there is the first thing you hear is a parroting of what was going on in the
mainstream media so essentially there there is not much going on other it
seems to be a massive movement of thought control and there is no real
alternative to it again just by bringing up the example of listening to how many
hosts have quote-unquote shows open their show or fill their show with what
the mainstream has done that day so that shows me that there is a a
complete tie-in there is still a almost a homogeneous movement on the planet or
homogeneous movement in consciousness that is guiding people and when you go
away from what is this mainstream thinking or let's say news parody that's
going on there is also the fringe aspect and if you look at a lot of the fringe
aspect of information being put out in the alternative again and that would
also mean a bookstore for example there's like these new-age bookstores
you know things like that that are called if you look at what they're
putting out as well I mean it sounds good it makes you feel good because it's
something different but if you actually look into what they're saying you'll
find this pretty much unfounded and it's not based on anything again one
thing we like to bring up is the baselessness of what humanity has been
pretty much been involved in and endorsing what I mean endorsing meaning
they are putting behind their full faith and credit and their word and
their actions behind things that are totally baseless whether it's the
financial system the monitor you know meaning the monetary system their
religions their sciences even their news again you know again that's a harp on the
alternative media but tune in to any alternative or majority of alternative
stuff you're either going to get this new-age baseless mindlessness that was
pretty much formed by some new-age movement a hundred years ago or you're
going to hear a parody or a parody of what the mainstream had put out that day
or the day before this endless cycle it's a self-consuming self-consuming how
would you say self-consuming circle where it's just if you know getting the
drabbiness of it is not that difficult to see so Seth are you back with us yes
yes I have been for a little while and I didn't want to interrupt yeah so this is
like I kind of spun off a little bit talking about like the state of affairs
when we because I brought up the idea of what is mental health this this kind of
came up in conversation during the week and again we've defined you know the mind
is being the spirit and they're not it's basically the same thing in a
different form of expression you almost don't need the word mental anymore you
could just if everyone just used the word spirit instead of the word mental
or mind it would actually simplify and allow economy of movement in
communication you know so that would be so mental is really a synonym of spirit
or spirituality you know which is it it just means communication it means a
state of being that is intangible it's of the mind of the spirit let's say and
this concept of mental health of being in a healthful form when you kind of
bring up the topic it's like what is it you know is it you know is it is it from
the ultra materialistic pseudoscientific point of view where it's chemical you
know where they tell you about all these synapses in the brain and chemical
imbalances and whatever or is it as defined the spirit of spirituality some
new-age rubbish or something that comes out of some religion you know is should
it be that because you look at that also it's it's rubbish rubbish meaning it
just it should be discarded you know you can go to look at things
qualitatively see if you go to a landfill there's a lot of garbage
everywhere that cannot be denied you know quantity but what is the quality
you know it's pretty low so when I say rubbish that's what I mean I mean
something that is a low quality or no worth is what people are pretty much
still engaging in wholesale from what they find to be alternative sources all
the way to mainstream and what makes it rubbish is that it's not founded on
anything or not founded on what they state it should be on so what is that
what effect does that have to do on the spirit or the mind you see it's quite
interesting isn't it what does the word sanity mean it perhaps you know it's
interesting it goes with sanitation or being clean or helpful doesn't it yeah
sanity is is health it's healthy insanity is unhealthy yeah and looking
at the you know the mind as spirits and not as the physical organ that the
spirit seems to use to you know interact with this with this body it's the root
the mind might be the root of the spirit that's why how many times I ever heard
of a kill shot to the head you've never really heard of a kill shot to the foot
or the arm or the shoulder have you so it seems to be the root of this maybe
it's an ethereal positioning but it does work you know a kill shot to the head
lights out you're finished where that's that's where the kill shot is guided to
so there is a found you can find the organ corresponding with the presence of
that spirit as well but to lean completely on the organ and the material
aspect of itself is kind of useless when you want to branch off it's even or
even the looking at it as a singular organ because there's one other place
the heart you will find what they call brain cells kill shot and it also seems
to be you know at least through observation and historically yeah yeah
that would be the heart yeah and by the way you're cutting in and out a little
bit so yeah so from that aspect you know here's another thing just to kind of
stay within this thing because we don't really need to come out and tell people
that they're mentally or spiritually not well maybe we could go around it even
though I kind of just did we can go around the roundabout way of just
describing maybe not the symptomology of it right which is attempted to be
mitigated through chemicals or through what they call spiritual awakenings and
con therapies and things like that which are mindless again and well they're not
really mindless because there is a spirit behind that or even albeit a low
quality one but you know what's interesting stuff I'm going to bring
this up I've been told Greek why don't you say this is very often when you when
you're discussing things in private with people from all walks they say yeah man
people have been dumbed down you know there's a big dumbing down but you know
what's interesting it's never them it's never someone they like a family member
or someone that's close them it's always just generally people that are that are
dumbed down you know you hear this pretty much from every aspect and guess
what folks you're all dumbed down you know it's at this point and am I
pointing a finger at anyone no it's it's we're all inclusive in this but it's I
last week I did discuss it's not only a it's that period has ended we're not
ended it's still continuous meaning on where let's say a cure for dumbing might
be information but is it really if you don't care you know being you know harsh
in discussion it was like well you know what do you know Luminati are really
controlling all this stuff for some oligarchical group but I'm like well
obviously if they're in control they don't keep their word what do you mean
well they're supposed to reduce the population down to 500 million I still
see 7 billion morons walking the planet obviously they don't keep their word not
that they should here but the point is what the hell are you giving so much
credence to all this stuff for you know what you know it's more than just
dumbing down now it's like no one's paying attention to what they're saying
but nonetheless to to look at again just the the idea of a healthy spirit or
a healthy mind if if the if it's intangible and it lies within the realm
of communication like I said earlier people are getting information
communicated to them that it seemed to be coming from some kind of a
homogenous mass or homogenous stream very simply again just not to harp on the
alternative media but look any pretty much effort that's being made in the
alternative is either going to parrot what is in the mainstream or some kind
of like sign of the times alternative new ag bullshit yep you got it
yeah bullshit's good for growing flowers but you know what makes it bullshit you
know that you hear on radio and print or in presentations that people are making
well you bring up discussions let's say regarding let's say ancient texts and if
you listen to what they're discussing about it you will not find it in the
text so what's going on right if they bring up discussions regarding
scientific matters you won't find it in the natural world because the scientific
matter or the science study of science is to pretty much give an explanation which
they fail to or description of the natural world give you folks an example
about that they speak about the the magnetic poles or magnetism or gravity
in the earth well this is a big subject but let's make it small and essentially
the consensus now is not by everyone but conventional is that magnetism of the
earth or let's say for us to say is gravity but specifically magnetism is
caused by the molten core molten iron core at the earth's center now okay that
sounds okay wow you know we know that iron is magnetic we put refrigerator on a
magnet or a nail or something and I mean put a magnet on something iron and it's
and it's ferromagnetic ferro meaning iron and it sticks so so kind of makes
sense that there's this huge molten iron core it's not just iron core that they're
saying that it's molten in the center of the earth that's causing this magnetic
you know bar magnet effect let's say with a north and south pole now no stop
and think folks okay that might sound good it makes you feel good right but
just all right don't stop and think actually don't stop and think why don't
you go and look at a little bit more about what iron and magnetism is about
and when you look at that you'll find out that when when iron is heated beyond a
certain point it fails to be magnetic it's called the Curie point right so and
the Curie point is where iron is no longer magnetic and that is well below
that temperature is well below before it becomes molten you know it might be I
think it's around 800 Celsius and the melting point of iron is almost double
that or actually a little less about 1300 or so so how can a molten iron
which is not magnetic be the cause of Earth's magnetic poles you know you can
look this up it takes a few minutes so when you hear a little bit of
information and it makes you feel good that's fine I'm not saying you shouldn't
feel like you're being made to feel good in a common way but just take an extra
step and inquire a little bit more now you not everyone has to do this but
there has to be a certain few that will and it seems to be lacking in the
society so again how does that tie in with mental health if people are walking
around pretty much believing things that are untrue so from that respect is it
just informational based it can be you know having the wrong information or
erroneous information does that have anything to do with having a good sound
mind think about that for a moment you know and essentially when you hear
about the changes that are going in a negative way why is it that everyone not
everyone but particularly everyone tends to want to blame it on someone else
I've always suggested that if you want to know who the problem is get a mirror
look into it why because the simplest way to perhaps approach anything that you
don't like is to say do I want to be a part of this or do I want to separate
myself from it and what's interesting about that when you look up what's
called let's say the holy writs of the world or spiritual texts let's say of
the mind or of the gods they never suggest you need to thrust yourself in
the midst of society be the change you know create change never always about
separating yourself from it so if the if their problems that exist within the
society or the world are made up of the individuals if the individuals decide to
pull themselves out of that problem will there still be a problem that's kind of
like asking is a room a room if no one's in it well you know we're from
architectural perspective yes but from a social perspective maybe no that's why I
very often lead people back to look up a book called the crowd by Gustave Le Bon
L-E-B-O-N well it's not the be all end all it's a good place to kind of start
and what's interesting there is some of the commentaries you don't have to read
the book even though it is there's an audiobook on there but there's some
pretty accurate commentaries about that book and what's interesting is it when
this these crowds form you find them through what's called activism or
activists or protesters or of any other level whether it's from the
geopolitical side known as lobbyists or political groups all the way down to the
earthy crunchy you know poncho slipper wearing people peace and love you know
all the way down to that from the suit and tie down to you know whoever you
will find that there's always a cause that they are gathered under and if you
ask the individuals within the crowd why are they doing what they're doing they
will pretty much cite that cause and if you take what they just cited and spend
a few minutes looking more deeply into it you'll find that what they had cited
as their cause really doesn't resemble what it originally was in the first
place you'll find this very much in a lot of the legal activism about
legalizing things have these people actually stopped to look at the
fundamental laws that were thrusted into society that made something illegal or
legal or they using the New York Times as their research and you will find it's
the latter so again what is what does this have to do with risk you know
keeping the health of the individual keeping a healthy mind because most
people can go throughout their lives essentially believing things that are
erroneous and untrue or unfounded now does you know they might seem happy they
might smile or whatever but when when it comes to the rubber meeting the pavement
and proceeding in any positive way it's tends to not really work well because it
could be because they're not really looking into what they think something
is you know one of my favorite things to mention is a lot of biblical cliches it
is an important text to consider I mean whether it's you know something to do
with some religious group or not is not the point because it really isn't by the
way like I've always like to reiterate there's not a religion on the planet bar
none that does anything that's in the text that they allegedly allegedly
subscribe to any religion Eastern Western or in the middle do not do
anything that's in the texts do not acknowledge anything in there they might
take something out of context I used to always discuss nature of religion is
basically meaning something that you do regularly but what what it has taken on
to is something to commemorate higher beings or gods or what again people like
to call spirituality and the state of humanity regarding these causes and I'm
talking also about the highest levels right now and we'll cite them like the
Vatican if you go to the Vatican the highest levels or your highest schools
of divinity your highest schools of biblical thought or teaching or your
highest schools of in the world of Islam or in the Eastern traditions as well if
you listen to what they say you will not find any of it in the texts that they say
their religion is based on I'm just going to take a pause there for a minute
to show you how ridiculous even that aspect has gone but but that is because
of the the way that the human mind is being led like right now any anyone in
the Western world can get a recipe for a chocolate chip chip cookie and bake one
in the form of the Virgin Mary and within a fact and if he tells people
about this you'll have a thousand people in a month worshipping that that that
whole scenario is and he'll be there standing about telling them how that
cookie crumbled and they'll all and he'll just take their money take their
effort take their mind and take their interest this is the level of stupidity
that humanity is is is involved in at this moment so again when when people are
when I hear people discussing yeah people are pretty dumb they're dumbed
down it's never them of course you know you know can't be you know think about
that folks for a moment you know are you common and look up what that means
so the sense here again you know how does that tie into being mentally what
what is okay the mental health aspect can it be restored well the thing is
what makes anyone think that it ever was in a position that you want to bring it
back to you know there's there's an interesting part of the formation of
things and if you look around society look at what's going on do you see
objectively a problem yes one can say that you know people are always yelling
about their problems in society well then can you see objectively if there is
a solution well no you know people want a solution or yeah they say this might
be the solution you know they're looking for things to save them they
don't know what they're going to be saved from but there's an insanity and
unhelpfulness that's going on and could that be also it's not only of the mind
but it's of the spirit which haha by the way means the same thing you know last
week we which which can be found in archives I kind of did a monologue for an
hour based on pretty much if I were to comment on it was do really people
deserve the truth if they're acting so undeservingly is that a judgment call
absolutely two of the things that I pretty much covered then and got into
for about an hour was first of all you don't even know how to keep time and you
don't notice and you don't care the Pope's work schedule or the Gregorian
calendar is not a timepiece never was intended to be and it never will be and
you can't keep time with it it is a work schedule for the Pope subjects period
that's something that really can't be debated because it's so simply clear
when you see it for example anyone that observes any day of the year will notice
that it's a different day of the week next year and it has nothing to do with
the Earth going around the Sun in an uneven pattern wake up folks no one
knows how to keep time and time is just the recordation of events so if
something isn't really worth recording maybe it's not really worth having if
you look at a lot of the events that people have been vanquishing about or
relishing about or celebrating pretty much based in worthlessness yes I'm
sorry to say that but anyway the other thing that I brought up is the concept
of are you in is your body in a healthful condition where you require a
cool head and warm feet how many times have people gone to their engineering
classes and requested devices that produce a rise in cold and a descending
heat like it is in nature so you have a cool head and warm feet if the answer is
none you are correct so you don't know how to keep time or record events
properly don't care and you've got a hot head and cold feet and you want the
truth that's a discussion for another subject but you see where that goes so
very simply there's something again about mental health and again you're not
going to get it if you're kind of like lazy and stuck in these things you know
there's there's a material aspect of it oh it's all chemical based that's fine
with Seth earlier we just mentioned you know the kill shot is the head you know
like the zombies cut off the head get rid of the brain you kill the zombie it
even works with them but nonetheless this this concept of restoring things
also why would you want to restore something which wasn't good in the first
place there's got to be a redoing of things greeting Seth yes yes we have
that's we have suffered through a hard reboot but we're back okay great and
pretty much went around the block regarding several things so the the
aspect of the spirit and being a health in a healthful state or the mind being in
a healthful state is very grim for humanity at this point it's not going to
happen there's going to be a general let's say leading through of pretty much
the way things are until things change because the changes that have to come
have to come you see but to pretty much consider the state of being of health of
things it's it's not very good but it doesn't mean that it's fatal you see one
can be in an in a state of illness or disease and still function right and
just this is pretty much just carrying through the concept of the health of the
mind and you can pretty much hear it I use the example of you know magnetism
of the earth and many other things that people really very simple to understand
they but they refuse to look into it into things objectively even though
they're pretty much simple you know which brings like the the concept of
memory how many times have you heard well I didn't remember that or I didn't I
don't really know that you know even though they came across it one thing I
want to bring up regarding memory is that everything is in your memory before
you one speaks or writes or begins to communicate they're actually accessing
little tidbits and faculties words sounds and things that are already in their
memory you know so this whole thing about people saying well I don't have a
good memory or I don't remember that it's not just the faculty or the
function of the memory itself because the very fact that they can communicate
and use more than five words semi intelligent intelligently strung
together means that they have some sort of memory and what's interesting with
that is the more weight that you can carry the stronger you are you see so it
doesn't mean that you need to be memorizing and imprinting things but
when you pay attention to retaining things and paying attention to what
memory is let's say which by the way mem means water and or means light those
look at the point of the root parts of it in the Caldean Hebrew the ancient
tongue it's very interesting so it's almost like water and light is what the
word memory can pretty much be described as and we have a lot of water and some
light and in ourselves hopefully so but the point here about coming up with the
subject of the mental health aspect is a big subject but the whole thing with any
truth of any matter is how deserving is the population for it you know when
they are not even asking the most basic aspects of their you know functioning
existence to be clarified you know and the thing that I like to bring up in a
judgmental way is the people don't know what how to keep time and they don't
care about it and they're not noticing that they're existing indoors with a
hot head and cold feet and they don't care about it either you see and by the
way folks that's why we kind of like tend to go back and say we have about
five listeners which is quite quite enough there's only a handful of people
on the planet actually that may even understand what's being said here it all
be it even as simple as can be you know Seth I think you might have been around
one day you and I were on a roundtable that was being broadcast and it was a
someone who was also supposedly a host of an alternative media came to me and
said hey Greek every time you speak I need babble fish to understand what
you're saying and my response was you don't need babble fish you need a
lollipop in a padded room but anyway so you know yes it's pretty easy to apply
that to to what's going on on the planet right now but the the uncommon aspect of
the discussion of mental health is first of all the connections objectively are
not being made there's still a refusal to go away from the fractional
compartmentalization of the definition of things like oh heaven forbid does the
mind or mental mean the spirit right people just don't want to acknowledge
that and how easy is it to actually learn about that as a reference point or
a meaning of the word quite easy again just to you know bring up it's not just
the definition of words but it's scientific concepts and social concepts
as well you know I brought up one of the concepts of the magnetism of the earth
being blamed on molten iron at the center of center but people fail to
realize that molten iron is not magnetic it's way beyond the curie the curie
point it's it's actually iron loses its magnetism when it's about red-hot before
and it's still solid so how can you see and no one and the whole thing here is
is it required for the entire population to hear a bit information and
then validate it let's just say this in secret everybody cover your ears Seth it
is okay I'm back yes you do so but okay so let's say everyone doesn't do that
because of their emotional or mental laziness is it is it up to maybe certain
individuals let's say a small percentage of the group to do it yet every again
everybody all listeners cover your ears Seth I'll tell you privately guess what
Seth it is they have to validate what they're saying yeah okay I'm back so how
many so how many people are actually validating anything you know you know
very little it's in it and how easy is it to and again the discussion whether
it's the definition of the mind what it is I mean people are not even shocked
when you bring up the point that the mind and the spirit are the same by the way
they're not even shocked anymore they just because they're in such a state of
refuel a refusal to acknowledge it right that it doesn't really affect them you
see just like when you bring up something in the scientific world or the
political world or the legal world those are all the same aren't they that's yeah
they're all aspects of religion again if we go to the religions you know right
now this is the Christian era secularly not to knock Christians you don't have
to because it's so easy I mean it's not fair to do that it's like shooting fish
in the barrel a lot of people are threatening that there's going to be an
elimination of Christianity by the New World Order and I'm like something has
to exist in order for to be eliminated because you won't find anything that is
Christian in anything that they say it's based on it is actually a culture or
tradition that's been developed it is not based on it's it's fiat the same with
any religion it's pretty much fiat when you look at their scientific aspect it's
fiat you know it's not based on anything they supposedly is but you cannot
validate it the same with the illegal society fiat I mean so how is one in
other words does does the very fact that pretty much what's being discussed
because remember I'm saying what's being discussed by people or what they believe
in is not based on anything meaning each corresponding subject that we just
brought up if you actually go look at what's been memorialized about what that
should be about it does not it's not in accordance with what people think it is
so does that have anything to do with mental health or one's mental well-being
you know I believe it does and when I say believe I'm meaning meaning that
it's a functional belief meaning something appears to be like this now and
it doesn't seem like it's going to change tomorrow so it is founded to say
I believe it is like this because it'll probably continue until it doesn't this
way absolutely I would I would say that looking at we refer to another way of
referring to mental health colloquially would be sanity or insanity as we
brought up earlier and sanity is a word that simply means health in the
language that it comes from English does that we like to take words and say okay
it means this now but if you look at sanity as as health and not just of one
aspect of existence but of all of them that you know we can observe body mind
soul you know soul being the breath not separate from you know spirit or yes
separate from spirit it's functional it's carnal it's carnally based well
like the body and the breath or the soul the requirements to contain the spirit I
know I would suggest that the things that are necessary for good physical health
for lack of a better term or good bodily health are the are the same things that
are necessary for good you know spiritual or mental health that when you
are addressing one in a proper manner you are actually addressing both because
the body is how the spirit interacts with the world around it so if you have
a sick body you know there's been recently there have been studies
published that I have not read but I've seen the titles of and the titles would
lead one to believe that there is slowly a recognition going on in some at
least aspects of study and research if not you know readily available
publications that are starting to address such things that poor emotional
like relationships corresponds actually to physical ailments of the heart where
they've studied people that have you know poor relationships with the people
around them relatively and after you know and the thorough physical
examinations or as thorough as this culture can come to a physical
examination there's been actually problems found with the physical state
of their their heart which by the way just to throw this in and preface
before I throw this said you know when I did a show with Chuck Ocelli called
Ocelli and the Greek and by the way for anyone wants to hear more of let's say
background behind the recitations we give here go to Ocelli and the Greek
dot-com you very simply you'll find places to get archives it's 36 hours 18
episodes of discussion and a tremendous amount of initial initialization of
background of what we tend to discuss here what Seth is found there but part
of the that and part of discussion is having guests and bringing other people
in and pretty much I've said that anyone I'd want to interview or have as a guest
is pretty much dead there are very few people that I believe that exist on this
planet today that can I'd be interested in bringing forward and interviewing
let's say there's still actually a couple and one of them would be Frank
Chester Frank Frank Chester as a chest of drawers and a Chester CHE STER you
will find Frank Chester there's YouTube's on there and these are YouTube's
that'll make you feel smart if you watch them right okay that's very it's very
I'm sorry to interrupt but I'm going to anyways I just wanted to say that that's
very it's interesting that you bring up Frank Chester I guess when speaking
about the heart it's of course but I was reviewing and sharing some of his I guess
demonstrations is what it would be two nights ago wonderful yeah see how it
coincides with yeah someone expressed a taste for patterns and things like that
and so I brought up a few patterns and like you you would take more from this
than the average person reviewing it you if you were already kind of aware of
some of these patterns so yeah again sorry to interrupt but please no no it's
not it's not it's exactly cuz I didn't really want to get into his work because
we just cited him and if you're if you're listening to us you're probably in
front of a computing machine and you could access Frank Chester you will find
the matters of the heart being discussed there by someone who I would call who is
one of the few master teachers or has mastership there are very few people that
have mastership and things anymore and he is one of them and he and also to sort
of use as a how do you say is an exception to the statements that I make
that older people have been reduced to fools these days he is one older people
that is not in in the matters that he discusses he is quite brilliant and I
would regard him as a master in his field to say the least would you agree
Seth I would yeah and it's quite an experience even if you have no interest
in the heart wink wink or haha it would be a well a well worth view or citing
this man's work again it's Frank Chester C-H-E-S-T-E-R as in Chester drawers so
Chester Frank Chester look him up you will be glad you did yeah yes indeed
regarding the heart yeah and we talk we we kind of harp on the alternative media
and the internet because it is well I mean that they it's so easy to do I
guess but statistically yes that is exactly yes and I would I would say that
a lot of the information that he speaks about is information that is not being
spoken of anywhere else in the manner in which he's doing it and he's he's very
good at it as well in illustrating these these concepts that he presents so I
would I would definitely second that encouragement to look up Frank Chester
and it's it's well worth the time yes absolutely and you will get more of
let's say a grip on you albeit a tight grip or a loose grip on what is going on
with the archetypal forms behind things so you know there's there's the aspect
of that you know that is pretty tangible and very easy for people to access you
know yeah absolutely but the the again that we kind of brought up out of the
blue let's say the idea of mentality or you know the the there's there's the
aspect of mental health you know and here's here's the interesting part of
any health when you're looking at it in a common point of view is there seems to
be you know something called the bell curve or the minimal acceptable standard
of something and when the entire group or the entire let's say quantity of
something reaches a low level of quality that low level minimum is then lowered
again you see so then everything is above that you see what I mean so there's
this lack of referencing to what is quality and what is not because it's
always being changed you know I don't like using the grading form with people
but there is grading of things like fruits and vegetables and livestock right
and that's why very much I like to say that what is the most degrading thing you
can do to anyone especially a child is to grade them grade them yes well it's
not only the grading itself strictly but what happens when you put people let's
say for example when you say grading you think of school when you put people in
a group that let's say is called a school what is that purpose right what
is the purpose again what is it based on right it was you're supposed to go
there to learn things right and we've discussed how we don't have an operating
system and such so when you bring up the concept of grading now you are
motivating them to learn through penalty the motivation now is penalty you see
right yeah so the person getting the high grade is getting the high grade
because he what doesn't want the low grade you see so now the motivations
behind these things are penalty just like for example have you ever heard
whether this is an urban myth or not it's a really good example how the
regulatory the health regulatory agencies were going around to hot dog
factories and they found that they all had rat feces so they had a
choice either close all of them down and have a revolution yes the only way
to have a revolution America is to close on all the hot dog factories by the way
folks but anyway either close them all down or raise the allowable amount of
rat feces and hot dogs which would be lowering the quality standard right so
they could all stay open so now you can have rat feces but you you cannot go
exceed this level which would be the lowest level of quality so they keep
changing the bar you see so why is this happening you know you see so this
quality when we like to discuss what quality is is it based should it be
based on something that is always fluctuating based on the norm or what
that what's commonly accepted or is there really a set quality you see and
absolutely and I believe that there is a set quality that can be determined which
goes back to the health of things you know whether it's the health of the soil
the health of the mind the health of the body you know playing around with the
quality for political reasons or commercial reasons is really a death
trap you see certainly but for the sake of of one's own health you know what
there is information available look which which we could reiterate you know
if anyone listens to the archives on these shows we'll find that we're always
repeating almost the same things always and the simplest aspect of health is of
course you know people here they want information on their health they go to
the internet or wherever and find all these various various plethora of
approaches whether it's allopathic mainstream or alternative but what they
have figured out to have missed and omit as being forward in the discussion
is are you eating within your environment in other words if you're
living in a cold place what happens when you eat food that was grown in a hot
place well obviously it will change your body's chemistry to living in a hot
place and you will not do well and vice versa so this lead eating seasonally
thing is an interesting approach we always kind of harp on harping because
people don't really want to hear it let's say in general why do I say they
don't really want to hear it I've had discussions with thousands of
individuals and when we do discuss health I say well are you eating
seasonally or within cross-latitude oh oh I kind of heard you mention that but
I forgot well it's something that bears repeating because it's something that's
very very simple and when it's pointed out it seems well that's that's obvious
if you're eating just on a to reiterate a point that we've reiterated several
times but you know if you're eating a plant that grows heartily in the climate
in which you find yourself chances are that is going to be significantly better
for you than you know the the reverse of that so yeah it's it bears repeating
it's it seems obvious once it's explained and it's it's very simple you know so
yeah well the aspect of the chemical aspect of it for example you know like
they'll tell you open adders have you know potassium it's really good for you
or oranges have vitamin C and vitamin C's been proven to help with colds you
know it's and all that like but wait a second folks okay you know no one really
knows what's in a banana no one really knows what's in an orange and when I say
no one I mean well yes there are some people that just they put on white lab
coats and they have brick-and-mortar buildings that are well endowed with the
credit system and they take oranges and bananas and they cut them open and they
dry them out and subject them to other chemicals and fire which is called
assaying and mining for example and they assay these things and what they do
changes it so much from its original living form they then write reports that
bananas have potassium and oranges have vitamin C yeah those things kind of
emerge after you do all those things to them in a laboratory you know so it's
like no one really knows what's in food you see the close the one who came the
closest to it was Rudolf Hoschka which we've mentioned before and he's the
father of vitamins and he found was looking to see what gave food its
vitality I think we've mentioned him before yeah so less last week yeah so
there's been a major pull away from that but again we always bring up the idea
that if humanity is deceived about headquarters how are they going to
proceed from headquarters into other things and adventure into other concepts
and again ties into the health of the spirit or health of the mind and if
you're deceived about yourself aren't you going to pretty much it you know
resonate with deception and pretty much emit deception and that's one of the
things that hasn't been addressed just like earlier I was saying you know in
private conversation or even not so private people that you run into of all
walks of life will admit that people have been dumbed down but it's always
no it's not it's never them you ever notice that you know it's never them
that they know and the other meme that you hear in society is like oh yeah
we're psychopaths we're being run by psychopaths oh yeah but it's it's never
you of course it's never it's no one in your family no one you know no no no no
no I haven't forbid you know it's it's quite interesting how there is this
retraction from objectivity that tends to not be acknowledged and also the the
aspect of everything has been created in the past century or lesser actually
right now it seems to be everything sort of came into creation about 20 years ago
it's very difficult for people to go even beyond that you know by listening to
the discussions you know so again you know yeah the concept of a healthy let's
say spirit or mind you know what is it what is it hinged on psycho psychopathy
is the is you know the inverse of that psyche and pathos being the roots the
root words of the psychopath pain spirit right well being pain and psyche being
spirit yeah and again we could keep reiterating it in the language the way
we communicate let's say in English being the langua franca franca what is
it when you see the word PSY in a prefix what is it implying get back to
that in a minute we're listening or several minutes folks listening to
American Freedom Radio and hopefully streaming on UStream to Seth Michael and
the Greek at Uncommon Sense yes and we're back we're streaming again on
UStream and we're on American Freedom Radio and this is Uncommon Sense with
the Greek and Seth Michael so yeah we were kind of getting this week into the
aspect of mental health and showing how you know what what is it what's going
on and Seth where do we leave off I believe trying to use the colloquial PSY
prefix which we find in the English language yes what would you say on that
we've been beating this horse which is still alive hopefully about the PSY and
then the PNU prefix for years now how would you sum it up before because you
might do it really well we don't have to go into it again but what do you think
about that the PNU was found in words that are common in English such as
pneumonia or pneumatics is air and the PSY is spirit mind one in the same PSY
so psychiatry psychology psychology would be study of the spirits or the
mind and you know pneumatics is the use of air such as in pneumatic tools air
air powered drills you know impact wrenches things of that nature that's an
easy tangible way to look at it and see it and also an accurate way to think of
it in your mind if you're trying to deconstruct words and find out what the
maybe what the sounds themselves originally connotated when they were
first being used and it's about also being mindful as also like being
spiritual in a way about it meaning you know in the DNA language or the DNA
which are the DNA people which are I believe derogatory called Navajo there
are the DNA people even in their language the term I believe us Nick day
or Nick Jay which which means spirit it means that the leader right it's
something but it's intangible one right and I don't recall their word for soul
but it actually means the breath right when it's defined so every culture in
the world you will find that the mind is the spirit and the breath is the soul
every culture in the world throughout history sans this one by the way you
will find that when the body dies the body is dead when the soul is dead right
and the spirit departs and these basic aspects believe me and I say believe me
meaning well the word belief just means that you know a bit of information that
holds true right now and you're not so sure if it'll hold true later but it
holds so much truth right now that it'll probably hold that truth later right
that's what belief is based on you know like gravity you know you believe that
you know if you drop something right now it'll fall but due to gravity there's a
pretty good belief that if you do it in five minutes or five years it will
happen that's all belief is it has to be founded on something that's why I said
believe me when you when I state that if you approach if you find this out to be
a good reference point right like learning how to read a tape measure on a
construction site so you can build things right when you discover what the
mind the body and the soul are and you try to discuss this with people you will
be met with opposition not not because we're starting some kind of
revolutionary group or trying to get people to oppose others no that's not
the point the point is when you come to even just the person next to you or for
someone you might meet or someone that is allegedly a teacher or not you will
be met with resistance on this matter what say you on that Seth would you find
that to be pretty accurate statement oh certainly resistance on an intellectual
level actually like an almost unwillingness to consider such concepts
in a way that they have not considered them before correct yeah it's about
considering you'll find a lot of the entitled classes whether they are the
you know the attorneys the scientists the religious or a quote-unquote
spiritual leaders which are different by the way because you can be a traffic
cop and you're very religious because you're doing something very regularly
just means you're doing it regularly so you will find when you approach people
in society that are specialists or self-proclaimed or others proclaim them
to be experts in a field if you actually look up what they are quote-unquote
practicing or putting out you will find major discrepancies and they will loosely
always state that they're basing their field on this body of work but if anyone
goes and looks into it you will see the hypocrisy that they're actually not
they're kind of making things up as they go along hopefully that other people
won't find out about it there's essentially one of the definitions of
what's going on in society right now I've seen this I've heard it I've
experienced it what I mean I've seen it by reading an article about something
and then looking up what that something is about and it doesn't match I've heard
it by listening to people speak on certain topics and then I look up what
they're supposedly basing it on and it's not there or it's highly inaccurate and
I've experienced it by you know wanting to let's say do something the way I told
it should be and then I look into it and study it and I realized that the way I
was told was not correct and there's a I don't think that most of the problems
or problems at all I think they're stemmed on a sick spirit or a sick mind
well one that is not doing well lacks lax levity you know and is also very
lazy mm-hmm lax nutrition and noxious there's there's there's a thought for
food perhaps yeah there are there are a few passages in scripture that uh that
speak directly to that and the idea is not to empower an individual to go like
a go-to type person this is what mankind likes to do right the idea is not to
empower them with all of your energy in that direction right like let's say you
run into someone who is says they're a healer or a spiritual person or a
scientific person or they like what they say you know someone who's got a radio
show or someone who is good at performing something in society the idea now has
been to empower that individual people just say oh I'll just send them whatever
they need and they'll just do what they're doing and I'll be fine because
what they're doing is what I need right see what's happening here is instead of
in fully empowering these people in society why don't you go ahead and you
know if you like what they're doing go ahead and support them but resist be a
little hold back a little bit a little bit of time and energy and look up what
they're telling you try to validate right so there's a lot of people out there and
let's say let's use the internet as an idea and they write books put out DVDs
some of them been doing it for 50 years they say and others just came on the
scene and everyone and everything in between and people I've seen it and
heard it wholeheartedly fall into subscribing to what this person is
saying as quote-unquote gospel and I'm not saying don't do this with
individuals but what I'm saying is if you're going to spend all of this energy
and giving them all of your energy to believe in what they're telling you
reserve about five or ten percent of it to actually look up what they're telling
you and see if it is so and the more energy you research what they're saying
you put into you the less you will find that you should be doing what you're
doing with them anyway and you become empowered you hear about a lot of these
gurus or teachers or masters or spiritualists or scientists or health
people or political people economic people and I've listened to them all and
I would say it's the opposite less than five percent of what they're saying you
will find to be true but yet most people give a hundred percent of their energy to
listening to these people instead of you know being more reserved and they
will find out if they start investing a little bit of time into checking up on
what they're saying there they will not it will be more conservative and not be
dumping energy I mean into here's a good example Seth are the megachurches in the
u.s. right I don't know if I would use the word good yeah but exactly a good
example of how people dump all their energy into something that is false yeah
certainly yeah it's a well yes yeah absolutely because what's being espoused
is not accurate right I have an interesting view of such things as just
simply being a social club like a like a brand a cult if you view the word cult
as the root of culture as opposed to taking it from the occult which I mean
is the same same root I'm not talking about something that's hidden I'm
talking about what's done in plain sight it's a it's the type of culture
it's a it's a brand it's a it's a brand of belief it's a brand of not having to
look anything up it's a it's the following the leader and if you're
following the leader the view never changes so but here's the thing just to
go back on what I said about them being false and what you brought up is
actually let's clarify they are not false for example this big evangelistic
whatever they always strictly tell you that this is about the church right they
they strictly they strictly tell you that pretty much law has been done away
with so now we have we look up the definition of what church means and it
comes from the word Circe or Kiriaki in Greek or Circe which is the goddess
which the circus was formed around which just means circus and then they tell you
there's no law so if you look at the two basic definitions on that they are
lawless and their circus so they're not lying to you really direct but the
thing is people are misinterpreting what's being said and is it spiritual
absolutely it's all of the mind right but then we go back to the rat feces and
hot dogs anyway that's another you see how they could what quality are you
doing you know what's the level of spiritual the quality is very low
obviously when you look at that right as it does it deals with an aspect of
the mind which is part of the crowd again we go back to the bonds comments on
that that whenever you find people in a group albeit how small or how large when
this group is forming because even a small group might stay small but the
mentality is still the same where they're joined regarding a certain
subject or a topic you know whether it's secular or non-secular and in
between you might find let's say a good example so is the UFO community right if
you look at you know the paranormal stuff they come under this concept but
if you actually look at what the end you know what it's based on you won't
find let's say a continuous or anything validatable you know it's again he said
she said it's very much also in the religious movements he said she said this
is what I believe it doesn't matter you know what you believe that I'm fine with
I was what I believe the same with the scientific community you know this is a
theory you know and by the way we've always suggested that people look up
what the word academic means because right now it holds prestige in some
capacity but if you actually look up what it means it means to be impractical
theoretical and never leading to a conclusion and also just to tie that
back in when you bring up the word spiritual everyone thinks it's something
good
oh he's so spiritual but it's not telling me what quality of spirit is it an
evil spirit is it a good spirit is it a dark spirit you see is it is it a lying
spirit is it a spirit of truth is it a spirit of death is a spirit of life
you ever notice that people oh he's so spiritual like yeah okay what kind of
spirit with quality of spirit oh well you know it's it's good what makes it
good well I like it like wow you know come on people let's get it together and
when I say come on people only addressing about five people I think we
only have about five listeners and by the way Seth we had about a hundred
somewhat views on the YouTube stream and we don't know how many archives are
viewed again you know meaning the archives and that's 20 times more than we
thought we'd ever get so appreciate that but this might be the only programming
that is put in digital format that is actually geared to about five or ten
people on the planet you know so that's why perhaps the discussions tend to go
the way they do absolutely I would suggest that if anyone wants more
information on a particular point or anything to email us uncommon sense
radio one right uncommon sense radio with the number one following it at
gmail.com or you can email me directly dear red shoes d-a-r-r-e-d-s-h-o-e-s
at gmail.com and eventually here and probably maybe perhaps even next week
we'll you know open the lines so to speak and have the ability for people to call
in and join the conversation for a little bit to further clarify anything
in particular because we do jump around quite a bit and the Greek and I have
spent a lot of time speaking publicly and privately on these on a lot of these
you know topics and subjects that brought up so some of it to us we might you know
blaze through something that is maybe not even difficult to grasp but might
need a little bit further explanation and so we'll we'll do that and until we
do that live you're you know you're welcome to use the this interesting form
of communication at our fingertips to contact us. Now Seth what's interesting is
I think you've also looked at the emails from all the emails we've gotten
have all been positive and encouraging and also we've had a lot of query a lot
of questioning and what I found to be in common with all of the questions they
tend to lead to the biblical aspect or topic of things and you and I briefly in
public stated that it's not time yet to discuss that with accuracy at this point
and yes anyone can gain accuracy on any subject all you have to do is engage it
directly and don't read into it read out of it you will be surprised what you
might find but just to go back to that topic even just this week we've gotten a
couple of emails regarding the nature of things biblical and when I say that
term I'm using it loosely in communication and I believe you and I
Seth have spent great time in public discussing how even started a few years
ago in public discussing how as you see time go on people will have an increased
interest in that subject and not only biblical but all spirituality none of it
will be accurate or worth mentioning as being accurate but the interest will
increase in that subject and wow isn't it interesting when you start to find
things that you knew were coming that actually manifest certainly I think some
of that has to do with the fact that you know it's spoken of in an uncommon
manner here and it's something that is almost take it for granted as a part of
you know the Western culture that we find ourselves in and so for it to be
discussed in a manner that is unique is there's going to be at least you know a
handful of people that realize that and catch on to it and want further
clarification and there's there's a lot of excuse me a lot of clarification to
toward any semblance of accuracy or before any any semblance of accuracy you
know I'm trying to learn languages specifically for the purpose of studying
old books but eventually what was something like the biblical text you'll
find out that there's no requirement to learn a special language and that's kind
of like the labor that's required in one way indirectly but I want to just state
one thing which is a fact that right now there seems to be holistically no
accurate discussion on the biblical text holistically there only is little
frack fragments someone might pick up something and say look at this it's not
what you guys think it is but as a whole there is nowhere to go on the internet
or in the physical world where you will get accurate information regarding that
text period what I mean by that is the way to identify what I just said is being
true is very simple if anyone it doesn't matter who it is high or low in
ranking social rank if they start giving something that is supposedly based on
the biblical text regardless of the character loosely defined or something in
an event if they don't preface what they're saying as reminding the
audience that even to this date what is known as the Bible has not been
translated out of Hebrew and Greek with the original scriptures what you have is
a version I loosely represent a loose representation that is actually more
erroneous than correct that exists in the world today in any language in any
version and it in other words the original text has yet to be translated
into English or any other language to this day this must be prefaced you know
and it is not and you have people from every walk of life all the way from the
schools of divinity which are an utter joke all the way down to the man on the
street who thinks he's got a good idea discussing matters that are biblical and
actually believing and thinking that what they have is the actual biblical
text in a version form and this is the first thing that will that needs to be
established that it is not available to the world in any accurate form even
today other than the how it's been preserved in the Hebrew and Greek and
that is really a sad state of affairs not because it hasn't been translated but the
sad state of affairs is the discussions and things that are built upon what's
called the Bible on something that's completely erroneous known as the King
James Version when all of the versions by the way are based on King James how
do you know if you open up a Bible it doesn't matter what version it is if the
first verse is in the beginning God created the heavens and the earth that
is a King James Version period so there is no availability and accurate access
to the text right now outside of the Hebrew and Greek scriptures where it is
still being preserved so that would that right there makes discussion direct
discussion about the text nearly impossible the only possible discussion
that can be a valid discussion on the text or any character in the text
whether it's Adam and Eve or Abraham or the Christ or anything beyond that the
only way to discuss these topics or characters or events or anything like
that is by first correcting the mistakes that are in the versions and bringing up
what should be said about it instead of what is been delivered to the
public and I believe we've done that several hundred times already in
specificity Seth you and I in public including on other things like you know
what what people are doing is when they approach the biblical text even in the
poor version that they have they have already their minds have been
completely misdirected through Hollywood churchy entity Sunday school
their parents urban myth about anything and when they approach the biblical text
and read it they are reading into it not reading out of it you know like the
giving another example or a specific example on that I had there's some
discussion about the burning bush coming up here and there and I I kind of like I
couldn't hold back anymore I'm like you know there is no burning bush what are
you talking about burning bush is that let's like Hollywood stuff man that's
stuff they teach you in church it's no go look at the text there's no burning
bush what are you talking about and one person said holy crap he's right look
it's right here and I'm like yeah where'd you get the burning bush from you know
it's it's really fascinating how that just it just took one person five
seconds to look it up and but yet you will go throughout the world and
billions of people think there's a burning bush absolutely so how do you
know and by the way should we just give them the spoiler absolutely it takes a
few seconds well there's a scene where Moses is a particular mountain or a
mountain or let's say we're alone in a rural area let's say and he sees an
angel that is giving off fire and the angel Moses is kind of astounded let's
say and he and the the angel stands puts a bush between him and Moses and the
statement is that the bush is not being consumed by the angels fire so where's
the burning bush in other words the what's actually going on here is he sees
a spiritual being that is emitting what looks like fire but that fire does not
actually consume something that is combustible so it's a different kind of
fire well there's no burning bush where's the burning bush the bush does
not get burned obviously that was the point it's just misdirection what you
yeah oh I'm going yeah and this is this is pertinent to every subject there's
people out there discussing Noah's Ark and the flood outside of there being
some rain and something that floats and some animals none of it is correct
none of the discussions none of the scholars there's someone who is touted as
the biblical expert on Noah's Ark or flood and you go to their website they
tell you it had three levels and you got to just do a double facepalm and say
wow this is really sad because it's quite interesting that when you stood in
the ark you had one floor below and two above you how many floors are there
let's say you walk into a building and I say you there's one floor below you and
there's two floors above you how many floors in total that would be four yeah
I mean we're talking about the most rudimentary basic discussion cannot be
carried because it's all hinged on erroneousness because people are reading
in they're not reading out you know this is this is this goes on with pretty much
every topic you know so where is you know how is this considered a spiritual
is you know mentally or spiritually healthy you know well let's just say
maybe people are really here to be based on stability on food clothing and
shelter I've ever heard that being discussed it's all about food clothing
and self shelter at this point and that would be the basics of existing and I
would say that most people on this planet have not gotten beyond that point
food clothing shelter when it comes to matters of thought when it comes to
matters of communication they are failing as a society I have a question
from the you stream chat here and that is are are the hosts familiar with the
scriptural works of Ernest L Martin absolutely I'm not go ahead yeah
Ernest L Martin was part of the UCG it was a movement back in the 50s and 60s
and I'm not going to be shy or about it but I'll tell you right now they did
some very good work excellent work pioneering work I was very high marks
from the grading point of view their pitfall was essentially greed the greed
there was they didn't have the balls or the cojones or the guts to come out and
and blatantly show that Christianity is 100% paganism what they did was they
mixed in the the cultural aspect of what's the cult the Christian era
meaning the world religion right now into their works and that was their
biggest problem and and they're always addressing the Christian aspect and
there is no Christianity in the Bible biblical text period at all it's only
used once by Agrippa as a derogatory term and the word means Messianic or a
zealot or revolutionary so what's interesting about Ernest L Martin he's
done some excellent work but you've got to really do shake your head and see how
he's directing it obviously from there's some kind of monetary gain you
see if you're discussing any religious text if you don't gravitate towards the
religious group that has hijacked that text you will be broke you will not be
able to make a dime doing it so in other words if you go out and study scripture
and actually do research to prove that it's historically accurate and do not
attach yourself to the human culture known as the human cultural aspect known
as the religious group of Christianity or Judaism which would be the two major
groups that have hijacked that text let's say you will be broke you will not
be able to fund anything no one will want to listen to you might have a small
little group of people here and there that are doing it because they want
clarification on the subject but I assure you no one will buy your stuff no one
will give you any money you will be broke you will be eating out of garbage
cans right and that is from the secular point of view but from a belief point of
view if you're doing the right thing even though it seems to be a bad business
decision because you're not accommodating a particular cultural group I believe
there's a higher force that will support you and because of that this group that
Ernest Martin was involved in had failed and that's what I know and believe and
the reason I'm bringing this up is because it's very good to study their
work and other work of others but the problem is they are always stuck on this
Christian aspect of things only because they wanted to support themselves what
there's nothing wrong with supporting themselves on that but what would it
obviously showed is that they had very little faith in a higher power even
though they proclaim to be bringing out accurate information on it that's that's
almost like a personal commentary on on Ernest Martin but otherwise he's done
very good work just avoid the allegory and comparativeness to what a Christian
should be and you'll be fine with his work hopefully wasn't too harsh yeah
yeah he's written a lot of good stuff there are others that are written really
good things as well that you that are less popular during that movement that
came before him that is there's there's quite a bit of accurate discussion but
none of it in one place at all and you will not find it anywhere right now in
one place it's all in pieces in other words the kingdom is in pieces it's
fractured and part of the end let's say endeavor stuff you and I have discussed
it is quite possible to bring forward a very good accurate presentation on what
the biblical text is in a neutral positive very accurate way right that
will edify humanity and it hasn't done yet but I believe you and I have
discussed the formula of it and it's very clear that if anything's going to
be brought out into public you must understand the timing there is a timing
to do it right and there's a timing to not do it and right now is clearly not
the time to do it in as a project as you know bringing it out forward you
know what these things mean and how they were meant to be looked at based on
what is in the text itself not what you think it is reading out of it this is
still not the time but getting very close getting very close and this is
regarding any subject whether it's scientific whether it's legal whether
it's biblical medical it is still not the time the let's just say the the the
wall of lies that people have been bowing down to as being the the be-all
end-all of all of these subjects is starting to fall apart the mortars
getting loose and the wall is cracking at this point but to break through the
wall to see what any of these subjects are truly about it's not time yet we
have discussed the basic parameters of it but not really presenting the truth
behind these matters whether it's legal scientific or religious I think we've
hinted quite a bit certainly certainly I would say that the method of
communication is something of value in in discussing and but I mean we use
words that's how we communicate thought and regardless of the language if you're
you know looking at something that's old it's good to know how those words were
used then and what they meant just as it would be now in you know a technical
manual of any sort you know you can increase your knowledge of almost any
subject by familiarizing yourself with the language that is used to describe it
be that you know anything anything at all so and it's all communication let's
just go back to the biblical text to show you a contrast of why it's not time
yet if you look at one of the institutions that's hijacked the concept
of the biblical text is the legal society you go into a courtroom and they
still not as much as in the past they ask you to put your hand on a King James
Bible and swear right I say you want me to you want me to make an idol out of
this this document here right exactly forbids idolatry and then you want me to
swear which this document also forbids very specifically yes go ahead yeah yeah
but the point here is this is say well okay so what is this book is it the
telephone book what is it a book set a cookbook no no it's the biblical text
okay so it's just black ink on white paper bound together that has a specific
communication known as the biblical text so it's not the telephone book it's not
a recipe you know a book it's not you know Mark Twain or anything like that
okay so it's still a communication of the biblical text but okay so if it's
about the communication of the information I have it downloaded right
here on a thumb drive I think I'm just gonna swear on that instead can I do
that no no no no you can't do that it has to be this particular book so you see
the stupidity of this it's paganism it's the rabbit's foot it's the paganism just
means ignorant right it's the it's a form of low-level magic what's going on
it's just a communication the biblical text it doesn't matter if it's simple I
would reckon people yes it doesn't matter if it's printed on paper or on a
scroll or on a thumb drive or download it on the computer or if you've
memorized it the thing is what are you getting out of the communication what
are you getting out of the information if the answer is nothing you're close
that's exactly what is going on you see it's like that with anything just let's
just jump around real quick to medicine you know there's this thing right now I
call it a form of bioterrorism to terrorize right is to inflict I guess
terror using the same word to define itself or fear on a population right now
the population is under a form of bioterrorism by these by the Institute
the medical and society by something called viruses you know you've heard of
that everything is now caused by a virus and even the most learned people that
are speaking so I almost I got the flu I must have caught a virus I mean
stupidity is just astounding but you know here's the thing if you go and
research the medical society's works on viruses and very simply you will find
the National Institute of Health and various other there's a corporation
called the CDC and other things like that which people think is actually
government it's not it's like GM General Motors you know it's just a company but
if you go look at all the academic works on this they're very thick documents long
PDFs and you say oh because this is 900 pages they know a lot about viruses but
do me a favor folks go pull up a document on viral research and read the
introduction it'll tell you the purpose of this research is to discover what the
viruses are and they're in their relationship to disease okay now then go
to the conclusion and they'll tell you that we still don't know what viruses
are or there's it's inconclusive that they cause disease why the hell would
you read the 900 pages in the middle well the same reason people swear on
the Bible because it's paganism it's ignorance and this is how you're being
ruled and terrorized by the way and by the way demos means terror and crossy
means to rule by or the state so you're anyway that's another concept right
there so again regarding the health of the mind or the health of the spirit
could it be that if what's in the mind or the spirit is unfounded or not based
on anything or it's just based on some kind of culture that is descended into
materialism and paganistic practices does that lead to a healthy mind or a
healthy spirit which by the way means the same thing and the answer would be
no and the question is here are you going to get one that is helpful no
you're not as a society you will get a little more clarity on these matters
before future events take place and as they're taking place but you will be
other than the few individuals that do the discipline in the work and get
strength in their minds or their spirit will be able to do better just like
people who are not feeling well when they tend to be recovering they say I
need some exercise now get out of bed and walk around and you feel stronger you
know the more weight you can carry the stronger you get and and that is a
level of laziness people don't want to carry things or remember things or learn
things so they remain in a state of weakness so you know the the aspect of
talking about things uncommon might lead back to realizing that things that are
uncommon are things that are quite obvious if we're going to look at things
as being common well that's fine too what is commonly being done that's okay
we tend to relax and you know want to be part of a group let's say actually you
shouldn't be but anyway if we start to try to validate what the common folks
and what is commonly accepted you will see that it's basically not founded on
anything there is no basis to it or what they tell you it is based on it's really
not so how does that lead to being you know pertinent how can you actually get
things done but apparently you might say Greek things are getting done we're
still building houses we still have boats and planes and trains and we do
all this other stuff yes okay you are getting a lot of things done in quantity
but what about the quality of those things in order to mind the quality of
something you must have a foundation to find out how you can measure and manage
what it's based on in a simple way to look at it as well as looking at the
financial system you know the legal system how can that be measured and
managed if you see what these things are supposedly based on you will find that
they're not in accordance with them at all they are not based on the things
that you believe that they are and that does not lead to a healthy mind or
spirit and it's very simple to to see that and the only thing here would be
the you know is there is there an effort being made and the answer is no you know
again if we're going to discuss what is uncommon it's very simple the obvious is
uncommon anything that's being discussed anything that's being looked at
has to have a basis in something let's say albeit physical perhaps or material
not always communication could be immaterial or intangible but it still is
very viable it is primary informative to before things happen when a command is
given that is a form of communication and the quality and the direction of
that command leads into action so you know again the you know how does this
have to do with the mind being in a good state perhaps one can be in a good state
of mind and everything they think they know is fictional or false or a lie you
know and does that eventually catch up to them that's an interesting point to
discuss as well because it can be easily easily assured that the majority
of humanity has gone from the craved cradle to the grave and pretty much
everything they believe or think exists does not and or pretty much everything
they think they know is a lie ever since they were from the cradle and until they
were an old man or an old woman everything they believe is a lie so how
were they in a healthful condition well one might say well they were pretty
happy all their lives you know even though they died believing you know that
voting mattered and going to church had something to do with the Bible or the
the molten iron core in the earth caused gravity you know I mean yeah they seem
pretty helpful and all that so you know there's there's an aspect to this that's
very subtle and what does that tell you maybe it wasn't meant for them to know or
you know hey they had a pretty happy life I mean there is a lot of old cats
right now on the internet still kicking around selling books doing websites
being interviewed all over the place and you know people flock to it and say hey
these guys are old they know what they're talking about and I could show
you how they don't anybody could show you how they don't eight-year-old could
in five minutes but everyone still likes it makes them happy so there's an aspect
to happiness and joy that can be pursued that that might might be transcending
mental health being even though the mental health being based on a lie you
know or not in other words if again someone can go from cradle to grave and
everything they think they know or believe is a complete lie and they could
lead a pretty happy healthful you know physical life and I assure you that's
the case of most people that have come to this planet and have passed away and
and the old ones that are still around and the young ones but the interesting
part of this discussion is that there are things that people call problems
things they call endeavors things that they consider to be things bigger than
themselves things that they want to establish and have things that come in
the way whether they're legal scientific political or what have you and they view
these things as problems and without these things as probably view problems
along the way that can't be solved or conundrums and the suggestion here to be
made that's uncommon is very simply if you put things in order if a topic is
brought up regardless of what the topic is if you spend a little bit of time to
see if what is being presented in front of you can be validated you will also
find this the source or the root of what you might call a problem to be there as
well okay it's very it's very simple like regardless of what the topic is
let's say religious matters you hear of all these religious groups always
fighting well if you go back and look at what their religions are supposed to be
based on you will find all the texts are very similar and it actually tells you
not to fight but you know if you bring that back to the groups that are
fighting they don't want to see it but they only want to see things that suits
their purpose or drive the same thing with the legal community if you go and
look at any legal societies texts that they supposedly are basing their low laws
codes rules and regulations on them you'll notice that by definition they're
not doing any of it they're not even familiar with any of it right they're
only taking a small aspect of it and using it right and same thing with the
scientific community same thing with the politicians as every aspect the
medical community does the same you know if anyone if you've discussed had
discussions with people that had gone to the medical society for help if it's
not a usual or common problem which you know what's another thing here they
typically all they do is subscribe prescribe painkillers and antibiotics
and if they don't want to acknowledge what you have they tell you you have
some kind of unknown virus so again they're not really looking into what
their studies are based on I had once gone to a dental technician or
practitioner also known as a dentist doctor and I wanted something done and I
researched it and when I approached him how I wanted it done he said wow Greek I
haven't heard that in 20 years since I was in medical school I said okay so
you're not familiar with this procedure I guess I am I haven't heard of that in
20 years and I said okay so how many of these procedures have you done in the
past 20 years says thousands of them I said when you mean you haven't really
gone back and looked at how it should be done properly I guess not this is the
level of existence of humanity at this point I think we have set back as well we
do have set back as well excellent so again uncommon is just the idea is to
just pretty much if you hear about something just investigate and you know
there's there's any good did you share any any links to photographs of viruses
yeah there no such thing by the way yeah you'll never find a photograph of one
you'll find a computer graphic right yeah yeah you'll you'll find a color
enhanced image of a damaged cell yeah broken mitochondria perhaps the smallest
of the smallest aspect of the cell probably be the mitochondria yeah yeah
it's just and what's interesting by the way since you brought up viruses again
if you look it up in any capacity the initial definition is a virology is a
branch of toxicology and all of toxicology has to deal with things that
emit through or by the liver so yeah there's there's a beauty in it you know
even with discussing words Seth you know when I bring up a word and I said you
know you use the word nice you know to people I said you know what that means
yeah I know what it means I said no it doesn't really mean that according to
the reference material well what does it mean then I usually tell them to look it
up themselves the reason why is it seems like when they look it up themselves it
seems to have about 70 or 80 percent more impact on them as if you know it
has to be done that way you know so you have to be kind of inefficient with
spreading information because people are still locked into the shock value of
seeing it for themselves which is actually appropriate as well you see you
know I rather have people yeah look it up and read it recently I was on a
private call and they were discussing something about the academics this and
academics that I said would you please go to an etymological dictionary and
they're like why and I said well do you would you just you know fulfill that
request for me just for a moment and they did and I said put academic into
the search box and I said okay why am I doing this I said because you'll see in
a moment I said read the definition and use the
terms they said oh my god is that what it means and I said yep that's what it
means and they're like holy crap I've been using that word wrong along that
thing academic means it's not doesn't mean anything good and I'm like yep
that's right would you believe would you have believed me if I would have told
you and they said no there you go absolutely and part of what we're trying
to do here is in part a sense of perhaps let's just say the more you the
more weight you can carry the stronger you are just like an elephant you know
why are elephants known for their strength well they inherently carry a
lot of weight on their own anyway right you know so the more weight you could
carry the stronger you will be anyone that goes to the gym will tell you that
you know and which which is also also what I'd like to bring back since we
were discussing mental or spiritual health how many times do you still hear
on the alternative media being banded around oh that's all fear porn that's
fear-based man you know these are the same people that tell you that you know
it's your intent love and light and your intention actually means something you
know but but anyway this whole thing about fear so yeah that's fear it's bad
I'm like okay let's just look at this a little closely now well if fear like
love and other things exist within society are we to run away and avoid it
or is it something that could be handled properly and efficiently and
effectively and I would say the second part is true if you fear disabled by fear
if you feel disabled by fear that means that you lack spiritual or mental
fortitude or strength and also you lack skill those are the two components that
are required loosely termed to deal with what is called fear and I've used this
analogy before Seth if I could go do it one more time like for example if you
do not know how to operate a dishrag or a mop you're in total fear of a glass of
milk spilling over right but if you're in the presence or of someone or if you
yourself know how to operate a dishrag or a mop and a glass of milk spills over
well you then go into your skill set of operating a dishrag in a mop and you
clean it up and the person who doesn't have that skill set is totally terrified
and you're like don't worry dude it's just spilled milk right right so so the
lack of skill and the laziness of lack of skill in these matters also builds
doesn't build but does the opposite atrophies the mind and atrophies the
spirit and they get weaker and weaker and weaker so from one aspect the fear
aspect is disabling and weakening but it's actually those that are commenting
on the fear that are promoting it you see so if you are disabled by fear or
fearful of fear it means that you are weak minded weak spirited same thing and
lack skill it's just again the alternative media how many times have
you turned into an alternative media venue and the first thing they start
talking about is what Fox News and CNN or the news of the day which shows me that
there is a continuous thread that goes through the entire society whether it's
mainstream or alternative it's the same stuff you know at one point I put a
comment and I when it when our microphones gonna cost a million bucks I
think that's the best way to stop the nonsense right because then anyway so
anyway if microphones cost a million bucks that'd be fewer people on the
internet so any that's another comment there I guess you know bullets should
cost a million bucks right I think there's a little bumper thing on this
tip yeah it's not the gun so it's the same thing so this is the thing is about
this fear the other thing I hear a lot about still is the Federal Reserve being
harped on nonsense you know Federal Reserve is just accommodating you the
petrochemical companies are just accommodating you the corporations oh
no did you Seth did you know that there are evil corporations or corporations are
bad did you know that Seth oh gosh man I've been listening to a lot of people
talk about how bad corporations are did you know that gosh I didn't know that
man I mean the position part of the corporation or not but yeah yeah this is
just ridiculous you point yeah but they they they all love it like you know
here's here's a deep dig and everyone's talking about the Federal Reserve is so
bad but they love the PayPal I don't care where I don't care how I get it as
long as I go to the store and get something for it but Federal Reserve is
bad oh man you know it's it's not yeah it's not very good state because no one
is really looking into it now here's the point when something runs you know that
there's the horse running out of the barn yeah you know you have the horse in
the barn you know you could deal with it if it runs out of the barn you got it
you could still deal with the horse it just takes more effort right but what
happens if the horse has run out of the barn broken its leg was shot in the head
and is in the glue factory what are the chances of getting that horse back
relatively slim yeah and that's the state of affairs of humanity right now
but on the other hand we always kind of talk about what's coming in the future
because yes folks we know the future and so do you if you put a little time into
it what's coming in the future now is a series of events that are going to
proceed before let's say come before you get what you have coming to you as a
society and that will be a perfect society on this planet yes no war
prosperity Liberty Liberty just means time off from the things you have
commitments to it's coming and it's right around the corner next decade
you're going to be experiencing the bastion of perfection and it will be
promised to you as lasting for a thousand years and you're all gonna buy
into it yes you are all of you and you know who all of you are if you're
listening to me and that is the great deception because it's only gonna last
for a short time so these things must happen but as a group as a society
you're not you're not faring well and you're not going to do well and that's
very easy to see I mean there's lots of people telling you you're going to do
better and there's lots of people telling you you're going to give doom
and gloom but I assure you none of them are giving you any specifics on how none
of them it's the same as going to a car mechanic to have the car fixed you tell
them what's wrong with it and before you leave you give them the keys and the
mechanic turns around and says to you by the way where is the steering wheel
and everyone says oh it's right there in the middle see ya whoa whoa whoa wait a
second you're telling me you brought the car to a mechanic and he doesn't know
where the steering wheel is how do you think the rest of it's gonna go you're
being had folks so this is part of what's being uncommon yes everyone on the
alternative media everyone in the mainstream when I say everyone I mean
statistically 99.9999999 percent there probably there's probably someone out
there saying something that we haven't heard of yet there's a small group of
people that have mastery in their fields like we suggested Frank Chester you know
there's a couple of more here and there but there's nothing going on folks the
lights are on and nobody's home well the lights are on and everybody's home but
no one knows Jack you know what and that's the state of humanity reported to
you this week again by Seth and the Greek at Uncommon Sense indeed and that's
not a rant folks it's the truth absolutely on the last few minutes of
the broadcast I'd like to just apologize again for my own technical issues here
well it's filled me dealt with but yeah we do appreciate everyone out there who
is listening if you'd like to contact us Uncommon Sense radio one at gmail.com
uncommon radio.com is the website it's like a business card and AFR can use
your help and you know how to do that folks yeah and thanks America and
freedom radio.com yep and thanks again folks we'll see you again soon