Greetings, this is American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
And this is the Uncommon Sense, Call it the Show, and you're with the Greek and Seth Michael.
And we'll have Seth here in a moment, folks, sorry about that again.
Seems to be the technical difficulty era for this show, but we're going to just see how
it works out.
Seth, are you with us?
Hello.
Shalom, I believe so.
Yes, you are.
Okay.
So we just did our, we're live on the air at American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
And this is Uncommon Sense with the Greek and Seth.
Yes, welcome.
Welcome to the program.
Greek, as always, it's good to hear your voice.
Yeah, great.
Same.
And, you know, what's interesting, we always like to say, you know, let's just get into
the matter, but it's very difficult to just jump in because, you know, there's certain
ways of communicating and people like a preface and things like that.
But one of the things we'll always preface is the reason we're doing this get-together
publicly is because we're trying to figure out why certain things that are so freaking
obvious aren't being discussed.
So maybe it should be called the freaking obvious subject discussion.
I don't know.
But just to get back to the things at hand, we have two hours, which seems to go by very
quickly.
I want to bring up a point.
We've always gotten very good feedback when I say we, meaning the Greek speaking and anyone
else about the subject matter and the way that it's broached on.
And I just want to start off, perhaps, Seth, I think I made you aware of a message we got
from a listener, and highly commendable, someone really actually listening to the details being
imparted.
And I was thinking of perhaps reading that message and going down that road, even though
it might be unpopular to most.
What do you think of that?
And we'll let you.
I think, yeah, I think that we can.
You shared the message with me just a few minutes ago and I read through it and my response
was what was my response?
Someone is really listening.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, it was someone is really listening and should just be held for private.
And I'm like, well, you know, it's a great topic for discussion.
Yeah.
It would be excellent.
And within the discussion and the message, and as I've been saying, let's say, for years
in public forums, is it's not time yet.
And Seth, do you think that sometimes a precursor or a trailer to the movie or an introduction
to something that it's not time yet for, but might be time coming up that maybe it can
be hinted at or introduced somehow would be valid?
I do.
Yeah.
So here we go.
Let's get into it because time is short.
Message reads thusly, Hi, Greek.
Looking forward to what you and Seth bring forth today.
In the last day, I've listened to your interview with Freeman as well as the first Uncommon
Sense broadcast.
You bring a lot of information forth, although not in too much depth.
I would like to know a little more about you and why what you personally feel the obligation
to tell men about what you see coming.
I'd asked you before how to study scripture.
During Freeman's broadcast, you said you don't recommend people start trying to figure out
scripture because most won't understand it anyway.
I'm confident over time you'll bring forth everything you need to say.
Yet what I'm not hearing is what scripture actually tells us to do to be pleasing to
the ultimate creator, basically how we should conduct our lives, if any certain way.
You said people can contemplate what you are saying, and if we see events start to pass,
we'll know the end is close.
I've always been told through modern evangelicalism to conduct myself a certain way.
Are we supposed to prepare for what happens when our spirit parts with our body?
I'd like to have an idea now how and what to teach my little ones.
I apologize for such a lengthy message.
If anything which can be discussed today, I'd appreciate it.
From someone who is interested, and I think you and I Seth agreed that here is someone
who is listening.
Let's just maybe talk about the subject matter at hand.
I made some bullet points off of that, so don't kind of lose it.
But you know what's interesting, Seth?
Whenever you bring up, let's just, we could talk about general communication and how it's
been obscured.
But when you bring up anything regarding the scripture or the Bible, the majority of the
consensus is, oh no, here we go, religious talk, right?
Or if you want to talk about, let's say, a certain chemical reaction, oh, that's scientific.
Or if we bring up numbers, oh, that's mathematical.
Or it's like, well, chill, people, right?
There's topics, there's general topics, and there's specifics.
It seems like a lot is lost in generalities, but we can get specific on these things, I
believe.
And again, what do you think, Seth, about whenever you discuss anything from the biblical
text, and we can explain what is really going on with the text itself as a way man perceives
it as well, which is another topic, but we might want to a little bit.
I would say that just in general, the first time the subject comes up, I am apprehensive,
I suppose, because there is so much, what is familiar in people's minds, or at least
what appears to be, is that it's traditions.
We're dealing with traditions.
We're not actually, when you and I speak about scripture, we're speaking about what is written,
what has been memorialized.
We're not speaking about the traditions of any earthly hierarchical society.
They've hijacked it, essentially.
It's just like if we say the word government, I assure you, most people's minds all of a
sudden go to politicians, which has nothing to do with it.
So on that aspect, here's the thing, and this might sound dogmatic to some, but I assure
you it's the truth.
If you think 2 plus 2 equals 4 is dogmatic, meaning, well, that's the way it is, and sorry
if you don't think so, would be maybe a loose definition of dogma, right?
You like going and saying 2 plus 2 equals 4 at the market or when you're teaching little
children math, but other statements that broach upon these traditions, let's say, and what
they're regarded as and what they're basing it on.
If you start discussing those things, it sounds dogmatic, oh, we don't want to go there, right?
We can explain that's part of human nature as well.
But what's interesting, Seth, I just want to say this, and I have been saying this for
over a decade and a half almost, is that if you hear anyone discussing anything when they
say the Bible or the scriptures or the biblical text or the scriptural text, let me say this
strictly but loosely, because sometimes it's not done, but it has to be done within a discussion.
If anyone is discussing, again, the Bible or the scripture or anything like that, and
they don't give a condition or say that we're going to discuss the Bible or the scripture,
but it has not been translated out of the languages of preservation into any other language,
all you have are versions of it, they're doing you a disservice, and probably what they're
going to continue and say about it is going to be erroneous, either half true, completely
off, where it has nothing to do with it, or just not really any merit or showing that
there's any basis to it.
So again, when we discuss anything regarding scripture or the Bible, the listenership needs
to keep in mind that those texts are preserved in Hebrew and Greek, and even to this date,
whatever day you want to say it is, let's say, it has not been translated.
And if you have an unabridged version, you could read the introduction and they are very
clear about that.
So we have a problem there as well, you see.
But nonetheless, we can go through the subject matter based on what people might know through
film, Hollywood, or the circus, or churchianity, or through tradition.
I think linking it back to that is important.
Absolutely.
I think that something that might be of interest, at least to the person who sent that message,
would be, you know, some of the, there were actually a couple of direct questions in there
that we could perhaps even provide some more questions for.
Because there's just too many questions.
And just to preface, there's a certain thought pattern that requires labor, let's say, spiritual
labor or labor of the mind.
And before you go and do any labor or run a marathon, you want to do a little bit of
a warm-up.
Let's just say a few things here, which are true, and again, it's not, you're not going
to make friends saying these things, because, and here's the thing.
People tune into media to feel liked, and they like to hear pleasant things, in which
we try to be pleasant, as close as possible to being pleasant.
But there's a Greek philosopher, and I'll paraphrase, he said that a friend to all is
a friend to none.
So that's an interesting thought.
Now that aside, the things that need to be said, folks, and which you might have heard
the Greeks said before, there's not a religion on existence right now in society that does
anything that's in the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
Not a single one.
It doesn't matter if it's Eastern, Western, or Central.
And I can say that specifically for the handful of texts that I have actually read through
myself.
Obviously, I haven't read all of them that there are.
But that has been, you know, that's something that we've discussed years ago, and that the
more I have looked into it, you know, I'm not the sort to just patently accept what
I am, what I hear in conversation, what I'm told, especially if it's something that I
am interested in having a knowledge base in.
And so I can, you know, I can honestly say that through my studies over the past few
years that I haven't found anything to contradict that.
And what's good about this is interesting, because let's say you heard that statement
and you wanted to check up on it.
And it was very easy to see, but just like an immediate thing, like a flashing, you know,
color or something, it would be really shocking to the system.
But when you hear a statement like there's no religion on the planet, bar none, that
does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to, it takes a time to
figure that out because you actually have to go and see the contrast and comparison of
that statement within what the religions are doing and their texts.
Right. And that is not very rapid.
It takes a long time, let's say, or some time.
And because it does that, the shock of that reality is gradual.
So it doesn't kind of like come across your head like a baseball bat.
Right. Which is fortunate because there are certain things, some things that could be
very shocking. And that's what horror films and slasher films are for.
But it's just as shocking when you discover there are seven billion or plus or minus.
Basically, the entire planet has been wholesale deceived and they just go along with
what's comfortable.
You see. And when that statement again is made, you know, fortunately, there is no way
to validate that immediately.
It takes a little bit of research and that little bit of time spreads out the impact.
See, I tell people, see, it's not the crashing that hurts you.
It's the sudden stop.
Right. So that's another statement that has to be made that the other thing is let's
just go more on what people can relate to, which they may or may not know.
There's a field of study amongst humanity known as history.
Right. And, you know, you have to wink, wink and be sarcastic about that.
But let's just say, put that aside.
The secular historians have considered this past two millennia, which would be 2000
years to be considered the Christian era.
OK, it's not it's it's secular.
In other words, we're not talking about religion as as as you might understand it.
But historically, it's been dubbed or labeled, you know, if you were to put this
2000 years in a jar and put it up on a shelf, it would be labeled by them the Christian
era. So when we say the word Christianity, we're not we're going to toggle back and
forth to what actually the traditions of it are and also the historical aspect of it.
So I just wanted to bring that up as well.
So to go into the the because time is short to go into the the message that we received
what's interesting is one of the first things was what obligation does the Greek
sense to tell man about this?
Well, that's a that's a very good question.
But what's interesting, there's a sense of responsibility that if you find out
something and all people do this, when they find out something that brings them joy,
where they find out, find out about something that can help someone.
I'm using that term loosely because generally people want to help other people.
You want to go out and tell others.
And initially, you bring the subject forward or the notion of whatever that is, very
generally, as if someone else already might know about it.
And when you regarding this subject matter, let's say the ancient texts and such, when
I first started discovering what was written, it was very much in contrast to what we were
told about it. And I started discussing this mostly with received without great
opposition. And that forces one to retract.
So I then started thinking about the sanity or how the well-being of what was being said
in terms of what the Greek was saying regarding these things.
And I went back and double checked on everything.
And I found it to be pretty much in accord with what I initially said.
So there is an obligation that one should say things if they're not being said.
There's an obligation to say things, even though if they're not well-received, if they
can be validated or verified.
And that's how I feel about it.
Now, the other thing is, I've said before, the reason why one should say things is to
clear themselves of future guilt.
Why is that? Let's say there's a dam and it's going to break.
And because of a defect and you're aware of that defect and no one else is, you need to
state it. Whether it's fixed or not, or whether the people take precautions to avoid any
kind of disaster, let's say, is up to them.
You know, the interesting point of that is to clear oneself of their guilt, because I've
also said in public before, it's interesting when you watch people in this day and age,
even in the past century, that go out and publicly say, let's say they have an invention
or a good idea. I'm doing this to make the world a better
place. What I say about that is if you're doing it, if you have something like that and
you are doing it to make the world a better place, do it anonymously.
If you focus on telegraphing or messaging that the preface of you doing this to make the
world a better place, you're going to make some really powerful enemies.
The reason why is most people would say, yes, there's a group of oligarchs that don't want
to see that and they will take you out.
But there's also a spiritual side.
There is a parallel community of non-tangible beings.
Yes, you will find that out later.
And they're divided into a benevolent and malevolent group.
Now, obviously, the malevolent group doesn't want to see the world be a better place because
they're malevolent. But also, we've come into a time period now where the benevolent group
doesn't want to see the world a better place because certain things have to take place to
clear the slate. So now you have both the benevolent and the malevolent spiritual
entities, let's say, in that realm against you.
That's why when you look at several people, let's say the inventors of the water car, the
inventors of, quote unquote, free energy or free power devices, cancer treatments and such
and such, once they go public and start saying, I'm doing this to make the world a better
place, they're screwed.
So the thing is to avoid saying that as good advice, do it anonymously.
But from another point of view, there are certain details about anything, whether you
can put the label on it for making the world a better place or not, need to be said
objectively. And that's why I'm speaking, because these are things that anyone can
objectify. And OK, now, another point that was mentioned in the message is the study of
scripture. And this person had heard me speak about this.
And what's interesting through society, there's a religion that has hijacked what's
called the biblical text or the scripture.
Actually, there's more than one.
But one of the religions promotes conversion and belief in their system and accepting a
particular character in all this.
And what's interesting about how this is being promulgated is that there's very little
study in what it's supposed to be based on.
Just as if you're talking to someone about the money system, they're always speaking
about things based on the credit based economy and never referring to lawfulness or what
it should be based on.
The same happens with.
Understanding the text, most people, when they discuss money, they just don't care what
it is, they just care that if they go into commerce, the merchants will accept it and
they get what they want.
What's interesting about religious groups that use what's called the biblical text, they
just get what they want, which is groups of people that seem to be happy and believe the
same thing. But if they actually look at the text, they will find that it's very
contradictory to what they are doing.
And they're supposedly based on that text.
So the reason why I've said the study of scripture, most people will not understand it
is because there's a problem here that when people approach anything in any reference
text and any subject, what they are doing is they're reading into it what they've been
told about it prior to them approaching the subject.
Right. Give an example.
For example, OK, let's just stick to the scriptural text.
If you're reading what's called the New Testament and you get to the point of the
execution of the Christ, instead of actually reading what's being preserved in the
text or written in the text or imparted in the text, you say most people will say, oh,
this is the part that I saw in the movie.
This is the part that they told me about in Sunday school or in church or, you know,
there was a whole bunch of movies made about this.
This is that part.
And they're not actually they're reading it functionally.
But they're not really comprehending what's being written at all because they're
overlaying in their minds what they've been told prior to it.
Very similarly, as if if you go to science, you know, they'll tell you that, you know,
electricity now is defined by protons and electrons or electrons moving down a wire.
If you study this academically, let's say it doesn't sound so outrageous because, you
know, you saw it in, you know, Walt Disney YouTubes or films that, you know, electrons,
this electrons that and you're not really paying attention to how the electrons being
defined. So the reason why I say most people will not understand and I don't recommend
reading scripture in general as a whole is because the individual or the people that
hear this is extremely difficult for them to overcome the the the nature of the
predetermined nature of what they've been told about it.
And whenever they approach the subject, they're reading into it instead of reading out
of it. And the other thing is that we are creatures of convenience.
Otherwise, people wouldn't want to buy microwaves or eat out of a can or whatever,
whatever. And the convenience right now is that they believe that they have the
information memorialized somehow in a version.
And like we stated before, it has not been translated.
So your versions, again, are erroneous at best.
There are other words to describe things like that, but it might seem disrespectful to
most. So that would be the point of why I have not recommended most people read it.
But in a sense, if anyone wants to look at anything, what anything is allegedly based
on, they could, of course, look at that, whether it's scientific, scriptural or legal,
legal. That's a real mess.
Again, just to bring up the legal society, there are no attorneys that know any law or
it includes the judges as such, very simply, because if you were in that legal society
and you started studying law, your own colleagues would oust you because it has
nothing to do with law. The same with science.
If you started actually talking about anything than just pure decomposing materialism
and talking about how things work as opposed to just describing them, you will be
ousted by your own colleagues.
And the same in religious circles.
If you are in any religious circle and you start studying what allegedly that religion
is based on, whether it being any text, because most religions adhere to some form of
text, at least in the Western world and most of the Eastern world.
If anyone in that field started looking at what it's supposed to be based on, they would
be ousted from that community by their colleagues.
And it's very interesting phenomenon.
And this might sound like a very general statement.
And yes, it is. But it's also can be many specific examples can be shown, actually
countless. So that has to be said.
So I'm not suggesting people go and not ever look at any reference material, but I'm
suggesting that they don't, because seemingly on the surface of the general approach that
people take looking at anything, they'll be wasting their time.
I think that a good preface for anyone who is wanting to study, you know, scripture is
Kohalath, which is the book Ecclesiastes in the King James vernacular.
And it is, it's a great, at least I've found it to be in my own studies, very beneficial
in the information that is provided because it speaks of the varying experiences that
many of us go through in life.
Some of it is in metaphor and allegory, but a lot of Kohalath is very direct.
And even in the version that is easily available in English, which would be the King
James version, any of the versions that are available in English are inherently currently
based upon the King James version, which is not good for accuracy's sake.
But it's, you know, chances are anyone out there listening to this is familiar with at
least a few of the phrases that come directly from Ecclesiastes.
Like this book of wisdom, let's say there might be called.
But Seth, I want to interject one more thing about that.
What's interesting in, it's OK, the level of writing, let's say, and the level of
comprehension that's required in many of these ancient texts, let's say, is beyond the
level of training that most people have through what's called the education system.
Right. So what's easier maybe would be to explain it in metaphor, perhaps.
And I like using the jigsaw puzzle metaphor for it.
And that is, most people understand what a jigsaw puzzle is, little things, little pieces
that interlock to form a whole and it produces an image that is rational and observable
where that image, when those little pieces are not interlocked, seem to not be rational or
understood. Right.
But what's interesting with the jigsaw puzzle as such is you let's say you were to
purchase one. They usually come in a container or a box and you see the picture of the
completed jigsaw puzzle on the box, let's say, cover.
And you take it home and you open it and you dump the pieces out on the table and now you
have to put it together. But at least you have a reference of what it should look like
when it's done. And you're always referencing the box.
Now, what's interesting is imagine doing a multiple piece or a many multiple piece jigsaw
puzzle without a reference picture.
And that is basically the condition of most of the studies that people are engaging these
days. To further on this metaphor, maybe beat a dead horse with it.
Let's say you get a jigsaw puzzle with a blue sky, a black mountain and a white snowy
field. Immediately when you dump all the pieces out, you look at the picture and you see
there's a major area of blue, major of black, major of white.
You could actually start fielding and separating the pieces, all the white pieces here,
black pieces here, blue pieces here.
And then this is how they actually fit together.
And you'll be able to go through it much quicker that way than if you really had if you
were just looking at each small piece and how it interlocks with another without that
general reference. And that is what is lacking in the world at large today is any
general view of any subject like that.
And that's what I call about the hijacking of information by certain groups.
That's why you have shop talk and academic talk and legal talk, scientific talk,
religious talk. And people hear not what's being said, but it's being said by a certain
specialist in a certain way.
Oh, that's not for me.
And that is what's keeping the information from everyone at this point.
And this will change.
Just to you know, also, I believe what was mentioned in that message was, you know, is
there a time, you know, over time these things will be understood?
And I think we've discussed the credits portion or it's not time yet or how to keep
time quite a bit, Seth.
Do you think we should go into it a little bit?
Why? Why there's timing involved, you know?
Yeah, I think that I absolutely I think that we can.
I think that this conversation is one that could be viewed outside, outside of time,
especially being that we've kind of started directly in with the subject matter that
we're discussing.
Like I said, you know, this is a great topic.
Is this one that should be discussed, you know, in private or is this one that we should
broadcast? And your response was, this will just be the the episode that never happened.
Right. So, so might as well.
Yeah, might as well.
Might as well.
I think that it might be perhaps beneficial to those listening to this conversation.
To dispel some of the, quite literally, actually, to dispel some of the the baseless
traditions that surround the subject matter directly that we're discussing, that being,
you know, the separation when when the soul is gone and the spirit moves on back to from
whence it came, because there is a lot of even those words and me saying them in a way
that is perhaps a little bit more uncommon than the common vernacular.
It's still going to immediately bring to mind pictures of of white clouds.
It's false. What they're talking about, the smell of brimstone, you know, et cetera, which
certainly have their place in in in the conceptualization of such things.
But the way in which they're used currently are just baseless.
Yeah, this would be as if, you know, you go to someone's house for dinner and you're
expecting a savory meal and they pull out ice cream with hot fudge and chocolate cake
and you're like, well, is this for dinner?
Or like, yeah, man, life is short.
Dessert is for dinner. Skip dinner, go right to dessert.
Right. Absolutely.
So let's say this is a bit of information that could be imparted.
I found out that a lot of people behind the scenes in media always say about you can't say
certain certain things.
You have to dumb it down.
The people just don't want to hear it or they don't understand it.
I'm like, screw that. That's that.
That is basically stating that the people are ignorant.
And I'm saying that ignorance is not the problem.
Ignorance can be solved very quickly.
The problem that the people have at large, the general majority of the people on this
planet is not the ignorance of something.
It's the stubbornness and resistance and rebelliousness to the information.
Right. Absolutely.
Yeah. What if you hear the truth and the truth and it's dissonant?
What if you don't like what is true?
That's why we keep going on.
I say we, whoever I've discussed this with in the past publicly, what is the definition of
the spirit, the soul and the body?
Why? Because we sort of perceive and we define ourselves by our perceptions and being
alive. And the three things that we're made up of is a soul, a spirit and a body.
And if two out of those three components are obscured by a democratic system, you've
lost. Right. So now you're lost in deception.
And if headquarters being yourself, your body, your soul and your spirit is deceived,
you're most likely going to just spread or be in resonance and just be involved in
deception for the rest of your life.
If headquarters is deceived, you're going to extend deception throughout your life.
And a lot of people have sort of come to certain realizations through being informed,
saying everything is a lie is a general statement.
You've heard that before. The thing is, well, if what you know about yourself, if you
think what you know about yourself is a lie, well, of course, that makes perfect sense
that everything else is a lie as well.
And like I've said before, if one wants to define the soul, the spirit and the body and
finds the definition of it, if you seek out beyond just the common person or man or
woman and you seek those that are supposed to be holders of that information, they will
resist you like I don't know what they will hear what you've said and they will come up
with a million ways to tell you it's nothing what a million different ways that it's
other than that and why it's not that.
But they will never address what you've just said.
It is the most fascinating thing I've ever seen with human beings.
I think it can be very entertaining.
And this doesn't happen with absolutely everyone.
But if you were to if you were to try to define the spirit, the body and the soul with
a thousand people, nine hundred and ninety, if not nine hundred and ninety five would
resist you and not want to hear it.
It's amazing.
It's more than ninety nine percent.
So really quickly, the body is the is the physical aspect and it can be divided down to
the twenty eight or so elements found in soil, you know, and then the other aspect is
the soul, which is your breath.
If you are breathing, whether you are insect, bird, mammal, animal or man or woman, you
all share the same soul.
You are breathing, meaning the soul being the breath, the inhalation, exhalation and
then the spirit is the mind.
The mind, which is your personality, what makes you you the way you think, the way you
speak, the way you your character, the way you behave.
And that is also true in the animal kingdom and in the mankind's kingdom.
If anyone has any pets and has had pets for many years, let's say dogs, you'll notice
that each dog is different because it has a different spirit, a different character.
Right. So that's all it is.
Your spirit is your mind and your soul is the breath and the body is, well, the fleshy
part. And that is very, very simple.
Now, the aspect that people are most concerned with when they get find when they when
they get a tangible grip on these definitions is they're concerned about the spirit
because, yeah, the body, I get it.
I get it. You know, I cut myself.
I put a bandage on.
It gets old. It's flesh.
Yes, I know. I know.
Like seawater or coconut milk is like blood plasma.
Yes, yes. It's very tangible, very material.
The soul is more difficult.
You know, if you're not if you're holding your breath, you've stopped your soul.
If someone is not breathing and you administer resuscitation or CPR, you're putting
your soul into their body so they can be a living soul.
And when they breathe on their own, now they are breathing with their own soul.
It's very simple.
It's sort of also materialistic.
But when these things are understood, then people are really concerned about the
spirit. And the spirit is intangible, but it isn't a basis
of information. Like, for example, you can buy a movie on a DVD
and it's a shiny disc or whatever, and it doesn't you can't see the movie unless you
animate it through the proper device or that movie can be streamed
through wires, let's say, and also wirelessly.
Right. So where did that movie come from?
Let's say you were to download one and you have wireless streaming.
It would be broadcast and sent to you from a source.
And that's basically how the spirit works.
It can be the mind is can be remotely controlled.
It could be remotely sent. It can be remotely initiated and remotely terminated.
And if I didn't lose most of the people, this is this.
That's a concept that is
albeit dealt with on the fringe, but that is a concept even
that some have tried to describe physically,
especially those familiar with alternative media.
The idea of the implantation of thoughts
or the podcast of thoughts, you know, for downloading the mind.
Yeah, absolutely. Those two are hard.
Yeah, it's possible.
It's actually so possible that the answer to that would be why not?
But the thing is, you know, going down this subject
without defining the three aspects and getting a firm grip on it
is kind of futile, because dare I say this?
There's a level of maturity that's involved, you know, within a society
or whether it's let's just say this within the vegetable animal
in mankind's kingdom, you have a concept of maturity in the vegetable kingdom.
It would be, well, let's say this fruit is not ripe yet, right?
It's not ready in the animal kingdom.
It would be, you know, the very young puppy or the little kitten.
And in mankind's kingdom, it would be the child.
The problem with mankind's kingdom, unlike the others, is that
when let me just I'll dare say this.
When people go out in society, they very invariably see
that there are less mature people physically.
They're small and they don't like the subculture of kids
or that they call children's.
They've created a subculture around children with kids, meals and toys
and things just specifically for them.
They're just small people.
That much hasn't been imparted to them.
Lacking experience, the entire kids culture,
children's culture, I find repugnant.
But nonetheless, moving forward, when they see someone that's adolescent
or in their 30s or 40s, let's say more mature or already
what's called an adult or someone really old with gray hair,
they discern maturity that way.
And let me just say it this way.
That is physical maturity.
But I assure you that most people you've ever met, regardless of their age,
have stopped developing
spiritual maturity around the ages between nine and 12 years old.
I dare anyone to approach, especially a scholarly type in any of
the talk that we're discussing regarding ancient texts
or what's called spirituality or biblical or scriptural.
And have a try to have a sober discussion with them
about how religions, no religion on the planet is based on any of the text.
And watch how their mind all of a sudden
is revealed to be roughly in the eight to nine to 12 year old mentality.
And most people take it for granted when they see an older person
walk into the room that this person is mature and has wisdom.
And I beg to differ.
And I will tell you, the majority do not.
So if you want to consider that the Greeks opinion, fine.
But it's a statement that needs to be considered very, very closely.
So this subject, again, requires maturity.
So let's go back to the spirit, the soul and the body.
Once these things are understood, then the rest can go on.
Like the discussion can go on.
What happens to the the spirit when it's, I guess, disembodied?
Right, because the soul dies when the body dies.
Right. And that's one of the first things that how do we determine
if someone is dead, right?
Right.
What's the mirror under their nose?
Right. See if they still have a soul, which is breathing.
Right. Right.
So, you know, it's breathing.
It's interesting.
And it's come up in conversation.
Some people have asked questions like, is it possible that they
they were buried and they still had a soul?
I'm like, well, that means they were buried alive then. Yes.
That's harder.
That's that's burying someone alive.
And then you have this other thing.
It's just the most ridiculous stuff, especially in the alternative media.
These people are soulless, you know, referring to certain oligarchs, you know.
And I'm like, well, if they're soulless, it means they're dead.
And if they're dead, it doesn't really matter.
Maybe it's their descendants you're talking about.
Then I don't I don't understand what these people are trying to say.
You see, you've heard that.
So if they're if you're not breathing, you don't have a soul.
The spirit or the mind is completely different.
So what's interesting about the spirit, it just like a DVD,
it requires a device, let's say, let's let's be materialistic on this
to animate that information or make it analog.
Because the spirit in itself is completely intangible.
You don't know the character of a person or even an animal unless they're animated.
You know, you can have a thousand people asleep in bed
and you can walk in while they're all asleep
and you cannot discern the character of the individual until they're animated.
You see, so the spirit needs to be animated.
Now, they still have a spirit.
They're just unconscious at the moment.
So what's interesting about the spirit is that it's incarnated,
it's excarnated and then reincarnated.
And I'm not talking about past lives.
There's no such thing. Sorry, folks.
There's a lot of people out there flapping their lips and gums
about being here before in past lives and all that.
And have fun with it.
If it brings you joy to be entertained with such erroneous information,
who am I to get between you and your pursuit of happiness?
But I'm telling you that it's going to be quite interesting.
And people will take it lying down.
Now, when people find out that most of the information
that they highly regard as being spiritual is absolute rubbish in the future.
I wonder if they're going to take it lying down
or there's going to be a lot of streetlights with rope.
I'm just I just think they're going to take it lying down and say, oh, big deal.
We got fooled. It's no big deal.
But the spirit is incarnated, excarnated, which is when you die.
It leaves the device incarnated would be you put the DVD into the DVD player,
excarnated as you remove the DVD from the DVD player
and then erase the DVD or write over it where it's just blank now.
Right. And it goes back.
Right. But it's sent into another realm that you no longer have access to.
Now, let's just get specific with this.
You know, what's interesting is there's something called the heavenly realm.
All right. Now, if you want to consider it a place where, you know,
that's tangible and can be located, which I in private can't say it can be
because we're given location of this, let's say, headquarters in the scripture.
But it hasn't been discussed and it can be discussed.
I will do it in private.
The the heavenly realm is where the spirit came from for mankind.
And when man is excarnated, it goes back there.
Now, whether they you know, I like to joke around and say that they have the big
master hard drive where you're just, you know, reinstalled into again and inanimated.
There's no consciousness there.
Just like when you have the the DVD player removed from the DVD player and all the power is off.
You're not watching the movie, you know.
Now, what's interesting, just in contrast to that, we're told in the ancient texts.
Now, by the way, when we're discussing this, it's it's not our opinion.
Anyone can look this up.
And the thing is, if you consider the this information making it forward to this modern day
and being preserved for so long as being frivolous, not important and based on opinion and
belief and the people that came before us.
Yes. Also, your forefathers, whoever is listening, people that came before you or worthless
idiots and primitives.
And this information means nothing because you have silly phones and you have rockets
and planes. Then this is obviously this information is not for you.
But if you believe that those that came before you took great I went to great lengths and
labor to make sure this information is forwarded to this day and should be considered as a
valid communication, then this information is for you.
I just wanted to throw that in.
But in contrast with man's spirit going into, let's say, back to the heavenly realm and
being downgloaded completely unconscious, the animal spirit, it's interesting, we're told
goes back down into the earth.
Wow. So the earth houses the minds of the creatures, the animal we call the animal
kingdom included the insects.
Fascinating.
Isn't that interesting?
You know, what a field of study on its own.
And I dare anyone to go down this field of study because you're not going to make any
friends and your family will hate you.
So anyway, what did I just say that publicly?
Hmm. OK, let's let's listen.
That's accurate. I can attest to that as well.
That's right. You will really find out what it means to be, quote unquote, human.
And let me just bring this bring this point out.
I like bringing this up for whatever reason.
Earth is a very violent place.
And someone said, what evidence do you have of that?
I said, I dare anyone to turn on any animal kingdom type documentary and show me where
something isn't eating anything else violently.
Right now. And a lot of people are talking about doom and gloom and oh, government
clampdowns, natural disasters, survivalism.
I'm like, are you kidding?
How ungrateful you are.
You should be thanking whatever force or just just existing that if no one crawled in
through your window last night while you were sleeping and didn't rip your liver out of
your body and if they if you caught them doing that and asked them why they were doing
that, they said, I don't need a reason to do it.
I just feel like it.
This is the real reality where you're living, folks.
And people need to stop taking things for granted because you are in a situation of
peace right now that you know nothing about.
Yes, there's over maybe a hundred conflicts going on all over the world.
But if you ask the people that started them and are involved in them, they're saying it's
just a freaking sport.
And you do like sports as a society.
So anyway, yeah, this is a very violent place.
But the thing is, people have failed to take they're taking too many of the pleasantries
for granted. So let's I think we covered a little bit about the spirit, the soul and
the body. I mean, we went over it quickly and sort of like interjecting certain conditions
about the information, which I think always has to be done.
Let's just go on and bounce around a little bit over here.
You know, like there's a question also about what is pleasing in the scripture.
You know, what is pleasing that what has been memorialized from the past or from a higher
vantage point, let's say.
And by the way, when I say the scripture and all that, you know, people say, well, who
wrote that? You know, well, who did that?
Or whatever, you know, that is really, really interesting.
And it could be valid.
But to me, those types of questions are that now you're looking at the delivery mechanism
and not the information that's being imparted.
Right. People say, who wrote that?
Whatever, you know, I don't believe in that.
That was written by whatever.
Here's the point. You know, it's kind of like, you know, people receive the post or the
mail. And when do they hold the delivery person?
Let's say the mailman or the postman accountable for the quality of the message that
they're receiving. When do they ever do that?
Hardly ever given the given the mailman grief about grammatical error.
Yes, so so you receive this, this is goes back to almost any subject when you let's put
the common man aside because this is about uncommon things, by the way, when you go to
the entitled classes regarding any field and you show them that what their field of
study should be based on or the basis of their field of study, they will hear it and not
want to address it and will give you a million reasons why you shouldn't say that or why
it isn't so. But never address what you're saying, what it should be based on.
It's simply a communication.
So, again, just to go back to it, what is pleasing and how should one conduct their
life? I guess that would be what's called setting ones apart.
Some setting oneself, oneself apart.
Once you get over the taking for granted things, once you once you establish that Earth
is a violent place and you made it by the skin of your teeth alive another day, and
most people don't consider that when they wake up, that they're fortunate that they
hadn't been eaten while they were sleeping by others.
They take it for granted. Once you get out of that realm and you don't take that for
granted and you are grateful, then you could see what's more pleasurable.
And that's by setting yourself apart from the rest.
And maybe we'll save more discussion about being saved, setting yourself apart, because
the other point was events that are come to pass.
And he also mentioned the evangelicalism, which I almost don't want to address the
spirit, the soul and the body we did.
And then he also brought up the point of the little ones.
What do you tell little people?
And thrown in there is the concept of the end.
So maybe we could just go through that before what being set being set apart is to find
pleasure and how that's recommended.
What do you think, Seth?
Yeah, I think that is a wonderful way of going about it.
We are about, oh, probably eight minutes from the break.
Yeah, let's let's get into time then, because you just brought up some time.
Absolutely. The three concepts here to consider is that first concept is if anything
is being discussed, because man has descended into materialism clearly.
Clearly descended into materialism, we need a basis for things, and I just got a message
that I'm not being heard if anybody else thinks that we're not everything looks good
here. OK, great.
OK, so there's a there's a material Rudolf Steiner, interestingly, made something called
the man's descent into materialism.
And when when one is extremely materialistic, one should seek out the basis of what
something is based on.
And interestingly enough, although it is a materialistic society, mostly everything is
debased. If you look at the money, they call it fiat money.
It's based on nothing. If you look at science, it's based on things that stories that
they make up and theory religions we covered already that they're not based on what
they're supposed to be based on, so on and so on and so on.
When we talk about time, what is it based on right now?
The planet, the surface dwelling earth inhabitants are of all agreed that they're
keeping time with what's known as the Gregorian calendar based on Julian calendar
dates. And what is simply what simply can be said with that in a short phrase, that is
nothing more than the papal work schedule for the papal subjects.
It is an arbitrary work schedule.
You cannot keep time with it.
And the purpose of saying that is very simple that anyone could evidence.
If you observe a certain date on that calendar system, you'll notice how it's a
different day of the week every year.
Very simple. And if you start researching how they formulate months and dates and
days and years, they are arbitrary.
And there is nothing wrong with that if you have an allegiance to such an authority
as a subject to perform certain duties.
Wow, that was a mouthful.
But you can't keep time with it and it's based on nothing, right?
It's arbitrary. For example, you can keep a schedule, you can build something, but as
far as the concept of time and being a recordation of events through our
perception, it's inaccurate and irrelevant.
And they make they try to make corrections to it, you know, over over the moons and
over the months, months and the ages.
But even that only gives it a an appearance of of a semblance of accuracy where the
accuracy is just not there to be had.
Or you could say it's cheese not made of milk, you know, and cheese is supposed to be
made of milk. You know, I was shocked, you know, cheese product.
Yeah, I was once at a supermarket and the lady said, do you like a sample of this?
What is it? It's cheese made with milk.
And I was shocked. I was like, are you kidding?
What is it? If it's not made of cheese, what are you talking about?
It's cheese made of milk.
What is cheese supposed to be made of?
And that's what the calendar is.
You know, it's the most funny.
And the thing I just want to throw in here again is there's a lot of people on the
alternative media bad mouthing the papacy, the Vatican, so on and so forth.
And I'm like, oh, what a ignorant hypocrite.
And first, all you got to do is ask them what day it is.
And you know what? They're going to say something between January through December,
Monday through Friday. They've just admitted with their own mouth that they're a papal
subject, whether they know it or not.
And they are speaking against their master.
Oh, boy. Do you think there's sort of problems with things going on?
Because people are anyway.
Yeah. So one of the certainly adds to the confusion.
Yes, it does. So there's the hypocrisy.
So the other thing I want to discuss is a statement that I've made is that the what's
interesting about a movie and I kind of feel bad giving movie references because years
ago, people didn't do that.
And it's it's part of the dumbing down of society.
But let's just do it for communication.
It seems like it's an easy colloquial reference.
It is. And they're very such of such poor quality.
But let's just give it this way.
If you had to shoot a two hour film, do you buy exactly two hours worth of film or do
you need two hours and ten minutes credits in the end?
Right. Yeah, that would be.
Yeah. Right.
Now, what's interesting is if you were to run a multi-millennial film and end it, how
long should the credits be?
Well, you know, that's already, you know, that requires a sense of discernment.
And if I'm just going to drop that information in a quantitative value, I don't think it
gives much value to it.
But what what I can say is right now, for at least 18 years, mankind society has been
in the credits portion of the movie.
Now, what's interesting, very few.
See, let's go back to the movie when the movie during the movie, people get very
disturbed if their view of the screen is blocked or someone is speaking.
They all get together and say, shut up, sit down.
The movie's playing. And here we are getting ready for the break.
So we'll talk a little bit more about the credits.
Greetings, everyone. And this is Uncommon Sense with Seth at American Freedom Radio.
Seth, are you with us? Yes.
Excellent. Great. And that was a good break for us.
And let's get back to it.
We're talking about the credits portion of human, let's say, society or man society on
the planet. And we discussed briefly how when the film is running, people get
disturbed. But when the credits come on, they're not as upset.
When someone is speaking or disturbing the picture, but technically the film is still
running. And what's interesting, I like to say when people talk about end times or
all these bad things are going to happen, I'm like, what are you talking about?
It all ended already and no one has noticed.
And that is the beauty of understanding or comprehending how the the the formative
aspect or the the the primary, let's say, the spiritual world interacts with the
physical world. They're very careful about not having too many disturbances until the
time for their overt presence is considered or to be manifest, let's say.
Right. So what's interesting about the credits part of the movie is let's just take
six thousand years of recorded history.
Would you say about 40 years is pretty ample for credits?
You know, so if we're looking at roughly 1998, you could add roughly around that much
time to it and then say, well, it's been cut short, so let's round it down a little bit
more. It's quite interesting, isn't it?
And what's what's interesting, I just want to throw something in in here for everyone, is
that when something comes to an end, when promises are made about something and that
something comes to an end, if a certain promise is not fulfilled or desire, people feel
cheated or they want to make excuses about why they didn't get what they were sort of
imagining they were supposed to get.
Right. So what's interesting about this and let's just throw out real, real serious
disclosure about the matter here is that regardless of who you are, when you've lived
on this planet, man, woman or child, you all like pleasant things.
What you like is peace.
You'd like prosperity, food, clothing, shelter.
When you're hungry, you'd like food.
When you're thirsty, you like drink.
When you're warm, you want to be cool.
And when you're cool, you want to be warm.
You'd like comfort.
You don't like violence.
You don't like disturbance.
You don't like chaos. And yes, there's a lot of talk about war and quote unquote terrorism.
But even if you look at that, supposedly they have a reason for doing those things to achieve a
certain end. Typically, I'm not discussing that violent side.
I'm discussing that everyone on this planet at any time, any given time wants, I'm going to put
this in very big air quotes, a perfect society.
What would be a perfect society?
It would be peace, prosperity, liberty, liberty, meaning time off from things that you have
allegiance to or things you said you were going to do.
Health. So on and so forth, all the pleasant things on a social level.
And here's the thing, folks, coming around what you call the 2020s, you're going to have a
society on this planet that is going to incorporate all of those things.
Yes, you are. So where's the doom and gloom in that?
The interesting thing, and here's the disclosure part, is that when this manifests, and I'm not
discussing a propagandized global perfect society, like, for example, one example of that
would be, let's say, the former Soviet Union, where you saw the people or being told you
are we're establishing a perfect society.
And what you saw was three thousand people online in knee deep snow for toilet paper.
That's not what I'm talking about.
A propagandized idea.
I'm talking about an actualization in the material.
Everyone can have everyone's going to eat beef and potatoes for dinner and have strawberries for
dessert. What if I don't want strawberries?
You're going to do exactly as we tell you.
Right. You're going to eat those strawberries and you're going to like it.
That's right. Not like that either.
To some extent, it will be.
But here's the disclosure on the deception that's coming that many people read about.
There's a great deception.
And this is it. Let's just say it.
Why not? Why the heck not?
When this is manifested in the late 2020s, roughly, you're going to be told, obviously,
again and again, you may not have to be told because it's pretty obvious that you are in a
very good golden age type society.
And this is how it's going to be for the next thousand years.
And most people will buy it hook, line and sinker and say, why the heck not?
Because, look, this is no propaganda.
This is manifest.
That is the deception, because shortly after this is manifested, the glitches are going to
start to kick in and the high command of your whether it's national or global level is
going to start making very unusual requests of the population.
And these unusual requests are going to be sort of unreasonable and pretty much unlawful,
but using certain laws to get everything on track again and to take care of these
glitches so we can get back on the road and have the next thousand years sort of be
perfect. And it's not going to work.
The more they're trying to fix these glitches, the worst it's going to get.
And this perfect society is only going to last a few years.
When I say a few, meaning a few, three or four.
So that is the great deception.
You you mean perfect.
It's going to be unlike anything experienced at the very least in recorded history, a time
of peace and prosperity for everyone.
That's right. And the reason why they're going to fall for it is because they're not going
to be able to go back in history and find a time on a global level that is anything like
it. And because of that, they're going to be so enthralled and enamored with the
achievement that any anything speaking counter to it is going to be met with, what
should we say, great aversion.
So, yeah, this is we just we just thought we'd drop this right now at this time.
And speaking of time, by the way, I'm sort of reckoning it's around the 13th day of the
second month. I just wanted to throw that in the second moon.
So but yeah, so this is a disclosure about what I mean about time and what's coming.
And that is the time where, for example, let's just entertain one thought within that
thought of the credits and the perfect society when everything is really going really
well and, you know, it's not.
But everyone else doesn't.
It's pretty easy to gather things together if you wanted to separate yourself, quote
unquote, air quotes again, being a survivalist and getting away from society.
It would be quite easy to do that.
An example would be, you know, if if the opposite of that would be like, let's say
there's a disaster being broadcast in the media and a few days later you decide to go
to the supermarket to stock up and all the shelves are empty.
You waited a little too long and, you know, the panic has been ensued publicly and
everyone is heated to the panic.
So see, but when when it's time, when you see this prosperity and everyone is very
relaxed, that would be the time to start gathering what you wanted to gather to be by
yourself and about a three days walk from anyone else.
And there's another reason why I'm saying three days walk.
But that's another subject.
So it's going to be very fitting for those that know and they're going to be very few
that actually can see it because almost everyone's going to be deceived into it.
So let's just say let's just put that that aside again, because it's about being setting
yourself apart. What's interesting here, let's bounce around again a little.
We have a little bit of time, but I have to watch it because it goes by really quickly.
The individual mentioned evangelicalism or whether it's that or any other form of
religion, I have to hearken back to the firm statement, which I will stand and anyone
can stand firmly behind it.
There is no religion at all, institution or group that knows or does anything that's
allegedly in the text that they subscribe to.
It's out of context.
If they say they do, it's very simple to see.
Very, very simple.
But again, going down this path, you're not going to make any friends.
And people like to have those sorts of things.
You know, they like to be part of a group and such.
So I really rarely I have addressed specifics about, quote unquote, Christianity in prior
public speakings in a way that is very matter of fact.
But the fact is, the purpose of giving information is not to address such an organization
or belief system because it's not.
We like to stay on things that are based on something other than belief or a cultural
phenomenon or social phenomenon or the reason why people should get together and believe
in something. That is not the purpose of discussing uncommon sense.
Anyone can clearly see the anomalies and the distortions and the unbasedness of any
religion. The symptoms are prevalent through all of them.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. Let's just want to mention them specifically would be
Christianity, Islam, Buddhism, Hinduism, Judaism.
You want to go down the line, go down the line.
They're all none of them are based on on what they say they're basing it on and their
followers at all. And one of the strong comments I like to make is if you consider
yourself to be a Christian or Jewish or Muslim and you go ahead and study the book that
it's supposed to be based on, there is no way you could call you would call yourself one of
those in that group. Now, there are many that have studied the text and they say, wow,
I seem to have an upper hand.
I sound like one of the more informative ones.
I'm going to take advantage of all these people following.
Now, I'm not talking about those people, the predatory types.
There are a lot of people within these religions that do comprehend what's in the text,
but because they are predatory in nature, they go back into the group and promulgate
whatever they do within the group.
It's a really sick system if you look into it.
And the same goes for the scientists and the legal society.
Yes, there are attorneys and judges that know law, but they're like, wow, what we're this
society has nothing to do with this, but I'm going to go back in because now I have an
upper hand and the same with the scientific community and so on and so forth.
And any individualized institution that mankind's involved with, there's always a within
the hierarchy of that entitled class, there is a predatory group that does know the truth,
but fails to reveal it and takes part in the group in a predatory perspective.
I think I said predatory enough times there.
So, so, you know, so again, there's the concept also of what to do that's pleasant.
Well, what's interesting is if you establish that Earth is a very, very violent place and
you've made it another day without being torn to pieces or eaten or put in a box, let's
say, however, whatever you want to call it, kidnapped in a prison, in a cell, in a camp
or beaten to death or anything like that, you should be very grateful.
Right. And this is not doom and gloom about something to come.
This is the situation of being on this planet.
And once you are such you, you are grateful of having being having a certain level of
health and peace in your life and you haven't been dismembered the night before.
It's it's actually a very realistic point of view to take, which most cannot because it
requires a certain level of my spiritual mind maturity to understand the reality of any
situation. But once you do understand that, you'll see that there's a way to set yourself
apart. And how do you do that?
Given the metaphor of what's called an operating system, you know, let's say using the
metaphor of a computer, you have an operating system and then you have a program and a
file. All operating systems come for mankind, come from your deity, from your God.
And this might sound dogmatic.
And yes, there is no such thing as a God.
It's a plurality.
Just like when someone says the word army, no one ever thinks of one individual.
It is a plurality.
And when people try to approach and define and defend or apologize for them using God,
they have no detail.
It's talking about the creator or the chief God.
They have no detail on it.
And it's no different than going to a mechanic and no detail on the automobile and asks you
where the steering wheel on the car is.
I mean, they're not much of a mechanic.
So we have a society here that is fully capable of comprehending details, functional
details, but refuses to.
OK, and they're being accommodated with these texts that are obscure and ambiguous, and
they go around talking about things that don't exist as the way they should.
So being set apart is figuring out what your operating system is, and that comes from your
God. That's why when you look at, for example, law forms, they always prop a deity in
front of you. And right now, the law form of the earth is a revival of the ancient goddess
religion known as justicia or justice or decay or Mott, if you go back in time.
There's always a God put in front of you, whether it's scientific.
They'll show you a Prometheus type character or a character holding lightning bolts.
There's always a deity behind an operating system.
And people are very neatly and conveniently based on their lack of maturity.
So this under the rug to acknowledge it.
Every nation has a patron deity.
Sorry, I'm not making this up.
It's very simple to observe in the literature, even specifically in this group of 50 some
countries that, you know, you and I find ourselves in.
It's it's very specifically in the literature that defines, you know, the the the purpose
of the existence of this country, justice and liberty for all.
Yeah. Which is a revival of the ancient goddess religion.
So the so right there, stop, everyone hit the pause button.
What do you know about ancient goddess religions?
There's plenty of it. Actually, there's not that much of it online, unfortunately.
But if you if you sort of are savvy with doing searching online electronically or digitally,
you will find things.
And guess what? It's not very pleasant.
It's a lot of cruelty. And it also happens at the descent of a society.
Most societies, let's just say the Babylonian, Greek, Roman, so on and so forth, at the end
of the height or the before the fall of their prominence, had adopted this type of goddess
religion. So anyway, we've we can go down the goddess religion path in the future.
But that is not the point.
The point is that your law form, when I say law, I'm not talking about what you call traffic
law, tax law or what they do in courts as law.
I'm talking about what you eat, what you wear, how you keep time, how you conduct yourself,
how you raise a family, how you form a contract, how you keep time.
All these things are your law form.
What why do you do what you do is your law form.
And that comes from your God, your God, I said, not the God, because there are many.
So pick one. Interesting, isn't it?
Greek, you sound really dogmatic.
Sorry, I'm just trying to give people a clear, concise report on what can be viewed
objectively. And I'm just really I don't I don't think I doubt that it's coming across
as dogmatic. OK, I just wanted to throw that in there.
And you will find there is some kind of deific or deification within the subject matter of
anything, even music.
They say this guy is such a good heavy metal musician.
He is a god.
You know, look at Elvis Presley and the immortalization.
You know, I mean, it's just it's just so blatantly in front of everyone and no one is
speaking on it. That's henceforth uncommon sense.
So moving forward, what does one do about being set apart?
Set apart is a very simple thing.
If you establish that you're getting a well-paying job, let's say working in the sewer,
do you jump in there naked and drink the water or do you set yourself apart by putting on
a full hazmat suit with breathing tanks?
Now, hopefully the latter, hopefully the latter.
And the way you set yourself apart is is really what is discussed in what's called the
scripture. Yes, let's just go ahead and say it.
Now, there's about there are a few hundred rules in there.
But what's interesting about it, about how to set yourself apart?
Yes, there are rules. Yes, you don't like that word, but that's too bad.
Most of the rules have to do with certain ordinances regarding a certain edifice which no
longer exists. And the other part of most of those rules are regarding the rules of the
people that were to operate that edifice, which cannot really exist in that way because the
edifice doesn't exist.
So the other small handful of rules is what you do when you're just basically on the earth in
general form. And it has to do with what to eat and why, what to wear and why, how you go into
business and why, how you keep time and why.
And actually the how to keep time and why is actually sort of obscure.
That's kind of spread out.
That would be like the white field on the jigsaw puzzle that you have to piece it together to
kind of see the whole picture.
Going back to that, so what's interesting about this is what does one do and how does one
set themselves apart?
Like I think we've once discussed the word holy is not in the text itself.
It's the word kodesh or agio, Hebrew and Greek corresponding, which means to set oneself
apart. And then the Greek agios means geos, meaning Gaia or earth, and a means without,
not non-worldly.
Very interesting. So setting oneself apart, you know, if you have an apple orchard and you're
farmer, when you do your crop harvest, you know, you have all the general apples, the ones
with been pecked with a hole in it go for the applesauce.
The fairly good ones get, you know, a grade A standard, but then you have some perfect ones
that you set apart for maybe a display or photographer or are sent to like a hot cuisine
type thing because they're almost perfect apples.
And what makes them perfect is that you've judged them to be such and you set them apart
from the rest.
There's one definition of it, perhaps.
Now, what do you do with the little ones?
Right. That was one of the concerns here.
Let's let's let's just be practical about this.
I've done discussions about how parents interact with children, and I think I've voiced the
yes, it's an opinion, how I find it repugnant that there's been a subculture for kids or
children, subculture, meaning they have their own entertainment, their own little meals,
their own little funny little toys and things like that.
And they're treated in an immature, quote unquote, way in some parallel reality to society
when, in fact, all they are is small people.
That the reason they lack understanding is because they have not been inputted, they have
not received the input or the experience.
And creating this subculture, I find completely repugnant.
But nonetheless, what do you do with the little ones?
Typically in this society, the model of society now is give them enough training to go and
function in the world with some sort of career and then function in some sort of
retirement. That little statement or a few statements that I just made cover a reality
of past year formative years, like four or five, six, all the way to perhaps later years in
life, maybe 40, 50, 60 years.
I've just covered there, right, of what's suggested in society.
Get some training, have a career or a job to fend for yourself, and then a retirement
golden age over a 40 or 50 or 60 plus year.
Now, how is that relevant if you don't have if you have roughly a decade and a half left
in society as you know it?
Not not where everybody's going to be killed or destroyed or the earth will be destroyed.
No such thing is going to happen, but society will be reset or rebooted.
Now, how does a 40 or 50 year plan work within a such a short span that's left?
Doesn't. And let me just mention a few things here.
How when anyone studies, it says that these things are written on the heart of man.
Well, OK, what does that mean?
Let's look at several examples.
You know, a thousand years ago in architecture, when buildings and edifices were erected
and constructed, they were designed to do such for a thousand years.
You can find most of them still available on the many of them are still standing.
Those that have not been intentionally taken apart.
Exactly. A hundred years ago, if you look at a lot of the primary skyscrapers in some
of the major cities, they were designed to last a hundred plus years.
Look at the, you know, the Empire State Building, the Chrysler Building and so on and so
forth. They're still doing just fine.
Now, what's interesting is that right now, when structures, at least in the past 20
years, have been installed on the surface and you could look at some of the big towers
that are, you know, multibillion projects, guess what their lifespan is?
20 years. Yeah, about 20, 20 years.
That's how they're underrated by the insurance companies and the engineering.
Don't don't believe it. Look it up.
OK, now what's what's even more fascinating.
What do you see with your own eye?
I was conveying on what they call a highway and I looked to the right and I saw what
they call a new subdivision going up houses for people and they were made out of
compressed sawdust.
Yes, that one more time.
That's yeah. Yeah.
They're building their homes now of compressed dust.
They called flakeboard, particle board, whatever you want to call it, oriented strand
board. But nonetheless, what it is, it is what it is.
I don't care what they're saying in an engineer lab that it's as strong as this or
whatever. We're conserving on recycling wood.
That's irrelevant. I'm saying that.
They're building their houses out of dust.
Need I say more. So so the thing here, what is going back to the advice of the little
ones? OK, let's say you have one that's five years old and you have roughly 15 years
left in society as you know it.
In other words, society functioning as you know, let's just take those as roundabout
numbers that will be discovered to have some accuracy.
So if you add five to 15 years roughly to a five year old person that puts them at
around 20. So it would be reasonable then was is that all of the things that people
suggest young people do now that they had done, let's say they're much older than
that. Things those things won't be around to do.
Right. So what I would suggest to any parent, take the age of your child at 15 years
and then see what number you come up with and then look at how old you were according
to that number. So let's say take a five year old at 15.
That puts them around 20. So what would be recommended to the parent to perhaps do is
say, what would I have done different up until about 20 years old?
How would I have based on what I know now?
Because now I have a higher vantage point, I've passed through this and maybe I would
have done certain things different.
Make a list of those things and impart them to the child.
This is what I would have done different at 20 or up leading up into that age.
And it doesn't mean do that with the child.
It just means impart the information.
And what most people will find is that no matter how as long as it's lawful and
relatively beneficial, you'll be able to do it.
You know, I've discussed the education system, kindergarten through 12th grade, 12,000
hours of what I have queried and asked people, what did you get out of 12 years?
Nothing. I'm glad to be out of there.
The reason they have you in school for all those years is because they need to capture
your formative years and spit you out as now as a malformed project.
Now, here's the thing. When a tree is growing, if you purposely grow it on an angle or
distorted for 12 years and you release it from that mechanism, what are the chances of
it straightening up? You have to cut it down.
It's not going to do it. You can't straighten it out at that point.
So here that's why a lot of people are wrestling.
And then I believe a lot of this has led to the emergence of the alternative media.
But like I've said before, the alternative media is not being used at its highest and
best form. I just hear a lot of opinion and I don't know what and a lot of maybes.
So anyway, how are we doing on time, Seth, and how any thoughts so far?
We've got quite a bit, a little bit is it's going to go by quickly, but this is the
subject matter that I believe we've covered in that message from this individual.
I think we've gone across the board without getting again, maybe into the specifics of
the person asked. You haven't given specifics.
Do you think we've given a little more specific than we usually have?
I would say so. Yeah, absolutely.
You and I have spoken a lot over the past few years in private.
So these are things that you and I have discussed in depth quite a bit.
But as far as being broadcast, yeah, absolutely.
And publicly, we've discussed this as well on air in many other places, I'd say.
Yeah. And speaking of being on air, you're listening to American Freedom Radio and
folks, I'm going to make this short and sweet and sweet as such, if it manifests.
There's something called keeping the lights on.
There's something called about, you know, things are available and things are free.
The information that you hear, the venue called American Freedom Radio is available and
free, but it costs it's not that the money needs to be sent to them for just sending
the money. It costs to pipe it to you.
And right now in this actual while I'm speaking today, let's say, and yesterday,
hopefully not tomorrow, American Freedom Radio does need some help.
There are donations that need to be gotten here quickly.
Quickly, meaning there are there are infrastructures that need to be infrastructure and
Dunning's or debts, let's say what you call bills have been thrust upon the station on
a regular basis. And this month, let's just say this particular cycle that they have has
been extremely challenging.
And it's up to you, the listener, the listenership, anyone hearing this right now to
perhaps be proactive and send something their way.
The way you send it their way is by going to their home page and you will perhaps find a
donate button or other forms of contact.
And I just wanted to say this because there's a way to present a fund drive.
But I don't believe it's needed.
But the message needs to be clear.
It is important that American Freedom Radio does get some monetary help here in the very
near future, because it is quite possibility you might be able to try to tune in and
it'll just be blank here just simply because it ran out of juice.
So let's let's get some throw some juice towards American Freedom Radio.
And that's what I'm going to say about that.
Yeah, speaking of radio, it's actually reached a critical point right now.
So please, anyone within even down the stream, if you hear this on the archive, feel free
to do so. And I would I would like to point out as well that we're not being
compensated monetarily for the time that we spend here speaking with all of you.
We're we're doing this.
I'm doing this because I quite selfishly, I enjoy it.
I enjoy being able to discuss the things that we are able to discuss here in the way that
we are. And that is, you know, that's made possible by, you know, American Freedom
Radio, the medium that you are hearing our voices on currently.
So you do have the ability to keep that going and to help out when you when you do
let them know that, you know, that you enjoy the conversations and that you would
like to keep them going. And, you know, actions speak louder than words, as they say.
So even if they don't enjoy it, if you want to just provide some funds for the
infrastructure, that would be great.
Right. Absolutely.
So, yeah, absolutely, Seth.
Yeah, this is it's interesting.
I mean, you know, even if recently I've heard I did some math on this, sharpened
some pencils and I figured out that if I switch to, let's say, LED bulbs, I'll be
using one tenth the energy consumption.
And I did so. And yeah, it is possible to reduce your consumption tremendously these
days. But even with such a consumption being reduced and a bare bone skeleton way of
providing a radio format as such, it still needs some infrastructure underpinning in
the form of donation or influx of monetary something.
And thank you, folks.
And we'll stop right there on that if you can do so.
So, again, back to the subject matter at hand, we kind of brought up the concept of
scripture and still what this is, is up to people to discover.
You know, I just want to throw out a name.
This is maybe just arbitrary within the discussion, but still part of the discussion.
There's a man named Ivan Panin, I-V-A-N, Ivan and then Panin, P-A-N-I-N.
And he is an interesting character.
He was a mathematician looking for a doctorate thesis in mathematics, which is hard to
find something unique.
He decided to look into the biblical text to see if there are any number sequences of
any significance. Go read with this.
This was a secular approach, by the way.
And if anyone wants to look up Ivan Panin, P-A-N-I-N, and look at his work, that is a
real interesting way to sort of in a forensics point of view, meaning in detective work,
look for what's called a fingerprint for identification purposes.
Now, the problem with giving references regarding anything biblical or scriptural,
again, as you will go online and you will find it, this information is again hijacked by
quote, unquote, religious groups.
You know, they will say, oh, here's proof of Christianity.
The Bible can be validated mathematically.
And oh, no, why did they do that?
You know, because then they're going to pop Santa Claus and the Easter bunny in there.
So the problem is it's really difficult to find things that are untainted by, like Seth
earlier in the broadcast said, the traditions of man.
So if you have a good B.S.
filter, you can find a lot of good things.
And it's easy to find a needle in a haystack with a magnet, right?
Something you want to attract what you're looking for instead of randomly sifting.
Right, so I just wanted to throw a little bit of that out for the validation of the text.
Now, the other thing is there's a concept called paganism.
Now, Seth, clearly the easiest way to sum up paganism is as what?
It just means that someone is, Seth, would you say ignorant perhaps?
OK, well, so we get Seth back.
So what's interesting is right now, anything like this has been idolized.
People do not want to look at what's called the purpose of anything.
And when I say that, I mean maybe in a general way.
Let me say what I mean specifically.
If you bring up the scripture, the biblical text, it is simply a communication.
Now, the legal society has hijacked the notion that one needs to walk in and swear.
Put their hand on a Bible.
Now, what the interesting thing I like to say is what if you say I don't want to put my hand on that book?
I have it downloaded here on a USB thumb drive or a DVD.
Can I swear on that?
And of course, they'll say no, because they've turned it into a talisman, a rabbit's foot, because it is paganism.
You know, wear this rabbit's foot and you will have good luck.
You know, this is what this communication has been reduced to.
Just the idolization, for example, iconography that you see through religion, symbolism.
There is nothing wrong with having a graphic symbolism in that context, but it has to be kept in its perspective as it is a form of communication to communicate something.
So we have another problem when we discuss things of the biblical nature because of the, quote unquote, paganism involved with it.
You know, to take things further down the line, I maybe want to say we have some time left here.
And maybe the only thing I have access to here is anyone in Skype contact and also the American Freedom Radio chat room.
So I'm going to take time and use the word maybe we'll do this democratically as we have some time left.
If anyone has a question to pose, at least in text or writing, do so.
And I will look at it at the moment.
But at the moment, I want to go back again to the message that we read off to be the theme of the subject matter of today's show.
And it was about getting into specifics.
So there's so many specifics, but the generalities have to be covered first and the generalities have to find some accuracy and the statements that we've made here today.
And if you just tuned in, you might want to check it up on archives.
You will find that they are accurate statements.
And again, to go back to the beginning of the show, as I said, a friend to all is a friend to none.
Many people like to or let's just say much media is designed to be accepted by the masses, whether it is in the alternative sense format or the mainstream format.
No one sets out and says, well, this might offend certain people or be accepted.
So everyone wants to make things universal.
And what I have to say that is to harken back.
I think it was Plato that said a friend to all is a friend to none.
The purpose of doing the show is not to consider being a friend to all, even though it would be quite pleasant if that were the case.
But in reality, it is not.
And also, I want to bring up the concept of offenses.
And this is a concept.
And I'll give what I seldom like to say is an opinion.
How many times have you heard the concept of someone saying, oh, that is offensive to me or that I have been offended by that?
Yeah. Well, what's interesting is when regarding when someone is in the let's say seeking truth, how is it possible to be offended?
If you're seeking truth, if the information is brought to you, you tend to want to be objective.
It is either true or false.
Where is the offense?
You see, I've heard that prior says, oh, I don't want to hear the Greek, I find him offensive.
I'm like, well, that doesn't tell me why they find I don't want to ask why I'm offensive.
That right away tells me this person has lax objectivity because the purpose is not to offend.
The purpose is to be objective.
And this is how one, I believe, should continue to use any form of medium of communication as its highest and best use.
So with that said, again, if we're not necessarily set up, we're going to take any callers.
But within the text format so far, I haven't seen any questions and we're waiting for Seth to come back.
He said technical difficulty again.
So in the meantime, I believe that I'm using that word belief here loosely that many of the specifics will be able to be imparted when the time is correct.
And we are coming upon a time right now where perhaps I'd say in the next two years, this particular time period is going to end.
And the next time period would be easier to impart things, new ideas.
And what I mean by new ideas is I can roughly say, if you want a really new idea, read a really old book.
And let's just put I'm going to say one thing here and I want to put it aside, which I keep bringing up.
But I'll put it I'll say it and then put it aside is that many people have an aversion to things that are old.
They don't want to hear things that are old.
They believe that they're modern.
And folks, if you are in if you think you're so advanced because you have a little silly phone and you have a microwave and all these other things that define that, go do a little bit of history and look at all of these civilizations that have fallen, had called themselves modern prior to that fall.
Let's say it's I find it very ironic.
But again, a friend to all is a friend to none.
So we might have a message here.
Let's just see.
I'm trying to walk and chew gum.
Oh, yeah.
One one question here is how about money as people's God?
Well, what's interesting here is that anything that's debased and has no basis in it from a material point of view, then it has no material substance based to it.
It has to go strictly on belief.
And the concept of God, there's also the concept of worship, and you don't question things that you worship, just like people don't like to question money.
How many times have you discussed or if anyone has the nature of fiat currency?
And the typical response that one might get is I don't care because when I go to the store, I get what I want with it.
Think about that for a moment.
How does a statement like that contrast when one is considering ethics and morality?
Hmm. Now, let's go to the next level and say, well, I don't care what I do as long as it feels good.
And then you might put that in the back of your mind and you'll hear a lot about certain people or of aspects of culture that are doing things to other people.
They shouldn't be doing too, because it feels good.
Where's the aspect of morality there or ethics, let's say, how those let's just define morals and ethics loosely.
So this is the type of society that mankind is engaged in.
And when I say mankind, I mean wholesale.
And if you're listening to this, I mean you as well, unless you can prove otherwise.
It's quite interesting how one can.
Let's say, hear about something and then disregard it from a moral or ethical standpoint.
Now, what does one do, let's say, for money as people's God, that's that's really interesting.
Yeah, that's interesting, because if we look at the concept of that, your law comes from your God.
What's interesting is that the things surrounding the current fiat currency or credit system are legal things, things of law.
And when you approach the current legal or lawful, what they call law society, which is not lawful, by the way, they're based on the money system, not money, but the money system.
It's quite interesting and no need to go down that path specifically.
But, yeah, that's that's a good point.
And the other thing I want to mention about money, folks, is don't be a sucker there.
Why? Well, why?
Why did he say be a sucker?
Well, when you go on the Internet, alternative media, there are dozens, if not hundreds of comp financial commentaries or commentators.
Yes, they have websites, they have Web pages and they have radio shows and subscribers.
And not a one of them, not a one of them is discussing the relevance of a credit based economy.
And how it should function as such, not a one of them is discussing the difference between lawful money and legal tender, not a one of them.
They might throw out the concept of silver and gold and they might always preach doom and gloom.
But I have not heard anyone address it holistically, especially the concept of endorsement.
Endorsement means you have no other choice.
What I mean by endorsing is that you're putting your full faith and credit in the system and signing to it.
No one is ever discussing, well, we have no other choice, but in the meantime, we can make it conditional.
You see, everyone is going into it unconditionally, and that is the part that is the most difficult to really discuss about money.
It's just the ethics and moral value of it.
OK, folks, I'm back.
It looks like I had a small technical as well.
So and Seth, I believe, is also gone on a small little break because of the technical issues again.
So we'll just continue and see if there's any other democratic aspect of question asking and such and appears to be not much at the moment.
I see Seth has departed from the conversation just momentarily.
He'll probably be back.
Another question here. Let's just maybe read it.
Information is communication, education and entertainment.
Talk about the entertainment aspect or any of them.
That's interesting as well, because what people are gathered in groups for is for entertainment value anyway.
You know, it's interesting. There's a concept that has come across the alternative media is what's known as activism.
And I find it to be very interesting because whether it's on the Internet or not, activism, you look at these rallies and protests.
And they sure sure, as you can imagine, have much entertainment.
They have bands that come and play.
They have roasts, barbecues, hamburgers and hot dogs and beers.
And they liked it. And there's nothing wrong with that.
But they like to have a good time while they're protesting.
It seems like any information, any cause has to have some form of entertainment around it anyway.
But what's interesting is that the entertainment value supersedes the value of the purpose of the activist.
I hate to say it, but a lot of people get upset.
You know, I do know some of them, quote unquote, activists.
And I always message them resistance is futile.
And they get really upset about that.
And that's fine. I'm just trying to be truthful, because there's a lot of purpose of being an activist or protesting something.
But the way it's being done may not be effective.
Let's just say if anyone's curious about how that this whole thing about entertainment and information comes together.
Read about there's a man named Gustav Le Bon that's called the crowd, the psychology of the crowd.
What happens when you get people together in a movement?
So it's quite interesting.
Let's see, we're getting leisure with dignity.
I don't understand that one, but this is just again going democratic route here.
So, folks, so what's what I want to say again, perhaps of information as communication.
Well, information should be communicated.
The problem is, again, there's a concept of people being ignorant.
There's a lot of people being apologetic about, quote unquote, masses or the people on this planet at large about their ignorance.
And I'm saying the ignorance is not the problem.
It's the resistance and the stubbornness and rebelliousness to actually look at what they think they want to know.
They really don't want to know.
So that's very important in the entertainment aspect.
I mean, what I found, again, just not to harp on the alternative media, there's this thing called YouTube that people want a lot of hits on.
Apparently it pays you something.
And, you know, you just go ahead and do YouTube with, you know, genetically modified octopus with purple tomatoes coming to destroy society.
And, you know, it'll get 30,000 views in six hours.
You know, so the sensationalism, the carnival bark, bark, barking and the sensationalism, the yellow journalism, the all this other stuff has been always viewed distasteful as what's still prominent amongst society, at least for the next couple of years when the time again will shift.
Right now, folks, you're still in the waiting room as a society.
What do you do in a waiting room?
Well, what is a waiting room before?
Let's say you need to go somewhere to for a matter of significance and you're not seen at the time when you arrive.
You have you're supplied with something called a waiting room and you'll see them places throughout society and people sitting around.
And they usually have places to be seated and some form of entertainment, either a magazine on a coffee table or a TV or something.
And if you were to observe that objectively, you'd say, what a lazy bunch of people.
And they're all kind of interested in their own little thing.
Well, it's a waiting room.
That's what people are supposed to do.
You know, so what's interesting, you're still in the waiting room aspect of society, except what's happening here is that you're being distracted.
So there's aspects of the distraction, there's frustration, there's confusion, there's you know, I've actually critiqued very much on what's happening in the alternative media.
There seems to be a cycle of a deadly virus, a missing airplane, a financial collapse and a bad political dictator, a deadly virus, a missing airplane, a financial collapse and a bad political figure, a missing airplane, a really bad virus.
You get my point. There seems to be this cycle of just nonsense over and over and over and over within the news feed, news media.
And no one is really pulling back and saying, what do these things mean?
What is coming?
What where have we been and where are we going?
And even from a purely secular sense, it is very clear and very easy to look at.
If one gets a notion of what's called, let's say, I'll just get to the point here.
I've said that what you're going to be looking for in the future is the formation of a Middle East Union type situation.
That's going to be the home base for the new world order.
Right. The thing is, it's not going to form right now because the requirement is roughly 10 nations and only nine of those nations exist at the moment.
And what I've said in the past is, you know, even four or five years ago publicly is that this will be coming in the new country that will be formed is the new Assyria, Assyria, A-S-S-Y-R-I-A.
There are people known as the Assyrians and they haven't had a country in twenty three hundred years.
Where it is is in northern Iraq and its ancient borders also took part in what we currently call is the political geographic landmass of Syria and Turkey.
So years ago, I stated that you're going to actually observe the precursors of the formation of this middle union and preceding that is the formation of a new country in northern Iraq.
But in order for its borders to actually have land near Syria and Turkey, you're going to have to also watch for conflicts within Syria and Turkey.
And guess what we're seeing very often today in the news, but no one really cares because it was just a good guess and no one's even told me that because no one really wants to hear that kind of stuff anyway.
So the point here is, folks, the seat of your future is going to be in what's called the Middle East or Western Asia or the Levant area, because it's actually part of that Asian landmass if you want to consider it as such.
And this is what you might use as a reference point or part of the jigsaw puzzle picture.
So when all these other pieces come in, you can field what is going on and you could see the interest and you could see, you know, the most ridiculous aspect is when I hear World War Three is coming or these people are being genocided or this is happening.
I mean, all those things are bad.
And yes, there are things that are bad surrounding those things.
But no, none of that is, you know, how it's just swept under the rug.
I've actually confronted someone recently who was emphatically in a panic about a disaster, impending disaster, whether it was from a comet, a solar flare or a government crackdown or collapse of the grid.
And I approached them.
I said, man, I'm so glad to hear you're in a much calmer state about all those things you mentioned.
He said, well, what things?
Oh, you know, you know, the collapse in the total disaster that was supposed to happen three months ago.
Oh, well, that was three months ago.
I said, wow, what a waste of energy.
The purpose of saying what is being said here is so you live your life with a little more efficiency than what you're hearing out there and out there or in there or wherever.
It's about efficiency, folks.
So let's be efficient and let's try to make sense of things.
And it's very difficult to do that if you're just relying on all the casual input, no matter how drastic it sounds.
Oh, here, I got hit with another question.
Does one have to learn how to love?
Well, thank you.
And this is coming from a good acquaintance named Steve.
Thank you, Steve.
Yes, absolutely.
The concept of love, I've done a little bit of public speaking on that on a previous project.
And, you know, what's interesting is it's another thing that's taken for granted.
And I'll tell you emphatically that most people don't even know what that means and they don't know how to do it.
What?
What did you just say, Greek?
How dare you say that?
Yes.
Yeah, how many times have you heard I'm falling in love and everyone gets complimented?
Wait a second.
If I just stated to everyone I just fell, the first thing is you're concerned for my well-being because it didn't...
Falling actually might do harm to someone's well-being, but yet when someone falls in love, they're complimented on it.
I think we're a little sick here, Twisted folks.
Because people that fall in love typically start high on the curve and then it's downhill from there.
Oh, don't think so?
Look at the high separation rate and the casualness of how relationships are taken.
Let's just say it.
One has to learn how to love.
And I want to tie in something that I haven't really said much publicly about the physical aspect or the emotional aspect and all this.
And they're all separate, by the way.
But the thing that I want to say is there's this concept of fear.
And everyone says, don't have any fear.
You know, there's an aspect of love that incorporates fear.
Like, for example, you might love someone so much that you fear that something bad happens to them.
That's why you make sure that the tires in your wife's car are up to snuff.
Or if, you see, you don't want them approached by some unknowing danger to bring harm.
And there's a certain fear involved and that's a healthy fear.
So, you know, there's this ambiguity that's being thrown and this absoluteness that's being thrown which need not be so.
And then there's an absoluteness that's being thrown which is ambiguous.
And this is what I see in society.
So, there's an aspect of things that need to be looked at.
But regarding love, again, if we look at what the ancients, especially the Greeks, they had three various forms of love.
The friendly, the philia, the agape, which is a higher spiritual thing.
And then the eros, which is the lustful type of love.
So, yeah, love is an interesting concept.
Thank you, Steve, for bringing that up.
And the interesting thing also I've heard is the opposite of love is hate.
Wait a second, folks.
Let's just take a moment here and imagine something here.
It takes a lot of passion to love.
But I found that it almost takes equally as much passion to hate.
Now, could it be that the opposite of love is not hate and it's actually apathy and indifference?
Think about it for a moment.
So, okay, we don't have Seth here with us at the moment.
His sonic connection has been severed electronically.
I just wanted to mention that to any of the audiences wondering where Seth is.
He is not available at the moment.
But I just wanted to also recap the message that we started this show off with.
And hopefully we've gotten over the points that we said we would with a little more specific, specificity, I should say.
And from that point of view, we typically want to call this project or sonic venture as being uncommon sense.
And we sort of brought up this message that we read from an individual who apparently is listening to what has been said before
and tried to give a little more depth to it.
I hope we've succeeded.
I guess, again, in the public fashion that we have available to us within two hours
to cover some of the points that were mentioned with more specificity.
But again, I just want to recap.
This is perhaps the second time we've come around.
We're not as plagued with technical issues as we were with the first episode,
which is archived on American Freedom Radio.
But we want to just continue with uncommon sense as this project is titled.
And many other discussions, we're going to go into various systems and things that are considered in society
as aspects of their society, the institutions, the philosophies, the notions.
And as many of the things that people consider important to them,
like let's not say health, but yes, what the human body is,
the physical nature, what are called the sciences.
And always what is most uncommon is how these things can be explained with great simplicity,
without the technical jargon from the entitled classes that have hijacked these aspects of society
and these various bodies of knowledge.
It is possible to impart knowledge, yes, knowledge,
and things that people can apply to themselves.
They don't have to go, they don't have to leave the room they're in or leave their body.
Let's not go down that route.
But actually beyond what they can experience within their own manifestations around them.
We've spoken on a previous sonic project around something called the container,
or how the body works.
And you don't have to go and read some ridiculous medical document
or some ridiculous alternative treatment.
It's just we discuss about what is really going on right there while you're sitting in your chair.
Discussing timekeeping, discussing various aspects of what many institutions,
including government and science and things like that,
can be doing, should be doing perhaps, and what are they doing,
and how you fit in, not using again their technical jargon and rubbish.
And not to be disrespectful, but that is actually,
if the qualitative state of all of these subjects that I just brought up
were to be explained politely, it would be called rubbish.
There are other words that could be used that would be more emphatic.
So with that said, remember folks, this is American Freedom Radio.
Throw something their way.
You'll find it on their homepage.
Please hit the donate button.
Please send something because they are pretty much providing the venue
to hear this venue and other things.
Give American Freedom Radio some consideration here in the near future as you hear my voice.
Again, this is The Greek with Seth Michael.
Thank you very much for listening to Uncommon Sense.