Greek, hello and welcome. Greetings. Yes, greetings, Seth. Greetings, everyone, and this is Uncommon Sense.
On American Freedom Radio, we could be also streaming on UStream and maybe other places in the future.
So, greetings, everyone.
You know, it's interesting, Seth,
how novel would it be to tell people roughly something about timekeeping?
But I think it's reckoning around the 24th or 25th of the third month.
So, I just wanted to kind of put that in there, meaning it's still springtime, or almost the end of spring going into summer.
Does it feel like summer on your part of the world?
Not today.
Today and the next few days, they are
forecasting to...
It's chilly, actually. It's kind of chilly outside. I actually had to kick the heater on.
Yeah, there's...
Allegedly, somebody's mucking about with the weather and the
jet stream from the north is being pulled down, like someone having their pants pulled down.
I wonder how that happens. One day, we'll talk about the weather.
But you know what's interesting? I think it was Samuel Clemens. He said, or Mark Twain,
everyone's talking about the weather. When is someone going to do something about it?
I find that to be very interesting, and I assure you folks, we will not be speaking about it on the typical human
activism,
because activism is best kept for
making bread, as in yeast. But either way, we will be discussing things
perhaps that are uncommon, wouldn't you say?
Yes, yes, absolutely.
So, yeah.
Historically, when people have done something about the weather, it's ended up poorly for them, at least. I read a story about
a guy that did some cloud seeding for
I believe it was California, actually. I don't remember the decade, but it was like the 40s or 50s.
Oh, maybe earlier?
Possibly earlier. Hatchfield, perhaps?
He ended up getting sued, actually, because
there was flooding involved and
yeah, so.
He ended up getting pranked, yes.
For pulling a prank. Pranked, yes, absolutely.
Which is really interesting. Yeah, speaking of pranks,
this is just a thought, just before we get into today, because today we might want to talk about some messages we've had from the listenership,
which all in all, it's easy to contact us at
www.uncommonradio.com.
You'll find contact information there. The reason I stress the www, because if you just do an Uncommon Radio search,
you'll get a lot of
other
sites that use that term as well, but we are the only
www.uncommonradio.com.
So,
we might want to get into
some of the messages that you forwarded as well that were sent perhaps to Seth and then forwarded to the Uncommon Radio.
Yeah, so yeah, but before I want to get into it,
I just want to kind of like having you notice this show might also be, well, it's not a dog and pony show.
We've got to figure another way to call it. It's typically called a show,
but it's very interesting how, haven't you noticed, might also be a motto, you know, of Uncommon Sense. Haven't you noticed, you know?
It's very interesting how
there's two things that seem to be
sort of in the media or in people's mind or discussion, not forward discussion, but some discussion, is that something that
kind of resembles
the
1960s revived to a certain degree regarding two things like open drug use and certain sexual
things in the quote-unquote news.
Like, you know, there's a lot of stuff about the use of public bathrooms
regarding people who like to cross-dress, right? And also there's the
revival of what's called cannabis or medical marijuana.
So, isn't it interesting how the 60s is sort of defined as a sexual revolution and a free
yourself kind of, free the mind sort of with the drug use kind of thing.
I find it to be an interesting parallel. Not that we're suggesting or I am suggesting at all that
we're going into an era that is the revived 60s, because heaven forbid the next thing we need is
wide lapels and polyester bell-bottoms again.
But I just find it to be an interesting parallel how that's roughly a generation ago or 40 years
ago, you know. And there's a lot to comment, of course, on the topic regarding the gender.
Let's just call it, that's what they're using, gender.
The sex subject, meaning, you know, the rights
that are being discussed regarding that topic, just like rights were being discussed in the 60s. And then, of course, there's the
again, just to reiterate, the cannabis use being, quote unquote, legalized or used again, which was quite popular back then.
So it's just an interesting comparison.
And there's a lot to be discussed on both of those subjects, actually, that could be more eye opening.
So I just wanted to bring that up, just something to think about.
Absolutely. Things like that in with the things coming back around, just to reference it, I guess.
Is something that you notice in music and pop culture as well, being, you know, a musician and kind of paying attention to such things.
The trends that happen in music, even outside of the like the top 40 stuff and within it as well.
The trends seem to come back around every, I wouldn't even say 40 years on that.
I'd say it's more like every 15 to 20 years.
You see the same things that were being done 15 to 20 years before that being sort of regurgitated or revisited in appearance,
sonic quality and, you know, what things that are being said and discussed even topically within the music itself.
So, well, ultimately, with music, if it sounds good, it is good.
I mean, but some people think that it was a Tchaikovsky's 1812 overture without the symphony sounds good.
If you know, I'll just for those who don't know, 1812 overture, there's a crescendo with cannon fire.
Very basic. Yes.
Yeah. So some people think that is just that itself sounds good without the symphony.
But anyway, that's another topic.
Again, there's a matter of taste, you know, and things, you know, you heard the term like being palatable.
And I like to discuss palette sometimes in terms of being juvenile or mature or corrupted or whatever, you know, discerning.
There's many ways to discuss the palette as well.
But the thing is, you know, the purpose of coming together is being uncommon or maybe talking about what's uncommon.
And I just want to give a little footnote on the name of the show came about.
I keep referring it to a show loosely is speaking with someone at AFR about doing a another sonic project.
We had done one before called Ocelli and the Greek, which you will find at Ocelli and the Greek dot com.
You will find archives there.
And there's also a disclaimer on there, which is necessary because what you will find there is highly unusual.
But I was discussing perhaps another some a sonic project and how the things that could be discussed or the Greek likes to discuss are not really for everyone.
And it doesn't quite accommodate the masses.
And the response I got was, well, you're basically, you know, it's basically common sense was the response.
And I said, well, actually, it's uncommon sense.
And that's how we came up with the name Uncommon Sense or Uncommon Radio.
So I just wanted to throw that in there because there's a thing that can be said, you know, discussing with people about anything.
Just take whatever it is and turn it upside down.
And guess what?
When you do that now, it's right side up.
How simple can that be?
Maybe because everything's kind of turned upside down.
But I think it's a good thing to a degree.
Absolutely.
Topsy turvy.
Yes. Yes.
And it's really more complicated than that, but simply complicated.
That's a twist on words, meaning that all we have to do is look at what things are based on and is it lawful?
So, you know, there's a there's a level of futility, by the way, that I've noticed that is within the time span that people encounter at various events.
is there are certain desires that people express
that never seem to be fulfilled, right?
And they seem to still engage in maybe referring
to what that desire might be attached to.
That might be a comment on internet radio
or just study, even all the way to university, for example.
And the futility there is, you know,
very often people will discuss, you know,
we are so advanced or the Greek philosophers
were so wonderful or we know so much.
Well, if that is all true and so good,
how well is it serving you?
The answer might be by most, not very well.
So then there has to be something uncommon
that is the underlying root of all these things.
And we would like to suggest that it's very simple
when you encounter anything, just ask what it's based on.
What could it be about, right?
What is the history of the thing or what does it mean?
You know, it's like being on a construction site.
You know, what does two feet mean?
Is there a reference?
You know, is there something that we can communicate?
What do these things mean?
What are they based on?
I was having a loose discussion about this with someone
and says, well, all that stuff's made up.
Anyway, all right, so let's just discount everything
that's come before us as being made up
so we can make up new things now.
I wanted to play something, Seth, regarding,
hmm, let me just put it this way.
Have you ever noticed when,
I'm gonna go back to what I wanna play.
It's called the Aesop's Fables, The Fox and the Grapes.
But just to preface, you ever hear on,
especially in alternative radio,
people like to use movie metaphors a lot?
Oh yeah.
And it sounds plausible, you know, why not?
You know, using a metaphor, an allegory is fine.
But after a while, you know, listening to this,
you know, they like to use the movie, The Matrix
and other current films, let's say that might be out.
I was like, okay, why are they stuck on that?
Oh, because that's all they know.
It's very interesting.
This goes back to the, when you look at the cultures
that have come before, people went to get information
from the circus or the public gatherings
and that's all they knew.
They seem to, there seems to be a disconnect.
But that's fine.
If at least they are making a metaphor.
But when you bring up anything regarding,
let's say any of the holy writs of the world,
any ancient texts, the people just tend to either
not wanna hear it or discount it as being works of fiction
or they wanna tell you what they believe it says, right?
Versus, you know, or some common accepted
erroneous explanation or lack thereof.
And the reason I gave the movie reference
is because the film Pulp Fiction,
I think it was Jules or someone,
right before he pops a cap in someone's ass,
he reads Ezekiel 25, 17 or something like that.
You remember that film?
I do.
I use that slang term by the way,
pops a cap and whatever, right?
What's interesting, I like to do Aesop's Fables
whenever I have a discussion with someone
that I recognize as an imbecile.
And by the way, if you guys know what Napoleonic law is,
you're guilty till proven innocent.
That's how that works.
You've got 7 billion imbeciles on the planet
and you have to prove that you're not one
and that's how you operate efficiently.
But by the way, I guess I did say that.
But before you address an imbecile further,
you ask them if they've ever heard of
the fox and the grapes and typically they say no.
But that's Aesop's Fables and Aesop's Fables,
like for example, have you heard of the tortoise and the hare?
These are like little children's,
now they've reserved them for children's stories, right?
That's Aesop.
And what's interesting about the fox and the grapes
is they typically reserve a lot of the fox
and the grapes type stories in Aesop's Fables for children.
That's interesting because they're not kids, folks,
they're just little people.
But Seth, what do you think?
Should I play, it's a short one minute YouTube
and you know, I feel a lot smarter,
I watched a YouTube today, man.
So if, yeah, all right, it's about 49 seconds or so
and we'll just do that, yeah.
We're not planning on uploading any of this stuff
for doing the YouTube thing.
So just to give credit anyway,
it's a YouTube channel called Free School.
The title is the fox and the grapes,
hyphen Aesop's Fables for kids, free school.
So here we go.
The fox and the grapes.
A hungry fox saw some fine bunches of grapes
hanging from a vine that was trained along a high trellis
and did his best to reach them.
He jumped and he jumped as high as he could,
but it was all in vain for they were just out of reach.
So he gave up trying and walked away
with an air of dignity and unconcern remarking,
I thought those grapes were ripe,
but I see now that they are quite sour.
The moral of this story is that it's easy to despise
something that you cannot have.
Interesting.
And I know we'll just tie that back into comprehension
and understanding and it's not that many things
are difficult to comprehend or understand,
it's that people don't want to.
It's the, I don't know, I don't want to know
and I don't care attitude
that has befallen society as a whole.
And this is a pretty general statement
that is fairly accurate.
And anyone can pretty much see that
it's accuracy holds true.
Go ahead.
I would throw in, I don't like it as well.
Yes.
While they're like touching themselves
and they have a blank stare on their eye,
maybe a little drool, you know,
this is your typical earth inhabitant at the moment, folks.
And if you don't see it that way,
they're using a lot of makeup
and current fashions to cover it up.
But typically, you know, what's interesting,
the level of futility, I call the dummy load.
I've done a show on it,
well, an episode called the dummy load.
And dummy load is basically a device
that just takes energy away from a system
before it's put into use.
Like, for example, someone running a mile on a treadmill.
That treadmill actually represents a dummy load.
It takes, it allows the runner
to go through the action of running,
but they're not going anywhere, right?
Or the hamster wheel.
Or people tuning in to various forms of entertainment
or information-based situations.
And they actually leave with a feeling
but don't know anything still.
And nothing is ever even being said.
They're just being dummy loaded.
In other words, there's a desire for people to hear
and be up-to-date and current or communicate.
And what I'm suggesting,
and I'm gonna be safe to say it's a suggestion,
everything out there at the moment is a dummy load.
And what I mean by that
is if you try to look up good reference material even,
you're gonna have to sift through some stuff
other than, you know, stuff that's non-literary
like, you know, scales and measurements and things.
So, yeah, so this is, I guess, 24 hours a day
by the wind-up toy known as the clock
times seven days in a week is roughly 168 hours.
So you've got 166 hours of dummy loading
and you've got maybe two hours of uncommon sense
which tends to be dummy load-free.
That's not, I guess, less than 1% or so,
a little bit over 1%.
So about 99% of the time, folks, you're being dummy loaded.
So with that said,
just to go back to the fox and the grapes for a moment.
So that's, I guess, the recap on that
is when people find something
that might require too much work or investment of talk
or investment of time to discover,
and they seem that initially they can't understand it,
well, guess what?
That information may not be good anyway, right?
That seems to be the idea.
There's even information out there
that you can link to on the internet
that is poor in quality to be generous.
There's, you know, the dummy load, as you said,
it's relatively ever-present,
and especially now with the technology available
at a large portion of the world's population,
why are we not all geniuses now
with the world's libraries at our fingertips?
Why are we watching cats be cats on the internet?
And that's probably a poor example, but.
Yes, no, no, it's appropriate.
Because maybe the metaphor of the computer,
you know, you need an operating system
to then you download the programs and then the files.
These would be the files.
The files are all accessible, aren't they?
But if you don't have the correct operating system,
even with easy access to the files,
you're not going to be able to read them.
Yeah, or programs download.
So I've kind of discussed,
this might sound dogmatic to people,
that your operating system comes from your deity,
from your God.
That's something to think about.
And right away when you say anything like that,
it kind of rubs people the wrong way
because from an academic point of view,
let's use that word loosely,
you could pretty much say the entire world
is fairly atheist or pagan at this point.
By definition, that would be very accurate.
I would say they're just unacknowledging
the fact that they're agnostics, but.
Right, yeah.
Well, the reason I'm saying pagan
is because pagan means ignorant typically
or like so simple that there's no advancement.
It was kind of used to refer to like country bumpkins.
Yeah.
Back when it was first being used colloquially.
And there's different.
Shouldn't be uneducated.
You could put an attenuator knob on there,
how severe or how mild the term could be used.
But typically, yeah, country bumpkin or ignorant.
But the interesting thing is some ancient place
wrote that people will take the curse upon themselves
and now they're actually people proud of being pagan.
So that's, and actually,
if you discuss anything with those people,
they actually tell you that knowledge doesn't matter.
So it's kind of like easy to prove,
but pagan meaning ignorant.
And then when I say atheist means lack of or no God,
what I mean by that is when you try to discuss that
with anyone who is a participant
in any of the world religions,
asking them about their God or the God
or whatever they're talking about,
they seemingly have no information,
lack specifics to the point
where it's as if they're talking about nothing.
You're gonna notice that?
Ask anyone that's in the major faiths of the world,
what do you mean by God?
And they're like, well, you know, you know, God, man.
You know, God, you know, you know.
Which one?
What do you mean, man?
Like the one, you know, the one, you know.
Do you have any information on it?
Nope.
Don't know, man.
You don't know.
All right, so that's why I mean they're atheists
because they have no information.
In other words, it's almost unidentifiable.
There's no referencing.
There's no, it's almost as if in the realm of fiction,
right?
So that's why I mean they're predominantly atheists
by analysis, by the way.
You know, if you're examining the thing, you know.
Absolutely.
We're.
Well, semi-absolutely
because I had to really give those definitions away.
You know, the analysis might work out,
but yeah.
So yeah, Seth, do you remember
forwarding some of those messages?
What did you, did you read any of them
or did you kind of go into it a little bit?
What do you think of it?
I did.
It's, again, you know, it's pleasant to receive
such things as feedback,
even if it's, you know, few and far between.
It's good to know that there are people out there
or there is a person even out there
listening and wanting to know more.
You did mention the Ocelli and the Greek program,
which some of the questions that were brought up
in one of the emails or a couple of the emails recently
were addressed, you know, with more,
more comprehensively in talks that you've had
with Ocelli in the past.
So if you, I would strongly recommend
pointing people in that direction
just because you and I have spoken to each other,
you know, over the last two and a half, three years
extensively publicly and privately.
And so we're, you know, more familiar
with a lot of the subject matter that we're discussing
and we do try and make it accessible
for those who desire to listen
and perhaps learn a little bit.
But at the same time, for us to go back
and rehash everything, you know, verbatim over and over
is, it can be kind of frustrating
because then it's like talking to a wall.
So there are recorded conversations out there
that can be accessed.
Is the website ocelliandthegreek.com?
Yes.
Spell that, would you spell that?
O-C-H-E-L-L-I-A-N-D-T-H-E-G-R-E-E-K.com.
By the way, just to cut in there for a moment,
it's called redundancy and it seems to be
one of the necessary aspects
for the surface dwelling earth inhabitant, right?
Over just repeating.
One of the, if you go through the email set,
if you look at some of the responses
for the past year or so or less
that I've given is, discussed this already,
please go to archives,
would be 90% of the responses that I give.
So I would say that redundancy is important.
Repetition, but you see, there's two types of that.
One is, is the repetition required
like working out in the gym
where an atrophied muscle starts to gain strength and grow?
You see?
Or like doing reps, you know, in a gym?
Does it make someone stronger
or is it because it eludes them
and they can't hear it in the beginning
and then they have to go hear it again?
Almost like as if, you know,
you ever watch a movie twice
and you see things you didn't see the first time
or read a book twice
and notice things that you didn't read before.
So either way, there's no fault, it's fine.
But it does seem to be required.
Yeah, and memory is, you know,
my own powers of memory are not as apt
as a lot of people that I speak with, actually.
So, you know, there is definitely value in the repetition.
That's, you know, that's a learning tool.
But at the same time, you know, like I said,
just being aware that there are
some archived programs out there
that people can go to for just a little bit more
comprehensive than we get into sometimes.
And there, I mean, you know, we,
again, we visit a lot of the same subjects
and we do get into things relatively comprehensively.
And if there, you know, again,
I do encourage people to reach out and email us
and with any, you know, questions or clarity
and we will respond as we can
or direct you somewhere
where you might be able to find that, so.
Now, without actually going into the email itself
specifically, the topics there, you know, being asked
are sort of a blend between political notions
and quote, unquote, spiritual ones,
meaning of the mind or of the gods, the realm of the gods.
You know, there's gotta be an easier way to sell that,
say that, basically the realm of the world
or society of the gods, let's say.
It crosses back and forth.
And one comment, and it could be taken as advice,
it could be taken as a comment for something to observe
and say, hmm, about, is you ever notice how people
that claim to be, have a strong faith
or subscribe to a particular religion
tend to blame the goings on in the actual physical reality
on their government or politicians
as if the gods have nothing to do with it.
So for example, I'll just use, you know,
a Christian fundamentalist, right,
is extremely concerned about the political condition
and is highly politically active.
The quote, unquote, born again Christians
are very politically active as if that matters.
The hypocrisy is just amazing.
So are you either, are you crediting the gods
with influence on this existence or with your mouth,
but your actions and other things you say
completely discredit the influence of the gods
and it's really some politician
that's actually been put there by the gods
to rule over you, by the way.
Isn't it interesting, do you ever find that,
do you ever notice that?
Absolutely, but then again, I view these groups
for what they appear to be and it's just social clubs
with varying constitutions of membership
and things like that, that they spell out
what they believe and why they believe it, baseless.
Yeah, baseless.
There's no basis to it.
But so I'm not, I'm less and less surprised
as time goes on.
It's not whether you and I do it,
it's just an interesting thing that should be pieced
together succinctly for the listenership.
Just to repeat it, watch how people that profess
to be adherents to a particular religion
or believe in God, because you can't say particular God
because they don't know anything about that seemingly.
If they did, they wouldn't be part of that religion.
How they are attributing the significance of politics
in their life and being the root cause of things.
You still hear people complaining about the Federal Reserve
and how the Federal Reserve, my favorite, by the way,
is we have to abolish the Federal Reserve.
Or there was a political figure that was insinuating
it should be audited.
You just gotta laugh at that, you know.
Federal Reserve isn't going anywhere, folks.
It's gonna be here till the end.
Yes, it will.
Why?
Because it is simply accommodating you.
Yes, it's accommodating you.
You love that kind of stuff, unlawful stuff.
How do I know?
Well, any time you look around,
you see people engaged in unlawful activity.
Something to do with legal or not.
It's just like you ask people,
why are they doing something they don't know?
Everyone else is doing it.
Which I like to hearken back to Gustav Le Bon,
I think we got into it pretty heavily last episode,
let's say.
Yeah, we touched on it across a couple of episodes,
actually, but it's worth repeating.
Yeah, someone, actually I've gotten some messages,
people ordered it on Amazon or such.
I'm not promoting it, but I'm just using it as a reference.
And by the way, it is available as an audio book, free.
And I do recommend audio books
because that was actually the lawful way
of engaging in literary works, by the way.
It wasn't until the 1500s or so
where silent reading was encouraged.
But prior to that, it was all reading out loud,
even if you were alone.
So an audio book tends to be in accord
with the way things were done for a very, very long time.
I am, I'm a big fan of audio books, actually.
I work with my hands,
but a lot of the work that I do is repetitious
and doesn't require a lot of vigilant thought.
So I'm able to read while my hands
and my eyes are busy doing other things.
And it's, over the last few years,
I've accumulated somewhere upwards of 70 audio books.
Most of them are just entertaining,
but I've gotten a lot of what they refer to as nonfiction,
which that's questionable.
But it's a, so you're someone who finds yourself busy,
but have the ability to listen to music or whatever
while you're doing your work,
consider downloading some audio books.
You can find them all over the internet for free
if you're tech savvy.
And there are companies out there that provide them as well
for relatively low cost and things like that.
And I enjoy them.
I do wanna, we did get a question in the Ustream chat.
I'm just gonna read verbatim here.
But it says, would you consider prayer as a patch
or upgrade to the operating system?
Continuing on with that metaphor.
I find my programs degrade without regular prayer.
Popular media is like meditation on the lower entities.
It is, well, look, very simply, prayer is a technology.
Just like if you joined the military,
I like to give military analogies.
As a radio officer, you're handed a radio
and you're shown how to operate it.
It's very simple.
And the thing is, what's interesting,
let's just go back for the Christian meme,
that culture, because it is a culture, it's a secular thing.
They pray in public and they're actually,
their leaders tell them, let's pray.
Have you heard that, Laura?
Let's pray at the dinner table, right?
People gonna say, well, Greg, what's wrong with that?
It sounds good.
Well, it sounds good, right?
But here's the point.
If you look at the text that they allegedly
supposed to be subscribing to, it forbids that.
It actually shows that as being something
that you don't do, right?
And if you study the architecture of places
that were lawful, temples, prayer areas
were small, sequestered things
that people didn't do it in public.
And this goes across the board.
You will see this in all the holy rites of the world.
I'm using that term loosely,
that prayer is something that's always done privately.
Just like, that would be the technical analysis of it,
how to technically access it correctly.
But most people, again, oh, I don't like that,
doesn't sound good.
What's wrong with praying at the dinner table?
What's wrong with it, right?
It's like, well, okay, just go ahead and make stuff up.
How's that working out for you?
I would, to further the technology metaphor,
I would suggest that there's a fair portion
of the population currently walking around
with dumb phones in their pockets,
which are little computers that are.
But hold on, hold on, they're not dumb phones.
They actually are smartphone relative to the user,
but go ahead.
But these little pieces of technology
that we use to communicate,
you can access the internet,
all sorts of things that you can do with them,
communication-wise, to take photos, things like that.
There's no one out there who knows anything
about the human body that would suggest
that these devices are more technologically advanced
than these bodies that we're animating.
Walking around in.
So to just as a further lending a little bit credence,
I suppose, to the idea of the prayer
as it's written about, at least,
being something technological.
We are capable, or these bodies, I would say,
are capable of things that we are not aware of.
Not that the information is not provided
in various forms, in various places,
throughout various times,
but just that we get blinded by the flashing light.
We like pretty things.
Or the cosmic censorship,
which I've gotten into quite a bit.
If the gods wanna censor you, you're censored.
And by the way, you said we were gonna read the email.
I've been glancing through it, Seth,
and actually, we've generally and specifically answered
all those emails because,
well, there were several emails that I was gonna address.
There was a mixture of the world of the gods
and the world of mankind.
And I just suggested that there shouldn't be any mixing.
You're either attributing the reality and responsibility
to the causality that you're experiencing,
control of reality, to the gods or to mankind.
But you can't do both from a formative way,
from a primary way.
Primarily, it's the gods that are doing everything.
Secondary, it's being manifested by mankind, right?
And where there's a lesson.
Yeah, yeah.
And there's an access to free will within that.
And it's a micro, not a macro free will.
And I think I've given that analogy with the cruise ship,
which is a cruise ship going from London to New York,
for example.
And it's a cruise ship going from London to New York.
And while everyone on that ship
is going from London to New York,
but while you're on the cruise ship,
you have a choice over the duration of the journey
to go on the top deck, lower decks,
go to the theater, the food court,
go to your cabin and relax.
Or, great, let's hear free will.
But the general scope of things
tend to be moved by the divine direction,
which people don't like to look at.
And we kind of discuss this in a way we're not discussing.
I don't think what we're discussing, Seth,
is accommodating the masses,
but it's accommodating maybe the four or five listeners.
Which, in one aspect,
actually dedicating a two-hour time slot
on an internet radio is kind of like overdoing it
for four or five listeners.
But nonetheless, who knows who might hear something
that might spark something off, plant a seed.
But just to go back to the cosmic censorship
and how the spark and things that,
if you're being censored cosmically by the divine force,
there's no way you're going to see it
if they decide to censor you on a subject
or for your whole life, for example.
I think there's even a couple of things written
that if I open a door, no one can close it.
And if I close a door, no one can open it, right?
So, yeah.
Yeah, and that's from the divine perspective.
But from even the cosmic censorship,
I mean, that's just a very simple way to explain it.
But if you don't acknowledge
that the gods are in control to a certain degree,
if not primarily the controllers,
you will not, the rest of it is meaningless, obviously.
Because again, we just said that most people
that tend to have faith or subscribe
to a particular religious affiliation
tend to always blame or have the inherent blame
of their woes and ills on someone else,
meaning of man or political or whatever.
Yes, they will dispense it,
but they are not the primary reason for it.
Well, actually the primary reason that goes around.
And by the way, Seth, you know,
I've been getting some questions like,
what is the meaning of this whole thing, you know?
This whole existence.
And I usually tell people in private,
but I'll just run it by in public
because, you know, there was a saying once,
if you wanna hide something from people,
put it in the public library.
So if you wanna keep a secret,
might as well just say it on radio, right?
Or what's called, you know, radio.
It's very simple, folks.
The concept of having the mind or the spirit animated
by a soul and a body.
And I mean what I just said accurately,
meaning that if you remove the soul and the body,
the spirit goes into unanimation, right?
Unconsciousness, which was another message
we got about consciousness.
But okay, so the thing is,
people are so impressed with big numbers
and the relative duration of their lifespan
to the relative duration of things.
The gods find that putting a spirit into,
in other words, melding spirit and material together
and have spirit animated by material, you know, biological,
is the highest form of creation.
But not only will they prototype or run this
for a year or two or three,
or do it once or twice or a million times,
they do it for billions of times and for a long time.
This is not an experiment,
but it is just to show that a spirit
can be animated through material.
That's all it is, folks.
That's why you're still subject to death.
You're subject to death.
And in the future, you won't be subject to death.
And that's like the next level of things.
That's basically the meaning of all this stuff going on.
The only thing is people are still simply impressed
by big numbers.
And I kind of touched that point.
You know, they're like, very often you hear,
well, there's 7 billion of us and so few of them,
meaning them, you know, of course,
the politicians or the rich oligarchs
that are making everyone's life miserable, allegedly.
And they're so impressed by these big numbers.
And those numbers mean not much
because having very large numbers
and long durations of time is very common in creation.
That's why I've kind of said very often,
just because there's 7 billion people on the planet
doesn't mean that there's any significance
of quality there.
There's a significance of the number.
But I assure you the quality is very low,
even though they semi-automatically conceive and reproduce.
How do you know it's very low?
Just look around.
When was the last time you've been outside?
When was the last time you turned on the internet?
When was the last time you turned on TV or the radio?
You getting any quality?
Answer that honestly, you will say no.
You wanna make excuses for it, go ahead.
It's not why I'm saying it.
It's very objective, very low quality at this point.
Why?
Because you're subject to this entropic existence,
which will be lifted and changed,
which is almost unimaginable.
It's very difficult to even imagine no entropy
in the universe or in existence,
meaning death at this point.
So that's pretty much the meaning of everything, guys.
It's very simple and it's not because I say so
or who am I to say that?
Well, you could say it
if you just do a little bit of homework.
And are you able to observe things objectively?
Can you objectify and what are they based on?
Well, we got a couple more comments in the chat here.
It's pleasant to see that that's being utilized.
But this is kind of a specific question
that doesn't really, I'm just gonna read it.
It says, arguably, Nebuchadnezzar's vision
of all the empires of the world places us
at the iron, quote unquote, or Roman empire.
What do you think the feat mixed of iron
and clay empire will be, question mark?
Well, it's defined.
Well, yes, you can think about it
once you discover the definition, correct.
Yes, you see how we could take apart a question
and actually the answer, right, is in the question.
By the way, the questions always come before the answers
and the solutions come before the problems
because if it was the reverse,
the entire universe would just fall apart.
It's there to make balance.
But what one thinks should be based on something
and it should be clearly defined and interpreted correctly.
And by the way, there's only one interpretation of a thing,
but there are many versions, right?
For example, this is kind of a spinoff answer here,
but if you're a prime minister going to speak publicly
in a foreign country, you bring an interpreter.
You better say what you're saying
as accurately as humanly possible.
Now, if you bring up something like Nebuchadnezzar,
and iron and the mixed feet and toes,
you could bet that, well, I shouldn't say bet,
that's not lawful, but you would,
I could pretty much assure you
that the answer is within that same text.
So now the answer is, should we spoonfeed this individual
or the public on what the meaning of that is?
And what do you think, Seth?
Should we just spoonfeed that?
Or should we just let them be
that they will find the answer
if they keep looking at what they formed the question out of?
What do you think?
Just give an answer to it?
Yeah, I think an answer.
Yeah, absolutely.
Very simply, you will see there are kingdoms there
that were resolved through a dream.
And the final one is a Middle East Union
that is the precursors of it.
The precursors of the precursors
are being put in place right now.
A Middle East Union, meaning a loose confederacy
of roughly 10 nations in the Middle East is what that is.
And that's why they, unlike the other kingdoms,
it's iron mixed with clay.
In other words, it holds them in position,
but it has very little structural integrity
because its purpose is to support all the others, right?
So, you know, and of course,
many quote unquote religious circles,
which absolutely cannot define anything,
tell you that it is a European Union, right?
But it doesn't quite make sense that way
because for first of all, the gods don't act in futility
and the chief God doesn't either.
And if you go down the line
and you look at the communication that's been given there,
it's basically the same stories given over and over and over
over a long period of time.
Attesting once again to the validity of repetition,
I suppose.
Yes, yes.
And where one picks up where the other one left off.
So that requires harmony, but very simply,
giving a very simple,
the text says it's very simple by the way,
but the text also tells you most people will be censored.
And that's another thing we just kind of briefly discussed.
And in regards to that, actually,
another listener in the chat asks,
in regards to cosmic censorship,
or I should say states that in regards
to cosmic censorship, I can attest to its validity.
Made the mistake of broadcasting widely and loudly
my intention to change the world
and paid the price rather dearly.
The question being, can one maintain these sentiments
quietly and silently and make them so?
I would say that you can't really do something quietly
and silently at the same time,
but broadcasting with the intent to change the world
would be kind of-
Inefficient.
Missing, well, inefficient and sort of missing the,
I don't know if there is a singular point
to the discussion that we're having
other than to encourage people to think
in an uncommon manner perhaps.
But that seeking out the idea of changing the world
is probably not a good thing to do.
If you want to change the world in a positive manner,
you could sweep your front porch
or you could help someone out that needs it.
But beyond that, it's, and I hate using the word,
but it's like a fallacy of egoism.
Well, setting yourself apart, Seth, is the solution.
But here's the thing, if everyone set themselves apart
from stuff that's crappy, then the crappy stuff goes away.
Right.
There's no reason to change it.
It's going to change regardless.
But the thing, here's the point about the efficiency.
If you know these things are going to happen,
so you have to understand what's coming.
If you don't, you'll be acting inefficiently.
It's kind of like you want to go on a cross-country trip
and the gas tank in the car is near E, right?
And you think you're not going to make it.
Well, actually you can, there's certain technologies
you can apply, but that's another discussion.
You're not going to make, so do you, right?
If you're going to bake a cake
or if you're going to do something,
you pretty much are familiar with its outcome.
But when it comes to things regarding the world
and big things, people tend to not want to look at that.
It's very easy to see, well, simple, not easy,
what's coming in the future.
And if you know what's coming and it can't be changed
because it's prophetic, and by the way,
a lot of morons say, well, we can change prophecy.
Well, if you could change it, then it wouldn't be prophecy.
Then it would be a certain scenario,
you know, and if this, then that, right?
Can't change prophecy, folks, that's why it's prophecy.
But anyway, if you understand prophecy
or understand what's going to happen,
you act very efficiently.
In other words, if you're going to bake a cake
and you know it needs 45 minutes in the oven
at a certain temperature, if you take it out
after five minutes wondering why it's not done,
it's no one's fault but yours.
Because you obviously don't know anything
about baking cakes, right?
So if you're going around thinking
you have to change the world or things,
are they going to get better or get worse
or what's coming in the future,
you don't know about prophecy.
You don't know about things that will come.
And by the way, the reason it's called prophecy
is because it doesn't change.
There are mechanisms in nature that show you time.
Like for example, it's in the stars, have you heard that?
You know, or in the cards, various forms of divination.
Those things tend to have a certain degree of accuracy,
but with the purpose of prophecy
is to show you the anomalies where that machine breaks down.
You know, it's very clear to see anyone
who works with metal in alchemy
that the certain planets rule over certain metals
like Mars rules over iron, the moon rules over silver,
lead is ruled by Saturn, right?
But that's another discussion again.
So, there's a level of efficiency.
The problem is right now all the information regarding prophecy that's put
out is either accurate in small little pieces or just absolutely incorrect.
And it's easy to say that, and you could say that with confidence
if you actually do the research.
So, I want to play, yeah, I want to play something, Seth, because another YouTube,
I hope everyone feels smarter since we're playing a couple of YouTubes.
This is, in short, we've been talking about a Middle East Union that's going
to be formed in the near future.
It's a very loose confederacy, just like the iron and clay, for example.
And one of the requirements is about 10 nations, but if you look at the count
or by name how many there are right now, there are only about nine of them in existence.
The 10th one is not in existence yet.
And the one we're speaking of, by the way, this is where things are quiet,
not noisy in the news, is a nation called Assyria, not Syria, Assyria, A-S-S-Y-R-I-A.
Yes, there are a group of people known as the Assyrians, and they haven't had a country
in about 2,300 or so years, and one of the reasons why is because if they did remain
as a national body, there probably wouldn't be anyone left today
because their primary industry was war.
So, anyway, what I want to play, I'll just click on this here, I'll open it.
It's Chris Bowen, B-O-W-E-N-M-P.
He is in the Australian Parliament, and the YouTube is called Chris Bowen, Assyrian Motion.
And I'm going to start it at around 420 or so.
And he proposes something, and you know how we've said when things are planted, it's quiet,
and everyone tends to like to look where the distraction or the noise is.
So, I'm going to start playing this for about a minute, and listen to it, these folks,
because it's a parliament, and this person standing up,
his name is Chris Bowen, starts proposing, okay, at the Australian Parliament.
...chance of a new life in Australia.
This is the problem, Deputy Speaker, but of course, we must have a view to the solution.
Having looked at this issue over many years, having worked with the Assyrian Kaldane communities,
having done much in relation to working with the Australian government
and the successive foreign ministers, Smith, Rudd, and Carr on this issue,
I've reached a view that the only sustainable solution is an autonomous region within Iraq,
administered by Kaldanes and the Syrians.
Okay, I'm going to play that one more time, okay?
...government and the successive foreign ministers, Smith, Rudd, and Carr on this issue,
I've reached a view that the only sustainable solution is an autonomous region within Iraq,
administered by Kaldanes and the Syrians.
In the northwest of Iraq lies the Nineveh Plains, a 4,000 square kilometer area
that is believed and is the traditional heartland of the Assyrian people.
The majority of its population is Christian, including many displaced Assyrians
who've come to the Nineveh Plains...
Well, you guys get the point, hopefully.
Now, that was not broadcast anywhere on mainstream or alternative media, was it, Seth?
No.
And it won't be, because the stuff you hear on mainstream and alternative is where the noise is.
And that's where the imbeciles go, oops, did I say that? Yes.
So, you always distract an imbecile with a noisy situation.
That's why circuses and carnivals and shows and movies tend to be noisy and loud.
And also, if you combine that with...
By the way, combine that with Libon, the crowd, if you think I use harsh language, he does as well.
The typical person who joins a crowd is considered an imbecile.
You have to be, essentially.
But, so, you're not hearing anything.
Well, you do hear a lot of things.
Unfortunately, no one is listening to anything.
They tend to repeat things that they've heard somewhere else.
And just a comment on the alternative media, we kind of always do that,
is that now they've gotten to the point where they are self-consuming,
where they're actually going to each other for their research.
They're in a self-consuming, dog-chasing-its-tail point.
So, anyway, we will be back after the break,
and we will perhaps get into some more uncommon things with the Greek and Seth Michael,
here at AFR and streaming anywhere else we can.
Absolutely. We have a couple more questions, even, that have popped up in the chat.
We'll address after the break.
And, yeah, like the Greek said, thank you for being out there and listening,
and we'll be right back.
Greetings, everyone.
Yes, welcome back to Uncommon Sense here on AFR, AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Thanks for being out there and listening.
I'm Seth, and I'm here with the Greek.
You can find us on the interweb at UncommonRadio.com,
spelled just completely normal, www.UncommonRadio.com,
and you can find a number of ways to get into contact with us there, if you would like to.
We're also broadcasting on uStream.tv forward slash channel forward slash second hyphen foundation.
I know that's a mouthful, but...
Or they can just go to the www.UncommonRadio.com and click on the uStream.
It'll be easiest way to be brought to it.
Absolutely.
Yeah, cool.
We should mention that AFR is, you know, carrying the program here and broadcasting us,
and that they can certainly use the help if you like what you're hearing,
if you enjoy the program, if you're actually listening and learning something.
You can go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and follow the links through to support them in any way that you can,
and we encourage you to do that.
Yep, they could definitely use it.
They don't do all this for themselves.
They do it so everyone else can tune in.
So, speaking of tuning in, I think we might have more, we might have been informed
there might be more than four or five people listening,
but nonetheless, we carry on as if there are only four or five people listening,
because the interesting thing is, if you do carry on with a lot of the things that you hear here,
and you actually impose it upon yourself to do some research and find out what we are telling you is look-upable,
based on something, lawful,
and you start repeating this to your average surface-dwelling earth inhabitant,
you will find yourself alone.
You will not make friends with this type of conversation.
I assure you that.
Now, there are friends to be made, friends to be had,
but this is generally not the way to start it off unless you are encountering someone extremely special.
So, we wanted to maybe address the question of the soul and the spirit again.
I think that wouldn't be a bad thing to kind of bring up, not because we say it,
but because whoever listens and does a little bit of work will also discover it to be true.
Simply said, Seth, the spirit is the mind, the soul is your breath, as in inhaling, exhaling,
and the body is the body.
Now, these things are assembled technically in a biological way,
what we are still seemingly can't understand completely.
It's just a technology, folks, and it's a technology of the gods that you're witnessing,
and obviously, if you're not acknowledging it as such, you are censored,
and everyone has a little bit of censorship because the last thing you want to do is be fully aware.
Actually, if you were fully aware and kept your cool about it and rational,
you would pretty much leave this stinking rock.
Yes, it is a beautiful planet, but what mankind is doing is pretty stinky.
So anyway, I'll digress from that.
Anything else we should bring up, Seth, regarding the questions?
Well, I know we don't do this often, but something that might be of help
to at least one or two of the people out there listening,
where could one go to find clarity, literal clarity,
as in something written in reference to the difference between the spirit and the soul,
and what those are, at least in reference to old books, scriptures?
Yeah, you will find it. First, the easiest way to do it,
let's just hold the hand, so to speak, and walk through real quickly.
Find any reference material, the closest one at hand, regardless of quality, and start there.
What you will find is right away that you might be naive,
and you might need more comprehension.
What I mean by naive is if you pick up a reference piece of material,
and it says the soul, it means the breath, it could also mean the spirit.
Well, then you go look up spirit, and it says the spirit, it's the mind,
it could also mean the soul.
Guess what? You're being conned.
By the way, con comes from confidence, like a con man.
What they do is they build your confidence, and then they take advantage of you.
It's known as pranking.
Confidence, the operating words there being, what, fidelis or fidelity?
With fidelity, yes.
Yeah, with fidelity. Fidelity being, what, truth or faithful.
You're going to do a lot of fun doing etymology of words such as truth, and faith,
and confidence, and fidelity, and stuff like that.
A lot of it leads in circles.
And usually the more important the event, or the more important the information,
more obfuscation and corruption is put in.
But it's put in a very simple way that is accepted,
or made acceptable because it's done at a certain time period.
Here's another thing.
Avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
The more important the information, you can bet on that it has been corrupted,
or twisted a certain way.
If you look at major events throughout history, how they've been explained.
You know, let's bring up 9-11, for example.
Not only do you have the official story, you have an entire movement that's trying to research it,
and they're all incorrect.
And by the way, if, let's just digress for a moment using that as an example,
it only takes objectivity to find out what happened there, right?
The same thing with all these other things.
If we're going to go back to the soul and the spirit definition,
if we look at the Greek nomenclature that's used in Western society,
even, by the way, when you look up soul,
they reversed it in the, or spirit,
they reversed it in the Strongsteens or Strong's concordances as well.
But the soul is where you see the Greek prefix pnu, like pneuma, means soul.
That's where you get the term that refers to the movement of air,
pneumatic, pneumonia.
And the mind or the spirit is where you get psi, psyche, or the PSY prefix.
So whenever you see anything with a PSY, psychology, psychotic, psychic,
means of the mind or of the spirit.
So your spirit is your mind.
It's intangible, right?
And it requires the soul and the body to animate it,
where the soul and the body are quite tangible.
You can hold up a piece of glass or glasses to your breath, exhale,
and it fogs the glass.
That's your tangible evidence of your soul.
Tangible evidence of your soul is if someone drowns
and you pull them out of the water and they're not breathing,
they have no soul because they're not breathing.
You can put your soul into their body until they animate and have a soul of their own.
Soul of animals and humans and insects are all interchangeable
because they're all breathing.
Very simple.
And this is very, very, very difficult to internalize or view as a good definition
because if you go out into the world,
and supposedly those that profess to be quote-unquote spiritual
and gurus and teachers and masters, they don't know it.
So you being a common person doing whatever you do,
going to someone who supposedly know these things disagrees with that,
you know, how does that make you feel?
Does it make you feel good?
So you have to bypass these people that, yes, there are people
and reference materials that have obfuscated the meaning and the clarity of it.
Because a little bit of research,
you could see what we are telling you in every language holds true.
They tend to obfuscate or corrupt the meaning of soul and spirit
because the last thing that those in power,
secular and non-secular, want humans to know
what headquarters is made of, what you are made of.
If you are made of a spirit, a soul, and a body,
and you could clearly define that,
now you know what's going on, at least with yourself.
And knowing thyself, that's the first thing that is sort of dealt with.
So if you can get people to not know who they are,
well, guess what?
They're probably not going to know anything about anything else anyway,
because you are headquarters for your spirit, yourself.
And if your headquarters is corrupted, well, you'll only resonate with corruption.
So it's very interesting how simple it can be.
It's not easy, because most people are social creatures.
They like to socialize.
They like to feel loved and befriended by others.
And I assure you, if you start looking at what things mean lawfully,
you will not make any friends with it.
You know, there is always an exception to that.
But, you know, then by all means, be the exception.
It will lead to some interesting conversations.
Yes, yes, until they start looking like they have a look in their eye,
like they're fixing on putting violence on you.
Right?
Then you better start distancing yourself.
Yeah, yeah.
But you will have a good laugh when you look at how supposedly people
who are trained in these matters,
whether mainstream or alternative, religious or not,
how they will give you a million reasons that the soul is not the breath
and the spirit is not the mind,
but they will never address what you're saying.
A well-trained animal just simply does what you tell it to do.
Yeah.
And how well do they do in their natural environment?
Could you imagine, by the way,
a circus bear that can like juggle balls and stand on a stool,
how well he'll do when he's put in with other bears in the wild?
I don't think the other bears are going to find it too interesting.
But anyway, even though he is smarter than the average bear,
to who?
So, yeah.
So any other questions?
No, no, not specifically.
A few comments here and there,
but it's all, you know,
things that we've been talking about directly,
such as the Ruach and the Strong's theme definitely need better reference material.
To which I just replied, you know,
in the text, what is being referenced is more clear
than the commentaries would have anyone believe.
And, you know,
dictionaries just obfuscate it further.
Lots of fun, sarcastically, of course.
But if basically what you and I are talking about,
when we say, you know,
soulless breath and spirit is, you know, mind,
is how the words as translated into English
are actually used in the manner in which they're translated.
This is not something that you're going to punch into the internet and find easily.
Hence, the idea and concept of, you know, study,
which I don't actually recommend anyone do too much of.
Anyone who is studying or wants to make a study of scripture,
what is commonly referred to, you know,
colloquially as the Bible, you know, that grouping of many books.
I recommend people start anyone, anyone at all,
regardless of what translation you're working with.
Or lack of.
Yeah, or lack of.
There is no translation, actually.
Regardless of whatever version you're reading from.
Start with what they call in English Ecclesiastes.
It's Kohalath is the name of the book.
But start with that and read it because it's very,
it doesn't take much, much background to understand what's being said.
And it's very, I would say it's wisdom.
That's what I'd say.
So I would start there.
Which is extremely lacking, by the way, in the world today.
Very much so.
Yes.
And we used to go to, when I say we, however you want to say that,
to the older people in society for that.
And now I assure you, they've all been reduced to fools.
And I say all, all, but maybe a few, which I haven't met yet.
But for all you younger people out there,
go ahead and strike up a conversation with anyone older than 50
and tell me if you get any wisdom severely lacking.
Generally, when, and again, this is generally,
so it's certainly not anytime, but most, most of the time,
when it comes up in conversation, just, you know,
through my own personal experience,
and after the conversation's gone on for more than two or three sentences or paragraphs,
I just start being asked a lot of questions, actually.
So regardless of the age of the listener.
So just to tie things back, let's go back a little bit, Seth.
I hit the rewind button.
Someone asked about breath and ether before, soul and ether.
This is an interesting thing.
Breathing, you know, there's a pulse, there's a rhythmic pulse to it,
which, what's interesting about it is that all living things have that
and all things are living to some degree,
like the earth inhales and exhales with day and night.
But in terms of people, because most likely a people had asked that question,
is that the main constituent in the air is nitrogen.
And if one does research on nitrogen itself,
you'll find there's not much information about it,
other than that it's a very significant gas in many functions.
But it's actually a pulsing gas,
and it assists that pulsation that is accommodated through breathing,
or by breathing, or to breathe.
And if we look at, that's still materialistic, not answering the ether.
But the thing about what is the ether, I like, and I'll say this,
my mentor who recently passed away, or one of my mentors, Trevor James Constable,
wrote a lot about the ether, as did people like Rudolf Steiner and Wilhelm Reich.
It was sort of brought forward post-Newtonian again
to sort of invent this thing to explain phenomenon.
But essentially, when we say the ether, when I say the ether, let's say,
I'm referring to the life force.
There's an underlying primary force.
And because it's so primary, it's very difficult to get a handle on it
being in a secondary existence, meaning locked up in this physical reality.
But it is primary.
But just like Oliver Heaviside said,
just because I don't know how I digest, it doesn't mean I cannot enjoy my supper.
So we don't really have a handle on the ether.
We do know how to technically access it, by the way, at this point.
That information is out there, albeit not very accurate in most places.
But it is accessible.
It can be manipulated to a certain degree regarding the weather and other functions
that are very subtle.
One thing that I can't say about the ether is the denser the object, the finer the ether.
And the less density an object has, the coarser or more dense the ether is.
It's a concept that Steiner talked about as counter space.
So now we're going to go off into an ether discussion.
Probably not.
But the life force is real.
It is tangible when an attempt to access it technically is.
Even not so technical.
A lot of the ancient cultures were accessing it for rainmaking and healing purposes
and to imbue vitality and invigor things.
So the ether is a big discussion.
But essentially, the safest way to employ discussion on the ether is by dubbing it the life force.
Just like there isn't any scientist or medical technician that could
explain to you what it takes to stand up from a chair and walk across the room.
They can't explain how that happens.
And that would be evidence of the life force directly and indirectly because it's so intangible.
But that was kind of a long, maybe direct, in some ways, indirect answer.
But by the way, that spins me off into another thought.
Folks, when you listen to things, you know, quote unquote shows, information, topics,
I hope you're being entertained because generally that's what you will get out of it.
Essentially, the ability to convey information and part information to humanity at this point
has become almost non-existent.
Everything seems to be in the entertainment phase right now.
I'll give an example.
I hear this often in the, not too often lately, but in the alternative media.
Oh, no one knows how the pyramids were built.
Wait a second.
What do you mean no one knows?
How did you, did you meet everyone to know that everyone doesn't?
Did you mean everyone doesn't know?
And they start bringing up these ridiculous comparisons to kind of guide you down
this ridiculous assumption that no one knows how the pyramids were built.
Even today, oh yeah, because today we're so advanced,
we don't have any cranes that could lift those big stones.
Excuse me.
When something is really, really heavy,
the most sensible way to move it is not to figure out a way to lift it, right?
Gosh, I mean some of the discussions that are supposed to be informational,
like bringing up the pyramids, how the pyramids were built again,
because it's come across in passing privately,
and I've seen certain people discussing it publicly,
and it's an idiotic subject, especially when you listen to the reasoning behind it.
You don't lift something that heavy.
As a matter of fact, there's a fellow called Wally Wallington.
You could look him up, and he moves 20-ton blocks by himself.
He could move them at a rate of, I think, several hundred yards a day by himself.
20 tons would be about the weight of five typical automobiles or motorized wagons.
But no one wants to really, you know, look at that,
because then the question of no one knows who built the pyramids kind of goes away.
It's very philosophical.
But the morons that do bring this up, no one knows how the pyramids were built.
Start giving your reasons, like we don't have technology today.
Who's we?
And what technology do you have today that you would apply?
That's the wrong way to look at it.
And when I say wrong, it's because it's very simple.
Yes, the pyramids can be built in a very short amount of time with very few people,
but you wouldn't be lifting anything.
You would be actually employing, and I'm just going to get off the subject here,
but the reason we call this uncommon sense is because part of it requires objectivity.
If you guys ever heard of the thing called walking?
Yes, when you stand up and put one foot in front of the other.
Oh, Greek, what are you saying?
It sounds pretty condescending.
Why do you have to be such an ass about that?
Well, here's the metaphor, and here's the reality of it.
Do you realize what's happening when you're walking?
Well, here he goes again.
Okay, you're standing up firm-footed, and you're balanced.
What happens is you put one step, or you lift one leg or one foot, and you move it forward,
and you plant it firmly on the ground, and you repeat the process, and we call that walking.
Okay, that's all the obvious stuff that's typically discussed or not thought about.
But what is actually going on, which anyone can see and admit,
is that when you proceed into that procedure,
which is lifting a leg or a foot to move it forward to walk,
before the foot is planted, you are actually displacing your center of gravity,
and you're in a state of falling.
And when the foot plants down on the firm surface, the falling state stops.
The displacement of gravity stops.
The displacement of the center of gravity stops, and you repeat the process.
An example to prove this is that if you were to take a step,
and let's say someone put a banana under your foot, you would slip and fall.
In other words, the falling process would not stop.
So the way you move very heavy objects is by finding their center of gravity and displacing it.
And I think we're going to end it right here,
because the last thing we want to do is talk about how the pyramids can be built.
Because this is, I gave this as a long metaphor, perhaps,
on are you really, are you folks really listening to what's being put out there
as quote-unquote information?
And that's why before I mentioned this is what's going on right now with communication,
especially with alternative media, is the self-consuming idiocy.
Like I, before the break, I said now it's gotten to the point where
the alternative media is actually using other alternative media for research,
which is kind of funny.
I just want to bring up one more point.
People in the alternative media researching, for example, 9-11 went through the Pentagon,
five masonry walls.
I heard one of them once suggesting a tomahawk missile.
And did they ever lift a finger to go and notice that a tomahawk missile has a fiberglass nose cone
that you could pretty much smash with a Fisher-Price hammer,
and it cannot go through five masonry walls?
But anyway, that's another discussion.
See how simple it is to just destroy the arguments or the things that are being brought forward?
Not that they need to be destroyed, because I want to preface,
these were brought up for entertainment.
But people are starting to take what's being heard and said seriously.
But are they really listening?
I would say no.
That's why we call it the dummy load.
Yeah, I would back it up just a little ways.
Edward Leedskalman comes to mind anytime I hear of the difficulty of building the pyramids
and whatnot.
Edward Leedskalman, the guy that built Coral Castle.
Yeah, now you got to realize when he did Coral Castle, are we looking at it practical?
See, what happens is we're shown something as being mystical and magical, and it's not.
There is some good eyewitness testimony.
He was very good at leverage.
And also the stones that he was lifting are coral, which are pumice, very lightweight,
relative, albeit they can be heavy.
A very large bay of hail can be very heavy, but it's still a bay of hail.
He didn't use anything mystical or magical.
He had a pretty firm grip on a lot of the energetic realities of things.
But people are trying to switch it forward into that he used some kind of levitation.
And just lifting your foot up off the ground is levitation.
And by the way, you lose levity when you're not feeling well, right?
That's why you lay down when you're feeling sick.
So levity is all around us.
It's direction of things.
But Leedskalman had a pretty good handle on many things.
His description of magnetism and electricity is fairly accurate.
It's not the be all end all, and it doesn't go into the primary aspects too much.
But if you do study Leedskalman's work, not what people write about him,
you will find pretty much yourself better off than before you did.
You know, it's very interesting reading, if nothing else.
Yes, especially if you want to entertain working in the field
of what's called electricity and magnetism.
And I would say that it's relatively uncommon as well.
I haven't read everything that he's written, but what I have read is...
Yeah, and it's somewhat validatable if you do his experiments.
Perpetual motion holder works.
And the spiraling of the electrical current is correct.
And then, of course, I see in the AFR chat,
someone put in attached lines of force, anonymous.
What's interesting about that is that would be the work of J.J. Thompson,
which is very interesting.
You know, I had a discussion with someone regarding UFOs recently,
and they showed me a photo.
It was more than recently,
and it was basically an old 1930s submarine that was levitated.
That's your cigar-shape UFOs that people tend to talk about.
It was back in the day.
They took J.J. Thompson's work and other work that he had done,
other people at the time,
and figured out that momentum and weight are not a factor of mass.
They're independent manifestations where these ethereal, let's say,
or semi-electric lines of force attach to objects,
so they keep them in motion.
Or when you try to stop them,
you notice the object tends to want to keep moving.
That is not the mass itself.
It's what attaches to it.
So if you figure out how to detach those electrical lines of force
that attach to everything,
you will have objects that could stop instantly or start instantly
without any energy input or much energy input.
So the problem is finding out this virtual ground.
And J.J. Thompson had stumbled upon this when he was trying to find out
what was the electron mass equivalent,
which is where you get the E equals mc2 formula,
which has nothing to do with energy.
It has to do with finding a relationship.
So I just wanted to bring that up, the electrical lines of force.
So if you really got more than one sharpened pencil in your pocket,
see, years ago,
a really good engineer was described as by how many sharpened pencils he had in his pocket.
So you want to meet,
so, you know, just for a common problem,
one sharpened pencil in your pocket's fine.
But something like detaching electrical lines of force from mass
is going to require three or four sharpened pencils in your pocket.
So if you think you've got that kind of capability,
go ahead and start meditating and thinking on the subject
of how do you find a virtual ground in space
to detach it from a particular object?
Right.
In other words,
if you find a ground that is not attached to anything physical,
now you can neutralize the potential that is attached to moving objects
and that object will cease to have momentum or weight.
And when you figure that out,
you can actually stop it or start it instantly.
And it's not affected by momentum or quote unquote gravity or direction that much.
So if you think you have that many sharpened pencils,
we've just laid out the outline for you.
And no one is talking about this, by the way.
Eric Dollard has brought it up.
There's a fellow named William Lyne who has brought this up.
I think he has written upon this as well, William Lyne has.
But if you go and read J.J. Thompson's work and other people around that time,
you'll find some very interesting things,
especially regarding the UFO phenomenon.
All right.
Well, we don't have any more questions in chat.
Well, there's one.
I kind of already answered it, but it's
what do you think will, if anything,
restore soundness of mind to our numb, dumb world?
He says numb, dumb selves as a correction, I believe.
That's very interesting because it's very relativistic in a point,
not as Einstein said, but that's rubbish, but relativistic, meaning
you're born and you die.
You have about 70 to 100 years if you're fortunate,
let's say, in the typical incarnation.
We tend to judge and rate severity and importance and significance
based on that perspective.
Right now, yeah, you're in the credits part.
There's no change.
In other words, live it out.
We had one email from a young individual who was asking,
he wants to live his life efficiently and such,
about food, clothing, and shelter.
It's a very good question.
But the whole thing is, yes, exactly, food, clothing, and shelter.
Make sure that your food, clothing, and shelter is of the highest quality
you can afford and make yourself comfortable and be lawful,
meaning fit and proper.
But what will undo anything is just, I mean, what undo,
what does a glass of spilled milk, I mean, how do you undo that?
Just clean it up.
The right now humanity is unrehabilitatable.
You have 7 billion pretty much unrehabilitable imbeciles on the planet.
So it has to be ridden out.
And you're going to have a mop-up crew going to clean it up.
I'm not talking about UFOs or some religious figure that you might know about.
Because, by the way, if you go look at things about the end of civilization,
meaning mankind's society, it's in every culture, right?
It has nothing to do with what religion you subscribe to or what god you believe in.
But it has definitely to do with the gods, absolutely.
And there's a hierarchy there.
And you're not going to do anything about it.
You basically wait for the mop-up crew.
But the problem with that is the last thing the gods want
is some sniveling human to give them an excuse later on.
You know?
Like, oh, we never had a chance to have world peace.
We never had a chance to learn.
We never had a chance to find out.
Yeah, you're not going to...
The gods don't want to hear that.
And because they don't want to hear that,
you're going to be thrust into, unbeknownst to you,
into a seemingly perfect society in the next decade.
It's going to last for a short time.
And you're going to be told that it's going to last for 1,000 years.
And you're all going to believe it.
Because what is there not to believe?
It won't be propagandized like the Soviet Union society,
where they said, this is a perfect society.
And you have 3,000 people waiting in line in knee-deep snow for toilet paper.
I'm not talking about that.
This is not going to be propaganda, folks.
And it's all going to come out of the Middle East area part of the world.
And I'm using the Middle East as the common vernacular.
Because if you took a map of the world,
you'll find center mass of the world to be that area.
Okay.
And you're all going to fall for pretty much what's going to be coming.
And the reason why you're going to have world peace and liberty
from things you have commitment to,
and economic, let's say, gain and spiritual knowledge
is because this way you will be without excuse.
You will be without excuse later on.
But when it's promised to last for 1,000 years, it will not.
But, you know, it'll be very convincing.
So whenever you hear, this is the part about the efficiency that is very uncommon,
is how many times do you still hear of pending doom and disaster?
Oh, let's prep for this disaster.
You know, this is coming.
No, it's not.
None of that is coming.
You're going into a veritable Garden of Eden
with a veritable, perfect, political, social, religious,
economic, judicial, artistic community.
And it's not going to be brought peacefully, obviously.
It's going to be brought with quite a heavy price,
meaning a lot of things are going to be rearranged.
But once they're done being rearranged,
it will exist for a short time.
You will have a lawful society on this planet for a short time.
So that's perhaps the answer to what does one do or how does one do it?
You know, this is what's coming.
This is where the cruise ship is going, folks.
Now, where you find your personal self in that main,
let's say, worldly circumstance is up to you, right?
Do whatever you do really well.
You know, here's the thing still.
People are told to go out and get a job.
Why would you want a job?
Why aren't you encouraged to find out what your talents are,
your natural talents, let's say, quote, unquote,
and encouraged to pursue those?
Because if you do something really, really well in this world,
as long as it's not telling people the truth, by the way,
you will do well.
If you fix on going out and making the world a better place,
and you actually know how,
you will be eating out of a garbage can.
I assure you that.
Now, if you tell people that you want to make the world a better place,
and it is a complete lie and a fraud, you will be quite wealthy.
That's just the way things are pretty much statistically,
you know, if you do the math.
So, by the way, whenever you hear anyone saying,
I want to make the world a better place,
or we have to make the world better,
you ever notice how unfounded what they're saying is?
If you ask them how, they don't really know.
It's because they're just talking, taking up time.
It's a dummy load.
You want to go somewhere that is, quote, unquote, positive.
That is giving you something that makes you feel good.
Because you have all of this energy inside of you,
and you want it directed so it feels good.
Who wants to take the biological energy
that's built up in the body through emotion,
and have it feel bad or feel not pleasant?
Everyone wants to feel pleasant.
So, you're going to gravitate to things that sound good and make you feel good.
But I'm telling you they're unfounded and baseless.
Well, actually, I'm telling you that because if you soon want to do research on this
and learn a little bit more, you will find it to be true as well.
Or you can go the fox and the grapes route.
You know, or you can, you know, however.
But in the meantime, all you will be exposed to
until this next two or year period or so is a dummy load.
There's lots of energy that's put out by systems,
including human systems, people's bodies.
And that energy needs to be used somehow, used up.
So, whatever you gravitate to, ask, is it lawful?
Is it based on anything?
What is it founded on?
And you will find that it's pretty much baseless or unfounded.
Or it's based on opinion.
Recently, I was having a discussion with someone regarding some technical matter.
And they were like, well, what is your opinion on this?
Is that I have no opinion on that.
I can give you a report on it that you will find to be true
if you replicate it or pursue it.
But I have no opinion on the matter.
And they kind of looked at me kind of like wondering what I was trying to say.
So, I think the thing is, what's lacking is good reporting.
And there's even criticism in that, right?
The mainstream media, you know, that's all fabricated, right?
Well, guess what, folks?
It's not just the mainstream media that's fabricated.
Yeah, I would say across the board as the colloquialism goes.
Yeah, in response to the question I just said, setting oneself apart,
whether or not that will restore soundness of mind is, well, I suppose not up to me.
But you can look at that as like you see a bulldozer coming
directly towards a group of people that you're standing in,
regardless of distance or speed.
Staying in that spot's probably not the greatest course of action.
You might, you know, walk over to the person operating the bulldozer
and ask them, you know, what they're doing and where they're going
to better stay out of their way, perhaps.
But don't lay down in front of it, right?
Yeah, that's not going to stop the bulldozer.
You might even, you know, wave a few friends over and be like,
hey, you might want to not stand there.
Yeah, well, that's where I discuss the thing about rights.
I always stand up for my rights.
Well, when they're fixing on busting people, it's best that you don't stand up.
Maybe have a seat at that time.
Because the tallest nail gets hammered first.
Yeah, and there's a reason.
If you want to know who the gods are backing up,
look who carries the sword, who has the weapons.
And you may not like it.
Regardless of what they say, yeah.
Exactly.
So, by the way, there's something going on called an election
in this part of the world, in the states.
And people are kind of paying attention to it and talking about candidates
and they all miss the point.
When I say all, they all miss the point.
What point is that, Greek?
Very simple.
It's an election.
Who does, do voters elect people?
No, you're being invited as a voter.
The word vote means to vow that the, that you will show up and register,
which means that form is worth about 50 grand or more,
that they will monetize and you will get nothing out of it, by the way.
But that just means that when you show up to vote,
that you are, have confidence that the system works.
And whoever the electors decide to put in is the one who's going to be
your next step forward.
Whatever leader of that particular position.
That's all the voter does.
He vows that the, that confidence in the system.
And on one hand, that's what's the reality of it,
whether people want to acknowledge it or not, go look it up.
The other hand is that the system itself, it's not cryptic about it being corrupt.
So, what's really going on from an objective point of view is that
the people are vowing to support a system that is self-admittedly corrupt.
So, I mean, this is not a secret, folks.
And you're all vowing to go forward with it.
And in the meantime, you know, this is the heart of the matter
is that voters vote, electors elect.
So, your vote is just vowing that the system works for you.
And this is the ridiculous of it.
And people ask me, who is going to be the next president, Greek?
The who, meaning the actual body that takes up is irrelevant,
but I can assure you for sure,
the next quote-unquote president is going to be worse than the one you have.
And just like the one you have is worse than the one before.
For the country.
Because the country is, boy, how do you get into that?
Here's the thing that people are not paying attention to.
How can you come across the ocean several hundred years ago
and slaughter an entire group of people
that would tend to be sort of spiritually minded
and not have them curse the land that you're taking over from them?
I mean, how naive can you be?
But anyway, that's an interesting thought.
Well, and they're currently not even following their own literature.
And it's said, you know, they were following their own rules
as put down when this conglomeration of countries was founded.
Because that's, you know, that's what the United States is.
It's a conglomeration of, what, 50 something.
Maybe there's like 52 different countries that are represented.
They refer to it as a nation.
I'm always amused when I hear people talking about America,
America, this America, then like that's two continents.
But North and South.
But there's currently, you brought up the elections that are coming up.
And when I see the vice president being the one that comes in second
as opposed to being chosen by the president
as is written down in the laws that they're not following,
then I will maybe begin paying a little bit more attention to it.
But they have, yeah, why would they?
You see, we've gotten to the discussion of the prankster.
Why do you want to make the world better?
It's one third of the population are pranksters,
are involved in prankstership straight up.
So we're talking about really the world needs to be made better.
It's the, how was, how did the guy in chat say it?
The numbness and numbness of ourselves,
not the world's works just fine.
It's been here for quite a while.
Well, the earth, the planet itself, yeah.
Wait till the people find out that the planet got a facelift
so man could be inhabited.
And the agreement was that the facelift, yeah,
the facelift will be done and man will follow these rules.
What are the rules?
Well, very simple.
If you get a job working in a pet food store, use the term loosely.
They'll tell you, for example, the rules, you know,
you'll get 10 bucks an hour and all you could steal.
And you give the dog food to the dogs, the cat food to the cat,
the fish food to the fish and the bird food to the birds.
Okay, yeah, okay.
But you know, when no one's around, you know, you're a prankster, right?
So you're going to give the bird food to the fish,
the fish food to the dog, the cat food to, right?
You're going to just kind of throw everything around and say,
hey, look, man, they're eating it anyway.
It doesn't matter, right?
That's what I mean by prankstership and rules, folks.
Do you know what people are supposed to eat to keep them helpful?
Healthful?
Probably not.
Might sound religious, right?
Do you know what you're supposed to wear?
Do you know how you're supposed to keep time lawfully?
And just because a dog develops a palate for cat food
doesn't necessarily mean that that is now dog food.
Yes, exactly.
So this is what's going on.
So the thing is, there's nothing that's why I keep saying
it's unrehabilitatable at this point.
You just have to wait for it to go down the drain.
And in the meantime, you know, do the best that you can.
Avoid the pranksters.
That would be all of your entitled classes,
the legal society, scientific society, the medical society,
education society, the religious society for sure.
But, you know, people like socializing there.
Here's the thing.
If you have 7 billion imbeciles on the planet,
you grab some of the imbeciles
and you put them in a special building for four years
and you tell them that now they have a degree
and now they can go out and get all the other imbeciles
to do things for them.
I mean, this is really bad, folks, what's going on.
But in the same time, food, clothing and shelter,
you can still seek out good food.
You could still seek out, like I say, seek out.
By the way, if anyone enjoys the art of cooking, let's say,
you'll find that going out into eating publicly right now,
it's getting harder and harder to find good places to eat
unless you're fortunate.
But food, clothing and shelter, find out what's lawful to eat,
what's lawful to wear and how you should form your dwelling.
And it's going to be real hard going to older people
asking for advice because they've all been reduced to fools.
Oops, did I just say that?
Yes, I did.
So, yeah, it's really a tough time right now.
But it's also, it's never been a time
where things are so easy to get.
Energy is still relatively cheap.
Things can be sent anywhere in the world relatively cheaply.
Information can be accessed.
But if you have no program or operating system
to process that information, it's pretty much worthless.
So, by the way, just to sum things up,
because we kind of like tend to bring up things
redundantly, maybe repetitive things.
Your operating system, your law,
I'm not talking about traffic law or tax law
or what pranksters like to call it law.
But your law is what you eat, what you wear,
how you keep time, how you raise a family,
how you go into a contract, how you deal with a neighbor,
how you deal with an enemy, how you deal with animals,
how you deal with your God.
All those laws come from your deity, from your God.
Now, I know you don't like that.
Typical surface-dwelling earth inhabitant
doesn't need a God, they think.
And neither do they want to know.
That's why I go back to saying they're unrehabilitatable
when it comes to this subject.
But those rules come from your God.
Yes, and my favorite is someone who says,
well, I'm an atheist.
What have you got to say about that?
I'm like, well, that's very simple.
Do you believe in the laws of the state?
They're like, yes, I do.
Well, the state is your God and April 1st is your holiday.
Very simple.
If you want to see what people worship,
ask them where they get their rules and their laws from.
And most cases, who tells you what to eat,
what to wear, what to say, how to keep time.
All your laws, in other words, all this stuff.
Now, what's interesting about it is when children are raised,
they have no concept of this higher deity form
in their formative years.
Their parents tend to fit that.
And it's the higher forms of reality or knowledge
or instruction are pretty much given to children from parents.
But now the parents are lying to the children.
So now the children grow up,
finding out that their initial perception of what was a God
or be all and all deity, entity or person, let's say, had lied to them.
So now you wonder why teenagers are so rebellious and rambunctious.
So the other thing is, the thing I give to,
advice I give to inventors and parents are the same.
Like with inventors, the biggest mistake an inventor can make,
if there is such a thing, let's say,
is to fall in love with their invention.
Because now they could no longer objectify it.
The biggest mistake parents can make with their children
is to fall in love with their children.
Yes, you've heard of favoritism.
Yes, some parents favor a certain child.
What does that do?
And also falling in love with the child, you can no longer objectify.
You see, so, but then again, that's another,
that's probably an interesting thing.
We've kind of tried to touch on love before,
how falling in love or falling into anything is not good.
Like falling into a well or falling down, right?
But why would you want to fall in love?
You have to learn how to love.
You know, people just say,
my favorite is when the morons that are in media,
all media say, all you need is love.
Really?
What if you go to the national,
if you go to the national pedophile convention,
what kind of love are they talking about?
What kind of a love does a serial killer have?
He loves doing that, doesn't he?
People got to define things.
That's why I keep saying,
humanity is unrehabilitatable at this point.
You just have to ride it through and set yourself apart.
Is that always, yeah.
I'm always curious if those who are telling others to follow their dreams,
if they've just never had a bad dream,
or just assume that no one else has bad dreams.
Yeah, well, dreams are inputted as well.
Follow your dreams, follow your heart.
We have to be asleep, right?
To do that.
Yeah, dreams, by the way, you're being plugged.
We did it on Ocelli and the Greek, did a discussion about dreams.
The dreams are not your own, they're a communication.
Yeah, we talked a little bit,
not about dreams necessarily in specificity,
but we did talk a bit, I believe it was last week,
about the input and output,
where thoughts come from,
things of that nature.
Yeah, it's all external input.
Humans, or let's say for lack of a better term,
you're not born with an operating system like an animal.
Again, the metaphor is if a puppy or a small,
very young, immature dog was raised by a family of gorillas to adulthood,
and you brought it home,
you couldn't tell it was raised by gorillas,
it would still behave like a dog behaves,
or how you would expect a dog to behave.
But if you had a six or nine week old,
or even six month old human child raised by gorillas,
and if you brought him home as an adult,
guess what he'll be acting like?
It's because you don't have internal operating system,
it has to be downloaded.
That's why humans and people have schools,
and instruction and discipline.
I mean, there's a school of fish,
but that's a different concept or context,
where the only creatures that require instruction,
discipline and training.
And right now, going back to the older people,
go out in public or anyone you know, family or friend,
that's older than 50 and try to have a discussion
and try to sort out what they're saying.
If there's any wisdom in them at all, you will find not.
That's one of the sign of the times, by the way, folks.
It's rare.
It's very, very rare, much more rare than it used to be.
I would say that one piece of wisdom
that was given to me from someone that was older
and actually secondhand was be happy.
Right.
Well, how do you do that?
Ask them how and they might fall flat on their face.
It was the answer to a question,
what should I do?
It was an answer to a question
that was very specifically seeking out wisdom.
But hold on, Seth, just be happy.
I can get a T-shirt that says that.
I don't need an old fool to tell me that.
Right, no, absolutely.
Absolutely.
But it was and that was the end of it.
That was the answer.
And yeah, how it does certainly beg the question,
how exactly is it complete?
People are still used to the half hour sitcom
or one hour sitcom where everything is falling to pieces
and they fix it in the last five minutes.
That kind of satisfies their notion
of being taken for an emotional ride and being lazy
because someone else will fix it
in the few remaining bits of interim of time.
But essentially, that is true as well.
If anyone's listened or wants to research the reality
that we've kind of laid out about the coming society,
you know, it will be cleaned up,
but it's not going to be like you think it is.
In the interim, you've got another couple of years
for the same stuff that you've been experiencing
for the past five or six years.
Not much going to change, folks.
The next two years,
there's going to be the next little period
that's going to kind of click in next seven year period
and you will start seeing some changes.
And the changes there are going to lead
into the support of this Middle East Confederacy
or Middle East Union
or all eyes in the Middle East reforming.
It's going to get kind of messy.
You know, everyone is always looking
where it's noisy right now.
Turkey, Syria, you know, a little bit of Iraq,
but they're not looking anywhere else,
but I can't blame them.
They don't know.
They've never been told.
They can't figure it out.
But if you do a little bit of research,
you will see that the country known as Jordan
is going to be going through a major upheaval.
So is Lebanon, what's called Lebanon.
And yeah, and also Iraq will be split.
And if anyone wants to look at the news in Iraq right now,
you will see that since the past two weeks,
several hundred people, if not a thousand people
overran the parliament that was set up
in what's called the Green Zone,
which is the federal district,
the foreign district there,
and ran all the politicians out.
They ran and they haven't come back.
Has this made the news?
Are you guys talking about it?
No.
You know, and actually there is a Australian,
Belgian and Dutch delegation formed
to discuss perhaps who should get what
in the northern part of Iraq
because it shouldn't be part of Iraq.
Interesting.
And none of these things are being looked at
at the moment or discussed.
Just Syria and Turkey, of course,
which I think you and I have discussed years ago
to watch Syria and Turkey
because when this new country is formed in northern Iraq,
it's going to take some land from Syria
and some land from Turkey.
So also watch the country known as Iran or Persia.
They are going to be unified more than ever.
What would you mean?
You know, well, they actually have two forms
of government there.
Yeah, you could go and research that on your own
if you see what I mean.
And yeah.
So yeah, these things are all going to be forming.
Look at Israel.
People don't like to, you know,
the quote unquote Jews have been demonized.
Now that has nothing to do with Israel
because Jew being a Jew is a religion.
There is no such thing as a race, by the way, as Jewish.
If you want to get more specific,
that word does not exist in the biblical text.
The word that is translated as Jewish is Judean,
which is a regional part geographically
or a bloodline from Yehudah or Judah.
So the level of inaccuracy right now
that's pervasive in the world
makes it nearly impossible
to communicate anything clearly and succinctly.
So until the corrections are made,
which hopefully I think the mindset will be open
in the next couple of years for more correction.
That's why again,
dubbing anything and everyone can access right now
as a dummy load is fairly accurate
until the next time we come around in a week or so.
All right.
Well, thank you, Greek, as always for the conversation.
You can find ways to get ahold of us
at uncommonradio.com,
email links to the various sites and things like that.
Again, check out ocelliandthegreek.com as well
for someone who's listening for archives.
Yeah, absolutely.
And yeah, great.
Thanks.
And we'll see you again next week, guys.