This is the first installment of this sonic endeavor with myself, Seth Michael, and The Greek.
We are going to stick with the moniker Uncommon Radio,
meaning that we are hosted currently at UncommonRadio.com.
If you're listening to this, you're probably already aware of that.
We will integrate with every format that we can to make it as easy as possible for the listeners to get to the program.
And so iTunes and things of that nature will be forthcoming.
This, like I said, is just kind of a test.
We'll call this episode zero.
And we're going to use this kind of as a primer for what is to come in this sonic endeavor,
as well as to test the capability of transmitting it to those who would like to hear it,
and even perhaps to those that would like to listen.
So I would like to welcome The Greek, as always.
Welcome, Greek.
Thank you.
And we're back.
We're popping up like toast.
So we're going to continue perhaps discovering levels of discernment and subject matters
and things that could be conveyed sonically that just simply are not anywhere else.
And maybe that's why we are doing it.
And welcome, everyone, and let's see how it goes.
What's on your mind, Seth?
Oh, what is always on my mind?
Scripture, I suppose, is what's on my mind.
It's left to me.
That's where we'll go.
Yeah, referred to as the scriptures.
By the way, I finished watching a series called Wolf Hall.
It was a novel written by a woman novelist around what they call 2009 on the Pope's work schedule,
and it was about the court of King Henry VIII, and the main character is Thomas Cromwell.
Not so historically accurate based on some critics on it, but a very enjoyable show.
Do I recommend it?
Perhaps.
It's called Wolf Hall.
Unfortunately, it's a streaming type deal.
You're going to have to purchase somehow.
It was on a PBS masterpiece theater.
The reason why I brought this up, because around that time there was no English translation.
This is in the 1500s.
Tyndale and some others were doing a reformist movement,
and what's interesting about that show or that presentation is there was the Roman Catholic precedent set of what's called
Christendom throughout the land, which England was a part of and King Henry tried to break away from,
but they repeatedly referred to the scriptures and how interesting the scriptures were
versus what the Roman Catholic Church, which represented and really founded Christendom,
was pervading throughout England.
So I just wanted to bring that up because there's a resonance in the mind still from watching that short series,
which I don't really partake in a lot of media,
and this was something that I came across and found interesting because it was a well-acted, well-done presentation around Thomas Cromwell,
and the scriptures were a main feature of this presentation.
So this is just something that's fresh in the mind, and I'm bringing it up because people have to remember that,
as we've said before many times, or I have said, the Greek has said, let's say,
even today in your modern time, you do not have an accurate translation of what is known as the scriptures.
Sorry, folks, that is the truth.
All of the versions that you have are not translations.
They're very loose reference versions, inaccurate, that convey the general story of what is in the scriptures, and that's it, period.
So you have no real understanding, no real information conveyance of what is in the scriptures.
Now, a lot of it comes across.
You will in the versions, but unfortunately,
when you combine that with the social aspect of how people read into works of information
or things that they revisit later on in life, that they were initially exposed to that subject matter as a child through various social institutions.
What I mean by that is if you right now pick up what they call a Bible and you read something familiar,
you get to, let's say, Exodus or the flood or Adam and Eve or the apostles,
most people tend to read in and overlay what they saw on television by Disney, Cecil B. DeMille,
what they were told in church or the circus or their parents.
And unfortunately, none of it is accurate. Sorry.
And what the reason why I'm saying it that way is because it's still a massive endeavor to delve into that thing we call the scriptures.
And what I mean by massive endeavor is it has to be retold or restated.
So with that said, yeah, go ahead.
With preface, with background, it has to be established that we're working with versions and not with a translation.
Correct.
That's easy to do for yourself.
If you'd like to find an inner linear, there are a number of them available on the Internet for free reference.
You can punch the one that always comes to mind first is, you know, what's called Genesis, Bereshit.
The first verse of Genesis, as it is the version that is available to English speakers and those who read English like myself,
the first verse in the King James Version is 10, 10 words in the Hebrew and the language that has been memorialized.
And it's it's seven words.
It could be argued that it's eight words because there's a V in there, which is in English.
We translate that as and and that's that's relatively accurate.
But at the same time, there are two words, two words in the first verse of Genesis that actually the same word.
So it's one word that appears twice in the first verse of that that book that is not translated.
And not only is it not translated, those that word occurs in in the scriptures between six and seven thousand times.
And it's been omitted. It's been omitted.
So just to sum that up one more time, because there are 10 words in the first verse of Genesis one, one in English in the version.
But there are seven in the language of preservation, but only six are being translated.
Right. Generally. Correct. And that would be the olive top.
And it would be the first seven words would be the first, the fourth one, the fourth word that is not being translated.
So what's interesting about languages and names and things, they are sounds that we attach to things.
Right. What is a name? A name is a sound that you answer to.
Right. So what's interesting about, you know, even we describe these presentations as being sonic presentations,
meaning it's of the sound nature of our perception, not visual yet because it's, you know, it's audio strictly.
So just for the audience, just to have an effect on the mind, just to.
And it's good to start at the beginning, which which we will find out later on that Genesis is not the beginning, I guess.
But that's for another discussion in Genesis, basically one one.
It says in the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth.
But in Hebrew, it would be something like better sheath, but all of him at Hashim had to audit.
Right now, what's interesting is better sheath beginning, but I would say created or presented Elohim, the gods at.
Which is the olive top, the first and the last, or would be the letters of the Hebrew alphabet or any alphabet,
which would be the A and Z or the alpha and the omega.
And there's someone who identifies themselves as being the first and last and the alpha and the omega.
Right. And then it was the heavens and which can be namely the waters and it's audits, which is the earth.
So there you go. And you don't get that in the King James or any version.
So guess what, folks? You open what's called a Bible.
You're on the first verse, the first of the first book of the first chapter of the first verse, the first book.
And you're already spit out on the other end with an omission.
How do you think you're going to fare on verse two or verse three of the first edition?
An obvious and obvious mistranslation in the first verse.
Right. Now, a lot of, by the way, the side note or footnote here, some scholars say, well,
the olive top is just a punctuation for him to show you something is important or it's a conjunction of some kind.
I've seen it presented as I've seen it translated as the word the or the which is is also inaccurate.
Right. That's because it's defined.
Is that that's right? Yeah. And how would be for plural or singular?
So so we're going into this kind of like head fast and I mean, a head first quickly,
only because there's something here that needs to be set in the mind.
You know, everything that we do or hear has an effect on the mind.
And that's how we tend to rationalize things.
And when I when I mentioned earlier, reading into subject matter that is brought up, that is biblical, as you know,
we're actually overlaying and reading into things because when we perceive information,
this is just a commentary on how the human mind works.
There's a there's a maturity level that people reach,
known as adulthood, and they feel that they can operate freely in the world and do what they wish.
And when they approach things, they are constantly comparing what they're doing throughout their day with previous experiences.
And that's how people read and that's how people interact. Right.
So, you know, if you, let's say, are walking on the street and you see a dog, you you actually see the dog,
but you're not really seeing the dog. You you see enough of the dog to know it's a dog.
And you immediately the mind compares it to all the other dogs you've seen.
And it's close enough. And that's just a dog. But if someone were to ask you what that dog really looked like, you would give it.
No, it's a dog, you know, but you're really not looking at it.
You're just I mean, you just kind of glance that it's enough and you've compared it to everything else that you've seen about a dog.
It's good enough. That's what I mean about reading into it.
So when people are also having conversations, I'll notice or reading something, if you ask them to describe what they just read.
Well, if the subject matter is familiar, they're not really paying attention because they're comparing it to previous things that have been downloaded.
That's where in I guess in media school years ago, they used to talk about, you know, man bites dog.
And people were like, OK, yeah, because it sounds like dog bites man.
That's pretty common. But man bites dog is very uncommon. Right.
That's the the story that you're always looking for.
Something that people see is familiar, but is very strange at the same time if you're paying attention.
So we're jumping into scripture. And basically, we're only a few minutes into the sonic presentation.
And we laid out pretty much a gem, I would say, about how you're not even getting anything true in the first verse of the first chapter of the first book.
So what do you think you're going to get in the rest of it? Very much similarly, the same attitude carries through.
So the I found it easier to discuss things that are written in the text with those who have very little to no experience with preferably with.
Preferably atheists or secular people that might be interested in the subject matter.
I've jumped into conversations at coffee shops, actually, where I heard, you know, something of interest to myself being discussed like.
But that's that's not what it said. And the ones I've I've many times, actually.
And it's it's much easier to talk to people that don't have miss misinformed preconceived notions to battle with when when speaking about it.
Mm hmm. Let's just jump into another concept, because we do bring up time very often.
It's almost the last week of the sixth month. And it's what you want to sound off the date.
Roughly what it is on the pope's work schedule. It's August something.
The 10th. Yeah, something like that. I think.
What they call 2016, I think. Right.
With the 25th of the sixth month. Yeah, roughly last week of the sixth month going into the seventh month.
So why is time important? Because you have to realize that when we start discussing, let's say, Scripture,
one of the things we'll bring up is that the word forever is not in there. Right.
The word being translated as forever is the word Olam and the word Eon, which means the age.
Yeah. Onto the ages. And an age is typically a thousand or two thousand years, pairs of thousands.
Right. So there is no forever. And the reason I bring that up is because you all information is only pertinent when it's registered as pertinent in the time that it's pertinent.
What does that mean? Well, if you're reading about, you know, horse drawn carriages,
you will find information that is difficult to understand if you're living in an age of what they call the automobile or the car.
Right. Because you're you've spent your entire life most likely being driven around,
as they say, colloquially in a rubber tired reciprocating engine, gas guzzling, gas eating machine.
You are not familiar with the basic common things of of what a horse drawn carriage is.
You know that you yeah, you might know that it's yeah, it's made of wood and it's got a metal strap around the wooden wheel.
So it doesn't break, which called which is called a tire. And there's an animal in the front drawing it.
And that's simple enough. But if you were to study, let's say the Casanova wagons and things like that, pick up some reference material on it.
The majority of information conveyed will be unfamiliar to you, even though they are simple terms and simple concepts.
And this is very much what scripture is like, because people don't know how to place the information within the time period that they're living in.
So that's why time is very important. So where what is important about time and scripture is knowing where you are in that entire story.
And that cannot be garnered until you've basically downloaded the entire thing or been familiar with the entire thing
and then pieced it all together rationally, just like the.
I guess the horse drawn carriage, because you can still access a horse drawn carriage somewhere.
So there's something about it that requires, let's say, an understanding of time.
What do you say, Seth? And how to keep time and things like that.
Absolutely. Especially if you're talking about something that is is referencing times when to do things or when things will happen.
And you're trying to trying to make proper observations about such things.
It's impossible with the pope's work schedule, as they call it.
But even with the pope's work schedule and mechanical clocks, time has to be measured accurately to some degree.
Let's use the mechanical clock. And I just want to throw something in right now.
There is a particular religion and culture on the planet that is allegedly adhering to this type of information.
And many people are under the misunderstanding that the day ends at sundown because a certain group says so.
A religious group, let's say. And if you study scripture with an open perception where you see it objectively,
you will see that the day starts at noon because very simply, you cannot make a measurement at sundown.
Sundown is actually the last hour. The noon time is using, let's say,
what you might call a sundial or just a stick in the ground can be measured very precisely.
Also, there is a concept that the new moon is the dark moon in scripture.
And that is another mistake because you cannot make a measurement with a dark moon.
It just sits around in the West and it's dark, where the full moon rises like the sun and it has its own noon time.
In other words, when the full moon is at the apex of the sky at the zenith, it will cast a very sharp shadow,
which you can compare it to the solar shadow taken that day.
And that's how you determine what's called the equinox.
It has nothing to do with equal day and equal night. It has to do with the measurement at night.
That's why it's equinox, equi meaning measure, nox meaning night.
If it was equal parts day and night, it would be equimodium nox.
So these are things I just want to we're kind of like randomly throwing in concepts here.
And just to throw in a few other things here, this is kind of like running into someone and pushing them around.
You know, and I don't mind doing that sometimes, but because kind of like a little bit.
The subject matter is not really something we're going to delve into other than the overall mindset.
Like we said earlier, there is no forever in the scripture.
It's the ages, which are chunks of limited times.
You will not find the word. The other one that's important to consider is you will not find the word church.
The reason I'm saying that is because from a secular perspective, secular historians consider this to be the Christian era.
And when the first thing you bring up in the mind or most people do when you bring up Christendom is the church.
You will not find anything that resembles that in scripture at all.
Zero. What they call church today is a revival of the ancient circus or the architecture resembles the ancient sex temples.
None of it is biblical at all. Zero period at all.
You will not find hell as Dante's Inferno when where bad people go when they die.
And there's devils with pitchforks and things like that. There is no such thing in scripture, period.
You will not find anyone being animated in a heavenly realm after they die, where you die and you find yourself with a light and a cloud and plucking a harp and doing all that.
That is a lie. You will not find any of that. Actually, you won't find any of those in any ancient texts.
Those are those are inventions of a particular character.
A group of characters inspired by a magician in the first century.
So this is the truth of these matters.
When you discuss the time, because you're in a time right now, people, where when this topic is brought up, you think of heaven and hell as plucking a harp in the pearly gates or being in a fiery infernal place with demons or forever or church.
And all of these things are completely irrelevant and not in scripture at all, period.
Give me a quick example. The word congregation or ecclesia, as it is in scripture, just means a group of people.
And that is being translated as church and what's called the New Testament.
And if you actually do some research, there's an unruly mob protesting or ready to do some harm.
And they're referred to as an ecclesia of people. Right. I think it's in the Book of Acts.
I think when Shaul was there, he roused up a crowd and they were and he was arrested for rousing up the crowd.
OK. And that crowd is referred to as an ecclesia.
So it just means a crowd or a group or people or, you know, group together.
So when you hear us say things like there's no such thing as a church in scripture or heaven or hell or forever, we're going to try to throw in a very fast reference on how to the how and why we're saying it as well, which I think is important.
Absolutely. Absolutely. We have we're doing this, you know, on our own independently from any other media outlet or anything like that.
Currently, it's going to be available just here. And I am fond of that idea. After having experience with sonic projects in other venues, it's a lot more comfortable to sit in our own venue and speak.
Oh, yeah, definitely. We don't have there are no time limitations. We can broadcast very, very short episodes or, you know, very long ones. And we can speak freely without the the implied audience that is coming to other venues.
So, yeah, media was I think it was Edward Murrow, someone that when the advent of television, meaning it was popular and available to most people, he said it's across.
It should be taken seriously because it's almost a cross between a national park and a library or university.
And a lot of the media that people partake in, known as Internet radio, can be viewed very similarly. And we've tried that. And we're very grateful that we're given the opportunity.
But if you don't have to be associated with it, why not not be associated with it is the point.
And in essence, being able to do this, being very grateful that the Web site can host it at the moment. And we'll see other ways to get information out.
I think the four or five listeners that we kind of like semi jokingly talk about will be able to access it.
So, you know, with that said, in terms of media, folks, I've heard that there's some frustration regarding media.
I hear that constantly, but people still use it. And I think we've mentioned in one of the sonic presentations that this is all a beta test.
What you've been watching throughout the human course of events with television, radio and the Internet.
Right now, it's just a beta test. That's why it's all junk. It's just, you know, just like I think we did an audio test here.
You know, get on the mic testing, testing one, two, three. Right. That's all you've been experiencing all your life.
There's there's events that are going to be occurring in the future where there's going to be an imparting of information.
There's going to be that there's going to be the witnessing of events in real time with audio and video throughout the world.
This is what this entire evolution, let's say, or an opening or unraveling from radio to television to Internet is.
So if you're frustrated about all the junk out there, yes, and it's all junk, because if it wasn't, we would probably be saying, go listen to here or go over there.
We wouldn't be doing this, you know, at least in private.
So what the attempt here is to give maybe a little bit of credence to maybe a cross between a national park and a university.
And by the way, folks, I want to throw this in as another commentary, because, you know, I kind of ramble, but I could try to tie things together.
You university folks, your academics, whatever, look up the word academic in an etymological dictionary.
To paraphrase, it means theoretical and practical, never leading to a conclusion.
If there is any benefit in the current system of academia and you live in a benevolent society and you have such free media available,
why can't you turn on the television or the Internet and have these wonderful universities that want to help mankind do all of their teaching online?
Because, first of all, this is the truth, folks. It's not worth learning from them.
They have nothing to teach you. When I say nothing, there's something there, because even a counterfeit note has to look like the real thing.
You know, sorry. And you've been pranked. You've been pranked by your parents to go to these schools.
And then where if you study intellectual minds of the 19th century, they have already received their graduate degrees by 15 or 16 years old.
They only went through several years of schooling. That's all you need.
The kindergarten through 12th grade in university is a prank that destroys your formative years.
It steals all of your formative years. Now, this might sound like heresy.
And by the way, the word heresy means what one prefers or one likes.
And this goes beyond that. This is trying to be objective.
So when you hear us discussing certain subject matter, this is the kind of stuff that makes academics crawl out of their skin or go into convulsions and fall on the ground and vomit.
Right. Because it is possible to take very large pieces or chunks of subject matter and reduce it down to a few sentences where the man or the woman listening or even the child can digest what's been said and understand it.
And that is one of the things we like to do. And it's based on discernment and clear, concise communication,
which is a big contrast to academia, which I think is just what anyone can think.
Actually, if you were to objectify it is a prank on humanity at this point.
And it actually has always been these public institutions.
And I'm not speaking against them that they shouldn't exist or anything like that, just like, you know, ice cream shops shouldn't exist or shoe stores or whatever.
But if you're trying to associate knowledge and learning with these institutions that are in place, you are really you don't get it.
Sorry. And you never probably never will.
So I wanted to bring that up because conveying and imparting information can be done very quickly, concisely and effectively.
And that might be one of the things that we might start, you know, endeavoring on these sonic experiences with.
I think that we do. I think that a lot of what is spoken about requires, you know, explanation.
And the more that we get into it and the more that things are explained, we'll be able to speak about them without the explanation and be able to refer back to where we have explained it, where it has been explained.
But I think that explanation is important, especially to anyone who, you know, makes it a habit to listen, to seek out such such conversation as as we have.
And I I require it myself for for my own knowledge.
I know instruction is something to be sought, and that's certainly a large part of why why I do this and why I have enjoyed the conversations that you and I have had over the years, public and private.
Mm hmm. Sit down here. Yeah.
And with this endeavor, I think that we have the ability to to do it in a more comfortable and more comfortable setting.
There have been you know, we've we've had some objectively or relatively good broadcasts in the past.
And I don't mean to speak derogatorily of any of the venues that, you know, we've spoken in because, well, they allowed us to speak.
And that in and of itself is relatively rare. But there's just there's no pressure with this.
And that's that's that's wonderful. So. Yeah.
In other words, you can have a beautiful venue and they serve food that is synthetic or, you know, bad ingredients in it.
Right. Let's say. But the venue is fine. We're we'd like to have a good venue, let's say, with good ingredients.
Right. You know, when when when we serve cheese, it's made with milk, not cheese made of whatever.
Right. Correct. Or if it's salt, it's real salt, not, you know, something from the aluminum industry.
So, yeah, but here here's the thing. Also, the the partial rant and commentary regarding Internet radio or other venues or academia or any of these things that are people are going to
where the hosts, the teachers, the professors, those professing, you know, those behind a microphone or a lecture hall or writing a book,
they are just part of the human collective that have decided to do such a thing.
And they come from the same, let's say, maladies and flawed aspects of the society that we're sort of being critical about.
Now, if you told me that a wormhole opened up and a bunch of people came from another dimension, let's say,
which is only one dimension or another universe or planet to be your Internet radio hosts or your professors or whatever.
Yeah. You might want to give a listen because they haven't been subjected and pranked by the the insanity going on on this planet by the human race for thousands of years.
You see, they haven't been subject to that. So it might be worth listening to.
But all of these professors and whatever, all these people pontificating, they they they have not realized that the majority of what they're saying is is a product of pranked them.
None of I mean, I shouldn't say none of it, but very little of it is accurate. Very little of it is based on anything.
It's just the typical social chatter that you hear, whether it's academia all the way through.
I mean, any form of media. So this is this is the point.
You know, can we can information be imparted in an objective, clear, concise matter regarding any subject to a surface dwelling earth inhabitant?
And I believe the answer is yes. And that might be the crux of this whole thing.
Absolutely. Absolutely. I would say that it can be.
But how whether the seeds fall on on fertile ground is I don't know.
Yes, there's plenty of fertilizer out there. Yeah, there is.
Flowers need a lot of bullshit to grow, but I think sonic experiences can be free of it to a certain extent, but because you're not really growing flowers.
But but the thing is, the the the the point of conveying information is also that it has to fit the time period.
So it's more relevant because I think we've mentioned how the nature of existence is very simple, folks.
It's basically where spirits animated through material, you know, the spirit, the soul, the body.
The spirit is the mind. The soul is the breath and the body is the physical matter.
And the three working together to animate the show known as everything that we consider a reality is the reality of it.
And that's all it is. It's very simple. It's not easy, but it's simple to explain what's going on.
And to to give information that is pertinent to a mind animated through material, OK,
is not being done effectively or efficiently on this planet at the moment.
It's just something it's astounding to observe. So that, again, would probably be the way we would like to discuss things objectively.
And as if you're just visiting a place and clearly and concisely.
And just to go back to what we started with, the interest in scripture, just to give a thought.
The reason we brought up the concept of maybe discussing scripture more.
And please, you have to bear in mind that this has nothing to do with any religious affiliation at all.
And even you folks out there that think you're non-denominational, that's just like going to a supermarket.
And instead of buying a particular brand, it's the generic white box. You know, that's not any better.
It's still macaroni and cheese with whatever in it. It's it's not.
We're not discussing any religious affiliation or any religious anything in that aspect, which I think I brought up.
There's no forever, no church, no heaven and hell, as people are just discuss it in certain religious circles and certain timekeeping things.
It's just the maybe a little bit of a preface. I would I would recommend that for anyone that is interested in studying such things or looking at things objectively.
Use the you know, the Internet only has what the Internet has.
But there are tools available there and you can find free interlinear software, things like that, that make it.
I wouldn't say make it any easier, but make it more fruitful.
Studying such things. I'd like to recommend Kohalath Ecclesiastes, as it's called in the English versions to anyone who is considering considering such things.
It's not going to make you friends. It will be a point of contention.
If it's something that you are looking at objectively between you and anyone that you speak about it with or anything in Scripture.
Yeah, absolutely. But there are tools available. How about this?
How about not a promise, but a consideration that if people adhere to what we're presenting and piece it all together,
they'll have a pretty good idea of the rhythm of of of what is going on.
And what I mean by that is, yes, Kohalath is important.
Proverbs are important. The Book of Jeremiah is important because those things are universal.
Those are pretty much for everyone. Most of the other things in Scripture are directed to certain groups.
Right. Just like you would go to someone's mailbox and they're being addressed specifically.
But, you know, those I just gave a handful of things there.
Now, that's a lot of information right there in a very short sentence.
But it is. But that's a lot of consider that anyone. Yes.
Now, the rhythm of it is let's give an example like the band Fleetwood Mac.
The first time you hear a Fleetwood Mac song, you're like, oh, OK, I see what they sound like, how they play music.
OK. And then you hear another song from them, let's say on an album.
And OK. All right. I could see it's the same band, but it's a different song.
And if you're familiar with, let's say, 10 Fleetwood Mac songs, if you were to go about in life and another song comes on,
you'll say, oh, that sounds like Fleetwood Mac, even though you've never heard it before.
And there's on the same on the same note, if someone plays a song for you and tells you that this is Fleetwood Mac and it's not,
you'll be like, this doesn't sound like Fleetwood Mac at all. Yeah, exactly.
So what we will do besides reading the Book of Wisdom, the Books of Wisdom and things like that,
and maybe the Book of Jeremiah, which is addressed to everyone, like Seth likes bringing up Ecclesiastes and rightly so.
Let's say we'll discuss certain very specific topics like like we mentioned, let's say the flood,
a very short thing about very specific interlinear kind of etymological aspect of a certain part of, let's say,
the flood in Genesis or like we just started out by doing the first verse of the first book of the first chapter.
We just gave an illustration of what's going on there.
We could pick and choose various aspects of scripture and go into it in great depth, very quickly and short and concise and objectify it all over.
And you will notice that it's obviously there. It's all tied together. It's the same band.
It's playing. It's the same. It's the same band, but different songs.
And let's say we do a dozen examples of like, for example, something in the flood, something in, let's say, the Garden of Eden,
something about when the Israelites left Egypt or something from what they call the New Testament.
And we'll explain it and people will figure out, hey, there seem to be these things have something in common,
even though they seem that, you know, they're all set, you know, separate instances and separate events.
These guys are showing us what all these things have in common.
And there's an understanding here how it's all tied together.
And the mistakes are pointing out seem to have a frequency and a rhythm in an app.
There's a mindset to what makes the versions that you're given so bad.
If you reveal that mindset and then we reveal the mindset that when you do research,
what is really being said in the language of preservation, you'll have a good contrast.
And just giving maybe a half a dozen examples like we just started out with the first verse of Genesis.
The listener then will be able to have almost a pretty good understanding of what is going on and when on their own,
like listening to Fleetwood Mac, for example. And so this is just an example.
So just like we gave the example right out of the gate, we will perhaps go into many other explanations like that.
And this is not a lot of people resist this because it goes contrary to what they believe.
But if belief is based on nothing, well, there you go.
If you say you believe in something and someone questions it in terms of why do you believe that?
And it's based on nothing. Well, then you just need to kind of like walk away because guess what?
Nothing is based on nothing. So, yeah.
It's like listening to music in a different tuning that is unfamiliar.
If it doesn't, if it sounds, it's going to sound discordant to many.
Now, why Scripture? The big question here is very simple, folks.
And we'll lay it out really quickly and really simple.
If someone has a lawful mind, meaning that when you have a communication and you have a lawful mind,
you see if that communication sets a precedent, if it's an important communication or is it trivial or is it, you know,
how much attention does that what you just heard or read require?
Like, for example, if someone says, excuse me, I have to go to the bathroom.
Well, that's a communication. But, you know, it's like, OK, fine.
It's common. No big deal. But thanks for letting me know.
But if someone if you read a communication that says I created the heavens and the earth and I am the supreme being,
that's a trivial I don't really believe in that. I don't care.
Well, you see, that's the typical mindset. But if someone has a lawful mind and they hear that, they're like, wait a second.
That is a really, really tall claim. Right.
And it sounds extremely important. And I mean, and has it been rebutted? Is it true? Right.
Or whatever. Right. So that's why we go to scripture, because you will find things that are claimed in there that are really tall claims.
I mean, we're talking big claims. And the majority of the surface dwelling earth inhabitants are apathetic to it because they don't have a lawful mind.
So that's why that is why I I would like to say from the Greeks perspective is why I have an interest in it.
You know, if if someone says, hey, I got to go to the bathroom or else, you know, I've got to go rearrange the sock drawer.
That is a communication, just like I created the heavens and the earth, for example, as a communication.
But they have different veracities. You know, one needs to be considered to see if it's true.
And if it is true, well, that is really important information.
And it's been hijacked, just like all information right now is been somehow conveyed through some corrupted kind of presentation or individuals that are loose and apathetic and don't really care.
And I say not all. But, you know, typically here, the reason I'm saying that to be ranty or critical is because I like the truth.
I like information. I like learning. This is a personal thing. Right.
And I like to see and hear that other people are doing this, you know, just like if someone likes, let's say, basketball.
They like to associate with other people who have a fondness for it. Right.
Or playing instruments or cooking or whatever. So I like learning. I like, you know, learning things.
And especially if they're big things that are important. And I have certain people that I communicate with.
And if I had found a source that was able to convey important information clearly, concisely and objectively, wouldn't be doing the sonic presentations at all.
I would just sit back and people that I communicated with, I would, you know, send them information, say, look at this, look at that.
Look at this guy here or whatever. Right. And I would you would not know about the Greek at all.
But the reason why I come out and speak is because no one is saying anything.
You know, I mean, I want to say no one is saying anything. It's just. Yeah, it sounds kind of arrogant or whatever.
But on the other hand, it's like, what the hell is going on? Are you people lost your minds? Are you crazy?
Oh, they're saying they're saying plenty, but generally what they're saying is just a complaint about the symptoms.
Yeah. Is anyone paying attention? Yeah. So, you know, sitting back, there's a there's a if I was not speaking,
I would feel that there's a level of negligence incorporated in my existence. So I have to come out and say, I mean, if you want,
if you folks want to know what I'm talking about, just go to the Internet radio and turn on anything. Right.
Or go to YouTube, start watching stuff. It's like, huh? What the hell is wrong with you people?
So anyway, you may not you can't really say they're wrong. Right. But you can't say they're right.
I would say that my interests and the reason that I, as I said, right when right when we started this,
that if it's up to me, that we'll we'll discuss scripture. I, I guess that I grew up in an environment where it was spoken of quite a bit.
And so I was familiar with it from a relatively young age and put together pretty early on that.
What is written and what is said in these congregations is very rarely congruent.
Not not even to touch upon what is actually done, but just just what is said, what is taught is not it's not there.
And there you'll get various explanations from any of these groups as to the why they apologize.
Apology. You'll get an apology. They'll speak in defense of it.
But so I've always it's I guess I've just kind of been drawn to it for that reason.
I'm going, well, there's there's good information here. It's obvious there are directions, lots, lots and lots of directions.
It's almost like a handbook for living on the surface of this planet.
And but it's it's ignored and distorted. And so I see this this object.
If you look at the scriptures as a whole, as an object, as a singular book, although it's many.
Forty nine. Yeah. Forty nine books that are being discussed, but not being directly addressed.
The only time that I could tolerate being in these places is when we were sitting in a circle and just reading passages and discussing them,
because it's very hard to skirt things when you have the ability.
But I can't. I can't. It's been many, many years since I've subjected myself to to that particular form of punishment.
But I've there's value and it's valuable. It's something that is rare.
You know, there are many, many textbooks and I'm sure we'll get into, you know, who edits textbooks these days.
But there's lots of information available.
But when you start going and looking for what this information is based upon, it's just it's not present theory.
Lots, lots and lots of theory going from scripture to what people refer to as science these days.
Science is just a word that means knowledge. It kind of is a pet peeve.
I suppose when I hear people talking about science, because that's that's simply what it is.
You know, knowledge being aware of it, being aware of something else.
It's been turned into a faith instead of being natural philosophers.
Now we have the priests in the white coat that call themselves scientists or that other people refer to as scientists.
It's just it's absurd. The the way that information is communicated, good or bad, currently is just absurd.
And there is so much that is left out. And when instead of things being discussed,
people start insulting people that do not agree with their beliefs, be them, quote unquote, scientific or even if the beliefs are founded on nothing.
Yeah. If you peel away the onion, there's nothing there. And then it just the whole process just brings tears.
Right. Right. One of those people that's just looked around and like this, the way that we exist, we I'm using very, very lightly, I guess.
But referring to, you know, service dwellers and what I've had the occasion and the opportunity to observe.
There's three words in a row is that it's it's just it's it's absurd.
And yet the absurdity is only referred to in art.
It seems art seems to be where the absurdity at least is reflected in a more accurate manner.
But. Yeah, punk rock and hip hop. Yeah. No, I'm just joking.
Surprise, man. There's lots of both now. Once upon a time, you could pigeonhole it.
But these days, music is one of those things. I'm I'm a musician, for those that are unaware.
So it's something that is it's certainly a passion. It's something that I've done since I was very young.
And it's all I've ever really wanted to do as far as work goes.
But it's it can be used.
You know, it's a medium like any other can be used properly or improperly.
You can impart good information or bad information.
So sonically using an instrument in the voice can be an instrument as well.
If you listen to opera, I want to go back to the concept of scripture, perhaps calling it a manual.
I haven't done that in a long time. A user's manual.
Now, whenever you have a benevolent creator of anything, they fit whatever they've created to the end user with a manual.
You ever notice buying something, even a very rudimentary appliance like a toaster or hairdryer?
You open the package and and what falls out a manual.
And you ever notice on these manuals, especially electrical devices, that the first couple of pages are filled with what not to do.
Danger could cause shock, potential injury and death. Do not submerge in water. Do not.
Right. You ever notice that? Yeah. Yeah. The first few pages are the dotes.
Right. It's not interesting how it. Yeah. Think about that for a moment, folks.
And it seems like right now humanity is they've got a product, let's say a blow dryer, and they've got the manual.
They're aware of it, but they don't they don't want to look at it.
So what they do is they take the blow dryer, plug it in and dunk it in water.
Right. Or they have to.
Current society. It's it doesn't. Oh, I don't like what I don't like that.
Like this is how it's done. I'm not going to do it like this.
It's like, well, OK, so it's interesting what we'll get into is what most of humanity is incorporated in incorporating their behavior and their actions and deeds and works are the don'ts in the in what's called the scripture.
Like, for example, I've stated before, there's not one religion on the planet that knows or does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
So that's a tall statement. But if if you are have a faith in one of the main religions, you might find that to be offensive.
That's too bad because you're not pursuing the truth of the matter.
And if essentially if you on a cursory level start looking, it would say whatever religion you are in the book that is supposedly based on,
you'll say that what I just said is not true and you don't see it because you're reading into it.
But if you actually sit down and study it, you'll find that you might want to light your hair on fire and run down the street screaming.
We've wasted your entire life following these ridiculous institutions.
But anyway, the other thing about about this that you'll find that what they are actually partaking in, no matter what religion it is,
is the don'ts in what the book that they allegedly subscribe to us.
When I say nothing, that they don't do anything, that that's a general statement.
But to get more specific, most religions are doing things that are in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
And the things that they're doing are the things that are considered abominable or forbidden.
I would say most most. I would say there are. And I'll be at a lot of them are just a disguise for something else.
But there are, you know, charitable organizations out there.
There are people out there feeding people that don't or don't have the ability to feed themselves, clothing themselves.
You know, there's still good being done. But what is what is discussed and what is taught?
It's honestly what is discussed and what is taught. It's kind of amazing that there are still good things being done.
Well, the good things that are being done are out of a guilt.
Just like, for example, I bring up the example, whether it's good or not, just something that is in your face.
After 9-11, you notice how most government officials started wearing these little American flag lapel pins to show how patriotic they were
when they were actually in on what was going on prior to it. It's to kind of like cover their guilt.
And it's not really I shouldn't say it that way, because the government I've never all governments and all throughout time,
current, past, present, any country in the world is the government you deserve, period.
There's nothing wrong with it, even though they might just be doing wrong in certain cases.
They are there to fit what the society is about. That's all it is. So, yeah, it's like a mirror.
You don't put a pink elephant in the mirror and expect to see a green giraffe.
You put a pink elephant in the mirror, you're going to see a pink elephant in the mirror.
If you don't like the people that are ruling you, you need to just look at your neighbors and your family and whatever,
and you will find that they are identical in nature.
So, yeah, that's why if you look at the things about wisdom is don't try to change any of this because you're not.
Just set yourself apart from it. It's like if you had a well-paying job working in the sewer or with high-tension power lines,
do you go in there with a tank top and flip-flops and touch everything?
Or you go in with protection?
Yeah, exactly. So, yeah, you don't want to touch, yeah, because you will be zapped or you will be dirty and stinky and unhealthy.
So, that's the other good advice is avoid people that talk about making humanity better and the world a better place.
Those people are clueless. They have no clue. They are just, yeah, it's just not good.
It sounds good, makes you feel good.
And here's just another note, folks.
This is not about pessimism or things being dark or evil or whatever, because you are at the precipice right now.
From an age, from the age's point of view, you know, the 30 seconds or 10 seconds to midnight where things are going to end,
the next stage of humanity is going to be so wonderful and so incredible compared to all of the things that have been recorded about humanity,
good or bad, that even the worst things that you've ever imagined done by humans will be nothing,
will be considered trivial when you compare it to the benefits and the wonderment and the existence that you're going to have in the future as humanity.
So, the most atrocious, horrendous things that have been done by people will be just like peanut shells falling on the floor
compared to the wonderful things that you will be open to.
You will fully understand all the misery, the evil, the mayhem, the lying, the deceit, the corruption,
and you will see that it has its place and why it had to be done the way it was done in the future, but not now.
And we will discuss what's coming in the future because there's only a couple of years left where you can actually discuss it,
and then those who know what's coming will not be speaking because it's going to be kind of dangerous to do so.
So, the reason why is because the closer you get to a point where things are going to go south, let's say, meaning not well,
the window dressing and what you're going to be shown in society and in your personal lives is going to be the opposite.
Things are going to appear to be getting better and better and better, judicially, economically, academically, let's say,
religiously, government-wise, financially, economically, all these things are going to be getting better and better and better
the closer you get to what I call the kill shots.
So, it's going to be very difficult to explain to people what's coming next when they're fully engrossed in a real society
with real things going on that are getting better.
Yeah, they're going to get harsh, and we will explain how and why with detail.
One example would be of what the future is going to be like in the next decade is if you run into someone who lives in a big mansion
and has a very expensive exotic car and fancy jewelry, and you say, wow, look how wealthy this guy is,
and then you find out that it's all borrowed and rented and the person is just one day away from being homeless.
People don't want to hear that.
They just want to see, wow, look at that expensive house that he has, an expensive car, and all that jewelry.
There's no way this guy is completely destitute and broke, and none of it is really his.
And that is how humanity, this is what humanity is going into in the next decade.
You're going to be exposed to the pinnacle of human society, but you are going to be subject to pretty much a condition
that's going to last three and a half years that is going to render the entire surface of the planet only with a small remnant of humans left.
And the reason why is because most people are unrehabilitatable.
You cannot have seven billion people with the mindset that they have right now to go to the next level.
And the remnant that's going to be left, it's not because they're better or only the good people.
No, it'll be a representative sample.
So the reason I'm throwing this in there is because this is part of the subject matter that I found is very interesting and can be conveyed.
It's an interesting basis, that's for sure.
Yeah, and you can rationally sort out the information, even though it seems irrational when you incorporate the mind and the body,
because the body likes comfort.
And when things are getting better and feel better in society, both personal and social, and when I mean social,
I mean geopolitical and personal and all around, when things are seemingly getting better and better,
people don't want to hear that the whole thing's going to crash next week or in a year or three years, or this is how it's going to go down.
They don't want to hear that because the body is comfortable and the mind is comfortable.
It's housed in this container that is experiencing joy.
You're a party pooper, right?
So right now, before these things are incorporated into society and this upward swinging tide comes through,
it's kind of interesting to those that have eyes and ears to be aware of what to be aware of.
And we will discuss that in detail as well.
I'd say that we've already gone into quite a bit of detail.
Yeah.
So what do you think?
What's the time on this?
Should we wrap it up or what do you think?
I think we've been going for like half an hour, something like that, a little bit longer perhaps.
Oh, that seems like hours.
Okay.
Anything else?
That much worth of information certainly.
Yeah.
If you would like to get into contact with us, the email is uncommonsenseradio1 at gmail.com.
I know that's a mouthful, but you can go to the website uncommonradio.com.
www.uncommonradio.com because if you put in uncommon radio as a general search,
we're not near the top of the query result query on that.
So www.uncommonradio.com brings you very close to it.
Right.
And there's a form there.
You can email directly from the site.
The sonic broadcast that will be forthcoming will be easily available there as well.
We also have a blog done by someone that really thinks the reporting that we've done
and the Greek has done is critical and important for others, and it's a blog, Just Greek Speak, I believe.
And there's also a Skype setup, which anyone that's interested in joining the Skype.
And there's also a chat in the blog, and I don't have that in front of me,
but you will find a link to the blog on the Uncommon Radio site, and it's listed as the unofficial blog.
And it's not done by myself or Seth,
but it's done by someone who has invested quite a bit of time into it
and has found that what is being said is being important enough that a blog would have been a good project for them to engage in
and invest that amount of time into it, and I'm very appreciative of them doing that.
They have their own way of expressing what has been expressed, which I found to be
you know, I haven't really spent much time on it.
I just put it up for everyone else.
And there's also a Skype setup as well and a chat there.
So I just want to throw that out, things to look for.
We might be more engaging in the future.
Yeah, absolutely.
And we will respond to emails when opportunity is there.
You can get into contact with me directly at dearredshoesatgmail.com, D-E-A-R-R-E-D-S-H-O-E-S at gmail.com.
And that's a relatively quick way to get into contact with me.
And yeah, come back.
We will be doing this.
We're not going to do it scheduled, really.
We're going to do it as we have the time and the topics to discuss.
Let's say weekly or four times a month or maybe not.
You know, roughly the weekly thing seems to be okay, right?
Maybe in frequency.
Certainly.
And we're going to do that.
If you'd like to help support the broadcasts in any way, you can email us,
and we'll let you know how to do that as well.
Everything is appreciated.
I'm glad that there are some people out there that are going to be able to hear these conversations.
And I do encourage you to get into contact with us.
We will, you know, explain what we can.
Yeah.
Perfect.
All right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, thanks again, Seth, and everyone who's listening and hearing as well.
Absolutely.
See you again soon.
Be well, and we'll speak to you again in the near future.