Greetings. Greetings. Alright. Yeah, this is the credits version or aspect to the 18th, let's say, Sonic event.
What do you think about that, Seth? Yeah. Absolutely.
Yeah, I was thinking, since it's the credits, part of the credits is showing what was done before
and probably things that were not shown on the screen or aware to most of the audience.
And I was thinking, you know, you and I didn't discuss this.
I was thinking of perhaps bringing up how we got into what's called alternative media, if there is such a thing.
Whether it's crawling across the living room rug with its diaper needing to be changed
or whether it's walking side by side or as an alternative to what's called mainstream media, right?
And anything in between would be where anyone's thoughts on the matter is, right?
So I was maybe thinking randomly, throwing out how I got into it and how you got into it.
So maybe you first. I know I'm kind of catching you out there, but let's be spontaneous.
I know you were doing some radio. Of course, you do music.
If you want to look up Seth, it's Dead Shoes or Dear Red Shoes previously.
And he does music.
And you're also a conversationalist that got interested in perhaps doing some late night what they call radio.
And I believe that's how we met. Maybe we've crossed lines.
And somehow you've I've heard of you speaking and myself speaking.
And when we met on late night alternative radio somewhere else,
we started keeping some discussions going both publicly and privately.
So I kind of filled that in because I kind of caught you out there randomly.
But anything you want to add to that, Seth? I mean, tell us a little bit more if you can.
But I got into this whole thing. I pursuit of knowledge, I guess, in a in a short phrase.
I was I've always been kind of a suspect of the way things are explained.
Anything at all. Pick anything all across the board.
And that's how I came across a lot of the alternative media, I suppose.
I found some books, read some books, decided that I had no true concept of the things around me.
I only was familiar with what was being directly presented.
So I went looking for information. And it turns out there's not a whole lot of information out there that is reliable.
But there is still quite a lot of knowledge out there. You can go looking for it.
Yeah. So I started I just called in to a radio program and ended up broadcasting a radio show for a couple of years.
A few thousand hours of broadcasting conversation, open call in.
And, you know, as you said, you and I, that's where we first conversed or held a conversation.
And it was it was interesting. I enjoyed it.
And we ended up doing it quite a bit and in broadcast.
And it was just we were able to talk about things that were not being discussed or take talk about the things that were being discussed in a in a different light than what is common.
So or some light versus no light. Yeah.
To say putting light on it. Yeah. Yeah.
It's interesting that you ask that, actually, because I was contacted by an acquaintance from from that just that time period last night.
Something like that. Yeah. I was called in and spoke for spoke to them for a few minutes.
And it's it's I guess it was the same thing.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. You got to understand the times. The times dictate the environment, which dictates people's thoughts and other things.
Environment meaning everything seen and unseen. So, yeah.
So is about the brief side. But is it about the fourth day of the sixth month?
I'm reckoning it's the almost it's the end of the week of the first.
Week, let's say, of the sixth month. And we've been trying to there's nothing to drive home here.
People, you either acknowledge or see what's lawful versus unlawful.
So this is something that can be determined by anyone based on their looking for a reference to mark things by, like, if you're a surveyor, you need a benchmark in order to communicate measurement.
Right. If you're working on a construction site, you need a benchmark.
It's called a tape measure, whether you're working in electricity, plumbing or whatever, framing concrete work.
You've all agreed on some benchmark. Now, what's been agreed to as being a benchmark by the current world society at large is the Gregorian calendar,
which is also I call it in jest the pope's work schedule for his subjects.
And the problem with it is that it's not a time piece. It has to be administered, meaning meetings and decisions have to be made on how it will be administered,
you know, or or, you know, the liturgy of society, how they will run on it.
That's why it's I call it the work schedule, because you have work week weekend.
It's not a time piece. Can't keep time with it. Let's give one example on it.
Now, lawfully, it appears to be the sixth moon or the sixth month.
And these measurements are always done in the light, not in the dark.
So the full moon is the new moon. And if you have been trained like a circus bear enough, you will not be able to hear what I just said.
So let's let's do a quick little experiment, which I always do today.
According to the pope's work schedule, it's what they call July 23rd and Saturn's Day or Saturday.
Right now, just to show prove the point again, we've done this for a few episodes already.
And what they call July 2015, I said it was the 23rd.
OK, that was what's called a Thursday. Right. Or Thursday, more commonly known.
And if we look at what they call 2017, because there's no such thing either, by the way.
What they call July 23rd is on a Sunday or Sunday.
So let me ask you, folks, is July 23rd a Thursday, a Saturday or Sunday?
Let me ask you to think about that for a moment. It's neither.
Again, just to recap, if anyone's old enough for before the electronic convention,
meaning when you turn on an electronic device that automatically had this demarcation of time on it, what you call time.
If you were growing up at a time period, you said, well, we need to go to get a calendar.
So we know what day it is next year during the end of the year.
You guys remember that anyone old enough for that? Yeah.
So and no one is paying any attention. And one of the reasons to go back to the discussion,
we kind of started was that I found out about alternative media through discussion to go here,
to go there on the computer and you will hear things. Right.
And I tuned into various stations and I was listening to what was being said.
And I just had to just have a moment of first review what was being said.
And then I went from one place to another, to another, to another.
And I found it to be pretty much a good cross-sectional representation of the thought processes in the mainstream society,
with some little tidbits thrown in, you know, what they call conspirology, alternative medicine, alternative this, alternative that, patriotism, such and such.
But the information, the subject matter was seemingly adequate, but the facts and the truth of the matter were severely lacking.
So I took the opportunity whenever there was a call in to call in and make a comment.
And I started interacting. And here, American Freedom Radio, I used to call in often to several shows.
And I was asked to perhaps do a show. And I said, well, you know, it's not really time yet.
You know, I've pretty much got a pretty good handle on where this society is and where it's going and what's coming in the future.
And right now is not the time to be speaking what I have discovered or what anyone can discover if you look at things objectively.
And time went by, time went by, time went by. And I said, OK, finally, I'll do something.
We did a sonic event prior to this one and then this one. But still, I wouldn't say it's an act of futility.
I believe that there is a time period coming, which if you know it's coming, it'll be quite astonishing to see it come.
But if you don't know it's coming, you'll just think it's a natural occurrence, which is people will start to learn to objectify.
Right. What things are, whether it's economic, judicial, entertainment, medical, scientific, mathematic, religious, all these things will be objectified.
Right now, there is no objectification at all. When I say at all, meaning there's so little that it's irrelevant.
It's irrelevant to say that there is so statistically. Right.
And here we are. And still, it is pretty much the just throw this out for those that are listening.
And, you know, we might only have two listeners, by the way, not four or five.
Like we've always been saying, based on some of the comments that I've been getting lately on Skype and email.
But not to discourage anyone. Keep communication going. It's adequate. It's fine. We enjoy it.
But you have about roughly two years left in this particular time period.
And I think we've said several times before on this Uncommon Sense show, it's going to be pretty much the same as you've been seeing it.
These little squirmishes going on, threat of economic collapse, criticism of corrupt politicians and missing planes over and over and over.
This is pretty much what you get, what you're going to get for the next two years or so.
And then is another time period that's going to begin that will be a little more refreshing to those that are truly seeking how things work.
But right now is not the time for that. If you are one of those that do seek how things work, what makes things go tick?
Typical human reaction is to go out and share it. Well, yeah, you're not going to be met with open arms.
Let's say the last thing you want to do is be super vocal about the truth.
And well, now, let's just not use this word, the truth, too much because it's been, you know, they've used it to mop the floor.
And if you don't believe it, go listen to what's being said on Mainstream and Alternative, all of it, not some of it, and do a little bit of research, just a little bit.
And you will see what we just said is true.
So, again, it's let's call this the 18th episode. It's the credits that you and I are getting together for this particular sonic experience.
So I guess with that said, that's how we got into it. A little bit more added in with time and the date being first the end of the first week.
So of the sixth month, which, by the way, we're just throwing a little more.
This might sound esoteric or occult, but six represents man, by the way, folks.
You know, five represents something that comes before man.
It could be animal kingdom. It could be a time period or an attitude prior to the man manifesting for represents something very interesting.
It's actually a center point. And let's go the other way. And seven represents the divine.
So just a little tidbit there. These things will be elaborated on more in the future.
If you'd like to stay in touch with us and Seth, let them know how they should try to get in touch with us.
Perhaps the email at Uncommon Radio, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Uncommon Radio dot com.
Yeah. Uncommon Radio dot com is the easiest way to find it.
Every for certainly until we get the next thing going, how we how we want to do it, then that's going to be the easiest way to to keep track of all of it.
Www.uncommonradio.com.
Yes. You'll find archives and other things. It's just a courtesy page.
Not into I'm not into doing websites or anything like that.
We tend to find that sonic experiences are the best way to interact.
They're also hard. Yeah. Yeah. It's just a courtesy calling card.
Yeah. So, yeah. Stay in touch, folks, if you're interested.
Yeah. You won't make friends, by the way, listening and discussing the things that you hear here, because people just tend to not want to listen at this point yet.
Does it mean they're bad? Definitely mean that it doesn't mean that they're good either.
Right. Someone asked me sometimes, you know, people ask things and they kind of look up to you regarding a certain subject matter and they're looking for approval.
And they'll say, well, am I wrong on that? And I'll say, well, you're not really wrong, but it's just not right enough.
You see. So there's just a there's is anything wrong?
No, but it definitely sure ain't right. That's for sure.
So, yeah. And the motto of what we do is to set yourself apart, folks.
Anyone talks about changing anything. You want to walk away. That's good advice.
Now, if you want to discuss it more objectively, you hear about this stuff they put in yeast and bread.
It's called activism or something like that. Yeah.
You know, there's an old saying about voting that if you want to really know, know what if you should vote or not have a five minute conversation with a voter.
If you want to know whether you should think about changing the world or being part of a group that does have a five minute conversation with an activist and be objective.
Ask them what they're protesting and ask them some objectifying questions about it.
Right. And you'll notice they know absolutely nothing about it because you know what?
It's activism, folks. Anyway. So, yeah, the aspect to these things is to set yourself apart.
That's the motto. Essentially, set yourself apart and protect yourself. It's called shielding.
Yeah. It's like as if you had a well-paying job or job that you had to work in the sewer every day.
Would you be would you be concerned about telling everyone to stop throwing their pooper into the into the tank and pulling the handle because there's too much poop in there?
Or are you going to think that you're getting paid so much?
Let's say that you're going to jump in there naked, skin dipping and drink the water. Can they pay you enough to do that?
Nope. Well-paying job working in the sewer requires.
Good amount of barrier protection, buffer zone, hazmat suits, breathing tanks.
So if you're on this planet and you're naive enough to think that you're going to change anything or any groups going to change anything, you're naive enough or excessively naive.
And by the way, folks, nothing exceeds excess. So don't be excessively naive.
That's all the way on the end. The best thing to do is to separate yourself from it.
Right. Shield yourself. You talk to someone who works on high power, high tension power lines.
I think they go out there and flip flip flops, a boxer shorts and a tank top.
Grab that thing. Hundred thousand volts.
Yeah. Pay attention, folks. Earth is a very violent place.
Yeah. Nature. Nature is incredibly violent.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And one day people will find out. We'll discuss this in the future.
Things that have been memorialized. Oh, yeah. Those really ignorant ancients.
And they're so ignorant and dumb. We're so modern now. So we have smartphones. Right.
I've read a read a quote that speaks directly to that recently.
I think it was Edgar Allen Poe actually had something to say about that.
It was good. Yeah. Something to say.
And the things that we've spoken on that same topic.
Actually, now that's that you said something there, Seth, is we can use the word say a lot.
When someone has something to say, you should listen.
But when people just say, say something, just walk away.
That's the mark of a fool. How many times have you heard?
We've got to do something. We've got to say something.
Yeah. Just like, you know, tilt your hat the other way and just keep walking,
because nothing going to come out of that. And that's for sure, folks.
There's an old saying. I think it was one of the Greek philosophers.
It says that a fool has to say something, but the wise have something to say.
Now, another thing, this is just like basic instruction on how to function on this planet,
is that the level of stubbornness and rebelliousness and resistance to anything that's fit and proper
by your average surface dwelling earth inhabitant is so high at this point
that they have this really tricky, almost conniving, insidious way of discounting informational flow.
And the way they do that, this is through conversation, is if you're bringing up a topic
and you try to impart or convey something that can be objectified or referenced by anyone
on the meaning of the word, let's say, or facts regarding a cause or a law
or something that's been memorialized, if they don't like it, what they're hearing,
they immediately insidiously discount what you're saying as your opinion.
That's what they say. So you've got to watch out for that also.
When you're talking to your average surface dwelling inhabitant, they will tell you that,
oh, yeah, I don't like what you're saying. I don't agree with it. That's your opinion.
You see, so they have a lot of insidious tricks that they use.
They're a pretty wicked group, anyway. I didn't say that, did I?
Okay. So you've got to be careful when you're communicating with your typical surface dwelling earth inhabitants
regarding discoveries and things that can be referenced.
The level of hypocrisy is so high at this point, meaning that people, when they go to buy shoes,
they want the right shoe size. So if you wear a size 8, someone brings out a 10 1â„2.
No, I want a size 8. I need a size 8. That's what I need, right?
An American or, let's say, a 42 in England or something, right?
And they also like, you know, if they need a door replaced, they want it exactly to fit.
I mean, they want it measured out and fit precisely.
You know, if they need a part for their engine or a tire or something or a window,
they want it measured out precisely.
But when it comes time to communicating ideas or facts or objectifying the reality of the economic system,
the judicial system, the scientific system, the religious system, that's your opinion.
We don't need to know that. I don't believe in that.
Well, what do you believe in? I don't know. I'm just happy with what I believe in.
Well, tell me about it. I don't need to know anything about it. I just believe in it.
Okay, this is what you're going to be dealing with.
And I don't know, what does this have to do with the credits?
I guess that's kind of like the sentiment of this entire 18 episode on Common Sense,
is beware of the fools that are traversing the surface of this planet.
And they come in all shapes and colors and sizes and races and creeds and language.
And it's across the board.
We're not criticizing Americans or Europeans or people that live on the continent of Africa or anything like that.
It's the entire group as a whole.
This is a message to the mothership, folks.
So be objective, be clear.
And that's the other thing we try to discuss is clarity.
How are you going to go out and do activism or discuss any subject?
I mean, one of the funniest things I hear being discussed is liberty and rights and legal.
You hear those terms without them being prefaced or defined.
You're listening to the typical surface dwelling inhabitant, tripe, garbage.
And it's everywhere, folks.
And yeah, clarity, you're going to need clarity.
That's the thing that is lacking severely.
Oh, but that's your opinion, man.
We don't need clarity.
I believe in what I believe in.
What do you believe in?
Well, that's what I believe in.
Tell me about it.
I don't need to know anything about it.
I just believe in it.
Welcome to planet Earth, folks.
So you want to go and change that.
Best thing to do.
Set yourself apart.
It's called shielding separation.
Yeah.
Act impeccably.
These people are dangerous.
When I say these people, typical surface dwelling Earth inhabitants.
So, yeah, I mean, there's a reason why things are the way they are.
So be objective and be clear.
What say you about clarity, Seth?
Language, comprehension of language makes it easier.
Clarity, you can, if you understand or comprehend, rather,
the words that you are using to describe anything at all, you will have,
there will be it will be more clear regardless of who's listening.
And if you happen to be, you know,
have a listener that is also familiar with what words actually mean,
then the amount of information that can be transmitted
and received is greatly increased.
And I think that a good thing.
Like communicating the shoe size that you're looking for to the appropriate measurement
and getting it makes for better walking.
Absolutely.
So if you're going to use words like liberty and rights and legal
and better know what those things mean and none of you do, by the way,
when I say none of you meaning guys with microphones and websites
and might have some things in print, you got to check yourself, man.
You're doing a big disservice to the public, but maybe the public likes that.
I've seen a lot of people demand these artificial sweeteners out in public restaurants
instead of real sweetener, you know, like something derived from a plant, let's say.
And they get quite upset if they're not offered that.
So maybe people want this synthesized stuff that gives them cancer of the mind.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's strange, but I don't want to know.
I just want to objectify and have clarity of it because saying that you want to know
and get involved means you're implying that you might expect to change.
And the thing is when you expect change,
one of the things of being a man or woman, by the way,
you might want to call it where we're at in the food chain or so forth,
you have enough information, the cognitive ability, and the information accessible
to know what happened in the past, what's happening now,
and what's going to happen in the future.
That's not a big deal, folks.
Stop falling for these new age idiots talking about past lives and reading your cards
and what dreams are and things like that.
I'm not saying stop it, but I have for sure.
I mean, nothing there.
It's entertainment.
Now, most people take these things very seriously, by the way,
what's coming in the future and what happened in the past and what's going on now.
And they do go to these new age crap.
When I say new age crap, that's just a quick label.
That stuff has been around for all the ages, by the way,
those taking advantage of the energy that people want to dedicate to these things.
They've been around for a while.
And no matter how serious these people that are telling you a lot of these esoteric things are,
if you kind of bring up the point that what they're saying is wholly inaccurate
and not even accessible in any way or not even real in any way,
they either run away, shut up, get angry, or they tell you, oh, this is just entertainment.
But the people that this is being imparted to through media or what have you are not aware of that.
They kind of take it seriously because they're naive and sometimes excessively naive enough.
So a word of caution, folks, before you get into researching
or accepting what you think is relevant information on any subject,
do you have enough clarity to see what's being said to you?
Can you ask questions in real time, meaning as the information is streaming to your mind,
from whether you're reading it or listening to it,
can you question what you're hearing or reading or are you reading into it?
You see, are you reading out of it? Are you listening to what's being said accurately?
Now what I mean by reading into it, most people read into things.
Whenever they hear something or see something or experience something,
the mind is acting very quickly, unbeknownst to them, to try to connect what they're experiencing,
whether it's sonic, audible, cognitive, visual, to things that they've seen before.
And if we have a close enough match, they fit it in.
So it might be an elliptical peg. They have a circle, a round hole.
They say, ah, they're both kind of round. Let's just squeeze it in there and that'll be that.
A good example would be biblical references.
When people open up and read that book called the Bible and they get to a certain point,
they're like, oh, this is the point that I saw in the movie.
And they're not even reading what's there.
I mean, this happens all the time.
It's bad if they put what was there in the movies.
Nothing in any of the films has ever been done.
None of the religions have anything portrayed in the practices,
either iconography or anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
None of them.
I'm surprised by it, too, because even with what culture seems to enjoy,
as far as cinematic entertainment, a lot of it is very violent.
And the fact that there's all of these incredibly violent things that happen,
and yet it's just, you can't turn on the television and see it.
It's kind of amusing, almost.
Some people don't need to turn it on because it's always on.
Right?
Just throw that in there. Yeah.
Television, by the way, which is audio and video, is very important.
Not television per se.
They used to call them television sets, remember?
Because some of them didn't have audio.
They had an audio and a video section.
But anyway, this audio-video thing, by the way, is a prerequisite in some ancient text
that says that in order to understand the information,
you don't need to learn a particular language or philosophy or go to school,
but you need to have eyes that see and ears that hear.
So something visual and something audio is going to be happening in the future.
And let's just give a secret out because what a better place to give secrets
other than a minor Internet radio with a minor show
and just two unknown guys that come around and talk stuff that four or five people listen to every week.
Well, what you're going to see encoded in a particular ancient text is audio and video code
that will be assimilated and presented in the future as well.
Yes, you heard me right.
That's why you have a proliferation of inexpensive devices that these phones give you video.
And the video and the visual is just as important as the sonic.
As a matter of fact, more so, because the speaker technology
and most of these small devices is still not very good.
And this is based on the entitlement that the current engineers in the audio business tend to enjoy.
What I mean by entitlement is you go through a particular level of pranking
until you get what's called a degree,
so you can hold a position in society that you could pull social rank on other people.
Yes, you know who you are.
You're called doctors, attorneys, priests, pastors, rabbis, you know, engineers, whatever.
You're pranking.
But these pranksters known as audio engineers refuse to accept a particular technology
that's been around for about ten years that make small devices sound very clear
and very audible and use less power because it was, quote-unquote,
discovered or slash invented by a non-engineer.
So you're still subject to this pranking from the entitled classes.
But in the future you won't be because it'll be like a wave that overcomes everything.
And this wave is going to be accessible audio-video information to everyone on the planet
regarding events that are going to be taking place at certain parts of the world.
And this is within a decade plus.
And this is why we mentioned before.
You might be in a want for water, a want for food, or a want for credit, what you call money,
a want for transportation, a want for liberty and rights, right, like you call it,
but you won't have a want for accessible to instant communication and audio-video form.
There's a reason for that.
And it has nothing to do with what you're doing.
It has to do with the way things are and the way things have to be.
So just keep that in mind, folks.
This audio-video thing is not going to go away.
It's going to increase and be more prolific as you go on in time.
So, yeah, there's many things that have been discussed and kind of stated once before
that I wanted to kind of go into each one of these sonic episodes as being more topical in nature
and getting into a topic a little more deeply than just mentioning in passing,
hey, did you ever think of this, right?
But just to reiterate, during the week when I was kind of thinking about what to talk about,
I kind of poked around in alternative media and listened around a little bit,
and I was like, you've got to be kidding.
I couldn't find anyone or anything on the alternative Internet at all
or mainstream that was even close to what level of subject matter we wanted to discuss.
I was like, you've got to be kidding me.
People are accepting this junk.
There is no way I'm going to come out and talk about water publicly.
There's no way I'm going to come out and talk about how the banks work.
There's no way I'm going to come out and talk about how the body works in a little more depth.
There's no way I'm going to come out and talk about how automobiles work.
No way.
I spoke to a psychic the other day.
You did?
Well, why did you have to speak to them if they're psychic?
Shouldn't they have been able to read your mind?
But anyway, that was what I implied.
It was, I was incredibly reserved in my, I just kind of was like, oh, okay.
And yeah, it was, I didn't speak much, but that happened.
It was, yeah, it happened.
It was, I'd say entertaining, but it wasn't really entertaining.
There's a short little YouTube, by the way, if anyone wants to look, it's called Psychic Fail,
and it's a French interview of a man sitting in a train car, and he's a reporter,
and he asks this older man, are you psychic?
He says yes, and then he just gives them a full-fingered, full-open palm slap across the head,
knocks him to the side, and he says, well, you didn't see that coming, did you?
And he says no.
He says, well, you see, I got a charlatan over here.
You're not psychic.
And that's what they're all going to get.
The entitled classes are going to get this kind of stuff in the future.
It's going to be seemingly natural, but if you know it's coming, it won't.
It will be pretty obvious.
So now anyone who's listening, or even if you're just hearing things,
you might be able to remember there's going to be a pretty drastic change starting in the next few years.
To sanity, wellness, by the way, that's what that means, I guess.
Seth, would you say sanity means wellness?
Yeah.
Insanity means unwellness, unhealthy.
Sanity is health.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Yeah, I am looking forward to the next sonic endeavor that we do as well,
getting into a little bit more depth, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
It needs to be done tastefully.
It needs to be done appropriately, meaning whoever, yeah, I think it needs to be set apart.
I don't know how it's going to be done at this point.
It has to be set apart.
Here, everybody cover your ears.
Privately, Seth, you and I, I'd like to not even do it on the Internet.
Anyway, all right, folks, I almost want to just write it on an old typewriter
and go to the old mimeograph machines that were loaded with this blue alcohol dye kind of stuff.
I don't know if anyone remembers that.
Or a woodblock print and just send it through the post.
Who to?
Yeah, exactly, to who?
That's the whole point.
But it's a strange desire.
Let's get less strange and, yeah, it will be on the Internet somehow.
We have a blog spot.
There's the www.uncommonradio.com.
A little Skype is being set up.
So, yeah, yeah.
And we're not going to talk about theories or Anunnaki or going to outer space
or liberty and rights and ridiculous stuff like that, yeah,
or how to change anything for the better in a social level.
It's going to be stuff that you can access immediately and you can see within arm's reach,
whether it has to do with water, automobile, what you call automobiles.
And they're not really automobiles, folks, because they're not auto.
They have to put fuel in them.
How to, let's say, change things in a car so it doesn't run like they tell you it does.
Discuss how the body really works, you know.
Just not some crazy theory and not allopathically.
We don't care about any substance that's illegal or needs to be legalized.
You know what I'm talking about, you stoners.
That's irrelevant.
We're not going to be talking about that.
We're not going to be talking about some stupid drops or something you make,
like you can't, you know, get on your own from within reach.
We're not going to be talking about, yeah, calories or blood pressure.
These are ridiculous things that don't exist.
Very relevant to the body.
Things that really, really work that you can access immediately.
Things that really work with water that you can access immediately.
Discuss how the banking system works, how money works.
If you can relax the mind enough, you will find that it's whoever you're doing banking with,
the local whatever branch, is ripping you off blind.
Not some Federal Reserve entity.
Yes, the Federal Reserve is the outline, but you'll see how whatever.
And anyone who talks to anyone that is in the arts of divinity, let's say a priest, a preacher, a minister, a rabbi or an imam,
will discuss what they're doing and what they should be doing or shouldn't be doing
and what these things that these people tend to represent really are.
Quote, unquote, religion.
You know, it only takes a few minutes.
You know, if anyone, by the way, if you have what's called a Bible,
if you have an under-bridged version, go read the introduction,
and you tell me if you want to continue reading.
They're flat out telling you what's going on with that.
Yeah.
They should put in there the disclaimer that they put at the end of films.
If anyone is alive or dead or whatever, it's just purely by coincidence.
So what is that disclaimer they use in film?
If anything represented herein resembles anyone alive or dead, it's purely by coincidence.
Yeah, purely coincidental.
Yeah, exactly.
Any person's living or deceased is purely coincidental.
This is a work of fiction.
Yeah, and then you have people actually pick up the King James and try to explain it.
I'm like, dude, don't you know what you're reading out of is not even legitimate, not even close?
I mean, they tell you.
I mean, it's just ridiculous.
It's just absurd, you know.
And this is actually explained in the text itself, but no one reads it anyway.
And by the way, when we bring up books, you know, there's still a lot of people out there.
They're like, I don't need a book to tell me anything.
I don't need to get any knowledge from a book.
I just believe.
What do you believe in?
I don't know.
I just believe.
This is the level of humanity, folks.
And they're really proud of telling you they don't know anything.
That's like being really proud of being stupid, folks.
And you know what?
That's also written about by the agents as well.
So, yeah.
They have like 15 different ways, I've noticed, in the past year that people express their pride of how ignorant they are.
But they don't quite say it that way.
I'm saying it that way.
You know, it's just excessive.
But remember, the pride comes right before the fall.
So, yeah, it's quite interesting.
So, yeah, we'll be discussing all these other things.
And if you're looking forward to it, Seth, hopefully others are.
I think these things need to be done, only because no one else is.
And it's thankless in a way.
I mean, there are some people that kind of say, yeah, you kind of took a little while to wrap around what you were saying.
I said, maybe because it's too simple.
Yeah, yeah, it's kind of almost too simple.
So, we don't discuss trends as such.
We discuss objectivity, clarity.
And you'll see that when you see things objectively and clearly, you'll see a trend is not really a trend.
It's not this random flow.
And you'll see why a lot of these things are somewhat shameful after they've been accepted.
You know, like if you ever have, if you're not old enough,
do you ever remember seeing a photograph of a parent or an uncle or an older friend from the 1970s
with the really strange colored polyester fabrics with wide lapels and polyester bell bottoms?
Man, they thought that was the best stuff at the time, didn't they?
Now they're kind of embarrassed.
Look how ugly that stuff looks, right?
So, a lot of the stuff that folks accept as trends and social things and changes
are met with great shame later on and embarrassment, typically.
So, unless they're glorified and romanticized, which tends to happen as well.
Yes, it does.
Worship of the past is relatively common.
And, yeah.
A bit strange, but relatively common.
Yeah, go ahead.
I always hearken back to the phrase, the quote, history doesn't repeat itself, but it rhymes.
People do it.
But it's not even that history repeats itself.
It kind of does.
All of these things are set, folks.
And you don't really want to know that they are set because it kind of scares people.
They like the uncertainty.
They like the idea of randomness because it gives them a level of control that they don't have to take responsibility for.
See, when you kind of admit that things are random and no one knows what's coming or what is going to happen,
then you don't have to take responsibility for it, right?
Because, hey, it's random.
No one knew it was coming.
But once you know it's coming, now you're in a different light.
Now you're in a different position.
Now you are held responsible for certain things and not necessarily the acts themselves,
whether you're assisting them or impeding them, you know, whether it's you said something about it, right?
So that's, again, folks, when you listen to media, get a counter and write down,
make a column of what the word you hear being said, like I don't know or no one knows or who cares or opinion or belief.
Make a column with these words.
I don't know, belief, who cares or, you know, opinion, especially the I don't know one.
And every time you hear anything in the media, it doesn't matter, any media, you know,
everything before this show and after this show, anywhere.
And make a column and mark how many times those words come up and you will be astonished.
And then start piecing it together with everything else that's being said as if you can now make the decision.
What you are hearing or listening to is coming from a source that knows anything about what they're talking about.
And if you answered, no, they don't know.
That's correct.
They've actually heard something that was popular to talk about from someone else or themselves and they can do it.
And it's keeping everything moving.
And that's called entertainment.
So but I think infotainment concept being informed and entertained at the same time is very good as well.
So I don't know if we make you folks laugh or cry or get angry or yell at the speakers like I used to when I was a kid.
When I listened to Internet radio, as I used to because I don't listen to it anymore.
But either way, folks, there's lots to be said, lots to be done.
But not to change anything on a social or cosmic level.
So maybe did we mention Seth on our next perhaps sonic presentations?
We might talk about what's coming in the future with great accuracy and specificity.
I don't think we mentioned that.
We've we've done a bit of that already.
Yeah. You don't need a crystal ball or psychic or reading tea leaves, folks.
Yeah. Got to know what it means to be a man or a woman.
Where are you? Who are you?
Also avoid avoid internalizing too much.
When you hear people say this is our planet, our skies, our plants, our children, our government, our legal system.
You hear that coming from someone run.
That's someone who's stuck on flypaper.
You ever see a fly stuck on flypaper.
You try to remove it leaves like the wings and the legs and the head behind.
Yeah. Those people are stuck there.
Yeah. They can't get over there.
They're stuck in the in the entire thing as it's moving.
It's it's like a conveyor belt with the meat grinder at the end.
You don't want to jump on that conveyor.
So this is what you hear.
All you hear is people taking possession.
Now what that means. Why are they stuck?
Why why run the other way?
Here's the explanation.
Very simply, when you claim something is yours, now you get the bill.
You take liability for it cosmically and divinely.
So when you're listening to someone say this is our planet, our government, our legal system, our medical system, our belief, our skies, our plants, our children, our oceans.
They are taking the hit.
Liability both divinely and cosmically.
They're writing checks with their mouth that they will be cashing with their bodies later.
So listen for that.
Make another column.
When you hear any listening to anything, anything at all, even university, make a column.
I don't know.
Belief, opinion, mine or ours or we and how many times these things are brought up in conversation or presentation.
Make a note of how many times these things are brought up and that completely shows you what's going on.
Be objective.
Tend to make a statement sometimes whether it's harsh or not.
By the way, when the level of bad behavior or criminality is high, the level of harshness of language is also required to be high.
That's why you hear us calling or myself calling people morons and idiots and imbeciles.
Because it's gone way beyond the acceptable point for anyone.
And no one is noticing.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
We also have just to jump in here.
We've got a little bit of time for the end of the first hour.
You brought up perhaps discussing scripture a little bit, maybe regarding wisdom and Psalms and things like that.
My response was, I don't know how we can do that publicly, because first thing you bring that up, they think of some kind of religion.
And then there was another comment being made about, you know, why don't we just talk about Christianity or these religions, all of them, not just Christianity.
There's no significance to Christianity, Buddhism, Islam, Judaism, whatever, whatever, or what they call Satanism.
These things are not as significant as people think they are.
They are social things.
And the significance that's brought forward is what is really going on with it, really going on with all of these religions.
And there's hundreds of them.
Would you say I think there's hundreds of various religions?
Could it possibly be in the thousands?
Yeah, there are forms.
I would say a little bit more than that.
They're social clubs with a form of, like, pseudo government, you know, use the word etymologically.
And they use the government.
I mean, they are the government, because let's say there's an overthrow revolution or whatever in a government.
You notice that the religious institutions tend to stay.
Yeah, yeah.
It was more overtly the case, you know, I suppose most recently, perhaps not even most recently, but, you know, with the Roman Catholic empire at one point.
Which is not Roman, and it's not really Catholic, which it is.
Yeah.
Roman meaning it's an offshoot of the Greek empire.
Right.
Well, I would call it the Hellenistic paganism empire.
Yes.
I don't think anyone would know what I was saying.
Yeah.
Well, let's give it a try.
And the other thing is it's not Catholic, which means universal, because not strictly, but predominantly the liturgy, the people, the things that people are involved in, is the revived Hellenistic paganism that was done in ancient Greece.
And the leadership is involved in occult Canaanite and Babylonian practices.
So those are the three major aspects of what's called Catholicism, which is not necessarily universal, because you just laid out about 95 or 99% of what it really is.
And it's a revived Hellenistic paganism with, when I say Canaanite, Dagon worship, human sacrifice, Babylonian, meaning overt structural embellishments, overt display of power.
Have you ever heard of the seven?
It's done, you mentioned even earlier in the program, that it has significant differences in the way that it's practiced in different localities, specifically like the southern American continent or even the southern North American continent.
It's practiced, widespread practice, but it's almost not recognizable.
Some of the iconography, I suppose, is very similar, but even what iconography is said to represent varies from one place to another.
Like here's, I guess, Seth, I just threw in, it's geographically, all religions are geographically based, regardless if you're talking about Hinduism, Buddhism, Christianity, Judaism, what have you, regardless, Satanism, all that stuff is geographically situated.
And also you have to remember, even though you might have different geographical locations with similar nomenclature, meaning, oh, this is Christian, this is Buddhist, this is Muslim, this is whatever, that's just the shingle being changed outside.
So it's just like, you know, you have Joe's hardware for 20 years, and then all of a sudden they change it to Phil's hardware, but everything's the same inside.
There are a couple of changes, right?
Still have hammers?
Yep.
They still have hammers, yeah, exactly, and saws, right?
And this is all they're doing.
So if you look at Islam, that's why you have all the various sects.
They're doing the same stuff that has been done since post-flood times.
Just call it Islam, but it's this type of Islam you see.
If you look at Christianity, you have Eastern Orthodox Catholicism, the various Protestant ridiculousness, the Quaker ridiculousness.
Then you come across the ocean.
You've got the Bible Belt.
You've got the buckle of the Bible Belt, biggest pork eaters in the world.
You've got the Utah version.
You've got the Texas version.
You've got the Jews for Jesus version.
You've got the Mexican version, the South American version of Christianity.
It's all the same geographical entity.
What I mean by that is we've always discussed how there is a hierarchy of rank and power, all right, in the spiritual realm.
Just like you have on Earth.
You have the homeless crazy guy that walks down the street yelling at himself to the street sweeper, to the storekeeper, to the mechanic, to the cop, to the lawyer, attorney, let's say, or doctor, entitled people, to the mayor,
to the governor, to the president, to the emperor, right?
And then different classes within that group are exempt from certain things, just like you see in society, but different.
And we'll get into that a little bit more, just like this is the end of the first hour, and we will see you folks on the other side of the break.
Greetings and welcome back to Uncommon Sense.
This is the credits episode or credits episodic sonic part of the presentation we're trying to bring here on American Freedom Radio.
And by the way, you folks, you're listening to American Freedom Radio, so do the right thing.
Go to the homepage and do the right thing.
You know what that is.
And Seth, are you with us?
You might be muted.
If not, we will continue.
Yes, I'm here.
Yes, good.
Before the break, we were discussing, as we brought up, you know, maybe discussing a little bit about Christianity or religion in general.
And the reason why we're not harping on Christianity, it's just from a secular point of view, a nonreligious, meaning academics,
who are self-professed atheists, by the way, consider this to be the Christian era.
And we had gone over more detail about what the Roman Catholic is and versus how it's perceived.
And a little more detail may not be against how it's perceived, but a little more detail, I'm not that anyone can discover about it.
And especially the high-ups in that particular religion will tell you this, but they don't speak it to their congregation.
And the various geographic aspects and the ranking system in the spiritual realm, does that sound about right to you, Seth?
Yes.
And it seems important to also discuss the geographical aspect of it, to rationalize what is going on,
because you still have, again, your typical surface-dwelling earth inhabitant.
Once the word belief comes in and you question about, ask them what they believe in, and you find out that it's totally erroneous,
which is typical, they tell you, well, leave me alone. I want to believe in what I believe in.
I'm happy what I believe in, even though I know nothing about it. I don't need to know anything about it.
I just believe in it. Right? That's kind of like idiocracy, right?
So you are in an idiocracy, by the way, folks, this entire society, high to low.
And by the way, just to throw in, as we were giving the description of the spiritual realm having hierarchy,
what's different about that, which is difficult to comprehend for most, is that man's system is a vertical system,
meaning the street sweeper at the bottom, the king is at the top.
In the divine, it's a lateral system. It's your inside or outside, and there's various levels.
If you've heard the term like inner circle and outer circle, and then there's all these concentric circles or rings that go out, right?
And it's a lateral system. And you'll find that's just a secret on how to comprehend when you're reading older texts regarding,
let's say, what we might call the holy writs of the world, which no one reads.
And by the way, folks, don't be impressed by folks that say they have a degree or academic.
Now, they speak very well because they're trained and polished to perform, just like circus animals are.
But if you listen to what they're actually saying, it has to conform to what the audience has previously been told,
which is probably some form of, anyway, inaccuracy.
So there's a level of discussion, and then there's a discussion.
And the level of discussion is when the audience is accommodated,
and then there's a discussion where you just spill the beans and say, this is what can be discovered.
This is how it appears to be. Any questions? You see.
So at this point, maybe we'll jump back to the geographic aspects of the spiritual realm.
So we kind of discussed these religions, how they vary from geographic parts of the world.
We went all the way from Roman Catholicism to the shores of America to the Bible Belt,
the buckle of the Bible Belt, Mormonism in Utah and South America, and how it all changes.
You know, the northern Europeans have Protestant, Quaker, all this other stuff.
None of it, absolutely none of it is based on anything at all that's in the text that they allegedly say they subscribe to, at all.
Not even a smidgen, folks.
Think about that.
It's difficult to talk about those texts that they claim to be basing their things upon,
because when they're brought up, what immediately comes to mind in 99.9 percent of anyone listening is completely and totally false.
Right. And here's the interesting part.
How long of a discussion do you have to have with a quote unquote believer of any faith
when you point out that what they're doing is either contrary to the text, forbidden by the text, or not in the text?
It usually takes about, I found, 30 seconds to a minute for them to resolve the whole thing and walk away.
They don't really defend it, I found out. Have you found that?
I would say that I've been met with a number of interesting conversations, actually.
But, then again,
That means, hold on, it means you're showing up to a knife fight with a knife.
You need to be a peacemaker, you need to show up with overwhelming force, and that brings peace.
Anyway, I'm just joking. Go ahead.
What ends up, it ends up, I end up answering a lot of questions.
I'll make a statement, and it happens, it hasn't happened all that much recently, I guess,
but just in conversations with random people at a coffee shop or something like that,
all over the conversation and offer a piece of information and then get invited into a conversation
where I'm essentially just asking questions, or, I'm sorry, answering questions.
I haven't been met with a lot of people trying to defend their points once they realize that I'm talking about what's just written.
Then they want to, like I said, I've been met with just a lot of questions.
Well, okay, where it says this, I'm like, well, I mean, does it, is that what it says, is a lot of it.
But, I don't know.
I haven't met with too many people just getting angry.
I suppose one of the conversations, the gentleman was being defensive,
and then when the defense didn't hold up, he was dismissive.
Yeah, armoring, he armored himself.
Yeah, what happens is that they have human society or human nature
or what's acceptable by surface-dwelling earth inhabitants to fall back on.
In other words, whether they're gaining or losing an argument, I don't believe in arguing,
I think just being slightly confrontational to offer a contrast, perhaps.
And by the way, asking questions, what about asking the answer?
Think about that, folks.
Everyone says ask questions.
How about asking the answer?
But think about that.
It's not a play on words.
That's going to require a little bit of chewing the cud.
But I found that when you confront these folks, what they want to do in their minds
and actually physically do is go to the people next to them and say, look, I've been challenged regarding this.
What do you think?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Oh, see, I feel better now.
So what they're doing is relying on the crowd that we brought up, Gustave Le Bon,
the crowd mentality where one gives up all rationale to join a group.
Look at the activists, right?
Look at the people that say we have to make the world a better place.
If you look at the topic and the subject matter that they're discussing in any depth at all, any depth,
beyond skin deep, you will find that they have no clue of what they're talking about.
But it doesn't matter because they have the plausibility that everyone, all the boys and girls,
are interested in this, and this is what they believe.
But essentially, folks, what you will find, going back to the geographical aspect of it,
that the earth is quite an interesting place, even more on the unseen than it is on the seen.
To find interest on what can be seen, one must comprehend the scale of things and how humanity fits in it.
There's a reason why we are the size we are, and there's a reason why things are the way they are,
when it comes to what things look like, you know, trees, mountains, oceans, how high, how tall we are,
and other things smaller and larger than us, greater and less great.
There's a scale there, and there's a proportion.
We've discussed this in the past.
Now, to go to the unseen, that seems to be unlimited to our little pea brain,
but we've been memorialized, or in the past there's enough memorialization that if we look at it,
whoever we is, objectively, and don't read into it, you will find there's a lot of specificity and detail.
Now, it's not necessarily based on what you're going to do with it.
Is it, are you even familiar with the information?
And the answer there is no.
Most people are not even vaguely familiar.
Now, there are groups of people throughout history who have been and have made it, let's say,
public works projects to put out propaganda to keep people from comprehending it
and giving them enough rope to, right, what do you do with rope, right,
giving them enough leeway that they're comfortable and proud of being ignorant.
And this is the society that you live in.
This is at large on the entire surface.
This is across the planet, folks.
It's celebrated.
And ignorance is celebrated.
They don't quite say we're celebrating ignorance, but in essence you could wrap it all up as that, yeah,
and they love it because they have each other, right?
They just look at the person next to them.
I don't know. I just believe.
That's great, man.
Pat you on the back.
I'm glad you do.
And then you throw in the pranking and all this other stuff.
But from a cosmic point of view, there are various aspects of the geographical layout of the planet
that have been established as dominions of certain spiritual entities.
Well, you know, whether you believe in what I'm talking about, whether you believe it or not,
that we're communicating something that you might want to listen to.
And when you travel a certain part of the world and set up a community or a society,
if you don't, let's say, how would you say, pay homage to, acknowledge that entity,
or do what that entity wants, in short, let's just keep it simple,
you're not going to be able to live there.
So henceforth, the various forms of Christianity that you see all over the world,
which are none of it is biblically based, right?
It's all based, by the way, all of the religions at this point are based on some form of talismanic rabbit's foot
kind of like, you touch this thing, you're going to get power kind of thing, you know.
And even those that have supposedly, you know, the pranksters, the priests, the pastors, all this,
even they, I've spoken to some of them and they say, oh, I read the Bible every morning.
I get up and I open it to some page and I read a verse and it's pertinent.
That's like that.
Wasn't there a game like that?
It was like an eight ball or something that you touched and it gave a message.
What's that?
I don't know.
You guys know what I'm talking about.
I think someone does.
Was it one of these things at the toy store they sell?
Magic eight ball.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
My sources say no.
Right, right.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, that's what they're doing.
This is the people that you guys are looking to for answers.
Just stick with the questions.
It's ridiculous, absurd.
But this is, does it mean that it's not, this is not unobtainium we're talking about.
It's not a material that's hard to find.
You can actually just start learning how to read out of things instead of reading into it.
I brought up how there's groups of people that have spent,
made public works projects to make sure that you don't find out what's going on,
not only with the religions of the world, by the way.
All of your biblically based movies that you see are false.
And how do I say that with great veracity and authority?
You've just got to go read the text.
Don't read into it.
When you read the text, even the crappy King James version, yes, I said the word,
even there you could piece it enough together that it will give some accuracy regarding any story that you find.
And you'll see that nothing is being portrayed on film as such at all, not even close.
Other than the time period and people maybe wore sandals and there were no airplanes in the sky.
Or anything that you read about Noah's flood or the flood during the time of Noah is not accurate other than it was really wet.
Outside of that, forget it.
And any kind of these Christ movies that you see are absolutely false, every single one.
Very simple.
You can be an authority on what I just said by just simply reading the text.
I'll give another example on the talismanic, the paganistic aspect of it.
I was at a lady's house one day and she had this big crucifix with the guy with long hair to a cross wearing a diaper, all that.
And I'm looking at it and I'm like, I thought you read the Bible.
What's that?
She goes, oh, he's helped me a lot in the past.
I'm like, who's he?
I don't know.
I just believe in it.
I'm like, well, I thought you said you were reading the Bible.
Don't you see that this is completely contrary?
Well, I don't really care, you see.
He's helped me a lot.
Now, what's interesting about that, this woman was definitely under the influence of that local entity.
So think about it, folks.
And by the way, when you see that iconography that they're being shown in Christianity, that's Serapis, right?
And Mithra.
And then there's an agglomerate, the one that you see with the Roman crucifix that was created around 400 or so A.D., 360 or 400.
It was a council to kind of like put together what are we going to show the people?
Right.
It's not in the text.
It's very clear.
The text is quite clear that when the Christ figure was taken finally to Pontius Pilate for the final say,
he said that this man needs to be released or use your law.
The Judean authorities should use their law.
There's no Roman crucifix at all, not even in the location, not even close.
They could use the word crucifix all they want, but if you look up the word crucifix, it is a botanical term.
It has to do with flowers.
And there was a particular tree that was flowering at the time.
But just to go back, we've mentioned this many times, what happened there.
The entire identity of anyone in the biblical text is secret, just like in the Koran and other writings,
Book of the Dead and all these things.
Anything that you're reading out of that is a secret, hidden in plain sight.
There's no such thing as the rituals that people are partaking in.
But just to go back, there's been groups of people, they even made public works projects to hide
and put in front of you and distract you, like the films.
All of the biblical films are false, all of them.
Even without mentioning his name, there's someone who recently did one regarding something,
passion of something that everyone thought it was great.
And I'm like, it's a great piece of fiction.
But the reference materials that you have access to, you don't have any translations, by the way.
None, zero, even to this date.
You're so advanced and so modern and you don't have anything translated, not even the Greek philosophers.
Sorry, folks.
And if you learn how to read a little bit of Greek, you could go back and read some of the surviving works
of Plato, Aristotle, and Socrates, and then go look at the corresponding English text, and you will say it is not so.
But you're quite happy with artificial sweeteners, I think.
So, even to this day, there's a tremendous amount of public works projects, private and public, funded, to distract you.
Like, for example, the economic system.
You're being heavily distracted.
There is not one commentator, period.
Say it again.
There's not one commentator, period, on the Internet or anywhere that is even slightly accurate about the economy or the financial system or the credit system.
Not a one.
That's very easy to defend that comment.
Right.
You're being shown television shows regarding what goes on in court.
Not a one is even close to being accurate.
Nothing.
You're shown medical shows of what it's like to be a doctor.
Not a one is even close to being accurate.
Why are you being so distracted?
Because you all have the ability and the capability and capacity to comprehend these things.
Because all these entitled classes, whether they're priests, pastors, rabbis, attorneys, doctors, mechanics, engineers,
do you think they come through a wormhole from another dimension every day, serve their function, and then go back home to another universe?
Or are they people just like you?
And you all have the same capacity.
But it's important for the pranking to go on.
See, if a prankster wants you to sit on a thumbtack and get off on you being in pain,
they usually don't tell you they're placing a thumbtack on the chair before they offer it to you, do they?
And then after you sit on it and exclaim how painful it was, they laugh and say,
well, I didn't tell you to sit on it.
You did it all on your own.
It's exactly how the legal system works.
I'm going to offer you a chair.
I know why, that I didn't know it was there.
It's exactly how all the attorneys are working.
Not some of them, all of them.
Why?
There might be some attorneys that found out that they got pranked into that field,
and they're like, holy crap, I've got to get away.
And they're looking for an exit strategy currently.
But all the ones that stay in there are pranksters.
Sorry, guys.
Same with your doctors.
The best a doctor can do is give you a description.
Can't explain anything.
Call up a doctor and say, I'm going over there because my ankle is sprained, let's say.
You show up to the office, he's like, oh, your ankle is sprained.
$150.
Well, I knew that.
Can you explain why it's swollen?
Why?
No, no, it's just sprained.
And they act all surprised, like you didn't tell them anything,
because they don't know.
They don't want to know.
They might act like they want to know.
Sorry, folks.
So you want to change this to what?
You're going to make the world a better place to what?
You've got one-third of the planet right now engaged in heavy pranking.
You've got the other third emphatically supporting them.
Then the other third, you do whatever.
So in order to make the world a better place,
what are you going to do with two-thirds of the people on the planet?
You think these pranksters are rehabilitatable?
And you've all been distracted by this new world order of bullshit, that's what it is,
that they want to get rid of all the world's population down to 500 million.
Yeah, right.
Uh-huh.
Sure.
Who are they going to prank?
It's not about pranking.
You hear about these morons talking about, oh, yeah,
that's just enough slaves to do their bidding or whatever.
No, it's not.
Don't be fooled by that.
But here's the interesting part.
You ready for this?
The Earth's population will be reduced to that, a little bit lower, actually,
in the next decade and a half.
And even when it's happening, you're all going to be saying,
what a wonderful world it is.
Well, don't worry.
We'll get back on track.
That's part of the great deception, folks.
Oh, what did he just say?
It doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, it shouldn't.
But starting in the middle of the next century, oh, not century, next decade,
you're going to have major changes.
When all these fires that are in the Middle East right now are put out,
you're going to see some big changes.
So I hope that kind of went around the block with the geographic aspect of the
religion.
But next time you hear about someone's belief,
you'll find out if you look a little closer that they're discussing something
that's geographically pinned or sourced and a variance of something else.
So, meaning, what kind of a Christian are you?
What kind of a Jew are you?
What kind of Buddhism are you?
All this stuff, man.
Here's the final analysis of the matter.
Get up on your hind legs, people.
You deserve a lot better than that.
And sometimes it's better not to speak than to speak.
Someone asks you what you believe in, and if you don't know anything about it,
it's best to say, I'm ignorant of the fact.
Because this thing about opinions that is going around,
especially to discount anything that could be brought forward as being true,
is just insidious.
And typical human nature.
But then again, let's throw in what Gustave Le Bon said, L-E-B-O-N, the crowd.
He was not there to explain the psychology of it necessarily on why people do it.
It's how they do it.
And some of the why was sort of an analysis.
But what I do like about bringing him up, other than others,
is that he was the most objective, objectified about how these groups form.
There's not much comfort when you start discovering and objectifying what's going on in this reality.
But once you learn to separate yourself.
Insulation.
Yes, you will be more comfortable when you're insulated, yes.
See, if you don't know that you need to be insulated
and you believe all the crap that we can make things better and all this,
you're being tossed about and you've got some stinky stuff on you
and you get shocked every once in a while and you're resilient enough to take it.
But once you realize you should set yourself apart and insulate yourself from it,
you start figuring out how to do that.
And once you achieve a level of insulation and separation,
you will find that then you might be able to relax a little bit.
Yeah, it's not that it's all misery and it's all strife.
I know.
Actually.
Initially it is.
Might not make you.
Yeah, yes, certainly it can be.
And it might not make you too many friends.
No, no, you won't.
Yeah, have a spouse and a dog if you need company.
Yeah, find a spouse, make a spouse and learn to love each other.
This stuff about love and peace and all that, no one knows what that means
and they still use those words.
So very nice people tend to think that love is the answer.
And if you ask them to define it, they can't and that's why they're very nice.
But, yeah, a spouse and a pet you'll find comfort in if you know how to love
or want to learn how to love, which is very different than just love,
which is another thing to discuss, which we have, I think.
I think the most that we've ever gone into any detail on anything regarding
other than some ancient texts and the biblical stuff is dreams, Seth.
We've pretty much gotten into that in some depth.
We've gotten into love to a certain degree in comparison with fear
and other things like that that are being tossed about on the world wide web,
which I wonder which spider, is it a poisonous spider that's weaving this web?
I wonder.
Carnivorous, I imagine.
Yes, yes, I think it's a really ignorant spider, but nonetheless.
Yeah, the main point here, guys and gals and little ones, is avoid being pranked.
There's a right time to call out a prankster.
By the way, if you go to a court scene,
don't call the judge a prankster or anybody else right there,
but there are ways to say it because that's what they are, all of them.
That's some of them.
Now there might be some of them in those positions now that realize what they're
doing is wrong and they're looking for an exit strategy,
which from firsthand experience I've met a few, I should say a couple,
three or four that were in the legal profession and they're like,
I've got to get out.
I found out what this is about.
And it took them six months to a year,
typically to get all their things kind of organized so they can sort of live
the level of luxury or comfort that they had without sacrificing too much of
their position economically, let's say.
And the same with the doctors.
But there are some people and they're looking for an exit strategy.
And when I say all of them, I'm not including those,
but those that remain for sure, yeah.
So just like you have, there's something that goes on in society,
it's been going on repeatedly, is when you have malevolent organizations,
no matter how big or how small,
they feel compelled to do some form of benevolent action or act, right?
You've heard of certain societies,
they build a hospital or certain religions are into charity,
feeding the poor and the homeless, right?
I mean, so when you examine the religions of the world as being just downright
demonic, I mean malevolent to the core, I mean,
which doesn't take much than a little bit of research to find out.
And then you, on the surface,
are always told how wonderful they are because they're doing charitable work.
You need to put those two things together.
And the third thing being that typically these very malevolent organizations,
regardless of whether they're economic, judicial, religious, political,
scientific, tend to engage in some form of charity or benevolence.
An interesting thing is there's a level of,
because this is a pagan society basically at large,
they're into iconography and talismans.
I'll throw this in there, maybe it'll make the 9-11 conspiracy theorists happy.
You notice that after September 11th,
X was in a conversation one day with someone who I had first met,
and he said it should have been called 7-11 because September was the seventh
month, and I was so happy to hear that from someone else.
It was the first time in 10 years someone actually paid a little bit of
attention and realized September means seven.
But anyway, going back to that event,
shortly after, do you notice how people started putting on American flag
lapels, especially the politicians, you know,
to show that they're patriotic or whatever, you know?
Oh, yeah.
To hide their guilt, yeah.
And also to distract, they don't know what to say because they can't say what,
you know.
Actually,
they do know what to say because they look at the audience and they see what
will accommodate them.
So it's the same thing that's going on.
So typically,
if you do a quick assessment of who is living on this planet and what they
subscribe to or are alleged to subscribe to and have their allegiances to as
being downright malevolent across the board,
when you do see this charity and benevolence being done,
it's part of the things that are instigated to give the plausibility,
because you'll hear that.
What are you talking about?
This religion is bad.
Look at all the charity they're giving.
Like, oh, boy, you can't pull that here, mister.
Sorry, doesn't work.
I'd also say don't let that stand in the way of being charitable.
Don't let these horrible organizations preempt that.
I think there are a few things better that one can do.
Speaking, we're kind of hard on those who claim to want to make the world a
better place.
And I'd say that it's those that claim such things,
because you want to make the world a better place,
help someone that needs help.
That's a good thing.
Yeah, help those within reach.
If someone needs shoes, give them shoes, a jacket, food, clothing,
shelter them.
That's good.
And there are a few things that you can do that are better than that.
If half the people on the planet helped one person,
that would just take care of the other half, figuratively.
Yeah.
And so we miss that.
And that's something that can be, you know, there's no comprehension.
There's no understanding that is deep and requires a whole lot of study to see
that that is accurate and that those things are good to do no matter who you
are.
So, yeah.
And when we say go deep,
have you heard of people saying how superficial things are, right?
When we say deep, I mean like just a few millimeters, folks.
Stop skimming across the surface on thin ice.
You know?
Yeah.
You can acquire a lot of knowledge without much depth,
but wisdom, if it's all a fountain and water, metaphorically,
wisdom is the realization that it is incredibly deep.
Yes, quickly.
And it's sort of like a counter spatial thing that you might go six feet or
eight feet or 10 feet into one thing and not find a lot,
or you might just go a quarter of an inch into something else and be more
than you can handle.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
So, yeah, there's many levels.
Pick one, but it's always safest to be lateral.
So insulate yourself, pull yourself away.
And by the way,
you made the comment earlier, Seth,
about making the world a better place and all that.
If you study about that and objectify it,
and also I've given historical references,
people especially in the 20th century that overtly came up with discovery or
invented something,
said we have to implement this to make the world better.
And you'll find that all of them, that some of them have been squashed.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
No, it's dangerous.
It's not good for one's health to loudly proclaim such things.
No, no.
Cosmically and divinely, meaning.
Unless you're not actually doing anything.
If all you're doing is saying something, it's not going to.
They, whoever they are, they, they seem to encourage that quite a bit.
Yes.
They just talk about it.
The fools.
Yeah.
They got to say something.
Rights, liberty, chemtrails.
What's the other one?
Vaccines, legalized cannabis.
Try and improve the world.
And by that, you know, society, not, not the earth.
The earth doesn't need any improvement.
It's pretty good.
Oh, the earth would be quite happy to go back to a black crystal floating in
space with no atmosphere, nothing at all on it.
None of these people will find those creatures crawling around all over.
Right.
Yeah.
But the earth has been remade.
So everything that you see here will,
you would be able to live on it as you are.
And in the level of ignorance regarding these things is so high that it's not
even worth discussing at this point, but it will be a point in the future.
Yeah.
Discuss it and actually go out into the society and discover something that
will or has the great potential to improve or change the society
dramatically or drastically.
Even I tried to smash those words together.
Dramatically.
Yeah.
But yeah.
Out of hand there.
It's not a safe.
Yeah.
And why?
If the spiritual realm controls the physical realm,
the malevolent entities don't want it, obviously,
because they want it to go south or bad.
But now you're at a point.
Let me say that again.
Now, meaning now, meaning this era,
you're at a point where the benevolent spiritual side is tired of you also,
and they don't want to see that put in.
So now you've got the good guys, let's say third grade level here.
Good guys, bad guys against you.
Right?
Right.
Stop watching the Saturday.
So imagine like from the Saturday, more what they call Saturday morning cartoons,
the superheroes, you know, you've got the villains and the superheroes, right?
Imagine the villains and the superheroes against you.
That's where you're at right now, folks.
So set yourself apart.
And, yeah, this will be discovered.
We'll be able to go into this in much greater depth in the future if you want
sightings and references and where to look for it.
But you've got to stop reading into it.
I've gotten a couple of comments, and not many, that, you know,
Greek, you sound like such and such or such, you know, this group.
Or you sound like it.
And I'm like, okay, let me go assess that.
And I'm like, not at all.
How did this person come up with that?
Well, reading into it.
Again, when people experience something through their senses,
the mind works so fast, what do you call it, involuntarily,
autonomously, that when you're taking in information or sensory things,
that you are trying to compare them to previous experiences in light speed,
rapid fashion, beyond light speed, it's instant.
And right now, I've noticed with most people,
it's gotten to the point where close enough is it, right?
If it sounds close to this, that's what it is.
That's what this guy is saying.
Just like this guy.
It's not even close in most cases.
So this is one of the pitfalls of reading into it.
Again, when you watch a movie on biblical stuff, you're like, oh, yeah.
Yeah, this I saw.
Yeah, I've heard about this.
I saw the movie.
Yeah, they don't say I saw the movie because it sounds ridiculous.
And then when they go and look at the text, they say, oh,
this is the part that I saw in the movie.
And it's not there.
They think it's there.
They keep reading.
Yeah, and they're not really paying any attention.
Yeah, it's a programming.
It's processing information through a faulty program.
Yeah, and virtually no operating system.
Or a virtual operating system that changes.
Imagine going to a computer every day,
and the operating system is different or no operating system.
This is how most people at large are operating.
No pun intended.
So there's nothing.
By the way, folks, let's just say, let's just be really forthright about this.
When you hear about making the world better, there's nothing to make better, folks.
It's unrehabilitatable at this point.
It has to go through what it has to go through, and then it's going to be redone.
And in the meantime, you set yourself apart.
I give an example of in firefighting, firemen, sometimes when they go to a structure,
they don't, if it's too far gone, they don't attempt to extinguish the fire.
Have you heard of that?
You know?
Yeah.
Too far gone.
Prevent the buildings around it from succumbing.
Yep.
Becomes the main concern.
Containment.
Right.
In this case, though, the containment has been put in place, and it's always been in containment.
Yeah.
That's why, for example, one way to rationalize things, not to convince,
but to rationalize the thought, because this is a big subject,
is if you look at things in the past rationally,
like look at the 20th century quote-unquote world's fairs
and what was even memorialized in film and television.
In the 1920s or even turn of the century up until the 50s,
they were telling you folks you're going to have jet packs and flying cars by the year 2000.
Oh, yeah.
You're going to have all this stuff.
Yeah.
You have nothing.
Your cars right now are still 25% efficient, the best cars.
That means that 75% of what you spend to put fuel is just wasted.
Yeah.
You're not going to get any of that.
You're not going into outer space.
None of you are.
Very few of you are, if that at all,
because no one that goes into outer space comes back and reports anything.
They'll just tell you what you've been told in Walt Disney fashion.
You're not.
Forget it.
Just get that out of your mind.
Your medical system is going to be exceedingly toxic because there is no medical system.
It's part of the legal system.
And it's going to go on and on.
Now, you want to make things better?
I'll tell you how there's nothing left to make better.
Children, little babies are pranked by their own parents at large and at wholesale throughout the planet.
Across the board, pretty much.
I'd say all of them.
Very few are not.
And you wonder why you're having problems.
When I mean pranking, look up what that word means.
It's a ludicrous trick done to their own children.
On the other hand, let's look at this.
If the future of mankind is reliant on the children,
there is no future because seemingly, especially in English-speaking countries,
all the children have been turned into goats.
Think about that.
What is a young goat called?
That would be a kid.
Yeah.
Oh, Greek, that doesn't matter.
That's just what we say.
Well, yeah, I know, because you don't say what you mean and mean what you say.
So look at these things, folks, objectively.
Look at, you know, a thousand years ago, public structures were built to last a thousand years,
and many are still here, that were not deliberately destroyed.
A hundred years ago, if you look at some of the skyscrapers that were built at the turn of the 20th century,
are still around.
Well, right now, when they're building these massive structures,
guess what their life expectancy is, folks?
Want to say 20 years?
It's pretty accurate.
Go look it up.
Go look up all these large towers that are being put up now, or have been put up in the past decade or so.
25-year life expectancy.
Is there something going on here?
I mean, this is obvious stuff, folks.
And one of the obvious things that I like to poke fun at this society for
is, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
You want to make the world a better place, huh?
What do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls?
That sounds kind of crazy, man.
Well, let's just put that together, or let's take it apart.
What is the word cannibal?
Yeah.
So that's a good place to start.
What is the word cannibal?
It's an old Chaldean Hebrew term, meaning, like Latin encompasses various languages,
Chaldean Hebrew encompasses languages of the Mesopotamic region.
The priests' religious order were called the Qahans.
And they had told the people to worship the balls, which are the lords.
Even today, how many times have you heard people say,
I was brought to the Lord, I love the Lord, I worship the Lord.
I don't know what they're talking about, and neither do they.
Actually, I do know what they're talking about, but they don't.
Now, the Lord is the ball, let's say, and the priest is the Qahan.
The Qahan would say the way you worship the ball is by bringing a child
and sacrificing him and eating a small portion of the child.
That's why eating human flesh is called Qahan ballism or cannibalism.
Still today, this word is being used.
That's why when you go somewhere and they are the priest or minister of the Lord,
that is nicknamed cannibal.
You guys still flock to him, millions and billions of people adhere to this.
That's undeniable.
Whether they say what they mean or know about it or whatever is irrelevant,
we're not here to defend them or poke fun at them or make excuses.
That's just a fact.
Now, that's why the eating of human flesh is called cannibalism.
It's the priest of the Lord.
It's literally what it means.
They had a proclivity towards conical hats as well.
Yes.
Now, when the parents went home and the child was missing,
the other children would say, where's our brother?
Where's our sister?
So the altar that was administered where this was done,
let's call them altar boys or girls,
they would assemble an effigy or something of a child known as a doll.
They tell the parents when you return home to the rest of the family,
you give them this doll to take the place of the child.
So now you know where dolls come from, folks, being given to children.
It doesn't matter whether you grew up playing with dolls or you like playing
with dolls or grandma played with dolls, or it's always been that way.
It doesn't matter.
We're just giving you the facts, folks.
So I don't know about making it better so far.
Does it sound like things are going to get better?
I don't think so.
Now, obviously, such a horrendous act didn't go over very well,
especially when the people were promised prosperity and they didn't get it
for doing these things.
So they said, let's do a parody of this event.
And the next child in line, we'll put him in a high chair,
give him a pointy hat like we wear, and we'll bake a loaf of sweet bread
and put lights in it and tell the child to make a wish of prosperity,
blow the lights out, and to show that it works,
everyone attending the ceremony brings a present for the child.
When I read that, I kind of hung around in the mind for about six months
until I figured out that's the birthday cake celebration origin.
So if you want to know if you're going to hell in a handbasket,
so to speak, no matter how many smartphones you have in your back pocket,
go to the nearest shop and ask them if they serve birthday cakes
or can I buy a birthday cake or anything like that.
And if they say yes, you're not doing so well,
at least from the divine point of view.
And now you know why the good and the good guys and the bad guys
are against you.
Yes, you, you, humanity at large.
Now, by the way, I want to bring up a little footnote here
because very often people say,
are you in the Jehovah's Witness Protection Program?
Now, what happens when certain ideas like this are grasped on a group,
a crowd mentality forms around it,
it's quickly infiltrated and another organization built around it.
That's what your Jehovah's Witnesses are, by the way.
If you ever met anyone that was in that organization,
yeah, greet Gustave Le Bon and you will see that as a perfect fit.
And usually, I shouldn't say this too much about them, but yeah,
once they're in, they're never out.
That mentality that requires to be in that group never escapes them.
Even though they leave the group, they still keep that on.
It's really sad to say with most religions,
but especially I've noticed with that particular group,
for some reason there's an entity attached to it, which I can't explain.
But we're not any, nothing like that.
There are many aspects of many things.
Again, like there's a benevolent label or facade that's put up,
but they're all malevolent, all of them.
So set yourself apart.
And if you're interested in the gods, plural, with the hierarchy,
and there's, by the way, let's just give the secret right now.
What makes the chief god, the almighty, the chief god?
Very simple, folks. He's not subject to death.
Death is subject to him, in fact.
Correct. And all the others are subject to death.
But think about that, too, on that. It's very simple.
Stop watching television. Stop going to these sex temples.
I'm not saying stop going to these sex temples.
Actually, they're very powerful.
You know what I'm talking about.
They have steeples and crucifixes and things and pews.
But the next time you walk into these religious places,
what do you think all the seats are there for?
Something that's going, a show that's going on in the front.
Just explained it to you, folks.
All of this right now might be insulting and offensive to some,
but I assure you that most of you will be wiping the floor
with all these things in the future.
The truth is often insulting.
Yes, because they're not seeking the truth.
See, people who don't seek the truth are easily offended.
There's an old saying that said,
never talk about politics or religion because you will offend the ignorant.
If you're seeking the truth, you cannot be offended.
Now, the hardest part about that is that people don't want to admit
they've been defrauded or been involved in a malevolent organization,
albeit they consider themselves to be good, quote-unquote, good people.
Right?
They don't want to admit that.
And that's okay.
You don't have to admit it, but you should definitely act on it.
And act on it not in a way like anything is going to change,
but act on it to insulate yourself from it.
That's the problem that people don't understand
is they think that action is social.
It's personal, meaning to yourself.
And if half the world did that and helped one person,
then everything's taken care of.
But it's not going to happen.
You still have quite an epic to go through in the next decade.
It's going to be quite interesting to watch.
And the level of deception, it's not going to be bad, by the way.
It's going to be actually quite good.
What's going to be happening is that you are going to have a perfect,
nearly perfect society on this planet.
That's what's good about it.
The deception is that you're going to be told that it's going to last a thousand years
and you're all going to believe it.
It's only going to last a few years, a few, three or four.
So, yeah.
And also, don't be impressed by large numbers, man.
Anything in creation is in large numbers.
The number of grains of sand on the beach, stars in the sky,
cells in the body, people on the earth, species of animals, insects,
the creators always use large numbers.
And also, don't be impressed with what mankind is doing.
They were given knowledge on how to work with stone, metal, chemistry.
Yes, you were given that.
There's no such thing as a Stone Age or a Bronze Age or an Iron Age.
You had stone societies, iron societies, bronze societies, so forth.
And when you're told about cavemen and Neanderthal men,
those are people that had a lifespan of five, six, seven hundred years.
This has been proven out by forensic dentists and pathologists,
and they were told to not talk about it.
And all those jaw bones and things were set in plastine with wide brows and things
to make them look more ape-like, and you're all being lied to,
to be made, felt insignificant.
Because if you did come from apes,
why do you have webbing between your toes and fingers and apes don't?
I thought you were supposed to come out of the water, not go back into the water.
You're being pranked, folks, not by some of academia, all of academia.
You're being pranked, not by some of the religious people, but all the religious people.
You're being pranked, folks, by not some of the attorneys, but all the attorneys.
You're being pranked across the board.
Sorry.
I don't know if it's bad news or good news, but just take it as objectivity.
And the pranking goes on.
Like we said earlier, pay attention.
Children are being pranked by their own parents,
who tend to have the position of God to them.
The parents are your God until you realize there is another higher power.
You're being pranked by your gods while you're still in swaddling clothes.
Yeah, that's a right start in this world, isn't it?
So, and I still see it going on by young parents and old parents.
I see parents that have very young children, they're young themselves,
and they're pranking the hell out of their children.
Yep, lying to them and everything.
So, yeah, there's nothing to make better.
Just live it through.
Like I say, man up, get strong.
You know, all this stuff they tell you about fear being disabling,
fear is based on how strong your mind is or your spirit and your skill level.
If you've got no skills and you've got a weak mind or a weak spirit,
you're subject to fear.
And there you have it.
Learn how to love.
Be clear.
If you don't have clarity, seek it.
And by the way, your law comes from your God.
I'm not making that up, folks.
If you don't have a God, then you believe in the laws of the state.
Well, fine, the state is your God and April Fool's is your holiday.
And the state, by the way, has a patron or matron deity.
They put it in your face all the time.
Look at their buildings.
They have the statues there, and they'll tell you what it is, and they'll tell you.
It's a God.
Right now you're under the revived goddess religion, Justice, Themis, D.K.
I don't know about them telling you that it is a God.
They'll acknowledge it, but they don't come out and they're not out there preaching it
as though they're not preaching it for what it is.
Nope.
Every nation, bar none, every group of people has a patron or matron deity, period.
Whether you believe in it or not, know it or not, is irrelevant.
That is the report back to the mothership.
If you land on a planet and see what's going on, like what's going on here,
that's a very simple notation that is about as accurate as accurate can be.
So what do you know about these revived religions?
And if the answer is nothing, yes, you're in good company.
Can much be known about them?
Yes.
So do what you've got to do in the meantime.
I think we pulled a song.
I don't know.
We've got about a few minutes left.
We're thinking of playing something for you folks, audible entertainment.
Yeah, a little bit, and we'll see.
We've got about eight minutes.
Typically we go to the four-minute mark, 54, and we've got two minutes or so.
I was thinking, anything else, Seth, you want to put in?
And maybe just cue it up and bring it in.
Bring in as much of it as you want.
I would say, again, that if you were interested in hearing what comes next,
to check out uncommonradio.com because as that comes to fruition and it begins,
that will be the easiest place to find it.
So www.uncommonradio.com.
Other than that, yeah, here's something a little bit different.
♪♪♪
♪♪