Greetings and once again, this is Uncommon Sense with the Greek and Seth Michael.
Today, Seth Michael will be joining us in the second hour and welcome everyone.
And this is also on American Freedom Radio and uncommonradio.com.
You'll also see there is a Ustream if you so choose to catch it that way.
And also there are some archives on American Freedom Radio.
And again, for everyone that's listening, remember everyone that is involved in bringing you –
everything that you hear on American Freedom Radio requires your support.
So please keep that in mind and you know what I mean by that.
So again, hello everyone and let's just get right to things.
And the things we like to discuss are things that are uncommon.
And what could that be?
Guess what?
It's the obvious.
What does that mean?
Well, what is tangible?
What can we base things on or what are things based on?
And it seems like this has escaped humanity in wholesale.
So one of the purposes of doing this broadcast, if one could call it such,
is to probably bring things to mind or bring things to recognition
and maybe provoke some inquiry to the listener.
And by the way, we just have about five listeners and that's all we need.
Anyway, that seems to be the small little bit that is probably required to hear something
and maybe chew on it for a little while and maybe the word will get around.
But again, just to bring up the concept of things that I like to discuss
and Seth as well and anyone else that likes to listen to these kinds of things,
is that probably one of the last things that is left for mankind to discover is what is obvious.
Now, what's interesting about discussing the obvious is keeping sort of a perspective.
It might sound philosophical.
It might sound critical.
But if one says that man has completely descended into materialism, that might sound kind of harsh.
But, you know, let's keep that in the back of the mind.
You know, when you listen to people discussing things, they always discuss it from a materialistic point of view,
whether it's nutrition, whether it's scientific things, even philosophical things.
Metaphors are given in a material sense.
But yet when we look at information and inquiring on what things are about,
are we being told the truth about this matter or so,
sometimes they are slightly immaterial or intangible in that sense.
And we require upon communication perhaps things that have been memorialized from the past.
So we don't make mistakes or let's say or maybe short that term for a second,
but maybe so we don't have to rediscover things that are really in front of us.
And this approach seems to be very uncommon.
Like, for example, now is a time of seasonal change across the planet.
You know, let's say in one part of the world it's going into spring and pretty much full force
and the other part of the world is in fall, you know, going from a cold to a warmer season
and the other place is going from a warm to a cold season.
And what's interesting about this seasonal change,
it's not necessarily reciprocal where you have winter on one side of the world and summer on the other.
It's sort of an equalization time period where it is possible to have the same temperatures
or temperament across the entire planet for what may be common for a few days or so
where it's fall on one side of the world and spring in another.
The temperatures and temperament even of the people seem to be equal.
So these things we call seasons tend to not be discussed very much unless one partakes in agriculture
and even then, you know, when we consider the agriculture being mechanized to the point of, again, chemical oblivion or materialism,
you know, when we say agriculture, we mean the changing of seasons.
So consider, folks, when you see the change of seasons that it's more than just the mercury rising or dropping.
And I like to bring that up facetiously because it's interesting how the temperature measurement doesn't tell you anything about quality.
It's actually the expansion and contraction of this liquid form of metal called mercury, which is actually toxic, by the way.
So, well, we would like to discuss things that are perhaps leaning on the quality and the nature of things.
But perhaps to go back to the concept of the seasonal change and it being springtime and fall,
let's say in another part of the world, because I don't want to negate our friends that live on the other part of the world.
But for this part of the world, it's going into springtime.
And springtime is regeneration and a planting of things.
And let's consider mostly the planting or startups.
And what's interesting is the starting of things.
Perhaps, let's say, could it be a planting of seed?
Could it be an event?
Could it be a thought?
It's a cultural drive to start.
This is all tied into the agricultural cycle, the agricultural nature.
So when people are trying to reckon sense or rationale out of events that are happening,
whether it be economic, geopolitical, social, and in many levels also things that are put up by the entitled classes,
you know, the legal society, the scientific society, the religious societies,
you'll see that spring is a building up or, I'm sorry, it's a planting,
where summer would be the building up and fall is the harvest, not only of events but of ideas.
You see it within the culture and you also see it within the activities of all of these little groups.
I call them little groups because the main group is humanity as a whole.
People enjoy doing whatever they find to be their lot in life and they have to inquire amongst the specialists
when they want to go outside of the field of their personal interest.
So also watching what is going on from that perspective, what is being planted and discerning.
For example, one way of, you know, what am I talking about?
You know, one way of looking at it is how many times have you heard, for example,
in the media discussion of an impending financial collapse in the midsummer?
Well, not good and reliable information because typically those types of things happen in the fall.
The summer is a building up period.
So discussing the seasonal changes beyond just flowers blooming or it being hot or leaves changing color in the autumn,
it is a cycle, it's a grand cycle.
It's cosmic when it comes to surface-dwelling earth inhabitants.
You know, the interesting thing here also, just to go back to the surface-dwelling earth inhabitant,
in a sense, is the body, you know, how the human body, let's say,
or any body of a living creature is very susceptible to its environment.
And many people have discussed and heard about making balance and the concept of what is health or healthful.
And it seems, again, to be discussed in the nature of stark materialism,
almost as if you're discussing something in a chemical laboratory.
You know, like vitamins are good for you.
This chemical does this and this little bug does that.
And again, the seasons need to be considered when one is looking at harmony in their environment.
And one thing we like to discuss, let's say we, the colloquial we, would be perhaps eating seasonally as well.
And you wouldn't believe how much commentary it can be heard on people having a state of discomfort
or not well-being during the seasonal change.
And it seems to coincide with seasonal changes.
People have what they call colds, flus, not feeling well under the weather.
And it's always attributed to some materialistic, would you say excuse at this point?
But what's interesting is if we consider the harmony that is sort of required to maintain a healthful condition,
why aren't the seasonal changes considered?
And, of course, if anyone's listened to what might be dubbed as Greek speak,
there's a concept of eating not only seasonally but eating from climate sources
that would enable harmony in the environment that you're in.
For example, if you're in a cold climate and you are eating food that is grown in the tropics,
could it be that that food will adjust your body to living in the tropics while you're in a cold climate?
And your body might say, well, this isn't correct, and you have mucus and lack of levity.
By the way, lack of levity just means you want to be horizontal.
These are really formative things to discuss.
And it seems to be there's been a big divergence in the distraction because of man's descent into materialism,
how simple things can be.
And it's not necessarily a cure-all,
but it's interesting how when one has a discussion with those that do feel discomfort
or quote-unquote illness during the seasonal changes, with even the slightest examination,
if you ask them about their quote-unquote diet,
I don't like that word diet because it has D-I-E in it, but nonetheless,
you'll see that they have typically a very chemical perspective or this form of bioterrorism perspective.
And what I call bioterrorism is the idea that the scientists are terrorizing the public,
that these little critters known as bacterias and viruses are the cause of disease,
you know, strictly and nothing else.
So anyway, that is a form of terrorism in a sense where you inflict terror on the victim.
And people are just running around not paying any attention to what is obvious.
One thing to consider, folks, and this is not going to be a two-hour talk on this subject,
but just throw it in there, might as well.
Jumping into the concept that little bacteria and things like that create disease solely renders all refrigeration useless
because we use refrigerators to put these little things into a dormant state,
and people are always giving the excuse that it's the wintertime that they catch these little buggers.
So something to think about.
Let's just be sensible to some degree.
But in essence, sticking with the concept of being seasonal, what could that mean?
And what could support that?
It doesn't have to be just agricultural in the sense it has to be also viewed from its formative sense.
You know, and typically when we discuss spring, it's a time of planting.
Not much is seen when things are planted.
You might have a fallow or just a plain dirt field that's been plowed,
and even though all of the things that need to be done in the springtime are done,
it doesn't look like anything has changed.
So keeping that in mind, if anyone is inquiring, whether alternative or mainstream media,
about geopolitical events, economic events, social events, judicial events,
just about every aspect, the scientific community, every community,
you realize that they also follow this unknowingly.
You're sort of locked into this, these cycles,
and the more you acknowledge and know that the cycle is happening,
the more sense and rationale it puts behind what you're absorbing,
let's say through the mind, the eyes and the ears, if they work, meaning being able to discern.
So again, when you hear about breaking down events,
they're usually reserved for the fall or the autumn.
The building up events are basically for the summer,
and the planting and the new things that are initially set in place happen in the spring,
and that is basically the season right now.
So from that point of view, very often when you turn on what's called media,
it's something called the news, it's a television show called the news
or a radio show is called the news,
and it perhaps would behoove anyone to approach these things efficiently.
What I mean by that is how many times have you spoken to anyone
that got worked up into a lather about a quote-unquote story they just heard?
And one way to rationalize what you're hearing is look at the seasonal effects of it.
Again, bringing up the metaphor again,
if you hear of a financial collapse in the spring or the summer,
it's unlikely it's going to happen.
And dare anyone go investigate all of the, let's say,
main economic Western world financial collapses.
They always happen in what they call late September or October of some sort.
And if anyone, any of you history buffs, yes,
because if you want to buff that thing that I call history,
most people today believe that everything sprang into creation 100 years ago.
Yes.
Why do I say that?
Because any discussion, whether academic or not,
people can't go any further than that.
And when they do, it seems to be based on some kind of urban myth.
Very little is inquired about any time before us.
When I say us again, I mean it loosely.
So yeah, just in case anyone doesn't realize,
there is a history that goes more than 100 years.
So let's pretty much think about inquiring about things.
Give me an example.
I don't like to bring up specific points that are in the current events unless I
get them more than three times from three or four separate different individuals.
And one thing I'm going to bring up,
which I've received from several individuals,
is that something about a gold yuan or renminbi in Chinese currency replacing
the dollar or the Chinese not using the dollar or Chinese policies with U.S.
Treasury and this term, the dollar being used.
And what's interesting about that is, and I won't say anymore, is folks,
you've got to research what a credit-based economy is.
Now I know no one wants to do that.
You're not going to be popular.
You're not going to make friends.
But if you have any interest in anything that is regarding financial,
get a good grip or even a loose grip or stick your pinky or small toe,
not even big toe, into looking or inquiring on what a credit-based economy is.
It's not a debt-based economy.
You're told that it is because, you know, like little children,
tell them little stories.
They'll believe anything.
Their child is an immature.
But essentially it is a credit-based economy.
Start digging into that a little bit and see how unpopular you are because the
closer you get to the truth, any truth, the less popular you are.
And that's where I like to bring up an old philosopher.
I believe it was Plato.
He says that a friend to all is a friend to none.
So the concept here is if you don't mind making your life miserable,
go ahead and study what things are based on and what things really are as they're
memorialized.
And if you like making things up and believing stories, then just, you know,
you'll probably be happy and have lots of people in agreement and you'll have a
concordance reality built around yourself.
Concordance just means that something is true because everyone thinks it's that,
right, this consensus.
And you'll be able to relish in plausible deniability and just move along and
just go along existing.
But researching and looking at things from an uncommon perspective will not make
you happy.
But then again, one should ask themselves, would I rather know some truth and be
maybe astounded, surprised, or a little unhappy about it?
Or would I rather just be in this concordant illusion about what everyone says it
is and agree with them and be happy?
So this is, again, a decision people have to make on their own.
But we won't waste time telling you what people think.
We will spend time on maybe showing you what you can see without really thinking
very much.
You know, what we like to do is say we, again, because Seth is usually with the
Greek here.
He'll be coming on the second hour and eventually we'll probably be taking calls
and also looking at input while we are on the air.
But the idea here that, as I started off saying, that the last thing left for
mankind to discover is what is obvious is not only quantitative but qualitative.
You know, for example, a couple of points that the Greek always brings up is,
like for example, you know you can't keep time with the Gregorian calendar.
It's essentially loosely called the Pope's work schedule.
You know, if your concept of recording events known as time is solely done from
using something called January through December or Monday through Friday with numbers
on charts and things you call dates, that is not a timepiece, folks.
I'll take a three-second pause before I continue.
It's not a timepiece.
It's a work schedule.
Yep.
Now, there's nothing wrong with it.
It's there for communication purposes.
But what I mean by it's a work schedule, it's arbitrary.
It's not based on anything.
Yeah, they tell you it goes about the Earth going around the sun and that and all that.
Yeah, show me.
It doesn't work.
You ever hear of a leap year?
You know, what if you date something what they call February 29th?
What happens next year?
It's gone?
Eh, it doesn't quite work that way, guys and gals and any other furry creatures that are listening.
The point here is are you paying attention?
Not to stay on that subject very much, but if you observe a certain date on that thing
they call the calendar, you notice how it's a different day of the week every year?
That's all I'm going to say about it.
Anybody paying attention?
Anyway, the other thing is people are making demands.
We want change.
We want this.
We want that.
Well, how are you going to do that in a comfortable, helpful way?
You know, the other thing I like to mention is, you know, everyone does whatever they like to do,
and they go to these entitled classes or specialists when they want to get something
or learn about something, right?
Even dentists need a dentist to work on their own teeth, or, you know, a haircutter
or a barber might have another barber cut their hair, so one hand washes the other.
We look at other people to fill in the blanks when we develop a blank,
but how are you going to do that in a helpful way, in a calm, cool, collected, rational way?
And what I mean by that is this is addressing all of humanity.
Where are you?
Are you paying any attention?
You ever notice when you heat or cool a room, the heat rises to the ceiling
and the cold goes to the floor, so you have a hot head and cold feet, right?
I thought we were supposed to have a cool head and warm feet,
but if we look at the natural environment, when it's hot in the valley,
it's cold at the mountaintop because perhaps in nature the cold is verified
and it rises and the heat descends, just like it should be in all biological systems,
but when you're creating that difference in heat and cold using degenerative chemical decomposition,
right, like you have a rising heat and a descending cold,
contrary to what's in the natural growth environment, and no one is paying attention.
In other words, why aren't the people on this planet knocking on the door of their heating
and cooling engineers and asking them for devices that heat or cool their homes,
buildings, cars, boats or whatever in the same way that nature does,
so you have a cool head and warm feet?
Why has this escaped everyone?
You can go on and on and on about simple things like this.
We've talked about the human body, for lack of a better term.
I call it the container.
They have this thing, they've convinced people that there is a blood pressure in the body
or a pressure.
Now, you don't have to go to any kind of special inquiry to realize that when you draw a vacuum
on a soft membrane, it kind of shrivels up, doesn't it?
Very much like your fingers and toes in water.
And you don't have to go to any kind of a specialist or anything to realize that when you have a soft membrane
or something and you put pressure in it, it kind of expands like a balloon or something.
So how many times have you looked at your body when it's cold or wet
and do your fingers expand like a frog or do they shrivel up?
Because perhaps there's a little bit of a vacuum in the body that keeps everything together.
And there's people running around even figuratively stating that I'm getting upset,
my blood pressure is rising.
Now, the only way you can evidence blood pressure is if you strap a cuff to a limb of the body
or the arm, inflate the cuff, restrict the flow of blood which moves under a slight vacuum
and then read some kind of diastolic, peristolic, ridiculous shop talk about blood pressure
when they're actually not even looking at blood pressure, they're looking at a zone between beats.
So why are we, anyway, why are we, you know, what's going on here?
Look how obvious things are around you or around us or the surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
What's going on?
You know, how can one make the demands or groups make the demands as they do without first addressing the obvious?
Now, what's interesting is what kind of a culture would actually fully submit to an arbitrary work schedule
that you can't even keep time with and presumably operate as if they are keeping time with it
or not noticing that their well-being can be pretty much dependent on a cool head and warm feet
yet they're totally oblivious to the way they're functioning in their living spaces with a hot head and cold feet.
How can this be?
How can there be an arrangement where people agree that these little critters called bugs and bacteria
are causing disease where on one hand they profess that and on the other hand they all have refrigeration
and depend on refrigeration to keep these creatures in a state of dormancy.
So how can they, if they're in a state of dormancy when it's cold, be contagions?
It just doesn't make any sense.
Yet people are professing all these things which are contrary to what they can see around them.
Another aspect, folks, to consider, very stark, did you know that there's not a religion on the planet,
bar none, that does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to?
Not a one.
Regardless if it's spanned the world, going from east to west and back around,
no religion on the planet at all, bar none, does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to
in context or at all.
Fascinating to see that.
So how can people say they're spiritual? Based on what?
Things that they make up as they go along?
Well, you don't need a book, Greek.
Well, okay, maybe then you don't care about those that came before you.
And maybe you want to just invent things because you're modern.
So what's uncommon here is what should be common.
Stop and think for a moment.
Actually, most people think they get into a lot of trouble,
so you've got to really stop and think and stop and think and stop and think.
Don't jump into too many things too quickly.
Again, this time of change, just to go back to it, regarding the seasons.
What's being planted now?
It's springtime.
Okay, this is when things are planted.
And like I mentioned earlier, it's not only purely agricultural.
It's also based on the way the cultures of humanity operate.
In other words, what is being planted?
Let's look at it maybe perhaps a different way.
You ever notice that when a lot of noise is being made, it tends to attract attention?
Could that be what's being reported on?
It's just noise.
Could it be that the real stuff is happening where it's quiet?
Does a forest make noise when it grows?
You see?
So the thing here is during this time period,
it would be sort of advisable to when one partakes in what's called media of any kind
and is inquiring about any subject of any kind,
might want to start maybe paying less attention where it's really noisy,
like, hey, look here, and look where it's really quiet.
Because that's where when the planting is done, you don't really see much.
And this is what spring is about.
Now, one aspect of spring, which from the ancient point of view, is when wars were started.
It was a time when the sovereigns went out to war.
And that's another concept.
You know, there's the concept of war.
And one day mankind will realize that war is a sport.
So I like to call it, you know, world sport one, world sport two.
And now people are talking about world sport three.
You're not going to get a world war three because things are happening.
So that will not be conducive to that.
And it is possible to know the future, folks, if you start understanding cycles
and if you stop ignoring those that came before you.
And knowing the future is not necessarily predicting the future because it's already been kind of laid out.
A practical materialistic approach would be if anyone embarks on an endeavor,
whether it's in cooking or construction or machining or going somewhere,
they have a pretty good idea of what will happen next with all of these simple processes.
But it seems to fall apart when we look at it at a geopolitical level
or at a mass social or cultural level.
All of a sudden it's taboo to not be able to discuss about what can happen next
or what will happen next based on the repeating of cycles
and also based on the anomalous nature of what's called prophecy.
And this is an interesting thing.
This comes up often and I usually tell people,
if anyone tells you that the prophecies can be changed,
well then those are not prophecies and they can't be addressed as such.
And every culture has them.
So the interesting aspect there is what are these prophecies?
They're anomalous events that are sort of not part of the regular seasonal clockwork,
the regular social repeating of things.
And that's where most people fail when they start bringing these things up.
And I can assure you right now publicly,
no one, very few if any out there have even been able to loosely touch on anything
with any accuracy about what's coming in the future.
And part of it is because there's very little or no discussion
on even the effects of the seasons on events,
whether they're social or personal or cultural and such.
So these things need to be considered and they're so simple.
You don't need a specialist.
You don't need anyone to read into anything or read out of what they believe
or that they heard from someone else.
There is a simple, let's say, pattern that is from archetypal things,
archetype meaning things that are the beginning or start of,
that seem to have been missed.
And that's why I like to perhaps today bring up the concept of the seasonality
and maybe strike that a little bit more.
Because the anomalies to these natural clockworks are what's called the prophecies.
And sorry, folks, very few people on this planet at this point
will be able to touch them with any accuracy because of the level of lack of inquiry
or correspondence to see how the seasons affect things
and also the lack of inquiry into the accuracy of what they're reading
and paying attention.
So the concept of things being prophetic, as you can see,
are being misused and very simply because it seems like no one can keep time anymore.
So anything that requires time marking or any sort of juxtaposition or reference
has been lost.
It's kind of like going to a construction site and seeing a bewildered carpenter
asking him, why are you so upset?
He says, I've been cutting this board twice and it's still too short.
So there's this concept that just because you're making busy work that you're doing,
you're going in the right direction.
You're not, as a society, in terms of inquiring and using what you've got.
So act with efficiency.
Be efficient in what you do.
Don't waste time, meaning you do what you like, but wasting time would be,
how many times have you heard people prepping for a geopolitical event that never comes?
So these things, understanding the seasons, understanding things to come
and how things operate makes one more efficient in what they're doing.
So I would say efficiency is really the key to anything.
And it's, believe it or not, uncommon.
Even the automobiles that have been around for 100 plus years are touted,
the best ones right now are touted to being 25% efficient.
That means that 75% of the fuel you put in it is wasted into heat.
And that is an interesting metaphor when you compare it to everything else that's going on.
So what do we see about the seasonal changes?
Again, just to perhaps be focused on the northern part of the world, let's just say,
could it be springtime, things planted require water?
Someone requested that I discuss that.
Well, you know, Greek, why don't you talk about water?
You know, you do a lot of work with it.
And what's interesting was one starts to discuss water and go into that subject.
First thing you do is try to inquire where it's easy to get information.
And what's interesting about that is jumping around and discussing water.
You know, that's all it is.
But if you're not going to jump around, it seems like people have come into agreement that it's H2O.
And when you discuss it as H2O, I say, wow, okay, if water is really H2O,
then why does a bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air where it shouldn't?
That sounds like a ridiculous statement.
According to the material scientists, it should.
You know, the molecular weight of water should be roughly 18,
and the molecular weight of air is roughly 28, 29.
So we're not getting proper answers here if we're using their methodology.
Something very unusual about this thing we called water.
And even metaphorically, when you water an idea, water seems to impart growth to things.
But, again, speaking on the material side of it, you know, the tangible, clear liquid,
it seems to be appropriate to discuss water when you discuss the planting of things.
And just simply that someone requested that I did discuss the simplicity of water from a simple point of view.
There is so much being discussed about it, and it's hard to say that it's untrue, but it's not true enough.
What is true, though, is that what makes water unusual is that it's the only material that once it gets cooled down beyond a certain point,
it starts to expand again. Right.
If anyone has put water in the freezer, notices the container could rupture or burst.
So it has a very unique characteristic from that point of view,
and also that it's transparent and pretty much dissolves everything in it.
And it provides life and growth aspects to pretty much everything as well as cleaning aspects.
So good water would require having water in the state that it likes to be in where its quality is the highest.
And where is that and how do you achieve that?
And very simply, one way to start with it discussing that subject is temperature.
Water is its densest at about 39 degrees Fahrenheit or four degrees Celsius.
So that means that if the temperature goes above or below that, the water expands.
Just like let's say the human body being healthy at ninety eight point six Fahrenheit.
If the temperature rises more than that or lowers more than that, the body doesn't feel healthy.
So the water body prefers a thirty nine degree Fahrenheit or four degrees Celsius point.
And when you get the water to that point, it develops a maturation.
It matures and it relaxes.
And that is a point where anyone can, let's say regardless what water source you have,
experience a rise in quality in water simply by keeping it in the dark and letting it come to that temperature for a short period of time, preferably overnight.
And what's interesting about that is coincidentally most refrigeration that's offered is in that range at thirty nine Fahrenheit or four degrees Celsius.
So when water is discussed, it's astounding how little it's discussed that simply leaving water in a dark,
cool place overnight or for an interval of time will raise its quality.
This is not discussing the chemical aspect of what's dissolved in the water that you may or may not prefer,
but just the actual quality of the water body.
If that can be recalled and remembered, that water likes to be in a cool and dark place would raise its quality,
would pretty much bring the entire interaction of humankind with the water body or water substance to a new level.
And it's astounding how little this is discussed.
There are thousands, if not millions, of people and sites and information bits that are thrown out there
and that fail to bring up the simple point and anyone can try it.
Now, what's interesting, contrary to what I said to what you will see in the stark material reality,
is that if anyone goes out to purchase what they call water in the bottled form,
you notice that they're in clear containers exposed to light and not at that temperature.
Only the finest quality waters or liquids are kept in containers that obscure light and in some sort of refrigeration.
So this is a very interesting, very, very simple aspect.
And perhaps as Uncommon Sense continues, we might give more water bits,
because there's then the aspect of chemically and qualitatively treating the water beyond that,
which is very simple to do as well.
But for now, folks, I was asked to kind of bring up, what about water?
Just imagine being able to increase the quality of your water by simply considering temperature and light.
So lack of light and having it as close to 4 degrees Celsius or 39 degrees Fahrenheit for a period of time,
so the water reaches what Victor Schauberger called the anomaly point, where water is its densest.
So it's a real simple approach to anything that will give you an immediate quality change.
Now, obviously, if we go back and discuss, well, you can't keep time with the Pope's work schedule,
what's a real simple quality approach to that?
There isn't one.
But you can imagine that if time is going to be based on something,
it should be on something that doesn't change and isn't arbitrary, folks.
And that's the sun, the moon, and the stars.
That's how time was always kept.
Now, the other thing we mentioned regarding heat rising and cold descending,
well, probably prevents one from keeping a cool head and warm feet.
That's going to be a little harder to do with your entitled engineers and scientists.
You're not going to quite get that, perhaps, in this society.
But you must maintain a cool head and warm feet to promote a healthful condition.
Go figure.
But no one at all is inquiring to the entitled engineers.
And what I mean by entitled is they have social rank, seemingly, over the common folk.
And the common folk are not holding them to any sense of responsibility to provide them with the technology,
providing the common folk, let's say, with a technology that's conducive to a healthful condition.
Let's say a cool head and warm feet.
With all of your technological advances, you still ignored or still do ignore the basic premise
that one should have a cool head and warm feet,
evidenced by the way you heat and cool all of your living spaces,
and the lack of inquiry and demand.
So when people come and bring up topics of concern,
whether they be cultural, geopolitical, religious, social, what have you,
I'm like, but you're doing it with a hot head and cold feet.
Why don't you go request from your entitled engineers ways of perhaps maintaining a cool head
and warm feet in your living spaces, and maybe that might be a good place to start.
And I guess I'm going to drive this home to pretty much show it as something that's obvious that's being negated.
So if the more obvious closer to home that concerns your health and well-being is ignored,
do you ever feel like you're being ignored when you're asking about other things perhaps?
You want geopolitical changes and cultural changes, economic and judicial changes,
health changes with your scientific community and medical community.
You're getting really far away from what matters, having a cool head and warm feet,
and there still is no demand on the engineering entitled classes to develop such devices.
Now whether it sounds impossible, whether it sounds probable, is irrelevant.
The inquiry and the demand is not being made.
You've been distracted.
So if there's no concern in keeping headquarters, meaning your mind, your soul,
which is your breath and your body, in fair order, how are you going to manage and request change
in the other things that are way beyond that?
Because no one can negate that the most immediate concern would be one's comfort to a degree or avoiding discomfort.
And again, how are you going to do that with a hot head and cold feet?
Because that's what you're propagating with the way your engineers are giving you devices to heat and cool your living spaces.
So just think about that for a moment.
And was there an element of hypocrisy there?
Quite possibly.
So I don't know, folks.
But that's all pretty much on the concept of spring from a materialistic point of view, and perhaps maybe not.
There's thought aspects and realization aspects behind everything,
whether you want to be materialistic or you want to look at the non-materialistic,
less tangible formative energies that also come through in springtime.
If you want to look at it as a building up period, as being a formative, hearing about things,
well, let's say a planting period that leads to building up,
hearing about things that are breaking down are not rational during this time.
They can happen but are very unlikely.
So leading and living one's life with efficiency might be the thing to consider when we look at the seasons.
So what's uncommon about that?
Well, it's pretty obvious.
That's what makes it uncommon.
There's a lot of discussion about topics that are global in sense, meaning worldly, affecting everyone.
And let's say in a negative way that have been coming across for many years now in many aspects,
whether it's academic or media or religious or whatever.
And it's interesting to see how no matter how much people or these groups are discussing this impending doom,
doom hasn't come yet because it won't, not in the way that it's being discussed.
So the lack of efficiency that humankind is operating in, if that were to be reduced in some way,
that would leave more energy to do other things, perhaps think clearly, perhaps act a little better.
What is better?
Well, you have to figure that out on your own sometimes because very often what we're told is not the best.
So this is going to require some inquiry, again, which we will discuss as this continues,
this venture we call Uncommon Sense.
And, again, we've got about maybe 15 minutes or so, and Seth will be joining us as well.
So, again, this is perhaps the fourth time or so Uncommon Sense has come around,
and we've been wrought with certain tech issues in the past,
and we kind of feel like this is a project that is slowly being launched in terms of gaining momentum
and conveying things that will hold true to the name and what we promise on doing,
which is perhaps what's called Uncommon Sense.
The simplicity of things and leading and living one's life with efficiency might be the thing to be considered,
simply because when we're not being efficient with something, we lose it.
It's considered a loss.
And what's interesting with the concept of being in an information age,
I found that no matter how much this is bestowed on people,
thinking that we are so full of information and easy to access,
tons of information from any subject or just rapidly through this thing that's been thrust upon society
known as the Internet with the silly phones and all these other things and computers and whatever,
where is the discernment on using these things?
Where is the discernment?
Is there discernment on information?
And can the information be vetted?
I hear very much.
I think that from having discussions with folks through the past few years regarding this information age
and things that are going on, people are less excited than they were years ago about it,
because they're saying, well, I know it's junk.
I know it's BS what's on the Internet, but I go there anyway, or I use it for this and I use it for that.
So when you hear these terms or when I hear them, I call them inefficient use of the medium.
And there's been a lot of, I would say, not necessarily social change.
Society hasn't changed much, but they've been numbed down now.
There's a lot of, what do I mean by numbing down?
There's a lot of talk about what's called the dumbing down.
Oh, yeah, society is being dumbed down,
or there's even like documentaries, the dumbing down of America or something,
and there's this dumbing down discussion.
By looking at this kind of closely, you'll see that it's really the numbing down that's going on.
And looking at it even closer, I would say that the majority of the people that are alive today have missed out on the dumbing down.
That began a very long time ago.
What you've been experiencing through this generation or one or two or three or four is the numbing down.
What I mean by the numbing down is the apathetic aspect.
In other words, no matter what is put in front of you, how good or how bad, how truthful or how deceitful,
if one is apathetic or numbed down to it, it will not take effect as it should.
So it seems like the people have not been reacting to the truth of many matters,
and they have not really been reacting so much to the deception of many matters.
And it's this numbing down.
And just to explain that slightly further is, let's say, from the conspiratorial side,
there are a lot of things that are being brought out as people being dubbed as conspiracy theories or conspiracy theorists.
And when you look at the subject matter or the topic involved, it's not that quite difficult to get to the bottom of it,
but they prefer not to.
It's really strange.
Like someone once says, there's no money in the solution.
The money is in the problem.
And I'm not saying the conspiracy theorists exist because of the money,
but it seems like there's an attitude that it's taken that might be branched out from Gustave Le Bon's book, The Crowd,
where in order to get people together under an idea, for everyone to get that idea generally,
that idea is so simplified and mostly oversimplified that it no longer resembles the purpose of the original idea.
Think about that.
So the numbing aspect, you know, if you look at a lot of researchers, you know, they get stuck on a point.
And if anything, concordantly doesn't agree with that point, it's not true or it can't be looked at.
So it's a numbing thing because, folks, it's not in the information.
And also from the deception point of view, what's interesting is now I noticed like there's things called false flag events.
And no matter how severe they're painted, yeah, it'll be in a quote unquote newsworthy story for a day or two.
And then everyone sort of brushes it off like no big deal.
Right. So where is the information affecting the individual and how is information really effective at society at large?
If you see this apathy throughout, it's an interesting thing to see.
Another thing is the extremist views that are abandoned almost immediately when there's a title change or a group of individuals decide that it need not be focused on.
Give an example.
Years ago, someone was felt quite compelled to do some serious survivalist storage, food storage, weapon hoarding type thing because of some comments that were going to destroy Earth and society.
And he was yelling at people that if they didn't do the same as his, he'd shoot them if everything went down and they came asking him for anything.
I approached this individual a couple of years later about his attitude back then.
He says, oh, oh, that's OK. That was then.
Now, now it's different. I'm like, wow, that was a very extremist point of view to take basically on nothing.
It's seemingly. So what's interesting, it's not only this calm, passive apathy towards.
Oh, yeah. Whatever. You know, it doesn't matter. That's your truth or.
Oh, yeah. So they did it again. It's another deception.
No big deal. But it's the extremist aspect as well.
And then it's just seemingly abandoned.
And I find that astonishing. I don't know if there's anything to do with having a hot head and cold feet.
But anyway, so this dumbing down that's being applied still, it's not as much as it was a few years ago.
I believe happened. I use that term loosely.
I believe I don't like to give a belief and opinion has ended a while ago.
And it's been the numbing down period in the 20th century through whatever events you chose.
So choose to inquire about. You know, so this this aspect again, the numbing down, the apathy, going back to it being a seasonal change.
Isn't that interesting how it all applies? I find that the seasonal changes being ignored, not through knowledge or lack of knowledge.
But it seems like there is an apathy, a numbing down of humanity.
And I have said it before on what I call colloquial Greek speak. Why? What's coming?
It's pretty easy for anyone to see. It sounds arrogant when someone says this is coming in the future.
And I expect to you folks, if you ever hear anyone telling you what's coming in the future, I expect you to hold them to it.
Right. Give you an example. There's actually more than an example.
I'll make a statement and I'll claim that every economic commentator, period, out there is doing humanity a disservice.
Every one of them is discussing doom and gloom every month and no one is holding them to it.
As a matter of fact, the more erroneous economic commentators are, it seems that the more their wallet grows through subscriptions and memberships.
It's a direct proportion. It's very interesting.
Every single economic theorist or public pontificate out there is nothing more than a carnival barker claiming doom and gloom.
And none of them, not a one, is discussing the anatomy of a credit-based economy.
They might talk a little bit about gold and silver or the US dollar or the note.
But I am telling you, there is absolutely no substance.
Their value is not any more than the stuff you scrape off the bottom of your shoe.
But anyway, this is all of your economic commentators.
But they love it because they rely on people's ignorance and apathy.
And since they're relying on people's ignorance and apathy, they have discovered that people are very reliable and they're not going to stop what they're doing.
And no one is holding them accountable for what they're saying.
And here's our break and hopefully we'll have Seth Michael in the second hour.
Thank you everyone.
This is Uncommon Sense on American Freedom Radio.
Greetings for the second hour.
Uncommon Sense as usual.
And you're listening to American Freedom Radio and Uncommon Sense or UncommonRadio.com with the Greek and Seth Michael.
I hope Seth is with us on the second hour. If he is, we will get a sonic indication.
Hello.
Hey, how are you Seth? Great.
Yeah, I went ahead first hour, gave our listeners an earful perhaps and welcome.
Thank you.
It's good to be here and to be broadcasting.
Yes.
I'm audible.
I imagine as you can't hear me obviously, so wonderful.
Yeah, I just want to jump in as some of the thoughts.
I'll just let you know if you were not aware of it.
It did speak about how all the financial commentators are really doing a big disservice to the public at large by the way they're discussing things
and they've discovered that the people are ignorant and fearful and they find that to be their hinge point or what they base their commentaries on
and no one is holding them accountable for their rubbish.
And people are still going around screaming about a dollar that's going to collapse and debt and such and such.
And just to bring up some comments in the chat, very valid about where does credit come from, the debt and all these IMF aspects.
And what people fail to realize is that the common person on the street, the public at large,
when they are dealing with anything quote unquote financial, that is all secondary market.
Primary market, the public at large has never even interacted with at all.
And what do I mean by secondary market?
Primary market, the primary market would be the rock concert and the secondary market would be the guy outside selling the T-shirts.
So whenever you're dealing with an entity known as someone from the legal society or a bank outlet, a clerk, a manager, credit card bills, taxing authorities,
those are all secondary to uphold some kind of plausibility that there is money, viable money in the system
where everything that's memorialized about anything financial or economic shows the contrary, that it's credit.
In other words, you're going to function temporarily on something that is based on promises alone until money is brought back.
And because people have totally abandoned the substance, now they are functioning strictly within the promise of the function
and makes it completely lawless and unfounded and not even legal.
And people, when you say this is legal tender, it's not even legal tender.
It's kind of like giving a metaphor.
If you look at any religion on the planet, what they are actually functioning in their traditions is actually considered an abomination in the text that they allegedly subscribe to, totally contrary.
So it's really a bizarre, bizarre aspect.
But in essence, one day we will probably do something about the money system.
But essentially, just to recap, the first hour was about the change of seasons, the planting of spring,
and just again the general numbing down that humanity has been experiencing for a long time and not the dumbing down.
The dumbing down phase is over.
It's all numbing down now, which leads perhaps to something else that people discuss.
I hate to use the phrase new agey.
How many times have you heard that, right?
This is new agey.
People need to take that matter a little more seriously because what was put in place at the end of the 19th century to divert mankind, let's say, from anything tangible or real
and to set him on the path that he's on now of the materialism and such within his modern age happened through that movement.
It's a solipsism.
Is it soliphism or solacism, where nothing matters kind of idea?
Solipsism, where you are the entire universe essentially.
Yeah.
And this total removal of people talking.
How many times have you heard these morons talk about, oh, it's consciousness, man.
It's your intent.
And I mean moron with a capital R.
You got to put the emphasis on that because this is now removing the creature, meaning mankind, from achieving any point of view that's going to be beneficial to anything that he does
and allowed him to be steered and guided by a small entitled group, whether it be known or unknown.
I'm not being a conspiracy theorist here.
And it's been working very, very well.
And one of these things, these new age idiots and conscious and awake and intent people talk about is fear, man.
Oh, they put out this fear.
You know, it's going to get you.
No one is rationalizing this thing they called fear.
And very simple, folks.
If you lack mental fortitude or spiritual fortitude, meaning spiritual or mental strength, and you lack skill.
You're going to be susceptible to different types of fear.
That's all it is.
The idiots that are out there, I'm using strong language because a high level of criminality requires strong language.
And the people out there, and this is not a rant, whether it's mainstream alternative or the man on the street that tells you that this thing called fear porn is going to get you and it's all about fear, is a moron.
Because it has nothing to do with that.
It has to do with taking advantage of your lack of desire to inquire and your maybe unconscious desire to remain lazy.
Let's discuss for a moment fear.
Fear is something that disables the being when that being lacks the mental ability to discern it and also the skill to deal with it.
And the example there, which I believe we mentioned, is if you have no skills at all in how to use a dishrag, a sponge or a mop, the very factor act of a glass of milk falling over is fearful and terrifying.
But if a glass of milk falls over and you have skills with a dishrag, a sponge and a mop, you'll say, no worries.
It's just spilled milk.
You see the point?
So this blanket statement that, oh, it's all just fear.
Fear of what?
What are you talking about?
Who are you addressing?
What?
Where's the venue?
Where's the thought?
Where's the completion?
Where's the actuation?
Fear of what?
Just fear, fear.
And it's the same with love.
They do this with love.
Oh, God is love.
You just need love.
Just got to love.
What are you talking about?
Love.
Define it.
You know, if the National Pedophile Convention or PDAVN, as someone once said, is a more accurate term for these folks.
They have a lot of love, don't they?
These child rapists.
What are you talking about?
Love.
What kind of love?
Where's the quality?
So this is the level.
I spoke about inefficiency earlier.
And there are terms that are, because of the apathetic sense and the numb down, not the dumb down, the numb down aspect.
Oh, fear, man.
You got to have love.
Fear is bad.
Love is good.
It's like, what are you talking about?
Qualify.
You've got to complete the thought because all of those things are based on what you know and how you can operate within those things.
So with that said, Seth, please add or take away.
Fear is a tool.
It is used for many purposes by many different people, some of them not even aware that they're doing it.
But the baselessness of it.
You know, like I gave the analogy of the if you have no skill with how to use a mop or a dishrag, the thought of something spilling over is terrifying, isn't it?
But if you can operate a dishrag or sponge or a mop, it's not a big deal.
Right.
So, like, again, going back to these these morons that call themselves financial, they have financial shows.
They're all over the Internet.
They have subscription newsletters, all of them.
They're always talking about a collapsing dollar.
Is anyone going to message this guy and tell him that there is no dollar and that there's a credit based economy?
By the way, folks, you know, maybe we'll give little tidbits whenever you hear, because I've had several morons send me stuff about the collapsing dollar.
And yes, they are morons, with a capital R.
A dollar is a weight measurement, like pound or weight.
I think 271 grains of silver, precious metal and silver is measured in grains.
What they're talking about, let's translate for the lazy, because these are people that are spiritually, mentally lazy that talk about collapsing dollar and concern of it.
Well, let me just translate in simple terms what is being said, what is being put out there for the public at large.
When they say the dollar is collapsing, how can it collapse when there is no dollar?
What they're actually saying, let me translate this for you folks out there, is there are certain companies, American-based companies, whether they're IMF or New York banksters or whatever, that have preferential treatment on financial transactions,
meaning that when you have something called the petrodollar, which is an erroneous term, trade being done with these large oil tankers or trade being done with bonds and stocks.
These American companies, because they're American-based, are given first dibs on the transaction and they broker the deal, whether who they're brokering it for is making a profit or not is irrelevant.
They are simply brokering.
They get a cut.
These are American companies.
So when you hear that the dollar is collapsing, what is really happening is that these American companies that are given preferential treatment on the initial front-end transactions are losing preferential privilege.
People are looking for other entities that are not American-based to have preferential treatment on managing these transactions.
There is no US dollar, folks.
There hasn't been for a long time.
And the price of gold is $20 an ounce, period.
So when they say it's 1,200 an ounce, that is according to 1,200 credits, not dollars.
So the price of gold or the value of gold, I should say, has never changed.
It's $20 per ounce, period.
There's no debating on that.
But the price that you, because you're functioning in private credit, you're going to have to come up with 1,000 or more credit notes or whatever you want to call them, book entries to get that ounce of gold.
But that ounce of gold would buy you a fine tailored suit 100 years ago, 200 years ago, 300 years ago, 1,000 years ago, and that same, it would buy you a fine tailored suit today.
So again, just to tie this without going into the gold and the precious metals is when you hear about a currency collapsing, how can something that doesn't exist collapse when it's based on credit?
And if anyone tells you that it's debt-based, they are stuck on the secondary market.
In other words, they've never been to the concert.
They're outside selling T-shirts or buying T-shirts, but they've never seen the show.
And the majority of the people have never seen the show.
They're outside on the sidewalk buying the T-shirt.
And you will very rarely, you can pretty much look through social media websites talking about debt-based currency.
There is no such thing.
You've been told that and you believe it.
Again, just to reiterate, maybe this is the third or fourth time, when you hear about the collapse of a currency, it's the preferential treatment of a particular brokerage house or banking financial firms losing that privilege.
So when you hear again about the American dollar collapsing, all it means is that world trade is trying to avoid using these American or US-based brokerage firms.
In other words, they get the first dibs on processing the transaction.
That's all it means.
As a matter of fact, the more – well, we'll save this for another discussion.
Perhaps we'll do something on just the finance.
Today was pretty much speaking about the seasonal effect of spring because we're almost smack in the middle of the seasonal change,
and whether it's spring or fall, basing it on the other side of the world that's going into winter,
and now we're going into summer, you have these transitional seasons known as spring and fall.
And what's interesting about that, at some point, the whole world, it's possible within the spring or fall time period for the whole world to enjoy the same temperature or temperament for a couple of days or weeks.
It's a very interesting time period of a homeogenous kind of setting through the world.
And it also – when you have this, what's interesting is when you have fall and spring on the entire world, again, not only is it temperature,
the temperatures can be the same, pretty mild and such, and leading into different degrees of next cycles.
Like in one cycle, you'd be going colder, and the cycle going into hotter.
There's still the contrast of spring and fall where spring is planting and fall is harvesting.
So on one end here, we're in the planting, and on the other part of the world, they're in the harvest.
So the focus of the past hour was pretty much on what happens during planting.
It's a quiet time, and even when a field is fully planted, it doesn't look like much is growing or changed, but it's all in place.
And the suggestion that was made in the previous hour was whenever there's a lot of noise in the media,
whether it's geopolitical, economic, social, what have you, that is not in accordance with the season.
Look where it's quiet.
Don't fall for the distraction was the point.
And actually, don't fall for the distractions ever.
But during these time periods, especially – see, fall would be noisier than spring.
And I notice it is fairly quiet geopolitically, and also I got into the idea that the future of many things can be known.
Such functions as cooking and machining and building things, one doesn't start on any of these endeavors unless they know the future of that endeavor.
But there seems to be a tremendous resistance on applying that concept or methodology to the geopolitical scene or the geocultural scene,
or the whole world at large where mankind is going.
People seem to prefer this really low-quality dribble and tripe and to negate anything that can be validated from a good – let's just say a good foundation or a good report that's been carried through a long period of time.
And that's why, for example, I stated earlier, Seth, that there seems to be a massive failure in the discernment and interpretation of ancient prophecy.
Massive across the board.
And the misinterpretation, the lack of knowledge in these things is just astounding.
But these things, I mentioned as well, just to recap, is that the purpose of these prophecies that you see every culture have in various orders and various degrees of detail is to show you the anomalous events or the anomalies that will be occurring in the normal clockwork that mankind is used to, like seasonal changes, what's in the astronomical bodies, things like that.
The purpose of prophecy is to show you the anomaly and also to show you a reference point.
But here's the point.
Being in this numbing down period, it doesn't really matter either way.
So it's not the dumbing down that mankind is experiencing.
That time has long been gone.
It's the numbing down period that they're engaged in right now.
It's not being made numb to anything.
Anything and everything.
Yeah, it seems like it's a numbing.
And I brought up the example of no matter how truthful or deceitful the cause is or it's still just viewed as a big deal.
Right.
So the truth isn't being acknowledged.
And also when you have let's say I brought up the concept of false flag events that seem very drastic and that it be the impetus of political change and new laws and things like that.
People just say, oh, that's just a news story.
We'll just put it out there.
So whether it's an element of truth being put through the venue known as the Internet or any kind of media, even academia, let's say, heaven forbid, I don't think they've put out anything viable in a long time.
If something could be beneficial, it's not really considered.
And if anything is viewed very negative or detrimental, it's not even considered.
It seems like mankind is under some kind of numbing.
Right.
And I think we've hinted why.
And perhaps going into some detail regarding that is seems like Greek speak repeat over and over and over.
But, you know, it's a really interesting thing.
But the thing we also brought up is the concept of water.
Water is very important during the seasonal change of spring and planting.
You know, you water things to grow.
And I just brought up the simple point that comprehending that anything being at its highest quality or regarding water, Victor Schauberger called it the anomaly point.
Water is at its highest quality at about 39 degrees Fahrenheit or four degrees Celsius, meaning that above or below that temperature, it expands.
The body expands.
It's not in its densest form.
And the suggestion was made that Greek, why don't you speak about water?
And I said, for now, the only thing that people can consider for just once is consider keeping water out of the light and keeping it cool, preferably at four degrees Celsius or 39 degrees Fahrenheit overnight before you consume it.
And watch how the quality of the water itself is increased.
And just simply is that the other chemical constituents and other physical constituents of water will get into and how to, quote, unquote, treat water and how simple it is.
You don't need much to do it to achieve a high quality of water.
And it's astounding with this tool they call the Internet how little to the point information is provided on this.
And the worst thing is when someone starts discussing it strictly as H2O and H3O and H506O.
And it's like they missed the point, you know, because if water is really H2O, why does a bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air?
It shouldn't.
So and it's just astounding the ridiculousness that mankind is fully engrossed in.
But it's not the dumbing down.
It's the numbing down.
So, yeah.
Here's something that I was speaking about the other day with someone they brought to my attention.
We talk we speak a lot.
You and I, you know, in particular of scripture, things like that.
And it was brought to my attention that in Eastern scripture, where they talk about the the work of what we would call the Elohim or the gods, that in where they reference that in Eastern literature, it's it's referenced not as as the work of the gods, but as the play of the gods.
Yeah, as in the Mahabharata, perhaps.
Yes.
The Mahabharata, the Rig Vidas.
And it's just that's one of the interesting points, because we talk a lot about the similarities, not only of the fact that there is, you know, no one following these these scriptures that they claim to be basing their their belief system or their religious ideas.
But no one, regardless of the scripture, be it the, you know, the Vedas or the any of it.
But it is still interesting to look at some of the the differences in the way just the beginnings of this experience, if not the beginnings of all things, are viewed differently east to west.
And that was something that, you know, in considering it was quite beautiful looking at it as not not the work, because here in the West, you know, we've been we've been made workers.
Right. Was it was it the Rockefeller, the one of the Rothschilds that said, you know, if I wanted, why am I giving so much money to the public school system?
Because I want a nation of workers, not a nation of thinkers.
It's like we are made, you know, we are programmed to work, to work, work, work.
And even using passages out of the King James as, you know, justification for such things or as a basis for such things.
And it's just interesting to think of, as opposed to it being the work of, you know, El Shaddai as seeing it as the as the play of these Elohim, as opposed to the work.
Because in specifically in Kohalath or Ecclesiastes, which is one of my favorite pieces of literature anywhere, it speaks about taking pleasure in the work of your hands.
And generally, when you're doing something that is work, if you were taking pleasure in it, it can be viewed as play.
So just I don't I don't really have anywhere to go with that, but I thought that I would I would bring it up.
And, you know, yeah, Mark Twain, Samuel Clemens, I think he said, make your vocation or your vacation your vocation and you'll be happy.
But the thing about the work that made your life.
Yeah, well, what is work? It's change and all things change.
And once in a private Skype group, I've been frequently recently, I said, everyone is trying to judge what they see based on how it's different from another.
Right. And how about I'll just do this exercise in public here.
Once let's look at it a different way.
What makes everything the same? Right.
What makes everything the same? And using that as a beginning of discernment.
And not only will you be able to discern the thing for its quantity, but you'll also be discerning it for its quality at the same time.
Yeah. You're ready for that. And and it's it actually works. Let's say we'll consider it four pairs.
The first pair is that everything what does everything have from an anthropomorphic point of view that we can interact with everything that we can perceive?
Right. The first pair is everything has a front and a back.
The next thing is everything has a left and a right.
The next thing is that everything has a top and a bottom.
The next thing is everything has an inside and an outside.
So let's just take anything.
Let's take something arbitrary not to beat up on these guys, even though they deserve is the legal society.
Let's discern the legal society. Let's look at what they're showing us in the front.
Let's look at what they're showing in the back. Let's look at what they show on the left.
What are they showing on the right? Right.
If anyone's been in a courtroom setting, you'll see it's discerned and set up that way.
What's being shown at the top of that society? What's being shown at the bottom?
And what's being shown about its inside? What's being shown about its outside?
And the same works for an orange, right? Same works for anything.
And going through these motions, it seems pretty rote.
You will not only get the quantity of the thing, but also a pretty, which what would I say, beginnings of the discernment of its quality.
Even in the political system, how many times have you heard that he or a leftist or he's a rightist, right?
And you've got the front and what's going on in the back, right? The corruption.
The front is there are leaders in the back that's corrupt, right?
And who's at the top? You got the different positions and entitlements.
And who's at the bottom? How are they being treated? How is the relationship there?
And then what's going on in the inside? You know, you've heard political insiders, right?
And then what's going on on the outside and look at the contrasts within these four pairs.
And you will not only see the quantity of the thing, but begin to go down its qualitative nature as well.
Very simple.
The next thing to consider is that all things change.
Even a diamond, most finely polished of anything, gold, these things that seemingly appear empirical, meaning not changing, do change.
They just don't change at a rate that's within one's lifetime or such, and we don't view it as such.
You know, it's interesting.
I've used on this experiment with many people.
If you've ever grown up in a place as a child near a very large tree, when you visit, if you if you've left that place and visited back after many years,
you ever notice that tree doesn't seem so big anymore.
Even though you might have doubled in size, the tree seems really small.
It's quite an interesting experiment, thought experiment to do.
But it hasn't changed that much.
But it has changed, of course, you know, trees change, everything changes to a certain degree, it could be measured.
So this rate of change is where the work comes in.
And before the work is done, the front, back, left, right, top, bottom, inside and out is considered, isn't it?
Before work is done, before change takes place.
So this is an interesting point of view, because if you look at what was just said about the four pairs and all things change,
that is how the formative energies appear to be working.
The formative before things are created, it seems like the front, back, left, right, top, bottom, inside out is considered,
because everything seems to have that.
And also it seems that everything seems to change.
Right? So these are formative things.
Could it be this is a discussion reserved for the gods?
Maybe this is what they're discussing.
And according to what's been memorialized through history, we are to join them at some time in our future, let's say.
Why do I say our future?
Could it be that when man writes history and records it, he's writing about past events.
And when the gods write history and record it, they're talking about future events?
From our perspective, certainly.
Yes. It's like an inverted world.
Here's another idea.
This is formative things now.
In man's kingdom, he always refers to things in a vertical sense.
You've got the king at the top and the street sweeper at the bottom.
You've got the top of the pyramid concept, right?
Right.
You've got the high and the low in a vertical fashion.
What's interesting when one looks at the ancient texts that's been memorialized.
And by the way, when I say ancient, people hate that.
They don't want to hear about this kind of stuff.
And I'm not speaking for them, but I've gotten a lot of feedback about that.
But when you look at what's been memorialized about the quote unquote gods or the Elohim or the plurality of them,
is that they function laterally.
They function laterally.
It's like, you know, the inner circle.
Right. Left and right.
You sit on the left hand or the right hand.
Right. You go in and out.
For example, just to use the biblical text.
When Solomon was asked, you know, he could have asked for anything, but he asked for wisdom.
And the reason was so he can know how to go in and out, up and down.
So it's very interesting.
Kingdom of the gods or their realm is not vertical.
It's lateral.
But right now, because they're interacting with us and we're interacting with the way we want to see them,
we see it as a vertical aspect.
It's quite interesting.
So, yeah, I don't believe we just said this in public, but we might as well.
Right. Right.
Yeah.
These are the formative aspects and mankind is.
And also the point I kept bringing in earlier, Seth, was how can people rationalize clearly when they have a hot head and cold feet?
I don't see anyone still making demands to their entitled engineering classes
or even inquiring for them to design and procure devices that create a descending heat and an ascending cold as it is in nature.
So if they're not asking or inquiring about how do we make our living spaces,
whether it's a car, boat, home plane, where the heat is densified and goes down
and a cold that's verified and rises like it does in nature.
How do we have cool heads and warm feet?
And no one is inquiring yet.
It's astonishing.
I mean, recently I went into what they call the Yellow Pages
and called all the heating and cooling engineers and physicists.
Are you guys getting calls yet about designing and procuring devices that create an ascending cold and a descending heat?
And they're like, never heard of it.
Like, oh, boy.
So no one is noticing the obvious yet.
But anyway, I just thought I'd throw that in there.
They're being distracted.
How can you be so distracted to not realize that you need a cool head and warm feet anyway?
Yeah, and there's no inquiry being made.
And something so basic and so carnal and materialistic,
and you have people trying to want to discuss spiritual matters in the realm of the gods
and they're not even inquiring about having a cool head and warm feet.
It's shocking and astounding.
What kind of progress do you think are they going to make in any spiritual matter that's purely spiritual, meaning of the mind?
Pretty much zero.
And that's what you see.
And there's a lot of discussion, by the way, about the new world order bringing in some new world religion, right?
One can say that to a certain degree.
But right now, what you consider, let's say, from loosely termed religions,
there's nothing there.
If you look at any of the world religions right now,
they're based on nothing.
They're based on the revival of ancient cultural traditions.
Absolutely no instruction.
Some of them have some laws, like dietary laws and things, very loosely adopted.
The interesting thing is there's still a lot of commentary about the destruction of Christianity.
There's nothing there to destroy.
If anyone professes to be of that faith, needs to inquire what it's based on,
we'll find nothing there.
It's just shocking.
It just shocks the mind.
You know, to realize this simple fact.
The emperor has no clothes.
So people are still up to do about nothing.
They're frustrated and very upset about nothing.
There's nothing there.
And the commentary that you hear regarding, let's say, the biblical text or anything regarding that is erroneous still.
Completely across the board.
There might be little spatterings of truth here and there, but who's discerning it?
Apparently no one.
So there's a very interesting time that humanity is going to be heading into here in the next decade.
Actually starting in the next year or two.
I'd say two plus.
That's going to lead to the next phase of humanity.
So again, very uncommon, isn't it?
To discuss these things.
Yeah.
But nonetheless, I'd say it's about the middle of this transitional season known as spring here and fall in other parts of the world.
And the things to be considered.
If people consider the seasonality and how humanity is locked into the agricultural cycle, not necessarily for growing plants,
but every aspect of every institution and every aspect of their, let's say, existence is also locked in more directly than they think into the seasonal changes.
And I guess that was the theme of coming together here today.
Because the uniqueness of what they call spring or fall is the ability for the whole world to be almost homogenous for a certain period of time.
It's, you know, you're transitioning from hot to cold or cold to hot.
And this is mid ground that's happening now.
And it's typically the planting or typically the harvesting, depending on which end of it you're experiencing, which are contrasting.
But from the temporary point of view, they're very similar.
And the discussion here for those folks going through the spring, it was to simply apply.
What do you know about the spring season, whether it's purely materialistic, agricultural or even metaphorically where it's a time of planting?
What what happens during times of planting?
What's required? What what impedes it and what promotes it?
And this type of thinking leads to the type of efficiency that one can incorporate in their lives.
So they're not wasting their energy or their thought energy or their motions.
Right now, you're going to come across, for example, political aspects.
Right. There's an election time period in the States.
And you're going to come across people ranting about debt economy, debt based economy or viruses or, you know.
And I suggest to completely ignore them.
And even if it's ninety nine percent of the media, alternative or mainstream.
Right. Why?
Because, first of all, they're crying and screaming about things that don't exist or secondary or tertiary, you know, and have become victim to the prank.
And very often in private, I do speak about people, let's say, coming together on certain subject matters, whether it be medical, scientific or judicial or legal society or political or even religious.
And they're trying to find their ways around these systems or how they can benefit or avoid the pitfalls of those systems.
And I'm like, the first thing you have to acknowledge that any of those societies or systems are not what they're saying they are.
They are pranksters. They're pranking you.
They're a victim of a prank.
And one of the maxims there is perhaps that avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
So if you know the legal, medical and political and scientific society are there to prank everyone, they are not providing anything of what they each prospective field is supposed to do.
They're simply pranksters.
You find that you have pretty much become a victim of a prank.
And when you consider it that way, the thing becomes very, very clear.
Because, for example, if you address a scientist about anything scientific being erroneous or self-contradicting, they don't want to address what you're saying.
They say, where did you get your degree and are you a scientist?
And if you do not fit that and can't listen to you.
The same thing with the legal society or the medical society.
You know, it's a legal society.
Well, you know, you guys have not followed this procedure or this law.
The laws don't matter. You do what we say.
Be a good citizen.
The same with the doctors.
Doctors will say, well, are you a doctor?
Well, then how do you know?
And I have to do my job.
I am limited. I can only say this.
Well, so you're pranking.
It was society of pranksters on the rest of the society.
It's very interesting in that respect as well.
And the pranking is going on across the board as well.
It's not just a single aspect of society.
It's the religious, especially every religion or pranksters as well.
And the believers now are becoming pranksters.
It's fascinating to watch.
Self-consuming.
The difference between disinformation and misinformation.
I think we went into that a little bit.
Yeah, the disinformers deliberately put it out to re-steer, re-guide.
And the misinformers are the ones receiving it and believing it.
And repeating it.
Yeah, and repeating it and not knowing that it was structured to be deceit.
Yeah.
And right now the disinformants have become the misinformants also.
They're actually believing their own sauce.
They drank the Kool-Aid themselves.
I believe that was coined from back in the day when they were,
I guess they spiked the bowl for something.
Yeah, this is humanity.
Folks, you're not being dumbed down.
That's long done.
You're being numbed down.
I'm going to try to, in Greek speak, colloquial Greek speak, let's say,
bring up something called cosmic censorship.
Meaning where the gods have actually censored mankind.
That started 2500 years ago.
Around the 500 BC, 600 BC is when that started.
That's when all the rise of most of your modern religions and sciences
and philosophies have succeeded from.
And you've been kind of pranked by the gods as well.
Sorry, guys, I hate to admit it.
There probably was a cosmic bet to prank mankind into becoming atheistic, meaning that if you lose complete information about a thing, you no longer know nothing about a thing, it's the same as that thing doesn't exist.
Currently, most of mankind, if not wholesale, it's safe to say all of mankind has lost any concept of the gods to the point where they might as well say they don't exist.
Again, you approach most people that are in any of the mainstream or alternative religions or even scholars, they cannot tell you anything about the gods that is founded anywhere.
So it might as well be atheist.
To me it means, I believe in this, and the whole concept of falling for the adversary is more than a concept, it's a realization.
The adversary is just going to be adversarial, it's going to be the opposite.
So actually what's interesting is the more spiritual someone says they are, the more they're actually pranking, because there's nothing there.
It's the emperor has no clothes.
It takes a child to say the emperor is naked, because the adults have been so programmed into believing that he can afford invisible thread, invisible clothing, that they cannot justify or rationalize in their mind that he's being pranked himself.
And it took the child's point of view to add clarity to that.
Absolutely.
So the uncommon thing which can be discussed for this sonic project known as uncommon sense is what is obvious.
That's very uncommon.
And it hasn't been discussed.
The obvious things haven't been discussed yet at all, at least for 2500 years, let's put it that way.
And if anyone wants to start doing any research on that time period, let's say it was an axial period of sorts.
If you've ever heard of, oh, the destruction of a lot of the ancient temples, the destruction of the Library of Alexandria, major shifts in power, switching over to the Greek system of mathematic philosophy and thinking.
This was part of the cosmic censorship.
And sometimes I have people pressing me, no matter how many ways they try to explain what cosmic censorship is to explain it.
I'm like, dude, if you ask me one more time, you're censored yourself.
You know, there's a level of cosmic censorship that plays itself.
But the interesting part about it, it's not very difficult to see through.
That's the whole thing.
It's a very thin veil.
But it's very universal across the globe about negating what's obvious.
And then I've led the other concept that I've brought up many times is something called the dummy load.
What is a dummy load?
It's something that when you develop a circuit or a device and you want to test it, instead of putting the real world load on it, you put a dummy load on it to test it.
If someone, for example, a treadmill is a dummy load.
If someone says, I just ran five kilometers on the treadmill.
Well, you ran five kilometers, but you didn't go anywhere.
A treadmill is a dummy load.
Or a hamster wheel is another form of a dummy load.
So what's being put out there right now about negating the obvious or taking something that is obvious, like the need for food, clothing, shelter, the desire to use money in commerce, the desire to have a spiritual belief?
All of these things are hamster wheels that are being put out right now across the board.
It's safe to say that, folks.
And the only way to defeat that, not that it needs to be defeated, but defeat as a function, let's say as a defeat function or a default function, is to start noticing the obvious.
But the problem with that is that there's so much numbing down and there's so much laziness that people don't want to inquire anymore.
Right. So one purpose of doing the uncommon sense is saying, hey, look, it's just right in front of you.
Look. Right. The favorite one regarding the body.
Someone asked to talk a little bit about supplements and things.
And you always got to go back to the basics of the body.
Are you in accord with the seasons or cross latitude?
Right. And are and are you have you been subjected to some anomalous fear that is contrary to reality, like little bacteria in cold climates causing disease?
Where that would render all refrigeration useless because the reason we use refrigeration is to put them in a dormant state.
So when you these things need to be addressed commonly and they're not, it's still being put out there.
It's getting cold. So it's flu season. What?
What causes that? The flu shots.
Yeah. Right. Well, you know, the other thing, you know, there's never been any study on vaccines on their efficacy.
You know, like, you know, a good what they call science, which is, you know, hypothesis, experimentation, conclusiveness and all that.
It's a religion. Yeah. When people start to find that out and it's going to be kind of interesting, hopefully they'll take it lying down.
It's it's it's a religion and a faith, both both any side of that argument.
Actually, I've witnessed firsthand, you know, how they say you can't bring up religion or politics without upsetting people, making someone angry.
Well, that's something I've gotten to witness recently.
But what's interesting. Yeah. The interesting part about that is you notice there's less of it.
People are less likely to be upset when you bring up a divergent claim.
Meaning like, you know, years ago, let's say 40, 50 years ago, if you were considered to be not nationalistic, people got upset with you.
You were considered a traitor, not patriotic. Now it seems to be it's OK.
You could voice that. Right. Many things now are being accepted because the numbing down is increasing.
It's quite gotten to the point, which is actually the heyday for the love and light people and the new agers, the consciousness intent people.
Have you heard of them? Yeah. Knowledge doesn't matter. It's your intent, you know, or law of attraction.
Yeah. Law of attraction. Yeah. Those people that this is their heyday, by the way, the jellyfish, you know, time.
So, yeah. So, yeah, it's quite interesting. It doesn't mean that it has to disable those that are curious about living a life of efficiency and having some knowledge.
And by the way, people still hate being knowledgeable or those that tend to pursue things like that because it goes contrary to what's been.
Let's say common or concordant, concordant, meaning if everyone agrees on something, that's what it is, even though it's contrary to the truth.
So, yeah, it's quite interesting. But again, just to harken back to being springtime in this part of the world, what do you folks know about planting?
What do you folks know about watering things after they're planted, meaning feeding them, even though you don't see anything being substantiated or emerging at the moment?
What do you folks know about the conditions during planting?
You know, it tends to be pretty quiet when the planting is done and things are starting to take effect.
What do you know about the seasonal change? You're going from a cold to a warm or from a warm to a cold in another part of the world.
You know, what's what's required there, you know, for what we call the container or the body, you know.
But just to bring up the point, it's still kind of in the back of the mind.
But you know, when someone asked me, what about supplements? Well, what about them?
How can anything be a supplement? Others? I don't like that point.
And then that would probably be referring to what we call vitamins, let's say.
If anyone is concerned about that, you should go study a little bit of Rudolf Hoshka.
I believe it's H-A-U-S-C-H-K-A, a man of German extraction or Austrian extraction back
at the turn of the century who did research on what gave food its vitality and played
with extracts and things like that.
And I assure you that if he was alive today and pursued and overlooked and examined what
people are pawning as vitamins and supplements, he would light himself on fire naked and
run down the street.
It's totally contrary to what his work had been about.
And he might be considered, or I would say consider him one of the granddaddies of that
field.
But...
I'm unfamiliar with his work.
Can you...
Rudolf?
Yeah.
Hoschka.
His name bears a brand of very high-end, high-quality women's makeup even today.
I believe it's H-A-U-S-C-H-K-A, perhaps.
But the wonderment of search engines these days, no matter how bad you screw up the search,
you're going to get some form of refinement that will lead you to it.
Interesting character.
Now, the interesting thing, I don't view these things as vitamins or extracts or supplements.
I view them as pairs or pairing.
If the next time someone tells you to take a supplement or anything, just look at it
as something you would consider as food.
And does it look like that to you?
That's a wonderful question, it would be.
When I...
It's happened actually relatively rarely in the last few years, but when I start noticing
my body reacting to the environment negatively, if I start...
If my throat starts itching, something like that, I generally begin looking to, okay,
what am I not...
What nutrient am I missing here?
What am I not eating?
Not what vitamin, but what...
Harkening back to the Hippocrates, food is your medicine, medicine is your food.
By the way, people say that's biblical and you will not find that in the biblical text.
Just throw that in there.
Yeah, no, no, it's...
It's a Greek philosophical point of view, yeah.
Yeah.
But that whole concept there, again, is if you look back at what's called supplement
and vitamins, it was originally the study of what gave these substances their vitality.
And just in short, what Hoschka discovered is that the vitality of these extracts was
very limited in time.
They only had an efficacy for a short period of time before they lost their efficacy.
And also he noticed that direct contact or mixing from the organism, from the, let's say,
the extract or the vitamin to the organism was not necessary, just proximity was enough.
And, of course, you're not going to be...
This is not going to be propagated to a materialistic mindset that is taught that the body
actually absorbs things like a filter bag, right?
I recently had a discussion.
Someone said, well, Greek, if the body doesn't absorb food, then what...
Does it matter what you eat then?
And I'm like, oh, boy.
This is where a little bit of information is good and more information can be detrimental
because the individual lacks the discernment of what's being said, you see.
So this is very interesting.
That's why very often I'd have a private discussion with someone and say, Greek, man,
I had to listen to you for three months before I was figuring out what you were saying.
Now I love it.
And I'm like, wow, is that because what I'm saying is not simple?
Or is it in such a stark contrast to what you formally took in as communication?
It was the latter, obviously.
I don't think one should speak to you on a level that any...
beyond any level that a child cannot comprehend.
Because, by the way, children are just small people.
And I find, anyone should find, recommending this, the subculture of kids to be disgusting,
creating an entire subculture with their own forms of entertainment and toys and shows
and things like that.
If you actually look at that, even though children are told they should be enjoying that,
it has created a subculture that does not demark when they should stop using that
and create serious spiritual damage.
They're just small people that lack instruction and maturity in many ways.
If you create a subculture called the kids stuff, right?
Kids toys, kids meals, kids this, kids that, which are baby goats.
You've actually created this subculture and it's really distorted.
And if you don't think humanity has been distorted since the emergence of that culture,
you're not paying attention.
And that is a criticism, direct and harsh, as it is aptly deserved.
The happy meal.
Yes.
And you look at the children and the small people and they've been thrust into this adversarial,
almost ridiculous, I mean, Teletubbies, right?
Just look across the board, Disney, right?
And the irony of it, look at the pornography and the lasciviousness that Disney has thrown in in the past, right?
Into their stuff subliminally and directly, not so subliminal.
I mean, we're talking about a level of depravity.
What's interesting is, you know, if human, if mankind is dependent on,
mankind's future is dependent on the young, the children.
He has no future because the children have all been turned into baby goats, kids.
So, I mean, it's just, yeah, it's beyond comprehension to examine the level of it.
When does a child now become, go from a child to a kid to an adult?
All right.
So, boys and girls, thank you again.
And say afar and uncommon sense.
We'll see you again soon.