Yes, welcome to yourself as well everyone and Seth and
Doing okay still on this rock with everybody else and we're here again. Hopefully as promised to give you a dummy load free
two hours
It's been about a week as they call it and speaking of a week. I'm reckoning the
Third week of the fifth month lawful timekeeping and I know there's maybe four people out there that know what we're talking about
That's all that's needed. Perhaps it'd be five
Everyone else is kind of like wondering what these guys are speaking about
How come they're not talking about all this other stuff that everyone else is
In so on and so forth. Well, yeah
Maybe that's why it's called uncommon sense because maybe any sense at all or good sense is uncommon
Don't you think?
absolutely
Yeah, and and you know, I think this is roughly according to archives perhaps of 13th or 14th
Episodic sonic experience and
all these things are limited try to keep them limited as
Presentation can go, you know Seth. I was thinking a little bit this week. It's like why bother right?
There's many there's many
Attachments one can look at attachments being you know, what one perceives and it's like why bother have you have you been well
Let me just ask this again to everyone you guys listening to what's going on out there
I mean in all media whether it's I don't hunt many people don't do print
Most of it is digital, especially if you're listening to us right now. You're probably
Getting a lot of your stuff on what's called the computer digital format. But so let's just maybe discuss that. I
Just find it to be astoundingly ridiculous. I mean
There's it's just there's nothing to really grab on to it seems like things are just being thrown around
there's no merit to what's being said and
On and on. I mean, I don't know. Do you want to just touch on that for a moment?
Why do you think the?
Forget about what we think what can be observed?
You know, what can be observed about what's called media?
Let's let's just limit it down to the Internet. I mean, you've got some major and minor Internet radio stations
You've got websites that give what's called the news
Got lots of people doing various interactions social media
What have you and it all just seems like a big load of crap
I mean look if you're a flower or whatever, you know, you need that stuff. That's what makes flowers grow
crap rain and sunshine, but I wish sometimes that enough rain and sunshine would come in to wash the crap off the Internet, but
Anyway, that's not like a little mini rant perhaps to start off
So, yeah, well we are being subjected currently I mean in any more it's it's very overt the
You can look at it as social conditioning
But if we're looking at the Internet in particular or any sort of broadcast media in particular, we're looking at
You know
Programs essentially and you know, what's it? What's a program if you look at our interaction with the existence around us?
It be that you know electronic or
more more overtly physical
We're simply running programs through our operating system. Yeah
Programs and the programs that are offered anywhere and anywhere. I don't even have to pick on anything
Everywhere across the board. They're just of a very low quality low
You know low effectiveness rate it's not
It's certainly not proper most of it is completely and totally baseless
And the basis that they do provide for things if you actually go and follow
Follow the the web to the center. It's there's nothing there. It's all it's all baseless. So we are observing the effects of
Not poor information distribution but distribution of poor information and poor quality and poor
Yeah, yeah, it's it's
You know, we've discussed and let's just say it again for those who are hearing maybe you're listening this time
the what you're experiencing with electronic media aka the Internet and all all the things that encompass that is
There's a divine influence behind it, by the way, and it's a beta test for
Something that's going to be necessary
in the future and that's pretty obvious to see
Because I mean look at what's going on out there
I mean, it's really piss-poor, but then again, how can you expect it?
Let's put the Internet aside
If you walk out the door and walk down the street and in start interacting with your average surface-dwelling earth inhabitant
Let's just discuss that for a minute what comes out of their mouths. What do you think is going on between their ears?
Piss-poor quality again. So of course it's going to somehow end up
in this form of communication. I
Think it's just what you know garbage in garbage out
So again, you know at one point it's like why bother? Well, you know, why bother Seth?
Do you think the you know, we kind of jokingly say there we have about four or five listeners, right?
And and you know, it's yeah, you know, yeah, I get some messages. Yeah Greek you have more than four or five
Yeah, but you know, there's I mean, there's a lot of people hearing this but are they listening, you know?
Are they really listening what to what's being said, you know?
so I but you know from that perspective, I think that getting together for two hours a week and
Revealing things that might be considered secrets that have been held for thousands of years that are secreted in open plain sight
Discussing them on this minor internet radio venue for two hours a week. It's actually not a bad cause
You know
Yeah
Yeah, that's it's one of the more worthwhile things that I am doing with my time certainly
Then mainly because most of what I do with my time is
You know go to work and complete jobs for a company
Right literally jobs. Yeah
Basically, but yes, I don't write much down but
Yeah, yeah, so yeah with that said, you know, there's a couple of topics
we of course, we'd like to a couple of topics we could get into today and also there's a we like to
Communicate overtly and anonymously with people that message us. I think it helps the the the entire mindset of
ourselves and the the audience very often if we respond back personally, which I stopped doing I prefer to pretty much
Do it on on air
So it's not this little private thing because if it continues to be let's say private communications
Answering things. Let's say or attempting to answering things. I think it's going to lean into jokingly what I call billable hours. So
In that case, let's just keep the thing open and free and just discuss certain things anonymously
and
Openly, but yeah that that topic
of
Being topical, you know what what to discuss the thing also by the way speaking of information, you know
We we don't have guests. It's basically the Greek and Seth discussing because I don't know who we'd have a get as a guest
I think anyone that I found interesting or actually brought some really good stuff
Imparted to human society was dead. I think most of the people that are worth listening to have died. They're gone
and
That's the funny thing too and believe it or not when I most of this
Media is formatted a meet mainstream and alternative on you have a host with guests and it's like
Yeah, it's just a show. It's it's like the dog and the pony or the pony and the dog
I haven't found anything really to be
Worth listening to and I know that might sound like harsh criticism
Why is he saying that but I think I'm speaking out for most of the people as well
There's just nothing going on anywhere at all and I mean anywhere so
Yeah, it's just
It's entertainment. Yeah, and when you press a lot of the people in
Mainstream media and alternative media about like it dude. Why are you saying this? You know, it's like, you know, it's not true
You know the person that you've got as a guest is a moron. Oh, but you know, it's entertainment
But but when they're coming on they're doing whatever they're doing it's like that it's packaged as if it's you know, I actually go to
Well, I used to look at a lot of the chat groups
Just to see what kind of feedback, you know, because you want to look at the audience, you know very often
You know if you go to a performance
Whether it's a film or play music
Everyone's always focusing on what's going on the stage. I like to turn around and look at the what the audience is doing
That's where the real interest that shows you what the interaction is, right?
It's it's interesting. I like to put the camera on the on the audience while the show is going on
You know, it's like they used to back in the day
We remember in the older films when they go in the film
They put the camera on the audience and the two people having dialogue
But you know what I've noticed is a lot of these shows they have chats and listening to the show
I'm like, okay. This is definitely you know, this is why we do the show and rant about how bad the Internet is
And I'm just gonna make a comment here
Which is a comment on a comment and very often I see people posting in great show and I'm like great show shit
I'd hate to see what a crappy show
What do you mean great show I mean, so so it's basically the accommodation factor here, I mean are the people just
Have they lost it? I mean, I don't know. Yeah, I mean actually I do know that's why we we discuss and rant about it
Yeah
All right. So what do you think Seth? Um, you know one of the there's a few topics. I just want to throw in
We don't well, we don't really discuss what they call the news
But I don't know if this is true piped or whatever, but you know, I haven't really looked at any deeper
But so I throw this in there's some some blurbs coming out today about
American dip Americans
Expelling Russian diplomats and vice versa Russians expelling American diplomats
Isn't this what Pete the disaster that people have been waiting for since the 50s?
You know, maybe they'll have an international incident start killing each other. Isn't that what people want?
I mean look at look at the literature the film and the video games and the mindset and all this and
Isn't this what happens when you put a lot of stupid people together just bad things happen or
They call it bad, but they love it
Yeah, they didn't they wouldn't make video games and movies and stuff about war death and destruction. I
Don't know. I just it's not gonna happen. By the way, you know, there isn't gonna be
Mass level of mayhem if the Russians and the Americans go to war
Okay, you know occasionally a war here a war there. It's a theater
So but but anyway, it's just interesting
I had to bring it up because you don't see things like that in passing too much
You know the Russians expelling American diplomats and vice versa
You know, but don't get your hopes up too high got a lot of things that are going to be happening in the future and got
nothing to do with
ww3
You know, right
Sounds like World Federation, you know wrestling. What's that play wrestling what acting whatever?
Yeah
One of the things Seth this is just kind of bouncing around is you know how we bring up in passing
the weather
You know, I know I'm kind of hitting you with this
On a bridged or I just actually non prefaced and we kind of say jokingly. I think it was
Samuel Clemens Mark Twain who said everyone's talking about the weather. When is someone going to do something about it and
I
want to play a short audio we've been getting into playing little audios here and there and
What I'm thinking of doing
Is an homage or honor someone?
His name is Trevor James constable folks
Another man you might want to be
Familiar with is
Wilhelm Reich or Wilhelm Reich now, I
know if some people listening might have heard of this these people already and have been
Keyboard warriors and they end up looking at all the crap online about it everything from
Ether
Which is not crap by the way, but just the way it's explained all the way to these little
things called organite where they they mix
I'm just jumping here around
Resins with metals and people swear how well it works and all that and kind of that's not what we're talking about
and I'm gonna maybe play a short audio clips about three minutes and
This was an audio clip from a tape that was done in the early 90s where Trevor was going around to Oh
Heads of state it was an introductory
introductory videotape on how to
Let's say do weather engineering and by the way
No one what you're when you're doing weather engineering or someone like Trevor or Wilhelm Reich and such. They're not making the weather
They're creating the conditions that allow for certain weather
patterns and events to occur
It's dealing with primary. So what do you think Seth? I want to display this. I don't think this is on the Internet
this is a discussion on primary energy and
I have possession of it. I have it in digital format and I'm just gonna play the first three minutes
Which is an introduction that Trevor gave to people who were perhaps interested in alleviating drought and things
What do you think I should just go for it for about three minutes go for it. Absolutely. Okay
There's a lot of talk about
Weather, so here we go. We're gonna cue this thing up and we'll see here in just a few seconds
Okay
The World Meteorological Organization the WMO
Published these two massive volumes
Subsequent to their conference held at Honolulu, Hawaii
In August of 1985 there's almost
700 pages here a
monumental academic labor of
the subject of weather modification
the weight of
Their scholarship is enough to terrorize anyone
anyone that is
Except me
Heavy reading my name is Trevor James Constable
And I have been in weather modification for about 17 years
But you will not find any paper of mine on that subject in that compendium
that I just pitched on the deck and
There's a good reason for that
My approach to the subject is unorthodox. I
Do not follow
recognized rules
Nor wholly except orthodox concepts
Now the kindest thing that orthodoxy might say about me is that I'm one of those guys that's
Way out there in left field
Out where there are a lot of loose things lying around that nobody has bothered to investigate
They couldn't get any money to investigate it or the local professor was against investigating it
There's all kinds of things like this
in the borderland of nature
Where I have been rummaging around
for the past 30 years or so I
carry out weather modification
via the ether
E-T-H-E-R and
That is certainly not a concept that is accepted by orthodox science
Nevertheless
With my associates I have hurdled over all the theoretical controversies in
Gone to work and technically accessed the ether and I'm going to show you on this tape
that it can be used to
control and
engineer the weather
Now since I am working so far from recognized and established principles
I'm going to ask you to sail along with me for the next hour or so
with three basic new assumptions and
With the aid of these three new assumptions, you'll be able to see for yourself
How these things work even if you do not fully understand them
All right. Here are the three assumptions that you need to make
Number one
There is a primordial mass free energy
That underlies the atmosphere in all its workings
Number two
That ether is technically accessible
with the aid of simple
juxtaposed
geometric forms
These are for the most part
Cylinders and cones and you're going to see these translators right here on the tape
Number three
I want you to assume
That the ether is like the ocean
It has tides
flows
that are specific to
latitude season and other factors and
That we attain weather modification by opposing
Our translators to the tide or ether flow
Now you aren't going to see the ether on this tape
What you are going to see is
the reactions of the ether
Translated into the atmosphere
into the realm of ponderable
Objectifiable
meteorological happenings
You are going to see these events take place from zero
We aren't going to do it just once
Give you a flittering glimpse or anything like that. We are going to do it repeatedly
Press down and running over
then at the end of the tape
You
Will be able to judge
Whether or not there is an ether you
Will be able to judge whether or not it is technically usable
For the purposes of weather engineering and weather control
You will know these things and be able to judge of them because you will have seen them happen
Now that's all the theory that I'm going to give you before I take you to sea
Along the way, I'll be able to fill in a lot more of how all this is done
Without of course giving away the central commercial secrets, which are invaluable
Let's go now aboard an ocean-going ship of the United States merchant marine as
she plies her trade route in the North Pacific and
one more thing
Whether you're a scientist watching this
Or just a plain intelligent lay person
Conceptually and perhaps emotionally you're really going on a trip. Let's go to sea now
Okay
That's from Trevor he's he passed away recently a few months ago, so I figured I'd just play that
Now that he's gone
Maybe some other people might want to look at his work
So, what do you think? What do you think Seth? What do you think about that?
I would like to use a piece of that clip actually for
the intro into a
Song that's that right there. That's information. You're not going to find being shared
on the internet anywhere
No, it's
Relatively it can't there are bits and pieces
that
You can find where it's it's talked about
but
yeah, that's
I'm glad that you had that one pulled up to play. I think that's probably my favorite clip that you've played so far
Good. I'm gonna pull up something that's more objective
There was a and by the way folks when you start looking online about all this stuff
We're not talking about organite or cloud busters and things like that. This is something different
along those principles and
you'll find a lot of stuff about organite and
Just listen to the people pushing that stuff
wholeheartedly in the yeah, just
There's no it doesn't translate much and I'm going to play an objective video of what can be done
In this kit, by the way, this cannot be done by getting a cupcake mold and pouring epoxy and metal filings in it with crystals
So I'm gonna play something
Here and just just for the mind a little bit
To show you what capacity there's nothing to do with harp and all that other ridiculous stuff people screaming about
All these things and but anyway, we'll just play something else here
this is from a
few years ago from Dutch Dutch sense
Everybody Dutch sense here 10 o'clock p.m. Central Time on Friday, October 25th
2013 and
I've got you over here on my website
We had an earthquake today
7.0 move it forward a little bit and I'm gonna go ahead and show you where the earthquake occurred to do that
Let me turn off the rings on this
And we'll zoom in
And here's our 7.2 magnitude earthquake off the eastern shores of Japan and it started out as 7.6
Now downgraded to a 7.2. Okay, listen up now over on my website
I've been keeping track of the tropical storm situation and hurricane situation this past week
now
Take you over and show you the current tropical storms. You're gonna see two that are blatantly missing that were there last night
And they're now gone. Okay, what did he just say?
I'm gonna play that back just for a second here
to
Tropical storms super typhoons. Okay that were there the night before and now are gone
Okay, I'm just gonna play that just for one second here just for the
This is not done with little cupcake molds and metal filings folks
Tropical storms, you're gonna see two that are blatantly missing that were there last night and they're now gone
And that was typhoon. Lekima
category three and
Tropical storm Francisco off the eastern shores of Japan
Now, let me go ahead and show this to you. Okay. All right, so
You know, I just wanted to bring that up about the weather it's got nothing to do with harp and chemtrails and all this other
stuff and
There's interest about it
somewhat in the world, but again, it's
Misdirection disinfo and if you think you're gonna go ahead and get some cupcake molds and pour some resin
With metal filings and do anything like that. You're dreaming. So anyway, we discuss what dreams are about also
So I just want to throw in a couple of things like that in a rant ish us kind of way that we do things
Here, but I just wanted to bring in a few things about the weather plenty of stuff people to bite on and by the way
I just want to digress for a moment back to Wilhelm Reisch and Wilhelm Reich a lot of people use that pronunciation potato potato
He got into the atmospheric work
after he discovered something called bionds, which is
Materials that are supposedly inert that when sterilized and under the most strict conditions
Started to emit living creatures. Yes, and he thought he could
contain them and
Maybe change the conditions and see if they still happen
So he put it in a Faraday cage, which was wrapped with metal and he noticed that when he did that
experiment under a Faraday cage the
Activity increased and he noticed that if you did layers of metal and nonmetal
Known as what he called an orgone box or an orgone accumulator
He noticed that certain events in the natural world were amplified
and then one day
being out on the property in northern Maine or
The inmate let's say with the state of Maine in America. He noticed that during a construction
Project he
noticed that pipes and water would affect the atmosphere and
Gradually associated that with the biological experiments tied it all together
But the problem with Wilhelm Reich and others it will have right met a terrible demise just like others
He had started to profess that this form of observation or science is needed to be advanced to what?
Make the world a better place folks if you've got something that is good
Just do it. You can discuss it
But the moment you start saying we have to do this to make the world a better place
You're going to be put between the hammer and the anvil. So just avoid those terms
So anyway
Just to go on so we'll digress from the weather a little bit. Just wanted to throw a couple of evidentiary
little clips in there and just to maybe I think it'll confuse a lot of people because when they go and
Become keyboard warriors and start researching what we just discussed. They're not going to find
What we just discussed in the direction that we discussed it in
You're going to be thrown off with
You know
various discussions and websites everything from making cupcake molds with metal shavings all the way to
putting metal tubes and water and
As yes
Yeah, anyway, so let's be objective
There's more to this than meets the eye. There's definitely more than what you were
Discovering on cursor research is on the internet and the weather is not empirical. It's ephemeral meaning it can be changed
and
That's my story and I'm sticking to it
All right, so let's digress from this for a minute Seth. What do you think?
What else should we get into that was kind of like a opening its topic and I'm just closing it or walking away from it
Again, what do you think?
Yeah, absolutely, we've got some interesting things in
chat as well off topic a little bit and
You mentioned a couple of the emails as well that we can get into. Yeah. Yeah, I've got I've got some here
What say you I mean in terms of grabbing on to the next thing here. Do you would you like to?
You want to go more at the matter at hand, which perhaps is the chat
Let me see if I can as the AFR chat perhaps
Anything pertinent or is it dribble? Oh, we can we can go anywhere. I'm always
You know willing to listen about the weather as well because it's as you as you said, you know
One's always talking about it
When someone gonna do something about it, I think that's Samuel Clement, right? Yeah. Yeah, I believe so
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, there's just no information
there is a again just to kind of
Mall about a little bit more. I mean, so maybe you know might have said we walk away from it
Excuse me. There's a
Lot of discussion, of course, it's in the typical mindset again about
geoengineering
Now whether they have I don't know who these people are discussing this the way they are
There's quite a bit of it
But I'll tell you they're
They're on the whiner on the whiner side, you know, like hey, they're gonna kill us all or
Yeah, it's just
Yeah, it's just not the yeah typical human mindset
Again, you're not getting you're not gonna get any rational discussion now is what speaking of rational discussion?
I was brought into several groups. There was an attorney and one of them
It's kind of explaining the legal matter of
Something that can be referenced by anyone and the person who was an attorney didn't want to even look at it
He says well, that's just your opinion
They they have a what an evil sort. I mean, you know
And and they just and people buy into that. Oh, yeah, that's just his opinion
We don't need to listen even though they can look up anything that was said
You know, so you got to realize when we discuss things like this
People have already gone down a path of ridiculousness and
You're not going to get them off it, but it doesn't mean that you can't provide something proper
Now what makes it proper? Is that it's rational and let just like I said
two typhoons do not disappear off the coast of Japan with
cupcake molds and resin and metal shavings folks
Yeah, if you think that does anything
There's a padded room with a cherry flavored lollipop for you. So nonetheless, let's just
We can discuss the weather as we've threatened to discuss water
And let's just maybe continue back we'll just jump off the
Those two topics for now, especially the weather that we opened up and maybe jump on to
Some emails or that or the chat if it seems to be rational. What do you think?
Yeah, yeah
The you mentioned dreams as well we got or I received another response in the
On that subject as well so we can we can get into that and even perhaps we've got plenty of time left
But yeah, if you would like to go address the chat, it's certainly going to move a lot faster than the emails will
Oh
Either way, it's not about moving faster
Maybe is there anything at hand on the chat that do you might use that screams out that should be talked about perhaps?
Yeah, yeah Nathan is
In the in the chat room there. I assume he doesn't mind me referencing being that that's his name in the chat
But let me see if I can find
Oh, oh, I see it. He's in a little bit of a panic. Maybe we'll leave it alone
It's a bit of it there. Let's just leave that alone
Yeah, I I would suggest leaving it alone. I mean, it's just too much to address. It seems like a there's a parallel dialogue here
Unless you anything like I said jumped out that we could address just momentarily
Yeah, we instead of following the whole thing. We can just go with the
He
When you're speaking about the the weather
He said I'll just read the read the comment here says alleviating drought question mark
How about we submit the deity sovereign over the weather rather than trying to work the system with our dams crop?
rotations and geoengineering
well, it's kind of backwards if you study and what's been memorialized about the sovereign and
the other gods
We were handed over this entire environment as stewards
All right, so he'll make things grow you've got a still so you've got a plow so and reap, right
There's a lot of parables about the lazy man watching the ants, you know
Yeah, this environment. Here's what people understand
We'll throw this in and this is what they're going to find out later
the earth was quite happy being the earth until it was time to pretty much decide that
The spirit or the mind that force could could be animated through material and
There was a big division in that
godlike realm
The division part of it was about well, you know, it'll materials corruptible
So if the spirit is solely animated through material that's going to be corrupt
But the other part was let's do it because it's the highest form of creation
right and
Where are we going to put them? Well, you know, they went out and
saw the earth which was inhabited by non corporeal beings and
terraformed it
To the scale that we see today
So you've got an atmosphere and or water and what's called a food chain and symbiotic relationships and things
Yep, the earth would be quite happy shedding the entire atmosphere and going back to a pretty smooth black rock
Laboring to keep this entire thing going the arrogance of mankind is oh look we're damaging the earth
No, you're not doing anything of the sort. I mean you are but
It's the way you behave to each other the earth can't stand
Am I speaking for it? No, I'm not speaking for the earth. I'm not speaking for anyone
I'm just trying to objectify what's been memorialized to a society that has no ears and no eyes
But you will find this out later. Yeah saying it pretty confidently because it's pretty confident
If the information is
Well worth speaking in a confident manner
So, yeah, it's about stewardship
Not working with the weather is like saying well we need to grow food
So let's just stand by the earth and watch what grows and eat it. That's fine, too. But there is
Lawful agriculture, right, right
Yeah, I mean you could forage, you know what grows naturally, but you are allowed and given permission
Let's say from higher authorities to
objectify stewardship
Right
Yeah, but the thing is, you know, it's just like the political scene, you know, look at all these people
mainstream and me and alternative complaining about the current political system and financial system and
oligarchy
Would you want those people complaining to be those in power? I would I think the people in power now are doing just fine. I
mean, they're horrible and evil
but
You ever walk out your door anyway, yeah
Yeah, I mean when I say horrible, I mean it's like what's being reported, you know, they're pretty hands-off believe it or not
Most of the oligarchs on the power base that runs the planet
They have a lot of in between errs. You call them entitled. Well, they're called the entitled classes. Those are degrees
Oh, do you guys love that? Yes, you do. Come on fess up. You love all that dumb stuff
So
Maybe we'll just jump into an email
Seems like the chat. We have a pretty
Aggressive text going on there and there's quite a bit going on. But okay, let's let's go into
It's just kind of like stay, you know
Cuz we're trying to structure the show here in a way one of the emails we've gotten anonymously is a hello Seth and Greek
It's numbered actually, I kind of briefly looked at this up. Can you offer any pointers for conducting research?
There's a lot of information to sift through and it's hard not to become tangled up in ideas that may
Seem lawful or valid initially, but over time turn out to be nothing more than wasted power making the hamster wheel turn
Yeah
Pretty much answered it right there. Well, how do you how do you do the research objectively with rational thought?
Think once it was said that takes a sane mind to think clearly, but an insane mind can think deeply
Start looking at
things objectively
If you read a book
about a subject
That someone wrote about who read another book that someone else wrote that someone else wrote that someone else wrote
You're not going to get it, especially if these people are academic
One question there would be do you mind drinking water from a street puddle or
Do you mind drinking water from a river where all the birds and fish want to poop in or do you want to drink water?
from a spring at the mountaintop
So what the spring would represent the source?
So go to the source very simple
Anything on that Seth anything else would you like to add or take away from that?
About research
Old libraries go find some old books
You know, what's interesting by the way, I've heard several
consistent reports the big library in New York City the ones with
It's kind of like this. It looks like a temple of marble and stone and there's two lions outside there. I think it's on
Fifth Avenue 42nd Street used to have it's a beautiful building and
a
Lot of old stuff. I've heard that over the past decade or two a lot of the old stuff's been removed
And by the way, the FBI does have a book seizure list
Folks and one of those things the most recent
Project was dictionaries
Yeah
Dictionaries around September 2001 there was a particular word that
Needed to have its definition modified
Go figure it out. So old libraries, you know, by the way years ago in libraries
All reading was encouraged to be done out loud
so when you built a library, it was quite a project you research some old libraries and
Documentation about them. You'll find that there were actually click construction large construction and maintenance crews
as part of the building
Because when you got your reading material you went and sat down a little booth and you read it out loud by yourself
So there's lots of doors lots of hinges that need to be fixed lots of cleaning out cleaning rooms and maintaining stuff
Yeah, this is a reading silent thing is a fairly recent occurrence
You brought up libraries for you to throw that in. Yeah, the internet only has what the internet has
It's become commonplace to rely on it solely for information
at the
other end of
experience I suppose so
You know, it's definitely a tool that can be used but it only has what it has
It's self-consuming though. If you have people that are ignorant of many matters or if all matters approach a venue
That
Venue in order to be successful has to accommodate that mindset
Right. So then it becomes a self-consuming. What do you call it perpetual? You know, what is it like when something?
Gets into a feedback loop and it can't break out of it
right
so in order for the internet to have the success that it does it has to put up a lot of stupid shit because there's
A lot of stupid people going to it
So then how does anything get better it doesn't
It's still there the if you know how to sift through it, but you have to remember it's accommodated
It's accommodating its audience. No one goes out into a venture that leads to success
without wholly and solely considering
Accommodating their patrons clients or audience
It's very rare that someone goes out and does anything
Without considering how they're going to accommodate those that are participating so
Yeah, but what that said, let's go is he's got number two. Can you go into any more specificity in regard to lawful timekeeping?
Oh
boy
Yes, what about this so-called equinox
All right, let's back up
Lawful timekeeping. What is time people still don't you know Seth?
I found that I've been saying this for over a decade and people still don't want to hear it forget about listening
You still have people saying well, there's no such thing as time, you know, it's relevant. It's relative
And I think we've played the Fox and the grapes before by the way
Aesop's fable ties into that
Right. Yes, we should probably play that again because
If you don't mind, we've got about 15 minutes. It might be good. Let's see if we could bring this up
Any any subject matter that
is brought up for public discussion that
It's not popular to comprehend. By the way, it is I've noticed them a
social norm that if people when they're when they're presented with some information and
they look around before they they delve into it and see how popular that information is or what the
Accepted responses to it. You ever noticed that
I'm not talking about when you talk to someone and their eyes start bouncing up and down like slot machines and things like that
Talking about when you bring up the notion of definitions the notion of what's lawful
They immediately pause and they're wondering in their minds what everyone else thinks about that topic
Yeah, that's Gustav Le Bon's the crowd mentality, by the way, but
I'm gonna do the Fox and the grapes because
This is what you encounter most of the time especially I mean there are people that have entire careers
I don't know how well they do on the internet with websites books
memberships and all this stuff based on the concept of
The Fox and the grapes and they don't know it obviously
But what we do
Yes, and we're gonna maybe play this short little audio. It's from children's books. Let's see how it goes up a hungry Fox
Came across a rich and luscious grapevine
A bunch of ripe grapes were hanging from a height a
Good way above the ground
The Fox made several attempts to jump up and pluck the grapes
But his efforts were in vain
Tired and hungry he walked off grumpily and murmured I
Am sure those grapes were nasty and sour
I'm glad I could not reach them
They were definitely not worth eating
It is easy to belittle what you cannot obtain
The Fox spoke badly of the grapes
Only because he could not reach them and was forced to go away hungry
To lessen his disappointment of not getting what he wanted
He comforted himself with the idea that the grapes were sour
There you go
many times if you try to have a discussion privately or publicly with people and they're like, oh
That's just a work of fiction. Oh, that's your opinion. Oh, that's that's the Fox and the grapes
Yeah, I don't get it it must be horrible
Well, you want to set yourself apart and just contact these surface-dwelling earth inhabitants only when necessary at this point
Did I just say that yes, I did
Okay, which could be quite often on occasion if you open a lemonade stand, you're going to be contacting them quite often
so
lawful timekeeping
Let's just give another way to explain it. Well, we just gave the preface on that
Let's let's look at this
At one point society was in the light and at another point society is in the dark
Let's describe what we mean by that at one point society garnered all of its materials from
materials that were produced in the light plant fibers
animal products
plant inks surface
minerals
Right things that were in the light
They started their day in the light at high noon solar noon. They started their year in
the light at the beginning of spring and
The new moon was the full moon which was full of light
Well, there's another society
that
Garners everything from the dark
If you look at something called crude oil
It's formed in the dark. It's black and it's been used on everything
plastics materials dyes
things made or
connected
Encoded with byproducts from this dark substance that is formed in the dark
their day
starts
the darkest part of the day
their year
starts the darkest season darkest month darkest week darkest day darkest everything and
Their new moon is dark
Should we say anymore
How can anything
Doesn't relate to darkness be accepted by such a society
Think about that for a moment
Hasn't always been that way. It's now. Yeah
Yeah, there have been societies in the past
that
You know, that's that's what they did they it was they kept time with the with the daylight with the light of the moon
Light of the Sun the light of the Sun. Yeah, absolutely
Yeah, what do you?
Look at that. For example when you say societies
By the way, just just to bring this up
I was in a sort of like a Skype call recently and there were quite a few professional people
they're highly educated older and
they were using the term academic quite a bit and I said, why don't we go and look it up and
They didn't know how to do that it took them about 10 minutes and they still couldn't get the etymology dictionary up online
Pull it up. My comment was it sounds like a pretty typical human group. These were like professionals people
They they were there there were censored to the point where they couldn't even look up the word academic
which by the way means
Theoretical impractical never leading to a conclusion pretty dark
lawful timekeeping
What is time
It is nothing more nothing less than the recordation of events. It's a form of communication of
recording events
Now that's another subject because the recordation of events has become so corrupt your history and your academic
Information is all false, by the way
And that would be history meaning recording previous events. So you've been so mind-plugged
About things being memorialized
That right now is most of society just actually truly believes that everything
Sprang into existence less than a hundred years ago
What I mean by that is if you ask one of these surface-dwelling earth inhabitants that they'll say of course not
But everything they engage in is pretty much can't go back more than a hundred years or so
And most people not even 10 or 15 years very difficult to
So time is nothing more than their recordation of events what makes it lawful is that you're not dependent on one thing
That you have to purchase or subscribe to or even if you were that thing is not fiat
Fiat means it's based on nothing
Currently, let's just discuss currently the world has accepted the Pope's work schedule. Yes. I'm going to say it one more time slowly
The Pope's work schedule is what's called the Gregorian calendar. What well, what does that mean?
it means that
For papal subjects, they know when to go to work and when to take days off. It is a work schedule
it has absolutely nothing with keeping time and
The the saddest thing is people that want to break away. They they do like certain study groups and they still follow it
And I'm just saying if they shouldn't I'm just saying it's sad to watch on one hand
They're professing to be the bastion of truth and facts and knowledge
And on the other hand, they start talking about things like Saturday
and Monday
Lost me folks
That's work schedule. It can't keep time with it proof of that. Let's pull up one of these ridiculous calendars today is what they call
7 9 2 0 1 6
I guess that would be I don't know. What is that? July 9th 2016 and it's what they call a Saturday
So let's go back in 2016
Okay, July 9th on 2015
Was what they call a Thursday or a Thor's Day
All right, you want to go back? Let's go back one more time just to
Wear this out just a little bit
On what they called
2014 July 9th was what they call a Woden's day or a Wednesday
All right
Everybody stop
So is July 9th a Woden's day a Thor's day or a Saturn's day?
Anybody answer that you can't you know why because it's not a timepiece
The earth doesn't go around the Sun in
364 and a quarter days no such thing
Can't keep time with the earth going around the Sun
knowledge of the earth going around the Sun or the earth bouncing around like an 8-ball in the corner pocket on a billiard table or
the earth being flat or triangular or
The shape of a boar's penis or anything like ridiculous like that is irrelevant
What's relevant? Are you mastering its movements with your feet on the ground? What do you perceive and have you mastered?
What you've perceived and applied it to your physical world to better your life and the answer to that is no
The rest of it is irrelevant
so
The worst thing by the way is you have quite a few people not as much anymore as I used to hear
Bad-mouthing the Vatican the papacy Rome
All right, ask one of these morons
What day is it today?
Now you didn't ask the day and the date you asked the day now the date and the day are two different things
We're not playing around with words here, but
And they'll give you a date based on the Pope's work schedule
So on one hand, they're bad-mouthing the papacy and on the other hand, they're admitting with their own mouth be intimately
They're a papal subject
So the next time you hear someone bad-mouthing the papacy
Interrupt them and ask them what day it is
If they respond with what's on the Pope's work schedule
There's someone that's headed for a padded room with a cherry lollipop
Eventually, so what is lawful timekeeping?
Well something everyone can access and it's based on something
Maybe we'll stop right there
greetings and welcome to uncommon sense again, you can find us at
www.uncommonradio.com
Put in the
www.com around uncommon radio because there's it's a common term on the browser and there you will find a way to
contact the Greek and Seth Michael and various other courtesies on that page and
So on and so forth. So you are listening to American Freedom Radio
We thank the crew at American Freedom Radio for having us on
and
You know what to do American Freedom Radio just like many other venues
Requires your participation and when I say, you know what to do go to the home page and
Make a donation. So with that said
Let's proceed. Let's see if Seth will join us again in a moment and
Maybe continue on a particular message that we got from a quote-unquote listener
We were discussing about lawful timekeeping and the nature of time and what its purpose is
Outside of this solipsism that nothing matters
You know people
are
engaged in this
grandiose idea that opinions are things to hinge one's belief on and
discussions if you ever been in a
discussion as I have
Typically electronic brought into a group and you'll hear someone just talking about the most ridiculous stuff
With five people standing around agreeing or not saying anything now typically instead of steamrolling the guy
That's just talking
I kind of want to get into the people that are around him saying this guy is obviously fallen on his face
Spiritually or mentally and no one's helping him get up. You're all just sitting there watching him muck and mire and
his own fecal matter and
There is a lack of support
That is persistent in society and it part of the thing is that somehow
somewhere
Opinions were given significance
So when you think about that
For a moment, let it set in because it is very contrary to what is lawful
You know, what is what things should be based on that means like what anyone can access
You know, we the going back to the the email here that we were reading
It was about can we get into more lawful timekeeping? It's it's very simple. Are you keeping time with something that is based on something?
Right now
We talked about the Pope's work schedule aka the Gregorian calendar with your work week and weekend
That is nothing more than a work schedule
Now you also have what I call the wind-up toy
It's a mechanical clock
These things are
hmm, I would say more navigational instruments than anything else if you know a rate of travel and you have a
Mechanical beat to it. You can determine according to that mechanical beat or the wind-up toy or whatever
a
Form of communication that will give you a time of arrival as long as everyone is using that system
But it is not lawful because these things can change
So so I hear an echo by the way, by the way back. Sorry. Yeah. Okay, and and
All right, so the the other thing here the just to continue on a lawful timekeeping we we have given this much in the past
Let's just give it again
Solar noon is when the day starts folks
Where you're at, you know, so if you put aside what you think, you know about reaping
Relevant a relative. Yes where you're at a solar noon put a stick in the ground
you'll notice in the morning prior to noon the shadow goes to the west and
You'll notice that afternoon the shadow goes to the east but there is a point
Where if you're on the northern hemisphere
The shadow is straight up and down or slightly to the north on the southern hemisphere be slightly to the south
All right, that's that's your time and you could actually divide time down to as many decimal places as you want
Depending on the the length of the shadow and other things if anyone is interested on an elaborate
aspects of
It's not a sundial
but
Solar timekeeping
Do a browser search on?
Sun clocks of India
They still have some quite elaborate ones in public parks and things. Some of them are three stories tall
Now you'll also notice if you do markings that are indelible with these solar markings as the year goes around
That particular day the marking is slightly off and that's a way to dictate the year
but again, if you want to go to your
Timekeeping authorities there used to be a prominent page on Julian calendar date on the Naval Observatory, which is the American timekeeping
Authority and on Julian calendar date on their web page now
I've heard I haven't gone there recently, but I've heard that it's been since taken down. It states that
For scientific and astronomical purposes the day starts at solar noon, but for the people it's civil midnight
So that's a good example of how the old dictionaries were written
Where you looked up the word oats?
It was defined as what they feed horses in England, but the staple of the people in Scotland
Kind of a put-down indirectly if you ask me
But solar noon is when the day starts
And then we could jump to weeks you have four
Divisions
Four weeks per month and the month is ruled by the moon
That's why for thousands of years
People settled their debts with the new moon, which was the full moon, which you can see and measure
Today, it's conventional that people get a monthly bill
For utilities and things
contracts
There's a reason why they call it monthly and
And
The full moon is the new moon folks, by the way, there's a long history and how
Astronomers and astrologers have gone into the it's actually convoluted history, but essentially
It has shifted to the dark moon as being new which you cannot really do any measurements on it's so gradual
There it casts no shadow. There's no marking. There's nothing that can be done for it
Then again, we talked about a society that's based on darkness
Now
Let's just give one little account a general account on why the new moon is the dark moon back in the
Egyptian and Babylonian Convention
These solar the solar the Sun and the moon. Let's say were important for timekeeping and recordation of events
practices regarding worship and other things and
When the moon was dark
People, you know, we're wondering if it stays dark
We won't be able to reckon time
so we need our leaders to be
Confined we can't have them traveling around
Not only leaving the border of their jurisdiction
Let's say the Kings and what-have-you the priests, but maybe we should they should just stay within their palace or their homes
till the moon reappears because if they leave and we have the people that lead us leave and travel and
The moon doesn't come back. What are we to do?
So they waited until the sliver was sighted in the West
Took a little while nothing much to measure
just visual and
it freed up the
authorities again
for mobility
Very interesting. That's why if you look at some ancient texts
There was a group of people that left Egypt and it was around the dark time of the dark moon
But the pursuit of these people did not commence until the moon was sighted it was actually several days later that the pursuit began
Put that together with what I just said, what's that? Well, maybe you've might have heard that something relating to that story
So your your timekeeping is based on things that are exist
It's not fiat
We just kind of evidenced that you can't keep time with the Pope's work schedule. We just did something with what's called July 9th
Showed you that it occurs on different days of
The week every year. So which one is it? Is it July 9th, or is it a Woden's day a Thursday or a Saturn's day?
It's neither. It's none of them and
You folks are operating like everything's just hunky-dory
Right because who cares?
But some people do care so
So Seth, let's continue on this a little bit about timekeeping which we've kind of done over and over I think you
Mentioned something about repetition once I think we're kind of experiencing it
Certainly
Anything else you want to add to the so far the Sun and the moon that we've discussed
There's interesting the book of Enoch was mentioned in chat earlier and it's just there's interesting references to
Accurate timekeeping in Enoch as well
We've never let's just spill this out the book of Enoch and the book of Jasher Yashar or the book of the upright
Are chronicles that were written by the temple priesthood?
at the time
They were there were chronicles in other words things notes that a certain group of people took
and
They were dubbed, you know one the book of the upright book of Yashar or Jasher
There's no letter J by the way before 1500 so mind that folks and also the book of Enoch
Yeah, it's not it was not written by Enoch and such so so I mean here
You know, I'm just putting this out as a very strong presumption assumption and probably some of the most accurate information
You'll ever get on those two
texts so
All right now
We talked about the Sun and the moon in the years
We're gonna leave alone because that's kind of like more than addition and subtraction, you know, but here folks
How can how can you how can it be the year?
2016 and you turn on a show regarding the dinosaurs and you notice how they always plug in 60 million years ago when they say
dinosaurs
Why isn't it the year 60 million?
2016 then I mean you're so far removed from anything rational at this point
I think going to discussing how the years work. Oh, let me just plug this in about the years by the way
You ever hear about this thing called the Jubilee and I think last year all these morons were making a big stink about it
You know one moron says something and then they all grab on to it
You know what? I mean by that or imbecile look up Gustav LeVon le bon the crowd
I'm not promoting the book, but it's got some good commentary on it. So
Yeah
These things can be determined and no it was not last year
Yeah, the Jubilee happened around 18 years ago folks, and you all missed it as usual pretty much miss everything
So let's go on. What do you think Seth?
Next thing is about the equinox
What about this so-called equinox? Well, think about it folks. It's just
Equally means equal and knocks means night. So it has to do with something about being equally measured at night and
you folks
Have been told
That it's equal daylight and equal night
It's real simple I think when they people are looking for the equinox to be equal daylight equal nighttime
I'm envisioning seven billion people finger painting on the wall with chocolate pudding
That's the level of maturity
Word means actually something measured at night and that's pretty much New Year's
What is what does that mean? Well, if you'll notice that the Sun takes a path through the sky
Equatorial perhaps and
This the path that the Sun takes through the sky in the summer is
The path that the moon takes through the sky in the winter and they switch places
Across the year, but during the spring and the fall typically
For one day the moon and the Sun will go traverse the
Path in the sky identical
To each other in other words the way that can be determined is by measuring shadows
And it's funny once I was discussing this with an academic
And I said well if the equinox has to do with measurement at night
How are you going to measure the shadow of the moon?
This is this is this is where this is where you're pranking your children folks
You're you're putting together all these credits and sending
Children to these morons known as University or college all of them are by the way, not some of them
right and
And this moron asks
How do you measure the shadow of the moon at night right this is this is the level of
Rationale right now. I don't know if anyone's been out during the full moon at night and the shadows are razor-sharp
So so there you go, that's your equinox and that will happen at the beginning of the year at the end of the year
Usually in the first month and usually in the seventh month I noticed a question in the chat about intercalation
Seth we've been discussing these things for several years together
And I believe you've experienced properly calling an intercalation
Which is a 13th month right once it was a couple of years ago, wasn't it?
Yeah, yeah properly calling it that means that I'm not going to get into that
Because it's more than just adding and subtracting
You know it's just beyond the pay scale of those that just want to hear about the subject
But it's definitely should be included on those that want to actually live it or delve into it
and I don't think that
Doing two hours a week on a minor internet radio station getting into minutiae as such
Especially things that are lawful like that is valid
But there will be another place that these things can be discussed hopefully in the future, but in essence
The intercalation is where you have a 13th month, and it typically happens three times every decade
So there goes your
You know argument of other 360 or 360
For or 365 days in a year because you can have it a year with 393 days
Okay, or 396 I've measured
almost 400 days in a year sometimes
So this has to do with things that you are not
Made privy to because it has nothing to do with going to work and so-called paying taxes
It has absolutely nothing to do with that so it has nothing to do with most people, but it has a lot to do with
Learning about what lawful things are about so that gets I think very complicated
to my son
Where does one research that?
Where does one find lots of research?
Direction earlier, it's an certain. It's a topic. That's not discussed
really any anywhere
Yeah, yeah, how does one research societies that don't exist anymore?
precisely
Yeah, and by the way when I speak of that
There's no such thing as a bronze age and iron age or a stone age by the way that is
And there's no such thing as neanderthal man by the way and chromatic all this other stuff you folks are
Yeah
Beyond pale
You can have a stone society or a bronze society or an iron society
Right, but there's no such thing as an age where everyone
Was banging rocks together, and then they figured out how to work with bronze and then iron
You're kind of being laughed at but you know at this point if you go to these places
of academia
Kind of like tying this into societies that don't exist anymore
Because what the reason I'm bringing this up is because what people think exists or it had existed doesn't never existed at all
So it's like a double whammy to go back and study societies that don't exist anymore because they're going to go into this
Iron Age Bronze Age Stone Age crap, right?
But if you look at
Academia that tends to pump this garbage out. They believe it also
They have to you know at this point because in order to move up that
academic ladder, you're actually going lower and lower in intelligence, but
I
gave an example the other day of
Go to a circus and you see a bear doing a trick
That's a really smart bear to the people you throw that sucker back into the forest man
It's gonna get laughed at by all the other bears
What the hell is standing on a ball and juggling oranges have to do with being out here in the forest dummy, so
This is how things are done. It's a dog and pony show and
Yeah, enjoy the show isn't that what they say about shows great show
Hate to see what a crappy show was like. But anyway, yeah
So your equinox is about measuring at night. So, you know, here's the the thing
How many times can it be said that everything that?
Pretty much people engage in think believe in is false. So how many times can one say that and not be true?
Hardly ever it's always true seemingly
statistically
Yes
Statistically, we can't say a hundred percent because then we have to go and recount everything again, and I don't want to do that
So maybe we'll say ninety nine point nine nine nine nine nine and leave the other
Point zero nine's out in case someone is in doubt
They can go and count all the grains of sand on the beach again. Make sure the numbers, right?
Absolutely
All right. Well, he says here about the equinox. I just
What about this so-called equinox are supposed to be equivalence in measurement between daylight and absence of light
Something is obviously wrong here. But once again who's paying attention?
Wow man a little attitude there, I wonder where you got that from just joking
So, I think we got the equinox and lawful timekeeping again cursory overview
It's like a smooth stone you want to pass your hand over not break out a chisel on a hammer
Start chiseling away at it and showing how it can be formed into
Things that people can use I think it's kind of scary when you start bringing people into what's lawful and unlawful
I mean lawful meaning it's based on something
Yeah, there's
there's practical applications that are
Present
in being set apart and and how you interact with the environment around you, but trying to
Explain these things
to
others is
It's very difficult and it will not necessarily improve
What do they call that public relations?
No, no, and they're not used to explanations there. They want descriptions
They're used to descriptions all of their science and the ridiculous matters that people tend to pursue are based on description
There's very little explanation
Very little at all the why or the how
You know the why maybe but the how yeah, there's not much on that
It's kind of like there's a film. I think called idiocracy. You know, what's what's why do you what's Brondo?
What's got electrolytes? What are electrolytes? It's in Brondo
Yeah, so what's that, you know, what are all these things what's electrons man the electrons moving down the wire, you know, really
Okay
So if I cut this wire live wire
I should be equipped with a really small dustpan to sweep up all the electrons that fall on the floor
Yeah, but things that flow in a conduit don't they the conduits broken don't they kind of like come out of the conduit?
You know, don't ask any questions. Who are you? Where'd you get your degree?
Yeah
You know, we're the ones doing the pranking here
The green that's a that's a
What a deodorant, right
Yeah, that's right because they do stink. Yeah, and and there's people still encouraging the children to go and become pranksters
Go to college man, so you could get a good job. And yeah, the children are like wait a second, you know
You've been pranking me all my life. And and now I got to go and be a prankster. Yeah, that's right
Welcome to planet Earth
Feel sorry for the young people. I really do
But anyway
We'll change the subject
Here a number three. Can you elaborate on the nature of voltage?
It seems to be analogous to density perhaps more or less lines of electrical force
Well, let's let's look at that objectively. I'm not going to do it now because I
Don't want to sound pedantic. But if you do some research on what voltage or volt means it
Goes something like this and I'm paraphrasing. It's the at the rate at which a magnetic field
Appears
Is produced or disappears or is dissipated in an electrical circuit. I'm not going to repeat that. I just paraphrased it
and your devices that measure voltages were
Very similar to all of your measuring devices of pressure devices. What I mean by that is
for a very long time people use
gauges and devices to measure movements and forces based on pressure a
the simplest one would be a balancing scale you put a weight on one side and
Then an equal weight on the other side will balance the scale if the weight is higher or lower
The scale is higher or lower respectively
based on pushing or
Pulling which is very similar
but
This is what your measuring devices are. They're based on pushes pulls things like that. They don't measure quality
And various other phenomenon and I can almost say that quality is a phenomenon these days
It's not being discussed again
Like when I look at some of these internet chat groups and they say great show I'd hate to hear what a crappy show sounds
like but anyway
Yeah, where's the gauge of quality? There is none
I
Guess filling up two hours with no pauses makes it a great show. So anyway
Voltage difficult to define you have to define what magnetism is and all these things by the way
the in the nature of electricity
Discussing this is difficult because of course we've just mentioned it's very plausible that everything
Was created less than a hundred years ago
And we're modern and we're so technologically advanced and we're so smart
Well, if you look back behind that hundred-year veil
You'll find that there was no such thing as science that were called natural philosophers
And if you keep looking and looking and looking and especially looking for those books that have all been taken out of the libraries
Oh, no books. I
Don't get my knowledge from a book. I get it from experience anyway
You'll find out that by reading some of the people Galvani Volta
Hertz
people before that
Even in ancient times that electricity was known to be a phenomenon or an occurrence that happened with biological beings
It was hand in hand with things that are alive
Even today I have heard several doctors in passing state
That the movement of the intestines and organs is an electromechanical function
This is your regular. Dr. Moron, you know the ones that you know, dr. Moron, dr. Moron calling dr. Moron
Yeah, but where is their electrotherapy if they self-admit that
The body is
electromechanical at least functions of intestines and organs are
Why are they just prescribing pills?
Where's the electrotherapy? Oh, yeah. Wait a second. They do provide electrotherapy in some cases, don't they?
So can be
called therapy
I'm sure that there are those that do but yes, well, here's the thing
It depends on which side you're on if you're on the receiving end. I wouldn't call therapy
But if you're the psychopath meaning the sick mind
Administering it it might be therapeutic for them
So anyway, by the way psychopaths just means sick spirit
Yeah pain
Yeah discomfort. Yeah, so if you've been on this planet for more than 15 minutes
This is the planet of the psychopaths folks. You just have different qualities
You have the psychopaths up top and then all the psychopaths following the difference is when the psychopath is up top
He commands that all the other psychopaths
Give 90% of their energy to him or his organization or her organization
And then just stab each other in the back for the remaining 10%
Now you could take any of the other psychopaths and put them in that position and it all assumes very much fine
So when you hear a lot of discussion about being ruled by psychopaths or 2% of the population psychopathic now folks, it's ninety nine point nine
nine nine percent
So and that's a fact you may not like it, but most people don't like facts anyway, so okay
So that's the thing about the spiel about voltage
There's too much confusion
Okay, so let's move on to the next question
There's a fellow named Eric Dollard if anyone wants to research Eric dollar do
LL a RD
Interesting individual he's come across many things that he's
Talked about over the years
You can find him on the internet research look at some of his videos
He professes and I profess also by looking at it that all electrical engineering
Pretty much ceased about 80 or 90 years ago
In terms of developing new weight ways and ideas and by the way folks this thing you hear about the electron
That was propagated that was almost abandoned by the way by the 30s and 40s
But it was heavily propagated by Walt Disney the atomic model the planetary atomic model spent millions of his own
Credits Walt Disney Walt Disney. Yes
Yes, he has a temple called Disneyland that you all worship at not all but enough people do
Yeah, he's the one that propagated that and why it's stuck today. So
And here continuing the answers higher potential to ground. Well, you know, here's interesting thing
We started off by discussing something about the ether and weather engineering now
This is one thing if anyone is interested in dabbling or pursuing this
The ether is completely imponderable and it goes from a low to high potential
You've been taught that all potentials go from high to low
This goes from low to high
it's like kind of like
Difficult to wrap the mind around if you could turn your head inside out like a sock you'll get a grasp on it
So here higher potential to ground well the ground also has a potential which is moving somewhere else
So that's a we'll leave this alone
Subject of electricity
Much of the concept of comprehension of the thing known as electricity or the phenomenon known as electrical phenomenon
Are difficult to discuss without hours of prefacing?
The nature of what can be observed objectively
Objectivity is where it's at like for example if you had real education real schooling or anything like that in any field
Whether it was in the spiritual arts
engineering medicine, what have you
90% of these schools or educational facilities would focus on objectivity and the last 10% would be focused on the topic at hand or
the matter that you were subscribing to
Think about that for a minute. Okay, how to think versus what to think?
Yes, and you're gonna have to learn how to learn
Think about that
Yeah, remember folks you may this might sound a little obtuse, but you're only gonna get this for about two hours a week
And it's kind of limited
and you know after we're gone you go back to all the other stuff that you guys are
like listening to or
participating in so yeah, so remember this is just if it's out if we sound rather obtuse or
Not in line with what you're used to
Good. Yeah, you might need a little nudge here and there
You'll most of you will forget everything you've heard here. Anyway, I'm not being condescending. I'm just being objective
And if you can prove me, otherwise, I'd be glad to listen. So here in the email
He also goes back and writes. Oh, I'll shut up. But okay. Well, hopefully you will provide a tiny tiny spoon feed
Oh, maybe we did. Thank you both for all you do
Thank you enough
Well, I guess that's enough of a thanks a little gratitude I guess so that was that email it covered several subjects
I think they were worth garnering the time for and
I'll kick it to you Seth. What do you think?
So far, we've got you know, two hours a week here and we're not looking to fill things, you know
For the two hours. We're not looking for filler
We're just looking for what can we say we have four or five people that are publicly listening and what can we make?
The highest order and the highest use of this opportunity
I mean, there's there's many things that we'd like to say. I think they're for not at this point
I think the timing will be more
apropos in the next couple of years to discuss a lot of the things that people will be questioning, but
Yeah, let's take a pause for a moment here something. What do you think so far?
Objectivity is
Rare uncommon about that extremely uncommon
We can we can move from that to
Another email. I'm not certain that this I think this one came directly to me, but it was in
response to us
Speaking about dreams and again, this is more of a singular case as opposed to something that is really common
But it's it's something we can get into
Oh, you mean we can just preface by saying you're beginning to feel very sleepy
That's you're just you're feeling sleepy the power of suggestion, right? Okay
Absolutely, I'll just I'll just read read through some of it
It's it's a little bit lengthy, but I can I can get through to a question relatively quickly
I think and anonymously and anonymously. Yeah
Hello. Thank you for bringing up the question that of the dream
And some good information came out of it, unfortunately, I already understand
Most of what was said is the Greek said it was mostly a broad outline in my own opinion
It is very hard to settle with this being simply a pranking intent
As I said, there is much quality in my dreams more than this creation
Nothing is hazy or unclear and I do feel sensations including pain
For example, I was stabbed in a dream recently and it was real to me that pain the feeling of adrenaline from blood loss
the fear
Begging this being standing over me to please stop. There's too much quality for it to be a prank
It would be futile. All of my dreams are not negative and some are very enjoyable simply from peaceful state of mind
This being the case from an objective point of view. It's hard to discount this technology of communication
there must be more of an importance to it because it may be the easiest form of communication to the other side and
it's dangerous for anyone to pass it off simply because there's
More lies than truths
That is just my opinion and I could be completely wrong but there is most likely something else behind dreams
I know I'm not the most
Knowledgeable person but like nature nothing is futile in creation
I've actually been listening since the psychohistory program. So I'm quite familiar with the public broadcast, but I just can't help
But feel so much is not being said and parts of truth easily get misinterpreted
But I apologize. I'm not sure what kind of answer I was looking for and that's yeah
They answered a lot of the stuff himself there is stated its opinion
So we know how what we think about that and on the next level the quality just because it's vivid and clear
I mean, I just mentioned there's
Looking at a lot of these internet shows I go to the chest to see what kind of feedback they're getting and I mean these shows
Are just total crap and the people are like great show
So I'm like what's what makes it I mean, where's that, you know
So if you think something is quality go to a McDonald's and people are just so glad to be there and eat that, you know
I'm not putting that corporation down or anything
You know, but you know, there's quality is very subjective
So this is extremely subjective, but I'm glad you read it. I'm not discounting it or pushing it aside
I do appreciate the communication because obviously as a strong effect on this
Individual but no, I I don't find it to change much or add or take away much. I think it's just one's experience
I think it actually
Underpins everything that we've discussed you yeah
Yeah, and that's that's kind of what what I got from it and what my response would be as well
I didn't actually respond to that email, but it's someone who listens to the program with fair regularity
so yeah, and actually listening and it's
The quality and vividness just
You know as you said underpins though, it's a clear form of communication
That's that's still
What's what's going on and what is behind it?
well, I mean
Sometimes you sometimes you just want it. Well, I
Shouldn't say it like this, but if it's better to make it go away than to figure out who's behind it
You may not want to go that way
Yeah, because we're talking about on their side the lowest being still have an IQ around a million
So you can try before going to sleep?
Standing up opening your the the door, you know the front door to your domicile and yelling get out
Really loudly and then slamming the door. Yeah, good. See give that a shot
Yeah, they get the message. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but nonetheless it's it's yeah
Well, by the way, we do appreciate that
That means that you're doing more than hearing you're actually listening to what's being said and reporting back
your experience
Which is one of many I guess it's like a snowflake
you know in a snowstorm you can examine a snowflake and it's quite unique and
just like most people you will have
a
Unique way of interacting with this reality, but nonetheless it's still a snowstorm
And at cursory view it all looks the same and it piles up everywhere
and there's lots of
quote-unquote accounts that people can deliver and communicate, but essentially
it's external the
The input is external the the understanding of headquarters. I call headquarters the soul
The spirit and the body which is saying the breath the mind and the body. That's what animates
The being at this point
And by the way still I am still met personally by the way in discussion
With just being a mint resistance to defining any of that
I mean the body they kind of like don't want to discuss it seems obvious even though it's not and
You bring up the soul man. Oh, wow people get so upset you try to define those things. I
Had a discussion someone the other days
Recently talking about how effective a blowgun is right, you know the dart through the tube kind of thing
I'm saying oh, I got a nickname for that. We'll call it the soul gun, right?
so
It's so practical. I think people still have an extreme resistance to practicality and
Accessing technically accessing at least in their mind what I mean technical access is you be able to communicate it with words accurately
pretty much anything in reality
They they still don't want that and I could see why
ultimately
you know the last thing that
You might want to have to keep this place under control of seven billion people that are aware and knowledgeable and can communicate that
awareness and knowledge
You know
You think about it because then you won't no longer have stupid people in large groups
The danger kind of goes away, and you might act rationally
Too rationally, so yeah
Those dreams things keep coming back don't they or dream stories or dream concepts, but Seth
You know I just want to throw this in we haven't pretty much discussed this in a long time
If anyone does a little bit of homework, they'll discover when they hear the word soul
It means the word breath, and it's pretty material, but immaterial like wind you don't really see
The wind you see its effect you don't really see the soul you see its effect it animates
It's a pulsing action, and you do share the same salt soul with everything else that breathes
Right like in other words something known as resuscitation or CPR or?
You know you can resuscitate an animal by putting your soul in its body and breathing in it
I know this is making most people cringe because you know they don't want to look at it
But that's whenever you hear in the Greek influence the prefix PNU new like pneumonia pneumatic
Pneuma in Greek that Pneuma that means
breath simply
Inhaling and exhaling put a piece of glass or a mirror up to the mouth and nose and exhale
And you will see it fog up that is your soul or the soul you're using
And the spirit is the mind in Greek. It's the psyche or the psyche so whenever you see a PSY
prefix psychology psychotic
Psychic psychology all that PSY it means the mind
When you go to a psychiatrist he's dealing with the mind and by the way anyone who wants to go see a psychiatrist should have
their head examined, but nonetheless
People will fight you if you discover this by the way to be the way
It's communicated you will not make any friends
No one wants to talk to you, but you will have a deep sense of satisfaction
You're getting a grip on communicating technically and accurately what is going on with headquarters meaning yourself
You have a mind you have a soul you have a body and no folks. They're not interchangeable and
When you go into something called a concordant definition that just means an accepted term of its use like
Concordantly the word nice means pleasant
Or good
Etymologically and what the word really means is foolish senseless and stupid
So let's just say this. This is not a nice show
hopefully
And if it's a great show
That's yet to be discovered. Please folks. Don't ever put in the chat. This is a great show
You got to come up with a different word because that doesn't mean much
But anyway concordantly
So there you go if you want to make people cringe
especially the people in the New Age movement those talking about the spirit and the soul and Ascension and
Peace and love and making the world a better place and all this stuff you usually hear
When you hear talk like that I
Kind of listen to it a little bit because I'm thinking the next thing that they're going to discuss with seriousness is advanced
nose-picking and underwater basket weaving
Advanced advanced nose-picking. Yes
They yeah, it's just bizarre folks. So yeah, here's your you know
Here's your commentary on what's going on and you will find it to be true. By the way, let's just throw this in
If you're looking at any ancient text in the Chaldean Hebrew
Aspect of it even ancient Egyptian you will find the Nef what's any any F phonetically Nef?
Is the breath that's why sometimes if you read some stuff out of ancient Egypt, well, you probably won't but anyway
You'll see that fish have an F also, you know, so they breathe and birds have an F doesn't mean spirit
They'll translate that as spirit as the mind to confuse just reverse it, you know
Instead of but if you want to prank someone who doesn't know where they're going
They ask you where they want to go. You it should be they should make a right hand turn up ahead
You just don't make a left. Why cuz you like pranking? It's so simple. It's just say left instead of right and
You know that they're going the wrong way very simply
So when you when you look at any of the ancient languages in the Middle East area or eastern part, you will see Nef any F
as meaning breath and that's all it is and
Rook or Rook means spirit or mind
So when you come across that
And we're not playing
word games here where
You know here rook, you know, like maybe the chess piece or something like that. It means the mind. It's something else but
Yeah, so you could
Pretty much land those definitions and technically access the information held within
But if you go ahead and look at your concordant
Hmm definition shall we say very loose. They will always switch
Spirit and soul definition not almost well almost always right Seth you look up spirit in
most I mean the text that I'm familiar with that have concordance I
Would say that there are
rare instances where it's
Accurate, but that only leads to the confusion
because
They're not consistent
With translating one word into one and one into the other
They will it's that's how confused that is
that even in
one passage where
You know Nefesh is translated as soul. There will be a later passage where it is translated as spirit
Into you know English, which is what I'm familiar with. But yeah, so it's just leads to leads to the confusion
That's why I suggest
Anyone looking at stuff like that, you know, there are tools available
Readily if you have access to the Internet
that make looking up the
memorialized text
relatively easy
It can still lead to confusion. I suppose but right for singular words
I mean you can it's relatively easy to do a word search and find each instance of that word and
What is being described in context and whatnot that can provide a little bit of clarity
so yeah grabbing the hold of the definitions of
prefixes and suffixes helps
as well
And you'll see how overt these things are. But then again, this is just an opinion. That's your opinion, man
Yeah opinion just washes everything away. You know folks when you are in discussions and
Something is either propped up or discounted or agreed with as an opinion or because a group of people are agreeing with something
Makes it true
You're all you know what you're really doing that is a group of space heaters you are just heating up the room
There's no purpose there. What's going on? So snap out of it folks
I've been brought into several discussions through
Several periods of time and I hear someone just talking about the stuff. That's just unfounded rubbish and
a
Bunch of people come out of it and say I agree with that and all of a sudden
The topic is done and it's closed and it's true because they agree with it
All right. Now we'll
go to the store and buy a whole bunch of space heaters and
Put on one of them
You know
The moon is made of cheese and then put a label on the other three space heaters
Let's say I agree with that and that's objective what I am objectifying in conversations here
Stop being a space heater folks
Snap out of it
Anyway, I just thought I'd throw that in as a mini rant
So I think some people do take offense by the way
describing
People as morons or imbeciles or idiots, maybe we'll just switch over to space heaters. I mean, does that sound a little better?
It's less derogatory to
To shoot then some of the other terms are yeah. Yeah, and by the way, they're not they're not sheep. Oh, they're goats
You know sheep have a very very particular diet goats will eat anything, right?
Yeah, boy. Yeah
So yeah objectified people if you can
Yeah
discernment discernment is
important
In you know taking in any sort of information
They're not validating anything, you know, there's a level of comfort though, you know, that's the other thing that can be discussed
They're the the physical body and the soul
The physical body and the soul
Tend to create the the background for the mind if the you notice if the body
Well, let's say let's go in reverse if something disturbing enters the mind
There's a change in the soul in the physical body, you know, like if you get bad news or threatening news
The breathing pattern the soul changes and the body becomes tense. Let's say or changes and vice versa
If the body becomes uncomfortable and the breathing pattern and the soul change the it's expressed through the mind as well
communication
so
One should kind of consider this tripartite existence
And it's a balancing act
It's very hard to have a clear mind if the soul or the body and the breath are suffering
or enduring
Something traumatic or challenging and vice versa if the mind endures something a bit of information
It is expressed through the breath and the breathing. Let's say of the individual or being and the body as well
So we've never really gotten into the juggling act between those three
Because you can actually just command one aspect
Like slow down your breathing that would be slowing down the soul
It has an effect on the mind and it has an effect on the body
Or just strictly
affecting the body, you know
Elevate the body or you know rapidly move
The body has an effect on the breathing and on the mind or then on the mind think about this
It'll have an effect on the breathing and effect on the body. So either
Affecting each individual one
We should be strictly the mind the spirit or the soul of the breath or the body will have an effect on the other two
So it's a juggling act, you know
in essence and we've never really gone into the details of that, but who wants to talk about juggling in detail anyway, so
And by the way, I'm just going to reiterate one of the things since we're talking about juggling acts
there's something interesting about
beliefs now one way to look at
an interesting way about how beliefs can or should work as
A belief is a process of technically accessing communication
Of something that has happened in the past or something that will happen in the future
What I mean has happened means it's tangible
Like a belief for example rational belief can be that you had a grandfather
Or a grandmother or a great-great-grandmother because you're here now
There is a certain biological interest in line that continues through that even though you may not have met them
It's very plausible that you did
Right or something, you know
Also another belief in the future would be like for example if you said you're going to meet someone tomorrow
And they're going to give you a silver coin
Well, it hasn't quite happened yet and between now and that event happens if someone asks you where you're going
You're saying that you believe you when you meet this person you will get a silver coin
It's based on communication information and something that is tangible
Now what you will come across typically in society is when people discuss beliefs
It'll be an unfounded irrational thought and they're kind of like winking and waiting for a response whether someone agrees with them or not again
Like that makes it real. So this term of belief
Has been thrown around in society again and has become
Part of the poetry or prose that people are engaged in which again has
Dropped fall of dropped flat on its face
people
being able to technically access rational communication
and all of a sudden there's an entire industry based on belief that the things that
Pretty much might defy the the term
Have we ever discussed that? I think we've discussed that in passing stuff
Perhaps what beliefs might be and what people believe in?
Yeah, not in-depth
not broadcast
Yeah, so when you hear about people
bringing up beliefs the mind
would behoove the mind to
Go and see
If what they're discussing is rationalized in any fashion or any form, you know very often, you know
There's a way to address people that are spiritualists
or people in the spiritual community about beliefs and they will
Also lack the rational comprehension of what they're discussing. See when you ask questions in any quote-unquote religion
About either the those that are part of the group or leading the group what their beliefs are based on
They will try to emphasize
That it's about belief and when you try to find out what they're believing in they don't know much about it
So it's a term that's been hijacked. I think it's an emotional
Place that people go to hide
it's been accepted and I think that once that term is is grabbed on to and looked at as
Being a form of you know, trying to rationally communicate something. I don't think people will be able to hide behind
The concept of a belief or belief system and I'm kind of waiting for that day
To come and it will be coming by the way in the future
There will be a time where people will not be so lazy and hide behind this amorphous
Irrational word. Well, that's you know, my belief and it's fine when they cannot describe or explain anything rational about it
And I it's a it's a human cop-out. I call it and
Stop doing it folks. And when I say that it's probably only four or five people listening anyway, so
Either you four or five that are listening. Yeah, be careful when you use the term belief
So I believe that these two hours are now over and we will probably be here next week
Thank you, Seth. Thank you everyone
See you again. Pleasure