Greetings, everyone. You're listening to American Freedom Radio.
And fortunately or unfortunately for you, you have tuned in to Uncommon Sense.
And greetings again, everyone. This is the Greek.
And we might be joined with Seth probably momentarily or later or not at all today.
So, again, everyone, if you've made the effort to be here,
maybe some of you can't help it being on this planet.
Well, we're here, and it's Uncommon Sense.
By the way, you can contact us at www.uncommonradio.com.
And I suggest putting in the www.uncommonradio.com
because Uncommon Radio in a general search does show a lot of other results.
So you're on American Freedom Radio,
and American Freedom Radio would appreciate for you guys to do the right thing.
You know what that is.
There's a lot of stuff going on about people needing donations.
And, yes, they are needed here as well, here meaning American Freedom Radio,
which I'm going to play something about being here in a little bit.
But, yes, so do the right thing.
Go to the homepage and help out the crew and the entire venue that is providing you Uncommon Sense.
It's the only two hours every week that you will get that I assure you is dummy load free.
Now, always kind of bring up the concept of a dummy load.
It's really an engineering term.
It's a synthetic load that's put on a system before it's put in the field to see if it will work in the field,
what kind of a load it can take.
For common vernacular, let's say a dummy load would be a hamster wheel,
like spinning your wheels and going nowhere.
And that's why, quote-unquote, mainstream and alternative radio,
when you push any of them to the corner, it is considered to be entertainment.
Now, just like if you run into someone who is into being physically fit,
they will say, I ran five miles today.
I said, well, where did you go?
He says, well, I didn't really go anywhere.
I ran it on a treadmill.
That treadmill represents a dummy load.
And the reason I bring up the dummy load on occasion is because as people,
let's say semi-cognizant beings, you have a desire to learn.
And any time there's a desire,
there's a certain amount of energy that's put behind it to accomplish that or seek it out or perform it.
And typically, people like to learn things.
Now, the quality of what they want and what they're aware of is put aside for a moment.
But people like to dedicate time to hear, like, for example, that television show they call the news
or the radio show they call the news, things like that.
They like to at least satisfy the feeling of being informed.
And in order to, let's say, satisfy a feeling, perform on a feeling or a desire,
one has to dedicate a certain amount of energy to it.
And people use this energy to seek out.
Various venues of information, talk, visual, whatever, what have you, whatever medium.
It used to be mostly in pulp, meaning paper.
And now it tends to be either terrestrial broadcasting or Internet broadcasting.
And I assure you, it's all dummy loading.
Why?
Well, if you look at what's called current events, the way that, let's say, the quote-unquote stories,
the facts, or let's just say some truth of the matter is presented, lacks substance, lacks quality, lacks depth.
You might say, well, you know, we know that.
Yeah, there's corporate media.
They're controlled.
Yeah, the government's whatever, and this is whatever.
But, you know, ultimately it boils down to one thing.
You have to accommodate the patron.
You have to accommodate the audience.
And you have to accommodate who you are presenting the goods to.
And I always give the metaphor, you know, a couple of guys I ran into got a few million
and they want to open this business.
I said, where is it?
They said, in the middle of the desert.
And I'm like, you've got to be kidding.
Yeah, but, you know, Interstate 10 is right there,
and there's almost a million cars passing every day on a weekday.
I said, oh, that's a really good business.
So you're there to accommodate the past survivors, you know.
Well, what happens if that highway closes?
No one to accommodate.
So, you know, there's an effort that's always being made to accommodate.
That scorpions and coyotes don't do well purchasing things at a convenience store in the middle of,
let's say, the Mojave Desert or so, or adjacent to it.
So on many levels, you're being accommodated on many levels.
And I would say that pretty much all levels, if you look at what's put out there.
Now, there's an effort that's always being made to accommodate the patrons and the clients.
So when you hear about people complaining or, let's say, making comments on this is, well,
mainstream media everybody knows is controlled or whatever.
Well, if you actually study their purpose, they're doing it for themselves, first of all.
It's a financial venture.
And second of all, they're doing it to accommodate a certain mindset.
If you look at alternative media, which pretty much strictly piggybacks on the mainstream media,
I wouldn't quite call them a parasite yet, you know, when an animal feeds off of another.
Because I don't think they're really going after the host as much as a typical parasite.
But they are parasitical in nature, alternative media, by the way.
And the reason I'm saying this is because when you listen to Uncommon Sense,
you got to pretty much put everything away and you're in a new place.
By the way, if you're visiting this planet for the first time,
it would behoove you to tune into Uncommon Sense at two hours a week.
We will give you a pretty much objective lowdown of what's going on.
We may not be the only ones being able to objectify what's going on,
but I'll tell you for sure we're the only ones that are speaking out on any form of media
that are doing it right now in wholesale, pretty much covering every topic.
So if you like, yes, and if you don't like what I just said, that's really too bad.
It might reflect on your lack of awareness.
But here on the other side, you might want to say that, well, if I'm just visiting this planet,
it's such a simple place and the simpletons that inhabit the surface are so simple
that it shouldn't take you more than 15 minutes to figure out what's going on here.
So we're kind of giving you an hour and 45 minutes beyond the pale there.
But anyway, Seth, I wonder if you've got your setup going.
And greetings, if you can hear me.
And let's see if we can hear you.
Greetings.
Hello.
Shalom.
Thanks for bringing me in.
Sorry, I was dealing with some new equipment that I'm working with.
So hopefully everything is sounding as well as it should.
Oh, yeah.
And speaking of new equipment, Seth is looking to, how would you say, forward
or advance the collection of little technical things like microphones, wires, and things like that.
So if anyone wants to contribute to Seth, that would be through what's called, well,
demanding for lawful money per Title 12, Section 411.
You've got to throw that disclaimer in there.
But through PayPal, perhaps through the e-mail, which would be, what would be the e-mail, Seth,
for direct contribution to Mr. Seth Michael, let's say?
Dearredshoes at gmail.com.
It's D-E-A-R-R-E-D-S-H-O-E-S at gmail.com.
So you spell it like it sounds, all one word, at gmail.com.
Dearredshoes.
Yep.
That comes from a band that I played with for several years that is now semi-defunct, I guess.
Now we're playing a couple of the same players, but different name.
And part of the wanting or the desire to acquire some cables and mics and things is I'm working on setting up a home,
like a project studio here at the house.
And I have recently been able to, through the kindness of others, been able to acquire a couple of key pieces of equipment.
So now it's just some sundry things that I'm needing to acquire to have the ability to record, produce, and mix for ourselves.
For those of you listening out there probably are aware, but if you're not, I play music.
That's one of the things that brings me quite a bit of happiness here on this rock.
So I'm working on doing that independently as I've met with frustration at having others in their attempt to help.
It's an art, and so when you're reliant upon others for a type of art, it's kind of disheartening.
So the idea is to be able to do it essentially all on our own and with the ease of accessibility to technology that we have currently.
That's something that's actually feasible if you have the equipment to do it.
That was not necessarily the case 20, 30 years ago.
And it just became easier and easier in distribution and everything like that for an artist such as a musician.
The Internet is one of those things that has made that relatively easy.
You no longer have to be picked up by a record label to have your music distributed worldwide.
You can do it with a few clicks of the mouse.
I want to touch on that just for a moment from some thoughts and things that I've brought up.
Folks, you are living in a society that's going to be going through radical changes.
And oh yeah, Greek, yeah, yeah, we know that.
But what you don't know is the specifics.
And one of the specifics is that this medium known as the Internet, whatever you want to call it, the World Wide Web, whatever, whatever, whatever,
will be increasing in its veracity in terms of being inexpensive, accessible, and consistently available.
Why?
I mean, well, we'll get to the why in a moment.
In other words, think of it this way.
You might have food shortages, housing shortages.
You might be pranked by the legal society, the government agencies, the religious society.
We'll continue to prank you into misery.
But the ability to get free, we'll say access or access if you don't have it, someone you know does, is going to be increasing.
You may not have water to drink, but you'll have Internet.
Why?
Because one of the prerequisites by the end of the next decade is that everyone on the planet, pretty much seemingly everyone,
bears witness to certain events that are going to be happening in, let's say, real time.
And the only way you can do that, spread out over the planet like that, is through some device.
So this is more than just a secular thing, meaning just technological.
Stop touching yourselves and feeling good about how wonderful you are with this technology, like a simpleton.
What you are experiencing is divine intervention.
It is imperative that everyone on the planet witness certain events that are going to be happening in the future.
So I just wanted to throw that in there because, yes, one of the side notes, perhaps, or side benefits, one might call it,
is now you can publish or publish, I guess you could call it, music as well as anything else pretty readily,
where before it was limited to a bunch of shysters known as recording studio managers and recording studio companies.
So I think that thing that you just mentioned, Seth, about being simpler,
many things that are attached to communication are going to be accepted as being for granted, not even thought about.
But I know you don't – well, from our conversations, you are very appreciative.
So again, if anyone wants to contribute to the venture, it's dearredshoes at gmail.com, and it's just how you spell it.
So with that said, Seth, I had a couple of thoughts.
Some people gave – well, we got a couple of emails.
Someone – I could just paraphrase.
And also we have – I'm reckoning roughly the end of the second week of the fifth month, roughly the 16th day of the fifth month.
So – but these people at this part of the world are considering it just to be a holiday weekend,
according to the work schedule that they run by, right?
And there were a couple of thoughts, and they said, like, well, you know, when you think of a country,
especially when you go west to what's called the Americas, the most objective way to look at what's going on would be –
let's say one of the most objective ways.
Imagine a really large store, I mean a very large store, like a commercial venue.
And it's open for business, but the customers don't really go home.
Once you enter this venue, this store, you kind of like sleep on the floor.
And the next day you're still there.
You're at the store 24-7, let's say.
That's America.
It's not a nation.
It's not a country.
It's a place.
It's a large store.
That's why when people kind of complain about how politicians are operating,
you ever notice like in a bar or a store they have entertainment, you know, background music or a television monitor or whatever?
That's what your political system is.
It's very simple.
And it's also by divine intervention, because here, folks, the more evil the society, the more evil the leadership.
And that conversation ends right there.
It's very simple.
Crappy people, crappy leaders, vice versa.
And also there's a little bit of fortunately people know not to bring ridiculous stuff to me or uncommon sense, like, hey, how about them Mets?
How about them Yankees?
Right?
Yeah.
Hey, how about that Trump?
Hey, you got any political interests?
Yeah, none of that.
We don't get any of that, folks.
But I do get it somewhat in passing, because they know better.
They ask ridiculous questions like that.
Or what did Santa Claus bring you?
Right?
You know, this is the stuff that this society is all about.
They will die for this stuff, by the way.
This is how ridiculous they are.
But I assure you, folks, if you have what's called an election.
Now, if you think you're going to vote in an election, I would recommend taking some really strong psychotropic pharmaceuticals, because the mind is obviously not working at all.
And you might be in danger to yourself and others.
Voters vote.
Electors elect.
So if you're going to go vote at an election, you've got some serious mental problems, and you're going to have to review things.
But then we just wipe the floor with 350 million people.
But anyway, from that respect, your next leader is going to be worse than the one you have now.
That's for sure.
Who it is, it doesn't matter.
What they say and who they are doesn't matter.
It's what they do.
And that's an assurance.
And the leader after that one is going to be worse than the one before.
And that is an assurance.
You can take that to whatever you call the bank or safekeeping and reflect on that.
But speaking of which, a little bit about monetary stuff came up again, Seth.
And I think we've said on here before, people will never understand the monetary system.
Now, fortunately or unfortunately, never is not that far away.
Meaning everything is as the way you consider it to be or think it will be.
And prophetically, people stop using it simply because they just stop using it.
There is no indication people will ever comprehend it.
They just stop using it.
It's kind of like walking instead of taking the car.
You know nothing about a car, how it works, other than the ritual of getting in and pushing one pedal and turning a wheel and rolling down the window.
But you stop using it and you walk from now on.
That's exactly how the monetary system is going to be interacted with with humanity.
And so when I say society at large and most people at large and private as well,
if you talk to 100 people, 99 and a half will not understand the money system ever.
In the ever that we consider the current society.
But it doesn't mean that it can't be brought up as a reflection, maybe just poking fun.
Not at the people.
See, I mean, not at the monetary system, but at the people,
because there would be no monetary system as such unless the people were accommodated by it.
Anybody tells you about Illuminati or Federal Reserve and all that,
it's the local branch and the local contracts you get involved with that are screwing you.
Go to a local bank, any one of you, and ask to tell her if they have Federal Reserve notes.
Watch how she gets confused.
Hold on a second.
Let me get the manager.
And she or he are handling this every day and they don't know what it is.
That's why I mentioned earlier, if you just came to this planet,
you could listen on Common Sense, you'll get a lot.
You'll get a lot more than anywhere else, that's for sure.
But on the other hand, we're here for two hours.
If you come from another planet and you've got half a brain,
you could figure out this entire society in 15 minutes or less.
So with that said, I want to play a skit from Abbott and Costello, 1940s, 1950s comedy stand-up group.
And this one, it's from that infinite bastion of wisdom called YouTube.
Yeah, all you guys who love YouTube, right?
Yeah.
Well, it's from a YouTube video.
It's Abbott and Costello.
You're Not Here is what it's called.
I think the channel is Top Ten Cats or something, but you could find it on a search.
It's Abbott and Costello, how you want to spell it.
And the skit is called You're Not Here.
It's three minutes long.
And I want to play another skit after that.
And the next skit after that is called Loan Me 50 Cents.
But I want to play the You're Not Here one because this is how the pranksters are operating.
And you folks love it, by the way.
How do I know?
Well, I just go out.
I have shoes, good walking shoes that I could run in.
And I talk to people here, there, and everywhere, digitally as well.
And, yeah.
So what do you think, Seth?
Want to let it rip?
Absolutely.
Okay, here we go.
It's starting.
This is an excerpt from the movie.
Oh, I see you're ready for bed.
Why lay down?
Not until I get ready.
I'm ready.
That goes for you, too.
And get this.
No noise while I'm here.
You're here?
Yeah, I'm here.
Who said you were here?
What do you mean I'm here?
Of course I'm here.
You wouldn't want to bet on it.
You want to bet me that I'm...
Are you crazy or something?
I'll bet you you're not here.
You want to bet me money?
Ten dollars says you're not here.
Well, that's a bet, chump.
Come on, put it up.
Hey, hey, you can hold it, too.
Ten dollars.
Bet you're not here.
All right, all right.
Well, I'll prove it that I'm not here.
What?
You're not in Chicago, are you?
Why, certainly not.
No.
You're not in Philadelphia, are you?
You're not in St. Louis, are you?
Of course not.
Well, now, wait a minute.
If you're not in Chicago, you're not in Philadelphia, and you're not in St. Louis.
You must be someplace else.
That's right.
All right?
Yeah.
Well, if you're someplace else, you can't be here.
No.
That's all.
Hey.
That's a good one.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna pull that on my boss.
Sure.
He needs a little humor.
That's all right.
You know what?
Let's do it.
Hey, does the boss know about this?
Oh, he don't know anything.
He don't know anything?
No.
I'll pull it on him.
Go ahead.
Hey, you.
Get up out of there.
Hey, get up.
Get up.
Come out.
What you got in there?
I want to bet you $10 that you're not here.
Hey, come on.
What's the matter with you?
I want to make you a bet.
I'll bet you $10 that you're not here.
You want to bet me $10 that I'm not here?
That's right.
Chance will make some money.
Come on.
All right, put it right here.
Here's mine.
There you are.
Are you ready?
Yes, sir.
Now, I'm going to prove to you that you're not here.
Go ahead.
Now, you're not in Chicago, are you?
No, sir, but I got an anthem.
No, no, no.
You're not in Chicago, are you?
No, sir.
And you're not in St. Louis?
And you're not in Philadelphia?
No, sir.
Now, if you're not in Chicago, and you're not in St. Louis, and you're not in Philadelphia,
then you must be someplace else.
That's right.
And if you're someplace else, you're not here.
Yes.
That's right.
Hey, give me back my money.
Who took your money?
That's my money.
You did.
I took your money?
That's right.
Now, just a minute, big boy.
Yeah?
Didn't you say that I wasn't in Chicago?
That's right.
That I wasn't in Philadelphia?
Yeah, yeah.
And that I wasn't in St. Louis?
That's right.
Well, if I'm not in Chicago, St. Louis, or Philadelphia, I must be someplace else.
Well, if I'm someplace else, I couldn't be here.
Is that right?
That's right.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, if I'm not here, how could I take your money?
There you go.
That's exactly how the banking system is doing it, folks, if you get it.
You ever get a bill from the electric company?
That's what they're doing.
They're not.
You ever get a bill from...
Yep.
Yeah, exactly.
And you love it.
Santa Claus is in here.
Yep.
All that stuff you're told about to believe in is not there.
Never was.
Let that sink in for a little while.
Get this on archive and listen to it again.
Now, let's go a little bit more into the money system.
Now, first of all, we said earlier that people are never going to understand the money system.
So I'm not...
This could be viewed as two ways playing these skits.
One is like poking fun at how stupid people are.
And the other thing is just showing maybe a metaphor.
There might be some humor that it's all about pranking.
But remember, folks, that when I say pranking, you're being ruled by pranksters.
And you are pranksters yourselves to allow it.
But at this point, pranks sound like fun, but many people can also...
We're talking about pranks that you are killed in as well.
Just like there was a film in the 70s called Rollerball.
It's a sport, you know, and it was all right to fight to the death, right?
But that's all right because think about it this way, folks.
It's called Planet Earth.
No one gets off alive, right?
Well, anyway, Seth, I want to play the next one.
This one's two minutes and 16 seconds.
It goes kind of fast.
It's called Abbott and Costello, Loan Me 50 Cents.
So I was thinking of playing it twice, but I think just playing it once.
And if anyone goes to any kind of search, just put in Abbott and Costello.
Just Abbott and Costello, Loan Me 50 Cents.
And you'll get it and watch it a few times.
And, yeah.
All right, so here we go on this one.
Listen, I've got to get you a job.
I've got to use the telephone.
Loan me 50 cents.
Abbott, I would like to loan you 50 cents, but I can't do it.
All I've got is 40 cents.
40 cents?
Yeah.
All right, give me the 40 cents and you owe me 10 cents.
Right.
All right?
Wait a minute.
What's the matter?
How come I owe you 10 cents?
What did I ask you for?
50 cents.
And what did you give me?
20 cents.
So you owe me 10 cents.
How come I owe you 10 cents?
Now, wait a minute.
Now, listen to me.
I think all that money I had in my pocket, I gave you 40 cents.
Are you going to argue with me again?
No, no, no.
You owe me 10 cents besides.
I asked you for 50 cents.
All I had was 40 cents.
So you owe me 10 cents.
How come I owe you 10 cents?
Now, take it easy.
Take it easy.
40 cents and 10 cents is how much?
That's, everybody knows.
It's 50 cents.
Oh, no, no.
25 and 25 is 50 cents.
Give me that.
All right.
Here's your 40 cents.
Give me back the dime you owe me.
Okay.
Now, we're even.
That's my own fault for asking you for a loan of 50 cents.
You tricked me too much into this.
I shouldn't have asked you for 50 cents.
How come I owe you 50 cents?
All I got left now is 30 cents.
Now, loan me the 30 cents and you owe me 20.
Okay.
Now, look.
I can start everything over.
You owe me 20 cents.
Now, make it clear.
It's clear to you.
Am I right?
How come I owe you 20 cents?
Since I gave you all the money I've got in the world.
All right.
I can't owe you that kind of money.
Here's your 30 cents.
Give me the 20 cents you owe me.
Okay.
There we are.
Now, we're all set.
We're all set.
Now, what are you hollering about?
I'm not.
I don't understand this.
You don't understand what?
It's not a transaction.
What do you mean?
Don't call me.
You started asking for 50 cents and I gave you 40 cents.
I gave you 30 cents.
My friend, it's the last time I'll ever ask you for the loan of 50 cents.
All right, but you got me all mixed up.
How come I owe you 50 cents?
All I got left now is 10 cents.
Is that all you got left?
That's all I got left.
Now, wait a minute.
Don't get excited.
I don't understand these transactions.
You're ruining my calculations.
You're ruining my finances.
Wait.
I'll tell you what I'll do with you.
What did you have?
I have 40 cents where I started.
Just a minute.
You want to take an I owe you for the 40 cents?
Is it good?
Well, certainly it's good.
Well, that's business.
I mean, after all, you've got a bank.
You've got to do that.
I do everything strictly business.
Well, that's all right.
I'll take I owe you.
You got a pencil?
Yeah, a pencil.
Give me a pencil.
I'll put I owe you on my piggy bank.
That's right.
Now, here.
I owe you 40 cents.
There you are.
Now sign your name.
You lose.
Customer.
Go.
There you are now.
See, everything is legal.
Here, here, here.
There you go.
So, long and the short of it, folks, is when you go to a casino, you go and get chips,
right?
Otherwise, you can't play in the casino.
When you're born into a credit-based economy, you're given a credit line from the treasury
and certain government agencies, right?
A credit line.
And you might want to call it social security number or whatever, whatever.
It's identified by the name and the number.
And the key is to not let you know that you hold all the credit because you're full of greed
and gluttony, typically most people are.
But all the agencies, the banks, the attorneys, the doctors, the hospitals, the schools,
the water company, everyone that you do transactions with that has what's called a CAGE code,
C-A-G-E, Corporate Government Entity.
They know you have all the credit and they've got to get it from you without you knowing that you've got it.
And this is what's going on and it all comes out of the signature.
All they need is a signature.
And that's how it works.
It's very, very, very simple.
And it's also, there's a lot of divine intervention there because once I believe I read somewhere,
it said that it's the love of money that is the root of all evil, not money, the love of money.
So what the gods did was they eliminated money, lawful money, and now the only thing you're left with is credit,
which is not money, and you're all pursuing it simply for the love of money.
Why?
Because there will be no excuse later when you're confronted on this.
Yes, later.
So with that said, I think that's kind of a wrap up, first 30 minutes now,
a little bit of poking fun at the inhabitants on the surface here and a little bit about the credit system.
But I'd say, Seth, that these two chumps, Abbott and Costello, summed it up really well.
Yeah, very well in an amusing manner.
But it's an accurate representation of the mode of economic operations.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, for example, if you're arguing the – by the way, folks, just a little bit more.
You don't get a mortgage.
Actually, people are so unable to communicate.
I've actually seen advertisements about getting a mortgage.
You give a mortgage.
And if anyone has ever gotten involved with any kind of transaction like that,
they tell you that you hold the property fee simple.
What is it called?
JESCA?
It's the Muslim tax, that if you're not Muslim, you pay a very strong tax, by the way, for privilege to live there.
Your property taxes are like that too, all that stuff.
All the taxes you pay are privileges.
They don't pay for anything, by the way.
If you folks are ever conveying on the streets and there's street work, it says bonds are paying for things, not taxes.
But anyway, if you look at what's called a mortgage, you give a mortgage.
And if you look at all of this stuff that they're doing, it's exactly like the Sabbath and Costello skit.
Exactly identical, identical to the point where it's scary and it goes beyond the pale of being comic.
It goes into the pale of being pranking.
And you will be killed by the pranksters.
Welcome to planet Earth.
You are being pranked.
This is known as the place of the prank right now.
And you're accommodating it.
The society at large is accommodating it.
So anyone that says, what are we going to do to make society better, that does not access or address the level of pranking that is going on is just a waste of time.
And what I mean by waste of time is such a fool has to say something, but the wise have something to say.
How many times have you tuned into any media and they say, we have to do something, we have to say something.
That is the mark of a fool with a capital O, folks.
So that's why we are here.
So you have two hours a week on the Internet where you might get some sanity.
And there's many ways to get sanity.
But the first way is to learn to separate yourself from what's going on and everywhere.
Because, folks, let me just throw this in about the pranksters again.
And this is kind of a repeated theme that we do here every two weeks because I guess repetition is important.
The first group or individual to prank you is the parents.
Yes.
Think about it.
You're being pranked.
So, you know, here you are.
You're going through your formative years and you're being pranked by the gods you are living with, meaning when you are very, very, very young and still in formation as an infant,
the parents represent not only large people, but they also represent almost a godlike status.
You have no concept of anything beyond them.
And they are pranking you.
So you have pretty much been imploded by pranking from the beginning.
And you go on from there and you can examine it objectively as you wish.
But, you know, we will disclose these realities to you on Common Sense.
So with that said, Seth, any interesting words for this week?
Onomatopoeia.
Oh, OK.
Word that came up.
I haven't actually done the etymology on it, but it is the most interesting word I've heard in the last couple of days, I suppose.
But now just we got, you know, a couple of e-mails.
I figure we might address one of those.
Is it?
We want to keep them anonymous.
I have one cut and pasted for me by our administrator.
A fairly recent one.
It's pretty long.
Hey, Greg, just wanted to start by saying thank you for the words you speak.
You have saved me lots of time rounding around in circles trying to chase this dummy load.
Is that the one maybe?
That's one of them.
OK.
I had a mentor recently passed away.
He's an old Catholic priest.
Figured out what really was about and turned away other way.
Basically, like what you described, set himself apart.
Now, by the way, when you folks are you folks out there that profess to being Christians, that's Catholicism.
There's about one hundred and something.
Set aside what you profess.
Being a million.
Jump up and down like a little child screaming about.
Set that aside for a moment.
That came out of the formation of the Catholic circus or church, which was initiated initially first, second, third, fourth centuries.
Its founder was a magician known as Simon Magus.
And you heard of all these church fathers.
By the way, when you use the word church, that means circus.
You may not like it.
You may not believe it.
But sorry, that's not my problem.
He was a magician.
He was very crafty, very wealthy.
Imagine a Houdini with Bill Gates's budget.
OK.
Even more.
And Simon, by the way, is translated into Peter.
I don't know how to get that.
Peter Piper, whatever.
That's when they talk about St. Peter.
That's Simon Magus, the magician.
And what what was finally settled on by the fourth century with Constantine and all these other guys.
By the way, it has nothing to do with the biblical text.
If there's any discussion with the biblical text, you're insane.
Just like the Constitution and American law.
But anyway, what they did was they settled on reviving Egyptian and primarily Hellenistic paganism, Greek paganism, as the liturgy.
I mean, as the function for the congregations, for the masses.
And they had a hierarchy of priests and bishops and so forth, all the way up to the pope himself.
And that hierarchy is involved in something else, which is a revival of the old Canaanite, Phoenician and Babylonian rituals of human sacrifice and parodies of that.
And that's all it is.
You've got a hundred and somewhat denominations of Christianity.
They all come out of that.
In other words, they're all the same.
They have the church.
They have this guy nailed to a cross, whatever.
None of that ever happened, by the way.
And also, there's a lot of people that I've noticed, Seth, in the past that have gotten into discussions and they agree.
And I find out these morons, their minds all of a sudden go to this Urantia book or other things stupid like that.
So what I want to say here, because I'm prefacing, the fellow in this email asks how to identify the Christ.
And I want to preface before I get into it.
Any biblical character you will discuss or think about is still completely secret.
And everything that's in the mind is false, by the way, folks.
I'm not a mind reader.
I don't have to be.
I've been on this planet for enough decades to realize what's going on.
So when you hear Abraham or Adam and Eve or the serpent or the Christ or this or that, get that out of your head.
Because if you actually go and research historically and biblically, you will not find what you're thinking about and what you've been told at all, at all.
But if you have to have the ability to read out of information, not read into it.
In other words, if you're bringing into what you've been told when you're studying these things.
Oh, no, here's he said that word study.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
You're not going to see it again because these things were designed to be hidden in plain sight for a later time.
So right back to the email.
So basically, I have let's say no one else turned to I know of the grain of knowledge at this days.
Thank you again.
When the day comes where we enter the family, is that OK?
Then he gets about mankind.
And also, if you could explain more about who the Christ was or is it would really mean a lot to me.
OK, I'm just paraphrasing bouncing around here, folks.
Sorry about that.
Where does the three in one concept come from?
That's the circus, the three ring circus.
By the way, that's something that they did put in.
If you ever see a Trinity or Father, Son, Holy Spirit type thing in your King James Bible,
and if you're spending too much time with the King James Bible, you'll get a disease.
It's called King James, King James version syndrome.
It's a syndrome.
I don't know what the cure for it is other than complete abandonment of those things.
But so he gets into these things that most people think are in the realm of religion.
And believe it or not, Seth, I think you and I in public here and other places, other sonic events,
have fully disclosed what's going on.
But you've got to remember that if a secret is designed to be secreted or hidden in plain sight,
you can actually point it out and explain it and it will still be secret because of the duration of it being in such a condition.
And fortunately, people are so conditioned or unfortunately, either way, that they won't see these secrets,
meaning that mankind didn't design this to be secret.
Which, by the way, when I asked you about the word, I wanted to bring up this thing.
I was talking to people this week about how they're functional or dysfunctionally functional
or how someone who wants to go vote in an election is somehow functioning but they're insane.
So what do they call that when you're functionally insane, I guess?
Even a society that has descended into complete chaos is still functioning somehow
because food, clothing and shelter is acquired.
So the word function, noun, one's proper work or purpose, power of acting in a specific way,
middle French, function, directly.
Okay, let's get a little more to it.
A performance and execution, to precipitate a particle sum of fungi, perform, execute, discharge.
So basically, to use, destroy, meaning official ceremony.
So it's all over the place.
So functionary, one who holds a certain office, functional, pertaining to a function.
So function is one of these things, I guess, that requires action, would you say, Seth?
And, yeah, these actions that you folks are getting involved in are not healthful, which, by the way,
it's a testament to the, I guess, durability, stamina and strength of the human body and mind.
How can a being be subjected to such disastrous surroundings, meaning not catastrophic,
but in a way that is just so functionally wrong, whether it's your religion, your science,
the way you raise children, all of it, every single aspect of it, in such a way,
and still be able to live and breathe?
It's a testament to the strength and vitality and veracity of the human body, is what I see it as.
That you could put up with a lot of crap and still breathe and be alive.
It's almost like a pressure test or a stress test on the being known as humanity, on what's going on.
There are many ways to explain it.
I just thought I'd bring that up.
So, any comments on, he was asking, essentially, about the Christ.
I think he mentioned a verse in particular, Way, Truth and Life, that were mentioned in that email as well.
That's really, you want to dig deep?
Those things, believe it or not, Way, Truth and Life, are defined by other books.
And those things have to be harmonized.
If that makes sense.
And that's really a large topic.
There are specific things as well.
That is a reference to, as you just said, things that are described in other books, collected in the same text.
Let's say a few things that are not being said anywhere else,
and maybe not been said for 2,500 years or 2,000 years.
And that is this, folks.
When you look at what's called the scripture or the biblical text,
and if you want to reduce it to 30 words or less, that is about two things.
Life and death.
It has nothing to do with religion.
Nothing to do with all these things that you've made it into.
Yes, it has a lot of things regarding those things in there as well,
things you do regularly and whatever.
But what people have done with it, just like anything else,
is completely removed from the source material.
It is about life and death.
So the purpose of the Christ is very simple.
Let's just lay out the secret, because if you want to hide something, put it in the public library.
If you want to keep a secret, get on a minor Internet radio station and start talking.
That's how you keep secrets, right?
So the secret is very simple.
The Christ came for one reason and one reason only,
and that is to prove that man is no longer subject to death strictly.
In other words, that the next level has been demonstrated.
He came to be a prototype before the mass production goes into effect.
That's it.
It's a complete secret.
Now, by the way, folks, all you guys out there, there's a lot of commentary,
oh, the God of the New Testament is different than the God of the Old Testament.
This, that, and the other.
Oh, boy.
Which one?
Yeah, exactly.
They don't even know.
I mean, this is just bizarre stuff.
But let's just go into another aspect.
But we've explained why all these things are similar, and pretty much it is continuous.
But this is, for the New Testament, only morons.
And by the way, you've been told to stay away from the other one
because you might figure things out, and then how is the prankster,
you know, these people that are priests, pastors, popes, ministers, deacons,
people that graduate from biblical school or divinity school,
these are all pranksters, all of them, every single one, folks.
They may not know it, but it doesn't mean that they're not a prankster,
even though they may have good intentions.
But they're wearing the uniform and saying the things that the pranksters have designed.
And the pranksters don't want you to figure out what's going on
because how are they going to get stuff from you.
But here's the point.
It's very, very, very simple.
And the whole thing coming around, and it goes around as this.
If you have no knowledge and you're really young in the subject,
let's say five- or six-year-olds or whatever in kindergarten,
and you sit in, let's say, graduate-level physics class.
Now, the young person would be the average person that's quote-unquote believer,
and the graduate-level physics class is the New Testament.
You could sit in that class for a day, a week, or a year.
And when it comes time to asking questions about what you're being exposed to,
all the children lift their hands up immediately,
and the question is, you got any candy?
And that's exactly what you're going to hear from someone who adheres to the New Testament
and knows nothing else.
You got any candy?
You know, I mean, and there is subjected to this a graduate-level, all the New Testament.
You will not find, by the way, anything that's in any religion
in any of the texts that they allegedly subscribe to,
including Islam, Hinduism, and Buddhism, by the way, and Judaism.
Judaism will strictly tell you, we don't go by the Bible.
We go by other things.
They're honest.
And if you pressure anyone in the field of the Christian field,
they will tell you, we do not go by the Bible.
We go by church tradition.
And the same with Islam.
We don't go by the Koran.
We go by these other books that were written to interpret the Koran.
The same thing with the legal society.
We don't go by the law.
We go by what you said, what you signed.
The doctor says, well, I don't go by that.
I go by whatever I'm going to prescribe you.
So this is the level of pranking that you folks on this planet are subject to,
which will, by the way, if you have a clear mind and you just visited this planet,
you'll figure this out in 15 minutes.
So anyway, Seth, go ahead.
You were going to interject something there about kind of drifted away again.
About the physics, about got any candy.
Yeah, it was the last thing I, you know, and it's deliberate, by the way.
If you want to keep, let's say you've got a five-year-old,
and you want to keep him dumb for the rest of his life,
the only thing you're going to subject him in the first and only, let's say,
form of study is fifth-year graduate physics books.
That's all you're going to give him.
And he doesn't even know how to read.
He barely knows what the alphabet is.
He will not ever learn anything, right,
because you missed all the progression and the building up.
And that's what you folks are getting out of the New Testament.
Here's the thing.
There is no such thing as the New Testament, by the way.
That's all in the stuff that's been given to you.
So there's a big level.
So here, just to go back to the email and answer that with veracity
and answer it directly,
the Christ is a prototype to show that death can be put to death.
And if death is put to death, there's no more death.
And if there's no more death, there's only, you get it?
Double negatives work in certain ways.
Yeah, one of those books towards the end,
I believe death is actually put to death.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And if death is put to death, there's no more death.
And if there's no more death, there's only, you guys can say it.
Yeah.
It's very simple as nothing going into an ancient sex temple.
By the way, folks, if you brought last week,
we spoke about technology and bringing someone from the past
and what they would probably be most amazed at is after 15 minutes
or a couple of days is how much and how proficient
and how well skilled you are as a society to spread tar everywhere,
known as asphaltic roads.
That would be the hardest thing to get over, right?
And if you brought an ancient into a Western society
and you walked down the street, he'd be saying,
hey, I didn't know you had a sex temple in your neighborhood based on the way it looks
and the architecture that we all know.
And guess what he'd be pointing at?
That why is there a giant phallus on top of it?
Yeah.
And not only that, it's the shape of the doors and the rooftop and all that
and the way the interior is set up.
Yeah.
Just like if you right now walk down the street and there's no sign on a store,
you could recognize an ice cream parlor.
You see all these refrigerators with glass and people with scoops, right?
Or you'll recognize a shoe store or whatever or a pawn shop.
You know they have the three large balls outside.
You bring an ancient into modern society from any society in the ancient world,
they will point at your local church or your place of worship as a sex temple.
Yes, folks.
Sorry.
And you should be sorry yourselves.
But anyway, yeah, that's very uncommon to say that and very uncommon to think it,
and it's actually a very common thing to know.
And you ever wonder why you have bad things happening.
So with that said, any other email that we could keep anonymous perhaps
and interject in here or do you think you want to just dwell on this one for a little while?
We can continue on with that one.
The other one that I was referring to is one that we began to address at the very end of the program last broadcast.
Okay.
And it's just a listener out there who's been listening to the program as we've been broadcasting,
and he's just curious about dreams for kind of a personal reason.
And so I figured I would bring that up because we didn't really get to address it much,
although we have numerous times in the past.
But as we've kind of discussed between ourselves, repetition is not necessarily a bad thing,
especially when it comes to information.
Information should be shared.
But it also happens to be hated, by the way.
Yes, absolutely.
With a lot of people just don't like it.
So go ahead.
So about dreams, yes.
The long and the short of it is that your dreams are not your own and you're being plugged.
It's a form of input that is being played on a screen in the mind, and you're experiencing it.
And it just goes to show you or shows to go you how much of what you are, what you think you're thinking, is exposed.
And who's plugging it?
The other side.
Various minor gods, imps, and demons, angelic beings, but of very low ranking on that society.
If you're going to get a dream from a high ranking being, benevolent being, they identify themselves as such typically.
And they tell you what's going on, where the low ranking ones, you know,
kind of bring in things that you think you're being entertained with,
whether it's experience A, B, C, or D, or whatever experience you have in life,
or whatever they want to plug into you.
And then hopefully you will get up and say you had this dream to someone else,
and they're laughing their asses off, high-fiving each other.
Hey, look, we plugged this guy pretty good.
Look at him.
He's talking about it, and he doesn't even know what's going on.
And I had seen a question, by the way.
If you know what dreams are, then why do you keep dreaming?
I think that was from Dylan on chat.
Hello, Dylan.
Very interesting.
Well, you know, just because, you know, the police are like private security guards,
doesn't mean they're not going to stop and give you a ticket and harass you, right, or whatever.
Just because, you know, there is no have any law whatsoever, you go to what's called a court.
They're not saying, well, the law is, and if you bring it up, then they're like, oh, we don't go by law then.
So these are adversarial, in other words.
So one way to, let's say just to address, well, if you know what dreams are, how can you keep dreaming?
Here's an interesting comment that we've gotten on, I believe I've gotten on IM and Skype.
He said that I had done a sonic experience with another host a while back, a few months ago,
and I spoke about dreams, and this person was very eager to contact me and tell me that when he heard that,
he stopped dreaming, but then the dreams came back even more vivid, right?
So that doesn't mean that it invalidates it.
Yes, you are being plugged by spiritual beings that are not you, and they're enjoying it,
and they'll bring you things in private also.
That means that you really can't do anything in private, right?
So, yeah, just because you know how they work, in some cases the dreams do stop
because it startles them on the other side also.
They're like, crap, man, I kind of figured out what we're doing,
and a bunch of other guys there on their side are probably saying, well, so what?
He's just a human. Just keep plugging away. Ignore him.
I would add that these entities seem to be – they're disingenuous.
What is shown is generally not accurate.
If you look at it as being tricked, that's – generally that involves some falsehood,
some deceit, or just plain lies.
I know of people that have dreamt of – like were actually –
what they thought were being visited by relatives who are at rest.
How are you going to be visited by someone who's at rest?
But in their dreams and after a conversation and listening and contemplation,
in the dream it happened again, but knowing that they actually mentioned it,
kind of a lucid sort of circumstance in a dream, and it changed dramatically in the dream.
I believe you told me this.
They turned into a pile of chopped meat instead of the dead relatives, right?
Yeah, it was –
Or something like that, yeah.
Yeah, they just disintegrated.
Yeah, because these were – yeah, they're sensory junkies.
The ones that are employing dreams into people's minds are sensory junkies.
Just like on the low level of human society, the lower ranks, social ranks,
people are generally sensory junkies.
I don't care how cheap that liquor is.
I just need some weed to smoke, or I just want to lay in front of the TV.
This is the level of spiritual beings that are plugging the dreams.
By the way, dreams are very significant in pagan cultures, and pagan just means ignorant.
I'm actually kind of happy to hear lately there's more and more people professing to be pagan.
Have you heard that?
I've heard it in public.
Well, I'm a pagan.
I don't do any of the –
Yeah, and I'm like, oh, great, man, finally people admitting they're ignorant.
Yeah, that's good.
That's a good level of honesty.
In a colloquial sense, it brings to – makes people think of like – what specifically?
Like Wiccan and things like that, but that's not where the term originates.
The term originates – I believe it was first used as a semi-derogatory term by the Roman military
and Roman society as just referring to those that were like the country bumpkins,
uneducated, not part of society.
Yeah, and not interested to be either.
Well, here's our first hour, man.
Let's carry this thought over.
What do you think, Seth?
I think I cut out there a little bit, but I'd –
You did.
They're essentially just referring to, as you said, the uneducated.
I'd say nation as opposed to ignorant.
When they were using it, they were generally referring to those that were not necessarily even like outside of society,
but country bumpkins.
Let's carry it over on the next hour.
Let's carry this whole thought over, the dreams.
All right.
This is the first hour of Uncommon Sense.
We'll be back.
You're listening to American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com and UncommonRadio.com.
And we're back, hour number two.
Seth, are you with us?
Yes, yes, I am.
There is quite a storm going on outside.
So if I'm interrupted in my ability to broadcast because of that, all those listening, as well as you, the Greek, have my apologies.
But we'll keep going until that happens for certain.
Okay, great.
You know, everyone is typically talking about the weather.
When is someone going to do something about it, right?
Remember that thing with Samuel Clemens?
Yeah, that's another subject we could get into, the weather.
And, yeah, the reality of the weather and what people are discussing about it is just there's no comparison.
It's like voting at an election.
Anyway, so we're on this topic of dreams.
And you brought up a few good examples, Seth.
Do you want to recap some of those?
Because I believe that, you know, just myself plugging away sounds pedantic after a while.
So go ahead, please.
Yeah, this being the beginning of a new hour, we can – I'll just start by saying we received an email.
And it was someone asking about dreams because this person is being affected by them.
And it's not a pleasant experience.
And so I wanted to share personal observations as well as, you know, what I've seen through conversing with others and whatnot.
What dreams are, very similar thoughts.
We've spoken about thoughts here on the program as well.
And what is commonly or collectively understood is that, you know, our thoughts are our own.
And I, you know, would say that that's not the case.
I'd say that our thoughts are coming into us from many different places, directly from sources and indirectly from a lot of sources as well.
That can be demonstrated with – very easily with technology, although it's not all quite so mundane.
But –
In other words, hold on.
It's where you tune into, and then there's bandwidth and all this other stuff, right?
Where bandwidth might be someone who's considered very proficient or, quote-unquote, smart.
And where you tune into are the things that people are focused on, like a station, let's say.
And very much like an Internet where you have a browser that you do a search, it's similar as well.
And all the memories in a cloud and so on and so forth, et cetera, et cetera.
So go ahead.
Yeah.
So, you know, the obvious examples being television and things like that.
Those are thoughts that are being taken in.
If you're sitting there contemplating an idea or concept that has been presented to you by a television or by a radio program or by a newspaper,
those are all thoughts that are being transmitted to you through one medium or another.
Like I said, that's very mundane.
I would also suggest that these thoughts, being that thoughts are generally intangible,
that there are sources that are not readily acknowledged, readily acknowledged as well.
So dreams being a type of thought and something that is coming into us, not just originating within ourselves,
then you have to look at, OK, the source of such things.
So if you're being distressed by these dreams, realize that these are communications that are coming in and not necessarily quality communications.
Just like a television program is not necessarily a quality communication just because it is coming to you on the television.
And if it's something that is causing you distress or adversely affecting the way that you feel emotionally or physically,
which are basically one and the same, then change the channel.
Step back and realize that you do have some control over it.
It's not perhaps as easy as using a remote control for the television, but the concept itself is still similar.
And if you can take and dwell on these thoughts and ideas, specifically, like I said,
we got an email from someone who is obviously being distressed by their dreams.
It's the second email even.
So that's the why of bringing it up and addressing it in an uncommon manner.
There is a, as you were saying, Greek, there are a lot of cultures and a lot of subcultures, even currently,
that's put a lot of weight on dreams and the meaning of their dreams and things like that.
But it's one of those things that is very, it's easily referenced material because most dream in one manner or another and to one extent or another.
And so it's something that's used to hoodwink people out of their common sense, I would say, through personal experience.
But being made aware of something is a good step towards addressing it,
specifically if it's causing any sort of problem or discomfort.
You know, you can walk around with a tack in your shoe all day and complain about the discomfort.
But until you realize that you're going to have to sit down and remove the shoe and take the tack out, it's still going to be there.
So, you know, it takes. It's difficult.
Yeah. And sometimes you could be like, you know, going down a flight of stairs and you can't do it right there.
You're going to have to wait a little bit. But I want to reiterate a few things real quick.
Yes. These are the malevolent entities.
And in order to pass off as a good counterfeit, you have to look benevolent if you're malevolent.
Right. Right. And I believe that this people's bullet, by the way, malevolent beings can do healings as well and show you future events as well,
because there is a place where all of our paths are are set and can be communicated to them, but not to us, for example.
So, yes, if and let me just preface, people say they're listening,
but honestly, most people are honest enough to say that they just heard something, which is good.
Now, if you're hearing things, that's fine. But if you're other thing now, if you're listening,
you'll find out that what's been said here is that the concept of counterfeiting is to make some to pass something along of lesser value that appears to have higher value.
So the malevolent beings or indifferent beings that are interacting with mankind or let's just say they are of low social rank in their community.
They are the ones that are plugging mankind with dreams. If you're listening.
Now, the second part of that is if you're going to get a dream from a higher ranking member of that society,
they will identify themselves that you are being you're getting a message imparted from a higher rank or being and they usually will impart themselves as such.
And the thing about the caveat on this is that guess what? Malevolent beings will do that sometimes as well.
They will actually mimic something that you've heard. But typically it won't be a higher ranking being as it is in reality,
but as it is in a religious text, like some being might come to you in a dream and say that they are a J.S.U.S.
and they have long hair and they're telling you all the stuff that you're being told in Christendom or Christianity.
And that is obviously a malevolent being, obviously, if you've done your homework.
It looks like a hippy.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Yeah, no, exactly. So, yeah, which is unlawful, by the way. So the thing is, it's very – is it simple? No, it's very complex.
It's a heist. It's a job. They're pulling off a heist. And in order to pull off something, they think it through.
They've got lots of time to think things through.
Now, going back to, Seth, how you were finishing up the thought of the persistence of the thumbtack, let's say,
being removed in order to bring some comfort back, I can give you several parallel experiences that when people –
it was suggested to people studying what these things are and approaching, let's say, higher ranking thought,
level of thought, and who these higher ranking beings really are, not what you're being told through religion,
but actually the source material that the religions are supposedly based on, you will stop dreaming almost immediately, typically.
Sometimes if people approach these documents and they're reading out of it, their dreams get worse, you see,
because what's happening is that they're making an attempt to make the dreams go away, but they're falling into the counterfeit stuff.
Like, for example, you pick up a King James Bible, and you start reading that like that's really what the scriptures are,
you're going to get pranked like you wouldn't believe. Your dreams will get worse, almost. I assure you of that.
So you're going to have to do a little bit of work on yourself and do a little bit of work, not by yourself, but by yourself to meditate on these things.
So if you pick up something, and it says it's a version, or it's an extract, or it's not cheese, it's a cheese product, right?
What are you looking for? Are you looking for real cheese that should be made of milk?
If you're looking for the scriptures, let's say, and it says this is a version, and the only reason it's printed this way is for marketing purposes,
and you see that stuff like, my name is the Lord, I am your God, well, right there, you're being pranked like you wouldn't believe.
This is no such thing. It doesn't say that anywhere. That's just what's being delivered to you.
So there's so many layers of pranking going on that, yeah, it's going to be difficult for the individual or individuals that are having difficulty with the dreamscape world.
But what I've, from parallel experiences, what I've noticed is people that have been, have taken the suggestion that go and study what really is going on on the other side,
without listening to all that God and Lord stuff, and get some, stop reading into things and read out of it, your dreams will stop.
One way to do it is by admitting that you want to pursue the truth, and there is truth to be known.
You may not like it. As a matter of fact, I assure you, you won't like the truth.
Think about the truth that, this is the truth, folks. It might sound dogmatic, but it's too bad.
It's too bad that when you were just a little toddler, the gods around you, a.k.a. your parents, because that's all you knew, pranked you consistently.
That's a really rough existence.
So, nonetheless, not everyone, but mostly everyone, been subject to some sort of prank by their parents, right?
We want you to do well, son or daughter, but just don't do better than us, is what they're thinking.
So, there's many levels to this. This is a very, very difficult place.
Well, it's a challenge, and like I said earlier, it's a testament to the virility and the durability of the human body and the human spirit to put up with this stuff.
So, other than studying and admitting that you're pursuing the truth, and, well, let's just say, let's not even use that truth word,
because everyone's been mopping the floor with that, from academics all the way down to the basic moron on the planet.
Let's just stay away from that word for a moment, because it's been hijacked.
Change the channel, right?
It's just like, for example, if someone says, well, you know, I'm not feeling well, and I don't know why.
Well, you're the only one who really does know why, because the way you're feeling is based on your behavior and what you like to do.
So, the easiest way to – it's a condition based on behavior.
So, the easiest way to change any condition is by changing the behavior.
So, if you don't like the way you're feeling, let's say physically or whatever, make a list of all the things that you're doing and like to do,
and then make another list, contrary to that, all the things you don't like to do and don't do, and then switch them.
Do the things that you haven't been doing, and nine out of ten times, if not ten out of ten times, the condition will change.
So, yeah.
These are just simple matter-of-fact things, and that's why it's called uncommon sense,
because if you just landed on this planet, you'll notice the ridiculousness here.
So, anything that's not ridiculous is strictly uncommon, folks.
So, let's stay on the dream thing for a little bit more, Seth.
What do you think?
Do you want to pursue that a little bit more?
Yeah.
You're still there?
Yes, absolutely.
Anything else on any of the emails regarding dreams, but they're pretty much the context and the message is similar, you think?
Yeah, absolutely, and I would suggest that if the listener out there in particular would like to email me back.
I did reply to one of the emails, but I'm not certain that it went through.
So, email me directly at deerredshoesatgmail.com, D-E-R-R-E-S-H-O-E-S at gmail.com,
so that I can make sure that the response is going, because if you're after something any more specific than that, if I have the time, I'll respond.
The only way to communicate what's going on is generally, because the specifics are just as specific as each snowflake being different,
even though they all seem the same, just like each spirit of each individual, each person that manifests,
each man or woman that manifests on this plane is very unique.
Yeah, so the specifics, the ultra-specific, the high-specific that will be most effective is up to whoever gets the basics down, right?
It's just like, for example, a sport like baseball.
Let's say you have the pitcher's mound, and based on the rule book and based on the game, the pitcher does certain things.
But if you look through history and what's being communicated in any baseball game,
every time there's a different pitcher, there's a different pitch, there's a different style, different efficacy, different effectiveness, right?
So the position of the player might be held as being the same, but the actual individual makes the game,
makes that pitching function very different every time.
So everyone's dreams are very different every time, but there are a lot of similarities.
Typically, the dreams, obviously, they could be rendered or judged as being a good dream or a bad dream,
good meaning however the individual sees it as being good, and bad, again, however the individual sees it as being bad.
But typically, they're telepathic in nature.
If you ever recall a dream and there's a conversation or someone speaking at you or with you,
you'll notice there's no movement of the mouth.
There's just a face, and there's colors and things don't really come through sometimes.
The textures of things that you're familiar with, with the senses, are not revealed.
It depends on the dream maker, and literally, there are dream makers.
So, yeah, I don't know how more specific, other than giving as many generalities as possible,
just like if you're going to a restaurant to eat lunch, they have a menu.
You're not going to eat everything on the menu.
You might want to pick one or two items, and that's all you can handle at the time.
So maybe just putting out a lot of specifics in a general way will allow people to pick
and choose what they think applies or doesn't apply.
But these things are simple.
We're not making this up.
Anyone and everyone has access to what we're discussing.
If you stop reading into information and just read out of it,
when you're given a piece of information, can you objectify it?
Can you have it validated?
Can you see the history of the thing?
Like, for example, I think, Seth, you brought up there's a lot of people adding significance
to the nature of dreams in the pagan reality, let's say.
There's a lot of Internet stuff on that, alternative radio stations that have hosts
that talk about these things like as if there's really –
as if the reality of the dream experiences are something else that they're projecting,
of some significance that doesn't exist.
So, you know, well, occasionally, fortunately,
people know not to come here with that kind of crap and say,
well, this person said the dream is real and it's really your subconscious
or your dead relatives coming back.
I'm like, look, that's just – you know, get away from here.
You know, that's the marketing aspect.
You know, this is – fortunately, we don't get too much of that.
We don't get too much of the reincarnation crap and the Jesus lived in India crap
and the – yeah, yeah, all this other stuff or Anunnaki stuff
or little gray ETs coming through the wall, yeah, or flat earth and things like that.
So we don't get the ridiculous stuff that people engage in.
We don't get questions regarding elections, yeah, and things like that.
So that's very fortunate that way.
But what else about the dream, Seth?
Anything else you think we can expand on if you're still there?
Or you might be muted. Okay.
Muted, apologies.
Yeah, that's fine.
I'm saying yes, I'm still here.
And rightly so because of what I think.
But, you know, the dream is also there's a concept of past, present, and future events being used in dreams.
You've got to realize there's something called vantage point, folks.
Let's just apply this directly and indirectly.
When people are given future events in dreams, it's very natural to assume –
let's be presumptuous, but it's more than that –
that in the spiritual realm they have a different vantage point that mankind does not have.
And that would be the analogy of the parade where, let's say, you and your buddies are standing on the sidewalk
and it's a long parade, a four-hour parade, and you're wondering what the last float is.
And you have to wait four hours to see what it looks like.
But if you have a friend in a helicopter, you could get on the cell phone and call him
and ask him what the last float looks like.
Why?
Because let's say several thousand feet up in the air,
they could see the front of the parade and the back of the parade all in one view.
And they could report down to you that the last float is a green pig with purple wings.
So you tell all the buddies on the sidewalk that in four hours you will see a green pig with purple wings.
And they're like, oh, Greek, I don't believe that.
And you're like, oh, yeah, so what?
Yeah, da, da, da.
Right?
Four hours later, here comes the pig with the wings.
Because you're able to get information from a higher vantage point.
So there is a very simple, maybe oversimplified way to how people are getting information about future events
through dreams, even though they are of lower social ranking in their world, spiritual world.
Yes, typically malevolent, but not all things malevolent appear to be as such.
Stop watching the Hollywood stuff where the good guys wear white and the bad guys wear black and they have fangs.
That's not how it works.
Think about malevolent and benevolent as how counterfeiting is being done.
You can't take a dinner napkin and a crayon and write a hundred note on it and go and spend it.
You know, as a counterfeiter, you know, they have to, they actually go through tremendous efforts to make it look like the real deal.
But in this case, what's interesting about dreams is that no one even knows what the real deal is.
It's just something they know that if they sleep, they experience and they, well, you know, pity the inhabitants on this planet
that have fallen through the pagan standard.
Oh, yeah, your dreams are blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Let me tell you what those mean.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Now, there is dream interpretation as well.
And dreams are, there's many reasons why they come.
But you have to understand what they are first.
And this somehow has escaped everyone.
It's like the money.
I don't care as long as I go to the store and get something for it.
I don't care if it's unlawful.
I don't care what it is.
Or, you know, we've got to say something.
We've got to do something.
Yeah, really?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Reminded of a few occurrences that have been recorded where the dreams of kings were interpreted by slaves, actually.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, there's what they call the Book of Genesis.
There's a significant one there as well.
Now, you've got to realize that the social ranks on Earth are also administered very similar like the social ranks on the spiritual world.
And, by the way, the spirit, when you, hmm, how do we say this?
As above, so below?
I don't like to give too much credence to that.
But nonetheless, you know, what's below, what's above, you know, it's kind of like proving that you're not here, that Abbott and Costello thing, right?
Because you're attached to everything.
But the point is that if you look at all the military, for example, ranking systems throughout history and through all the nations, they're all very similar.
It's because they're copying the military ranking system from the other side.
I had a discussion with a moron known as a scientist a while back,
and he was trying to explain to me that all these basic tools and things that mankind is engaged in is just basic science.
And I'm like, no way, because most of them had come into fruition very quickly without the type of experiment we like to engage in.
And, by the way, folks, when I bring up science, there's no such thing that's a very recent establishment.
Prior to that, they were known as natural philosophers or natural philosophy, which used to pursue natural events and things.
But if you look at a lot of the things that mankind used back in the ancient days, that was all given to them.
And, yeah, it might sound kind of crazy because you're so technologically advanced right now, right?
But also, folks, I just want to throw a few things in here as an addendum to the dream concept.
Stop reading into the – when you look at things that were memorialized from a long time ago, stop reading into it all the crazy stuff that you're being told by the
quackademic establishment.
Like how many times – one of the things there – have you ever heard of an ice age or a bronze age or a stone age or an iron age?
There's no such thing, folks.
There might be an iron society or a bronze society or a stone-based society, right?
Like, for example, now there might be some nation somewhere on the continent of Africa that doesn't have the technological stuff, right?
Like iPhones, as prevalent as they are here, right?
They might be more of a wired society instead of a wireless society.
These are all parallel.
All of these things were in parallel.
You could read in ancient texts where a certain group had chariots made of wood and bronze, but the other society had chariots made of iron, wholly made of iron, right?
So there's – yeah, there's no such thing as Neanderthal man or caveman.
This is stuff that was invented by the crazy people at Oxford and Cambridge because they wanted to get into the booming archaeological business.
They wanted to – the academics always want to get in there.
Like look at all the stuff that's being touted about computer technology.
The universities kind of missed out on it other than what they developed as communications amongst themselves.
Most of the technology that you see, by the way, is not developed in universities.
It's in someone's kitchen or backyard.
But back to the cavemen, there's no such thing.
Neanderthal men, all those bones and things that have been played around with, the skulls and the jawbones and teeth have been reset to make it look more ape-like.
But what you're looking at, those large skeletons that are anthropomorphic are people that lived for centuries.
They had a lifespan that was several centuries, if not more than several centuries long, and you're being lied to.
I'm not asking anyone to believe what's being said here, but just make a note of what's being said.
It's not important that you believe in what we're saying.
It's important that you make a note of what we're saying and file it away for later.
That's very uncommon.
With a good little note of thunder there from Seth.
So speaking of thunder, have you got any more thunder, Seth?
Oh, I don't know.
I'd say that's about it on dreams without going into anything that – it's one of those things that's kind of difficult to converse on with specificity once we're talking about something that has been recorded.
You could throw out a lot of specifics in a general fashion like a menu and see what applies.
But let's just address one more thing.
If you cognizantly, in your being, really mean it when you kind of bring up the desire to not have dreams, whether they're good or bad, don't fool yourself.
What I mean by don't fool yourself is you're going to have to get some quiet time, slow down the body because when you slow down the body, the mind gets active, and sort things out just like rearranging a sock drawer.
Yes?
It takes a little bit of time.
And make a little bit of an effort to discover things that have been memorialized about the truth because as time goes on, you've been distracted.
Because remember, whatever country you're living in, whatever traditions you have have not really benefited you much.
I think, Seth, you and I have been on various sonic experiences during the years and we had certain people touting the benefits of Egyptian science and spiritualism and Greek philosophy.
And I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on a second.
If all that stuff was so good and so readily accessible, how well has it served anyone?
It seems to have served some pieces of, I don't know what, the oligarchy, the aristocracy.
You got to remember the oligarchy and what the elite are, they're hands off.
They have the pranksters as a buffer zone, you know, the guys with college degrees.
You ever come up with a really good remedy and discuss it in public or discover a really good remedy and someone in the group will say, and where did you get your medical degree?
You know, as if like if you don't have a medical degree, it washes everything that you say away.
Or if you bring up anything regarding any ancient text, a biblical word, where did you get your degree in that?
There's always the people are supporting the pranksters.
You're being ruled by pranksters, right?
Anybody who's ever been into a judicial court, you will know that it is run by pranksters.
Anyone who's been to a doctor, a medical doctor's office, you'll know that there are pranksters.
If you've ever been to a religious building or ceremony, you know that you're being pranked.
It's all pranking.
Now, typically, the people don't know that it's a prank, but if you've just visited this planet taking notes, that's the only thing that you could record it as being.
Because you cannot have a society functioning as it does, based on things that are based on nothing, without it being an intended prank.
So, yeah, and it sounds very, very matter of fact, but do your own research on this.
We have to give these reports because, well, you know, otherwise, if we don't, we'll just sound like everybody else does, heaven forbid.
You know, searching on what news article or what kind of a guest to bring on to talk about things that don't exist.
So, regarding dreams, I think we've pretty much summed it up with enough specifics that can be generally picked from.
Anything else, any other communications that you think we could publicly discuss?
Those were the, we kind of addressed the two that were more, you know, after information than commentary, I think.
The one talking about the actual personages of the Meshach and the Christ, as opposed to what is traditional, as well as the idea of the Trinity, the circus, the three-ring circus.
By the way, if you do study ancient stuff, there is a Trinity, but it's not discussed, unless it would be the creator.
It would be the interceder of the creator, and then mankind.
That would be a form of a Trinity, but it's not discussed because it's not, yeah.
Yeah, and speaking about the Christ, by the way, how can we present, here's the thing, everybody shut your ears for a moment.
Seth and I are going to have a private discussion.
How can we present something that is not difficult to discover, but difficult to comprehend in public, that's been held overtly in secret for over 2,000 plus years?
You know, it's like plastered on billboards, or everyone has access to it, but no one sees it.
And how can you discuss this? Are we the only ones that see it?
No, there are others, but is it very few? Absolutely.
Are we the only ones speaking out with such precision on the matter?
Yes, at the moment that we know of, and if anyone out there has any idea of anyone else speaking about even this specific topic with such precision, please let us know.
I would say, being that this is a private discussion just between the two of us, I would say that the best way would be to present a simple description,
and not necessarily a simple description that you would give to someone who has convoluted concepts of what's being discussed already,
but as if you were describing it to someone who has no convoluted concepts of what it is already.
It's someone who has just read a word and is asking, what is this in reference to?
Who is this person that's being referenced when this is being…
So, if you were describing this personage to someone who's been on the rock for, let's say, I mean…
Or uncorrupted.
Yeah, someone who's uncorrupted, like what we would think of as a foreigner or an alien to this society.
Okay, a simple way to do that is…
They see the word, the Christ, and they ask you, so what's this? To whom is this being spoken?
Well, what's interesting to identify the purpose, it would be like, what's the purpose of this, right?
There was something that had to be done to be shown to mankind,
because mankind had known that what they all have in common is that they all die, okay?
And they're subject to death.
And in order to show mankind that there was a promise and there was a premise
that there will come a time where he's no longer subject to death, they had to prove it.
Remember, the Christ only came for this sole purpose, was to prove to those who knew.
That's why when you read the text, it's very interesting.
It's spoken of, this was a promise to people, certain people.
Not everyone knew this, that this would be proven out.
And a divine being manifested in the flesh to be put to death,
to show what happens when death is put to death as a prototype.
It's very simple.
That's why his identity, per se, is still secret.
There are no imagery, iconography, or any story that even comes close in public
to how he lived and who he was.
And the way you get how he lived and who he was is by reading the scripture,
and also historical context.
But if you go to what you will conveniently find as religious context, all of it is false.
Not some of it, but all of it.
You can't even figure out what day it is.
So we have a very interesting thing, that the Christ being a who is not as important as being a what.
That's why he defined himself as the truth, the life, and the way.
Those are whats.
He had to show that these whats can be manifested.
And his personage, who he was, is actually a secret,
because that's secondary to the things that had to be done.
It's kind of like, think of people that are in special forces.
They go into a society to perform something for another society in secret.
And their identities are never known.
But the acts are actually done.
I mean, there are special forces guys that are trained to be dropped into a society
in their pajamas to take down the grid in 24 hours.
You never know who they are.
And when you see them, you don't recognize them as that being their purpose.
So this is basically a tough thing to discuss, even in private as we're doing right now, Seth,
because it is a secret.
But you can know a lot about the secret.
Most of it cannot be discussed openly, even though you can know it,
because the situation and the circumstances regarding it,
the truth of the matter is very contrary to what is held in tradition and in the culture established.
And what I mean by that, established all the way to the brick and mortar, right,
and the iconography and the culture, the film, what people have on their minds.
You're not going to be able to go against that.
It's kind of like having, I've had certain discussions with pretty high up people in various societies,
legal society, religious society, and such.
And when I bring up certain realities that can be confirmed within their own memorialized works
or writings, they always stop right here.
And I don't want to go any further.
And by the way, who are you going to tell this to?
You know, what that means is, in other words, we've got everybody by the balls, folks.
Anybody figures out, no one's going to believe you anyway.
This is the established tradition.
We're good.
Go for it.
Yeah, yeah.
You think you're going to go out and tell, no one's going to hear you anyway.
And you know what?
They're correct.
And by the way, this is why we do Uncommon Sense for two hours a week,
because I assure you this is the only two hours a week you will find anywhere
with these things discussed with such veracity and accuracy.
And Seth and I have got lots of things to do.
They're meeting here regularly every week.
And if you think that anyone else out there is discussing these things
and bundled up with such accuracy and just so much in two hours,
just let us know because we'll just refer everyone who is listed,
the four people that are listening to this Uncommon Sense radio to that.
Give us a link.
Give us whatever.
And by the way, the reason I'm bringing this up being kind of sarcastic is
because I have gotten a few things like that.
It shows me people are not listening.
They hear things.
They hear sounds.
You know, they hear like the word the or is or was,
and they think that we're saying that, yes, we are saying the word the.
But outside of that, no, there isn't anyone else discussing these things in one place like this.
And I believe that they have to be done.
And we're doing it.
So, yeah, it's very similar to maybe renaming this the show that never happened.
And by the way, I believe this is the 15th Sonic episode we have.
And we said that this was going to be a limited excursion, perhaps three more.
The number 18 seems to work well.
And then maybe we'll take a pause and start another Sonic excursion,
if all things are in place or willing to do so.
But maybe the next Sonic episodic venture could be called the show that never happened,
because this is exactly what this is.
You're hearing things that never happened in your mind because we're discussing things,
whether it's regarding the human body, the legal society, the religious society, life on Earth,
all of these other things in a way that you've never seen it in the culture and tradition that you've experienced.
So because what we're saying is not memorialized in the traditions that you're used to
and the cultures that you're used to, it can't be.
So thus, the Greek and Seth getting together and speaking on these things never really happened.
Just don't listen to these guys or who do they think they are?
Everything that we're discussing can be accessed by anyone if you just take a little bit of time.
But we've also discussed you will not make friends in the matter of a family in the matter.
It will tear your family apart, I assure you.
And if it doesn't, you're very, very, very rare.
You are so rare that you're up there in the astronomical odds.
So with that said, welcome to planet Earth.
How many times have we said that, welcome to planet Earth?
That means we're not addressing the people that are used to it here, right?
So there could be people where they are, though.
Some seem to lose sight of that every once in a while.
Sometimes when I'm surprised, I have to tell myself, well, you are on planet Earth.
And it's like, oh, yeah, I shouldn't be surprised by this, of course.
Yeah, yeah.
Here's the thing.
The applicability of this statement is very high, by the way, that if you were sleeping wherever you were sleeping last night
and no one came into the room where you were sleeping to tear the liver or kidney or body organ out of your body, you're fortunate.
So if you think you've got problems, you're taking that for granted.
And by the way, if you had confronted them while they were there to rip your organs out of the body, the organs your body is using,
and you asked them why they were doing that, they'll say, we don't need any reason because I feel like it.
And this is how it is to be on planet Earth.
So stop taking things for granted.
It's a very violent place.
And if you bear that reality in mind, you will not be taking things for granted.
And you maybe might want to look up what voting means and what electing means.
You might want to look at what the religious societies are thrusting on you.
You might want to look at what the legal societies, the medical societies and the scientific societies are thrusting on you.
Is it as bad as having a body organ ripped out of the body while you're sleeping?
No, not as bad.
But is it done in the same spirit?
Absolutely.
It's good to know what those things are, to have a different perspective than what is commonly held when viewing such things.
Because these societies are very much the various priesthoods that are in control of common thought, common perception currently.
Where did you get your degree from?
What gives you the authority to speak on such things, etc.?
And they all have their different garb.
Some of them wear black robes.
Some of them wear white coats.
Some of them wear that symbol around their necks.
Some wear pinstripes, right?
Right, absolutely, pinstripes.
Some, yeah, nice shiny shoes.
Some are barefoot.
But yeah, so take these things for what they are.
And if you're not certain what they are, look at them really hard and don't believe what you're told something is.
Look for what it really is.
One way to structure a functional belief is that belief should be based on something that happened if you believe in something in the past.
Or something that you know is going to happen in the future.
Like, for example, if you have to go to the bathroom, you believe that if you go to the bathroom, you will be in the bathroom, right?
Right.
That's a pretty good belief, right?
So in other words, or another belief would be like you know that if you walk X amount of distance because you saw something on the map that was X amount of distance on the map, you will find it there, right?
You have something to go by.
And while you're walking to where you're going that you saw on the map, if someone asks you what you're doing, I believe I'm going to this store here that I saw on the map.
That's a fairly good belief because others can reference it.
And you know what?
You're going to get there.
But when you confront most people and say, well, that's what I believe in.
It's good enough.
And I don't need to research it or I don't need to know anything else about it.
Now you're talking to a Muppet.
And the difference between a Muppet and a puppet is the workmanship.
Like a Muppet, you could pretty much go into a sock drawer, stick your arm in the sock, put a couple of buttons.
You got a Muppet.
Now a puppet usually requires a little more skill.
You've seen them, you know, performed and they're usually made of wood and clay and plastics and they're animated.
So you're really in bad shape when you run into people that are that lazy that they can be reduced to Muppet-dom or Puppet-dom.
And this is pretty much what you're dealing with with the majority of the people on this planet when it comes to terms like belief or faith or things like that.
And it's really sad.
And by the way, when we have another 15 minutes or so, when we depart from the two hours that we do here every week,
pay attention to what you're listening to everywhere else and you will see what we're talking about.
It comes in many varieties, many forms.
So what else can be uncommon, Seth?
Anything else that we could discuss perhaps from the listeners or those that have reached out to message?
No.
Like I said, we pretty much addressed the two that stood out in my mind particularly.
And I think that we addressed them in an acceptable manner.
Again, the dreams is a difficult one.
We could keep plugging away at that because, by the way, folks, just to bring it up again, is that if you are having issues with dreams,
like in other words you want them or don't want them or whatever, you want to deal with them, it's not that easy.
It's going to take a bunch of work to deal with it.
But I think what we've discussed in the recap would be study what the truth is about the dreams and what you want to do with fortitude.
Put some strength behind it spiritually, meaning with the mind, and you will see the change.
It doesn't mean that they may not come after you because these critters, these spiritual beings are just as different as people.
Like, for example, you could be traveling along the road minding your own business and you're stalked by a car with flashing lights
and they want to kill you or give you all kinds of things and show up in front of a court with a priest with a black robe and all this.
Or the same person, another person could be going down the road and a stalker with flashing lights comes up to him and says,
Oh, just be careful next time. Have a nice day.
You don't know what these situations, there's no consistency.
But what is consistent is basically the framework that we gave that you are being plugged by outsiders, outside other spirits other than your own.
I think that enough.
The knowledge of it, you know, how does it go?
The avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
Now, if dreams, whether they be good or bad or trappings, that is up to the individual to decide.
Because we, again, preface that most societies on the pagan side or the nation, how would you, again, please define pagan or paganism for us?
The uninformed.
That's a very accurate single word.
That's another word.
It's just the uninformed.
And by the way, like I mentioned earlier, there are quite a few people coming out these days, meaning past few years.
They're quite proud of being that in a way, which is fine, by the way.
I'm not certain they're aware of what the word that they're using means.
But that's, you know, shouldn't be surprising, I suppose.
Yeah.
Right.
Exactly.
It's just, yeah.
I just find it amusing.
I mean, you might want to call it part of the personal entertainment.
Right?
I guess.
Years ago it was, you know, maybe some soft shoe tap dance, maybe somebody juggling on a street corner, you know, maybe a card trick here or there, someone telling a good joke.
Now the best entertainment I get is people calling themselves pagans.
But anyway.
So it's, yeah, it's just beyond belief.
But, yeah, if you – yeah.
So anyway.
So, yeah, that's the thing.
Oh, the other thing I wanted to bring up perhaps in passing, just got into the mind.
You ever notice that when there are social changes, typically things that are considered abominable, deviant, or unlawful, when they're established and integrated into society, those that don't agree with their establishment in society are known to be phobic of that particular existence or condition.
You ever notice that?
Like, for example, I'll bring up – there's something called – if you are speaking – I'm not – this is just a general comment.
I've been seeing this a lot, the LGBTQ, RSTUV, whatever community stuff that's being thrusted in society right now, right?
If you are speaking out against it, those that are either indifferent or for it call you a homophobe, right?
Like you're afraid of it or something, right?
Like an arachnophobe, right?
So if you don't want spiders in the house, you're arachnophobic.
Phobic, by the way, folks, means fear or phobia, to be afraid of.
Can we get a definition on phobia, by the way?
It's P-H-O-B-I-A.
How about agnostophobia, fear of the unknown?
But, you know, be careful, folks.
Watch what's being thrusted on the moronic society, that when there tends to be a disagreement with a certain agenda, you're phobic now of it.
So that means that there is no rational conveyance or rational thought or discussion.
You're branded as a phobe or fear because you don't feel or understand or want to rationalize the acceptance of a certain group or action.
It's because you're afraid of it.
There is no more rational discussion of the matter, whether it's lawful or whether it's moral or proper.
You're just strictly phobic.
Watch out for this stuff.
This is very interesting, and people kind of go along with it.
It's kind of interesting to see how the word phobia is being thrust on those that are looking to engage into some kind of a rational discourse regarding a subject.
And if it immediately is contrary to that subject, you're a phobic.
It's very interesting.
I just, yeah, it's an abandonment of rationale here.
And they're very quick to brand, just like if you bring up a notion that is part of a particular society, they ask you if you have a degree.
Otherwise, you have no business speaking on it.
It's like the hijacking of rational discourse.
But anything else on the word phobia?
Directly from Greek, panic, fear of, from phobos, which is simply fear, became widespread popular use with native words from about 1800.
Phobic, being related.
Irrational fear, horror, or aversion.
So how do they – I don't understand the homophobic thing, because here comes a very feminine guy wearing lipstick and a purse and high heels with a hairy chest and a beard, and he's acting like a woman down the street.
Everybody run!
We're total fear of him.
Does that make any sense?
No.
That doesn't make any sense to me.
But that's what's being thrust as the label.
I don't understand – well, this is what I do understand, is that the prevention of rational discussion is paramount.
It's got to be what group – what do you believe in?
Hey, what's your political view?
Hey, how about the Mets?
How about the Yankees?
If it's anything outside of that, wow, man, you've got to be thrust into a category of something that is not even relevant.
How can there be rational discussion?
It's almost to be avoided.
And, of course, if you've just come to this planet and you've been here for 14 minutes, maybe in the next minute you'll figure that out.
That's what's going on here, folks.
And for the four or five listeners that we have, they pretty much tune in to hear or listen to what's being said here as well to maybe garner something,
so they can see that there's very little rationalization of anything going on.
But, yeah, I just wanted to bring that up.
Thank you, Seth, for looking that up.
Just keep in mind, folks, any kind of agenda that's thrust onto you, and immediately if you're not – if you're looking to look at it more rationally,
you're considered a phobe.
Let's just add that to the list of ridiculous things that are being done here on this planet.
There's an interesting list of the various words commonly used using the word-forming element phobia at the end of them.
Philophobia is an interesting one.
Okay, fear of friends.
Or plants.
Feto would be plants, yeah.
Agnostophobia.
Is that one there, agnostophobia?
Because if you know a little bit – yeah.
Yeah, it's a word-forming element, so essentially you can add it to another word.
Yes, you can make these up all day.
Yeah, absolutely.
Can I list a Greek prefix?
Say that again?
Triskaidekopphobia.
You're the number 13.
Oh, okay.
That one comes from Trice and Deka, three and ten.
Yeah, and phobia.
Phonophobia.
Probably not going to speak to many phonophobes through the radio, but phono being sound.
Yeah, anything else that's unusual.
Absolutely. There's a lot of fears out there.
How about aletheophobia, which is fear of the truth?
Yeah, alethe meaning truth in Greek, or emet in Hebrew, or truth in English,
or cierto or verdad in Latin or Spanish, right?
Veritas.
So, yeah, I think fear of the truth is – people hate the truth, by the way,
and yes, if you're listening and you hate the truth,
it's going to make you feel very uncomfortable to hear that.
You know, I think I mentioned – by the way, Seth, I was recently in a conversation
with someone who got all heated and saying that,
I don't get any knowledge from a book, I get it from experience,
and I just love to hear stuff like that because it just confirms why we do this show.
Speaking of doing this show, I guess we're going to call it two hours or so,
and Seth, thanks for coming and listening.
Yeah, again, thanks for the slight tardiness, but yeah, we'll be back doing it again next week.
You're listening to American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
This is Uncommon Sense, and you can find us on the Internet at UncommonRadio.com.
www.uncommonradio.com.
Thanks, everyone.