Thank you. Welcome everyone as well. Greetings. And we're here again. Yes. Reckoning the end of
the first week of the fifth month. Boy, did we lose most of the audience by saying that.
What the hell did you just say? Yes, it's the fifth month, folks, appears to be finally,
appearingly the end of the first week. And how is that reckoned? It's reckoned in the light
versus in the dark. So, hey, by the way, ever heard why the sun never sets on the
British Empire? Because, you know, maybe you can't trust the British in the dark.
Yeah, it's a little thing to bring up for what they call current events, I guess.
I don't know. Current events. I don't know. Don't touch that current. You might get zapped,
maybe. But if you're already brain dead, it doesn't matter. So either way, let's just I want
to just jump into something regarding the current events. Hey, Seth, have you ever heard about
somebody talking about a coming Middle East Union perhaps in the next decade?
Pavlovian bells are ringing. Yes. Yeah. There's something interesting about that. I mean,
how many people are discussing that? I mean, just you and I, maybe, you know, there might be a
little smatterings about it here and there. It's not really well understood. But we've been
basically emphatically saying this for I have for over a decade with great specificity and
does anyone care? Well, yeah, we've already established there's about four or five people
listening to this conversation. And by the way, this is when you say we get together to do this
as a conversation piece, perhaps primarily. Yeah, that's certainly my end of it.
Right. And maybe the other end, I don't know which one's the head, which one is the tail. But
I'd say that maybe bringing a slight highest and best use of this medium known as, I don't know,
digital telephony, Internet radio, communications in the open public sort of venue, because I'll
tell you, there's very little going on, folks. But yeah, speaking of which, very little going on.
Some of the staff at AFR last week kind of asked, would you like to hear talked about
just briefly said, let's talk about technology. Now, what do you think of that, Seth? What does
that word even mean? Do you want to do a little bit of keyboard surfing on that?
In the meantime, I can do the technology study of ology. Then we that's a technos,
which also means child and to be deceived in certain parts of the Greek language. But yeah,
technos meaning technical, let's say from techno and lology, meaning the study of mechanical
industrial arts, 16 tens of discourse or trusting on art or the arts. Let's see.
Let's go to the techno word forming element, meaning art, craft or skill.
Let from later technical technology from Latin, nice form of Greek techno,
combining form of technique, you know, technique, et cetera, art, skill, craft and work method,
system and art system or method of making or doing. OK, so basically, craftsmanship skilled,
you know, like it could be even thrown in there like underwater basket weaving or advanced nose
picking, things like that, you know, things that are considered to be the height of mankind right
now. But OK, so in essence, let's let's boil it down real quick. It's just the making of tools,
let's say, to impress others or perhaps not just to impress, but to use. Right.
Typically, when you think of a craftsman versus just someone freewheeling it or freewheeling it,
let's say you're thinking of tools and things that are being made versus like someone who stands
up and sings, for example, that then they're using the voice as an instrument or a tool that can be
tuned. But nonetheless, it's the making of tools and to sum things up, by the way, let's just fast
forward the state of technology today or the height of it in many cases or in most cases, as it
relates to the population, you know, the mass, let's say the large numbers, what you will see
if you objectify is the the height perhaps of mass production, making not just hundreds or
thousands, but millions and billions of things. And also the height of miniaturization, making
them smaller and smaller and smaller. And I'm referring to many of the electronic circuits
and things like that and even little motors and things like that. So in essence, one can easily
maybe one way to describe what's going on technologically is an appeal towards mass
manufacture, mass production and miniaturization. Perhaps that would be a rapid way to broad brush,
objectify at least the the advancements that are when you say technology was considered to
be advances, small and many of them. The other thing that could be easily looked at is,
well, you're ready for this. You know, some people don't like it because sometimes it gets emotional.
But here's good emotion, the vanity of it. You know, like what I mean by that is, well,
let me just preface, you know, the ancient Greeks said, you know, fashion for clothing is irrelevant
because the human body doesn't change. Why does the clothing always change? Right. So what's
interesting, you really want to mess around with the species, you know what I mean, species, the
average human surface dwelling earth inhabitant going to what they call a car dealership, which are
nothing but horse thieves, by the way. But anyway, you go in there and you say, well, obviously you
haven't figured out how to make it right because you're coming out with a new model every year.
Right. Because if they figured out how to make automobiles correctly,
well, they just make them and sell them or put them out. But they keep changing them. Why? Because
there's a vanity aspect, you know, like, you know, Tom on the block gets 2015 and,
you know, Joe down the street gets the 2016. Aha, I've got the newer one. Right. See,
it's just a matter of looking different. So there's a lot of vanity in technology.
Also, it's just vain, I guess. But let's just look at the state of technology today. It's basically
geared towards communication. But if you look at the communication, well, I shouldn't say just
geared towards. There's a lot of interesting things going on, but not that interesting.
Again, if you tie in the miniaturization, the mass production and the vanity aspect.
Anything else you want to throw in, Seth, regarding describing technology today before
we dig in a little bit deeper? Well, yeah, there's the different aspects of it, but the
essentially it's doing the same thing better. There seems to be little
real innovation in doing something in a different manner. So like you said, mass production,
smalling, you know, smaller, smaller size, scaling things down,
which are, you know, not necessarily bad things. They're done correctly and for a purpose.
But that's basically the height of it. Something that's using relatively old technology
in a new way currently would be, and it's not even really new, but on the virtual reality,
the implementation of such things like that on a larger scale is just around the corner. You're
already seeing it trickle in. It's going to be interesting because it will make the internet,
which already is, you know, kind of a place unto itself. It will make it pseudo-tangible
in many different ways, you know, tricking the mind.
Right, or appealing to the mind or accommodating certain desires that people are told they should
have. Right. Absolutely. Yeah. If you listen to that carefully, people have desires that
they told they should have. Anyway, I think we gave the definition of puppets and muppets earlier,
but that's another story. Okay. You know, we had an email regarding automobiles, cars,
reciprocating motors from a fellow, and I've answered it a while back, and I think we were
going to talk about it. Maybe now's the time to interject a little bit in there what's going on
with the car engine. And by the way, how many times have you heard people saying it's the same old
technology from 100 years ago? Yeah, it is pretty much. But not only is it the same old technology,
it's not even being addressed. Everyone is being given the notion that, you know, you have these
pistons that go up and down and there's explosions and gases and fuels and things, and it's the boom
and the bang and these, you know, that make the thing go. And if you actually study what's going
on in a car engine, you'll find that the common stuff that's discussed about it is just simply
not true. Now, what is not true about an automobile, a reciprocating motor, is that these
violent occurrences inside the motor are driving it, and there's rapid, you know,
changes and things, you know, and there is actually, if you do what's called a compression
test, which you measure the pressure of the piston, you'll notice that there's no change. What I mean
by that is when the piston goes up and down and you have the violent explosions, if you measure
the pressure in the chamber, you will notice there is a very little change. What happens is when the
explosion happens and it pushes the piston down, you're thinking, oh wow, you know, like you see
in the movies, an explosion, a lot of pressure, shock waves. Well, you'll notice that the pressure
is at a certain point, and then when the event is over and the valve's open to exhaust all the gases,
the pressure is still the same. Why? What's going on, right? Well, very simply, when the
explosion happens, the pressure starts to increase, but the piston goes down, increasing the volume,
which stabilizes the pressure, keeps it very close to what it was before the explosion.
But then as the piston comes up to contract, you think the pressure is going to increase again
because you're taking the given space and squeezing it, but cold air and cold fuel are
being deposited, which creates a rapid contraction. You see? So whether the piston is going up and
down, explosion or no explosion, the pressure in the engine is the same. Now, you could look at
compression test graphs and you will see, yeah, there are little spikes and things like that.
That's basically what they call valve lash or valve bounce and the valve's opening and closing.
But generally, the pressure is in the high hundreds or, you know, between 120 and 200,
let's say, typically, with little fluctuation. So there seems to be a natural, just like in nature,
a balance that's being made and it's not very much in accordance with the intuitiveness that
people have about when they hear explosion and things like that, right? The other thing I want
to mention about the car is, or the reciprocating motor, is you're ready for something that sounds
ridiculous, actually, that actually will prove that it's not. Well, you know, no one has ever burned any
fuel in the engine to make it go. Well, that sounds ridiculous. Well, why are we, you know, when we
have a gas tank, it goes down to empty, we can't go. Well, the reason you're putting fuel into the
reciprocating motor is to burn the air. Think about it, because you could, let's say, you're using
petrol or gasoline, you could substitute that with alcohol and other fuels, methane, propane, like
they do in warehouses and things like that, right? Hydrogen. You can substitute the fuel for many
things, but the ultimate goal is to ignite the air. So if anyone out there's got more than two
sharpened pencils in their pocket, which is an old engineering term for meaning you're good at
designing things, coming up with ideas, let's say, why don't you think of alternative ways to make the
air burn instead of what you're being told, right? And then there's another concept, there's
something called the ignition, the spark that ignites everything. There's a hell of a lot more
going on with that. And speaking from firsthand experience on developing those types of things,
little ignition systems that shouldn't work the way they, you know, do, that needs to be looked
at as well. High voltage, there's a lot of phenomenon going on with very high voltage,
which I dare anyone to define what a volt is, most people can't. So I just wanted to throw that in
maybe to satisfy a little bit more, and maybe we'll talk about the automobile in the future a
little bit more, but I just wanted to throw in those concepts right now regarding the automobile,
because it's based on vanity. If you look at all they do is they change the way it looks. And
they're still, by the way, very, very inefficient. 25% is probably your best efficiency on the small
engines, you know, typical car engines. And even if you go to a lot of the government regulatory
websites, they tell you that 80 to 90% of all your fuel is combusted where? In the exhaust system.
So for every given amount of currency or credits you spend on buying fuel, remember,
80% of that might as well just dump it on the ground, because it's just turned being turned
into heat, it's not making it go. So it's not very difficult to reverse that, by the way,
to make the engine 80% efficient 20% wasteful. I mean, it is it is because there are a lot of
redundant systems put into engines to make them indifferent to change,
like computers and things like that. Now, if you tamper with it, and that, but you know,
this is a consideration for the young folks and the folks that are have an open mind in that
direction. Consider that what you're being told and the thing that you think is going on with that
thing called the reciprocating motor is not so when you observe it. And just like anyone,
and that it knows these things that are in the, let's say an authoritative figure in that field,
when you explain it to them, or describe have a conversation like this, they look at you and
they don't want to address what you're saying. They're like, Yeah, but who are you going to go
tell this to? Because no one really cares, or everyone thinks it's the other thing anyway.
So this is for those that are willing to blaze forward and look at things a little differently.
So that's, that's, that's the story about cars, and I'm sticking to it
for now. But let's maybe continue a little more with technology. You know,
I've heard a lot of people, by the way, Seth, or let's say a lot meaning because more than three
say that we should disregard what is old, because we're so advanced right now technologically.
And that obviously is the mark of a simple simpleton. By the way, they over have oversimplified
the vanity and the impression that they've gotten from being modern. And they feel that
things that have before should be heavily discounted into oblivion. And I've actually
heard this from several walks of life, high and low, if you want to look at that that way.
And robots are going to free man from labor, right?
Yeah, perhaps.
That was that was predictions about that's what that's what should be going on.
That was in the World's Fair typically in the 19 what they call the 1930s. They were promoting
that a lot, which is, yeah, they're promoting flying cars by the year 2000. By the way,
folks, you're not going to get any of that stuff. And you notice back in the early to mid 20th
century, there was, you know, the Jetsons. And yeah, all these things were so advanced, you know,
hotels on the moon and flying jetpacks and you know, all this stuff, you can get none of it.
Absolutely not. Not now, at least never, you're never going to get it, let's say,
because never is running out here pretty soon. Another less than two decades,
decade and a half or so. Things will be so different that you will not consider these
things. But I want to go back to the mindset that says that we should heavily discount anything
that's come before us because we're advanced now, right? With instant communication. It's not the
tool of being able to instant communicate. It's what are you communicating? You know, look at it.
I mean, look at what's being said in the media, alternative and mainstream. It's laughable.
It's a big joke. But anyway, here's the thing. Since I brought up being old, things that not
being old, but things of the past, you ever ponder what? Well, you might have heard of what's been
said about it, but ever ponder what would happen if you were able to transport someone from ancient,
let's say from two or 3000 4000 years ago into the modern day society, how they would observe
things I've actually pondered and written about it. Short little narrative and want to explain
that. But what do you think would happen if you brought an ancient Seth into the modern today
current society and you know, they stepped out of whatever they want to step out of the transport
device, you know, let's just keep it figurative here. And they're walking around, let's say in
a big city or wherever. Because even if you go into rural environments, you'll still be subject to the
influence of the current technology, right? To some degree, what do you think they would be
impressed or shocked or, or find relevant or irrelevant or whatever, you know, how would how
would I've got a pretty interesting few interesting thoughts on that. And what do you think, Seth,
you think they'd be impressed or not? No, not really. Exactly. It wouldn't be would take 15
or 20 minutes, maybe an hour, a day or two or three to get used to it, maybe. Yeah. Now, here's
what I discussed and wrote about. I believe I, you know, if this were to happen, what would be the
most shocking thing? Well, you know, to to an ancient brought into modern day society. Now
before let me just preface this, this is not you know, I don't know. But this is a way of rationalizing
things. By the way, other than walking through society and pointing at all the sex temples that
have been built, you know, meaning houses of worship, by the way, they all use the architecture
of the ancient sex temples. Yep. And you bring children into them and you worship there. But
anyway, all of them. But asphalt, they would be in total shock to see this black stuff spread
everywhere on the ground. What you've done with this dark substance. Think about it for a moment.
Yeah, yeah, the lights are the lights will make sense. You explain what's going on, you know,
it glows and it's hot. They had things that glowed and were hot made light as well.
But the concept of spreading this coal tar mixed with gravel everywhere would be the main feature
that would be just difficult to get over with. Or just kind of like, why the hell did you do that?
Well, makes for a smooth road. Yeah, but still look at it. And no one is paying attention to
this. Isn't it interesting? Now, by the way, I just want to throw something in what we'll kind
of maybe move forward on technology or not. You ever hear of water safety regulations and EPA,
you know, environmental protection laws regarding like runoff water and storm water and things like
that don't contaminate it, right? Don't don't put anything in the water. You know, don't pour
anything down the drain that might be harmful to the fishes or the processing plant or storm
sewers tend to go directly back into the environment or something. Anyone ever want to do a little bit
of research on the chemical constituents in asphalt and the propagation and leaching rates
and what comes out of asphalt when you pour water over it? Yeah, go do a little bit of research on
that. Look at the hypocrisy. How much water runs off of asphalt in the modern societies?
Most of it in many cases. What do you think is leaching out of the asphalt and running in? Yeah,
so yeah, that's that. I can't look at that, though. No, no, no. We can't look at that.
Can't regulate that. Yeah. So yeah, it's an interesting thought. It's the coal tar
spread everywhere that would just shock the living daylights out of an ancient product today.
Maybe just the coal tar being used everywhere. The darkness. I think we've described briefly.
Have you ever heard of let's say I'm paraphrasing here a caveat. Beware the workers of darkness.
You know, and of course, most people use a lot of petroleum products that are all made in darkness.
Yes. And well, their behavior. See, the thing is, it's not just visible light. It's the
behavior that's attached to that. You know, years ago, people dealt with materials that
were produced in the light. Plant fibers, animal materials, plant dyes, surface minerals,
right? Things like that. Things that were usually felt or found on the surface and used.
So the material was garnered from things produced in the light today.
It's kind of you'd be hard pressed to interact with any material that hasn't been affected
with anything that hasn't been derived from petrochemicals, which is under the ground,
which is derived from darkness. Petrochemicals or petroleum, rock oil, by the way, is made in the
dark and it's black. So you're spreading this dark substance everywhere. It's an energetic
sense that sources the dark. You know, years ago, the full moon was the new moon. Now it's
the dark moon is the new moon. Years ago, you reckon the day at high noon in the light. Now
you reckon the day when? Middle of the night. And years ago, the new year was reckoned in the
light and springtime in the day. And now when do you reckon your new year? On the darkest month,
according to the Pope's work schedule, at the darkest part of the month, the darkest part of
the day, the darkest part of the year. Pretty dark. Pretty dark group of people.
Now, the spirit being in the light, let's say, gets sick in the dark. And the spirit that is,
let's say, maybe intended for the dark, gets sick in the light. Every time you ever hear the term
psychopath, psycho, meaning the mind or spirit, and patho, pathos, meaning sickness. And there's
a little bit, you know, you know, a discomfort or just, yeah, not the way it should be. There's a
little memes, you know, people, you know, like, remember, years ago, people discussed,
oh, this left brain, right brain, man, it's all about that. And then it became
flat earth now. No, I keep as the earth round again. Right. And if you ask anyone about these
things that they discussed, and especially alternative media years ago, that was back
then we don't really talk about that right now. Well, there's been a lot of talk about
not so much now as it was about these psychopaths ruling everyone. Listen, folks,
you're all psychopaths, entire human race, except for those that are want to heal that condition,
because you are sick. You're in the dark, you're workers of darkness. This is not a critical
point of saying you're bad, you're just sick. People that are sick are not bad. And they're
like, well, what about those that had a conversation recently? Again? What about
those that are ruling? Is there the psychopath? Well, no, here's here's what's going on.
People that rule are definitely put there by certain influences. And what they Yes,
they could be they're psychopathic, of course, by how we just mentioned it. But they're ruling
another group of psychopaths. And those the groups that they're ruling are taught that they should
give 90% of their energy to the psychopaths that are ruling them, and stab each other in the back
for the remaining 10%. Right? So if you eliminate any of the quote, unquote, psychopaths that are
ruling the rest of the psychopaths, you prop up another one of the common psychopaths, and they
will behave that way also. And they will tell the remaining psychopaths to give all their energy to
them or 90% and stab everyone else in the back for the remaining 10%. So you're all pretty
psychopathic until you realize it, and realize it's something that needs to be addressed.
So another moot point regarding the information that people are getting being given. But anyway,
they're just being accommodated. It's like the self consuming thing, you know, look at again,
with technology. Why don't they just make the same car? No, they figure out how to make it right.
Because they have to accommodate vanity, a sick mind, let's say, I'm better because I've got the
model. You know, you know, people always want wish well, well wishing to everyone else, I want you to
do well. But in their mind, they're like, just don't do better than I'm doing. Right? And even
parents, by the way, folks. Yes. Maybe what's uncommon is to talk about things that can be
objectified. Parents stop pranking the children. Stop lying to the children, stop pranking them.
All I hear is things like the caveat. Yes, son or daughter, the education system is worthless and
damaging. But I went through it. So you have to go through it. So yeah, so you're so the psychopathic
starts with the parents, the parents in general, this holds pretty true across the board, except
for very, very, very, very few exceptions, down to maybe so few that it's very safe to say generally
parents are pranking and lying and harming their own children. Objectively, how dare you say that
Greek parents are loving and they bring you into the world? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, all that stuff.
I'm not negating that. But let's just look at the picture. Objectively, parents information.
Yeah, yes. Yeah. And disinformation. Santa Claus, you know, holidays, telling children what to do.
Children ask, they can't answer. So yeah, it's really it has to start with the parents. By the
way, you know how you increase the let's say this uses word loosely education level of a society.
The easiest way to do it is by educating the women.
Focusing on that because the women are the ones that spend most of the time
raising the children to their formative years. And if the women are educated, well read, well
versed in many things and give good instruction. The children during their formative years, you
know, from when they were born till seven or eight will be exposed to that. So you want to educate
raise the level of a society, raise the level of the women. And I'm not talking about guys dressing
like women. Anyway. Yeah. So yeah, these things are very, very simple. And they're not commonly
discussed. Why? Because maybe you just talked about psychopaths. So let's go back to the
technology. What do you think, Seth? Oh, there's psychopaths, too. Yeah.
Well, the technology or tools, man is trying to make better tools. But, you know,
they're tools that look better. You know, there are certain things, by the way, in technology that
are extremely simple, new ideas and the way you get a new ideas by reading a very old book, by the way.
Yeah. So, yeah. And also understanding the times, certain times, you know, I had once read a thing,
you know, you remember how inline skates or roller skates were popular even until the 90s,
like it was kind of a still see them not as much. But but, you know, you had the quad skates,
you know, the four wheels, you know, two wheels paired up, you know, next to each other. And
they were metal and made a lot of noise in the 50s and all that. Well, in the mid 19th century,
the inline skate, all wheels made out of wood or rubber were put together by a fellow in the
mid 19th century. And he wanted to show this thing off or introduce it. And he was at a soiree,
you know, people of, let's say, a certain society. And during the the ball or the
dance, there was a break and he comes out rolling inline skates and he was so excited.
He, I guess, had a little mishap and he went through the French doors over the balcony
and was killed. Bad accident. And they all said, oh, that was a really, really bad idea.
Let's never do that. I did not know that. That took about 150 years to be revisited.
So, yeah, a lot of these things that we discover are and I want to just yeah, well, I was going to
talk a little bit about Frank Chester's comment on the difference between a discovery and an
invention or inventing and discovering. Inventing typically you find when something is, quote unquote,
invented, you find there are several parties throughout the planet or a place in society
or many societies that are working on the same thing unbeknownst to each other.
And so, yeah, there's a lot of things that we discover where discovery is something very unique.
When someone makes a discovery, it's just one person or one individual that makes it and that's it.
So there's an interesting thing. I just want to credit that to Frank Chester,
which if anyone wants a good, relaxing, mind-opening way to look at things that are called
geometric forms in relation to other things, look up Frank Chester as if Chester drawers,
C-H-E-S-T-E-R, that is Chester Hedren, a seven-sided figure. Very interesting.
Just a little fun there. He considers himself to be a master teacher and I would agree he is.
Yeah, if you master these.
Seven-sided shape with equal area.
Equal area but not equal, right. So it is lawful, yes, in terms of area.
And I like him because he discusses what's lawful and unlawful.
In terms of his, I like his discussion based on
things should be proven out. By the way, when things are proven out, they're considered lawful.
But no one cares about lawful, right. You're talking to a group of psychopaths that are
immoral. Anyway, I shouldn't get into that. But yes, there are four or five people perhaps left
that might want to consider something lawful.
So yeah, so technology here, we're making tools where we, whoever we is, the corporate we,
collective we. And based on the mindset of vanity, people, if you tell someone something is so,
so many times before they get it, they establish that it's so, and then when they get it, it's so,
even though it's not. Well, what did he just say? How many times have you heard,
the new phone is coming out in three months? Oh, wow, it's going to do all these things.
It's the greatest thing. Everyone's waiting and waiting. Now, if you objectify it and look at it,
it's a piece of crap. But you know, you've been told so much that it's so great and so advanced
that when you get it, you just don't care anymore.
They haven't made one of those that works right yet either.
Yeah. Yeah. But you see, you see what's going on, how you're set up for it. And you still have
people saying, well, we're so advanced now, man. You can't look at all this other stuff yet.
Yeah. Yeah. The psychopath speaking, you know, the sick mind is addressed. See, you address sick
people differently than you address people that are healthful. Right. So, you know, how many times
have you heard? Well, if you've ever been in this situation, you know, you know, your little sister
didn't feel well today. She stayed home from school. She's six, you know, so when you come home,
you know, it's a different setting, you know, your sister sleeping. Don't wake them up. Right.
Right. Either they need their rest. Yeah. So they rest. So the way most people rest is by
enduring this self-consuming consumerism. By the way, the consumption was known as TB.
Tuberculosis was a disease, by the way, when you talk about consumption or the consumer.
Someone had the consumption was a consumer. That means the end, right? Yeah. Con, with, and
summation would, you know, some being the root there, the end. Right. And the consumer would be
the end user of something that's produced. I would say with, you know, and like you just
leaning towards the mass production aspect as well, a lot of what is considered, you know,
higher technology and stuff like that is more readily available to a larger population.
I'll be it. I mean, the population is currently larger than it has been in
a easily accessed recorded history. So I suppose that's some of it. But the
easy access to potable water is one thing. Indoor, you know, not indoor plumbing itself, but the
indoor pressurized water, although that's been around for, you know, millennia.
Yes. Multiple story buildings have running water in ancient days. Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely. It was it was done. But on the level that it is, you know,
with everyone having, you know, the faucets in their homes and things like that, easily,
easy to it's not it's not a new technology. It's just something that's been made more widely
available in different forms. But as far as being, you know, new or novel, it's really not.
It's just the the newness of it is the ease of access for a greater number of people.
It's one of the things that is overlooked a lot by the, I guess, the naysayers of how
how terrible everything is, is the fact that there is it's currently
easier to access clean drinking water on this planet relatively than at any other time.
Yes. So even though water is still not really understood, speaking of which, by the way,
you know, the Romans were known, let's say the most recent when you speak of ancient times,
the most recent ones would be the the Romans. There's a lot of references. And by the way,
there's no such thing as the Roman Empire or the Roman this or Roman that it's all Greek,
by the way, it's a splinter that broke off from the Greek society. So that's,
you know, when you hear a lot of people badgering, this is Rome, right? All this other stuff.
What about Romulus and Remus and that wolf? And yeah, sure. Well, let's look at it. But,
you know, look at other societies, you know, like if you go to Sicily, for example, you know,
it's all Greek, right? You look at all the old writings, it's all in Greek. It was a penal
colony, just like, you know, Brazil was a penal colony. Australia is a penal colony. New Zealand,
I guess, maybe not, you know, you know, all these other places that were, you know,
you shoved certain things there, you know, or people to create an alternate society,
for example. Say again? 19 crimes. There was 19 crimes you could be
sent to Australia for committing. Interesting. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, good. I haven't heard that.
Yeah. So like the states, what they call America is pretty much, you know, they were English
subjects predominantly, you know, and the others that came across. So Rome is a splinter group of
the Greek Empire, let's say, expanded by Alexander. If you look at a lot of the things
of faults and flawed aspects of society that people blame on Rome, let's say you might look
at Catholicism or the Vatican, that is nothing but the revival of Hellenistic paganism that
was developed by Simon Magus, incorporating rituals from Babylon and Canaan and Amorite,
basic, you know, the stuff that was considered don't do. And, you know, so it's basically,
again, Hellenistic paganism. What they call the laws, those came out of the Athenian democratic
states, you know, and derived through Roman, just like many things now are considered American,
but they're actually derived from English. So, but if we look at the Roman, go back to the
water aspect, you know, they had public works projects, where they would have people that
were contracted to bring in water sources that would come into the gate of the city or the center
of the city. And they would be judged by the leaders of the municipality on their on the
quality before it was tied into the network of pipes and culverts and things to deliver it to
the people. So what they would do to discern the quality is they would bring out the people and
have the water gathered in a well or a large opening where the water accumulated temporarily
for several weeks before they incorporated it. And they would judge the quality by encouraging
people to throw coins into the water. And looking at the coins after a certain amount of time,
for example, if the coins became encrusted with calcified material and things, they said,
well, the water is not very good. Or sometimes they would throw coins into the wells and these
open areas, and the coins would dissolve, like that water is not very good. So that's a little
bit of history and where you get the wishing well, you know, people throwing coins into the water,
there's an actual practical chemical engineering aspect to it. Just wanted to throw that in there.
So you still do a lot of things. And you've been told there for certain reasons. And it made sense
that they were considered wishing wells because you wanted the new water source, you wish that the
new water source was viable and potable and met the mark of good water, right? What if the water,
the new waters that were being brought in were not fit? Well, you wish they were. So they were,
I guess, dubbed wishing wells, right? You wouldn't wish the water to be bad. So yeah, so this is
where, you know, maybe certain we'll just throw that in as being an uncommon thought. But yeah,
the water aspect. Yes, that was around as well. In many societies, they had multiple story buildings
with water flowing, they elevated water and made the water flow in different ways they understood.
Were they moving it through straight pipes?
Actually, they attempted to make it the distance between the distances were, you know, the shortest
distance between two points is a straight line. And they attempted to do that basically, because
it was less work and less material. But the actual pipes themselves, for example, in certain places,
they were slightly tapered cones that one fit into another with a pressure fit, right? And by virtue
of it being a cone created an undulating motion. That would almost make it a vortex. Yeah.
Yes. As it's flowing through there. Wow. And because they didn't move solid rock and
they would rather go around natural formations, they had a more of a meandering line. See,
today they'll blast and bore to make it straight, right? Back then, if there was a big boulder
somewhere, they'd say, well, let's just go around it. And you got that little bit of meandering,
which allowed the water. And also, by the way, if you do build a very long straight line with
liquid flowing through it, you will get standing waves and you'll get things wanting to
not behave properly. So they knew about that as well. Yes. And they kept it dark and they didn't
use ferrous materials. They used wood and terracotta typically and things like that.
And the water was more, it was able to breathe more. They didn't have these plastic seals and
things and welding devices to make things really tight and shut and very strong pumps
to push things, chop the water. It allowed it to flow more naturally in many cases.
So yes. So technology regarding water. Yes. I think I've said in the past,
if you've been around in other conversations, I've said that when mankind understands
or fully comprehends how to integrate and disintegrate water, he will master the material
world. And maybe that's the case why you're still told water is H2O. And maybe that's why
when you go and purchase water, it's in clear containers with flat bottoms exposed to light
and warm. Or water should be dark and kept cool. So yeah, we'll do the water thing one day. But in
the meantime, folks, if you do use water, by the way, for potability or drinking, make sure it's
not in the light and make sure it's in a cool place, meaning at least 39 or 4 degrees Celsius.
And you will find the water quality increases when you do that. That's basically the crux of the
matter of keeping water in a quality state. But yes, technology and water are interlinked.
What's interesting, by the way, look at the most of the simpleton mind will say,
look how technologically advanced. And they're referring to the computing and electrical devices.
Right. They require special types of water to keep things clean as well. So again,
without this type of deionized, super clean water, they can't make these circuit boards.
Well, they use a lot of other synthetic chemicals also, but it's very important that they have
extremely clean water for certain things. But for technology, folks, it's just a matter of tools.
And I would consider the vanity aspect of it. You know, here's the thing also, even with the
computer thing, you know, that's the phones, which are now, you know, smart phones, I guess,
because, you know, they never say the user is smart. You ever notice that?
How about dumb phones and smart people?
There's an idea. Yeah. So but but nonetheless, again, they're doing the thing with the vanity.
Let's just contemplate the matter and make it correctly. But no, they've got to have a new phone
every year, every year, which starts in the darkness. So the people are kind of in the dark
about their own vanity. You know, vanity, vanity, everything's vanity.
Yes, yes. You know, I want everyone to do well, but just don't do better than I am doing.
Right. So this is your typical mind set of the prevailing mindset of the species.
Let's just say. Yeah. So I guess with the technology aspect, what more can we say?
I mean, objectifying it to a certain degree is the best way to do it.
Absolutely. Instant communication. Nearly instant.
Oh, yeah, it sure is. Skype is an interesting thing. There are several things that appear to
be instant, no time delay. I would say, yeah, that's for for all practical purposes. It's
it's been achieved now just needs to be slightly more consistent and reliable.
Yes. But, you know, there's there's an interesting thing about that, you know,
something called a utility, you know, the public utilities you subscribe to it. Right.
It's the subscription office that's mucking things about, you know, they've got to create
again, because there's vanity and gluttony and greed in humanity. You can't give them free
access to everything because they're just not going to be as conservative about it.
You know, what do you think people are going to do when they find out all the utilities,
water, phone, all that stuff is already being paid for?
And what the reason they're being billed every month is so it kind of like regulate them?
You know, if they had a different mindset, it would be understood, by the way, when you
deal with I want to bring up utilities. All of these things are public works. You know,
the water, electric, gas, phone, those are paid for already. But the only what they've
done, the legal society is behind the scenes, they know human nature. And they're like, well,
we tell people it's all paid for. They'll leave the house with the water running and all the
lights on and everything going in the windows and doors open. And if you ask them, you know,
why are you doing that? Well, I don't care. It's paid for. Right. This is your average
surface-dwelling human. Now, not in all cases, but average meaning look up what the word average
means, by the way. And so what they do is they the only way they well, predominantly,
the only way to use that word loosely, is that the people have access to these utilities is by
first going through what's called the billing, billing subscribing office. So when you interact
with the water, gas, phone people, you're not really interacting with those that are providing
the service over put the thing together, interacting with a very specific group or an
office that was set up, whereby contract, you now become a subscriber that has to be billed for,
and for it. And if in somewhere loosely, it defines it never really defines that if you don't,
quote, unquote, perform on the bill, they'll cut it off, you know, or short you have that.
So but it's kind of like commonly known that, you know, parents, they prank the children who
you've got to get a job so you can pay the bills. Well, you know, well, you know,
this is your parents, folks. But anyway, what's interesting about this is that it's all paid for,
but you can't tell the people that. So yeah, these, it's very slight of hand ish. You know,
if you look at some of the legal aspects of paperwork regarding this, they'll tell you that
you have subscribed as a billing billable subscriber. That's why you're in the situation
you are. So the key folks is to how do you gain access to these public utilities that are paid
for, by the way, how are they paid? Well, it's credit. How do you gain access to it without
going through the subscription office, and they make it very, very, very difficult.
That's why if you've ever looked at a utility bill, wherever you are, it's never within the
jurisdiction that the services are rendered to. So if you are any particular city or town,
you'll always notice, if not, I'm going to say always, 99% of the time,
you're supposed to send the payment of that bill, quote unquote, to some place that is not near you.
It's always somewhere far away. There's a reason for that too. So yeah, but no one's paying
attention. And I think I've described in the last show, we wanted to maybe talk about how the money
system works, but people will never understand it. And this is prophetic, by the way. In the future,
it is written that the reason why the money system will not be sustained is not because the people
will comprehend it or understand anything about it. It's because they somehow and wholesale decide
not to use it anymore. Right? These merchants will go away because the people decide not to
use it. It never states that they will understand it. And when I say never, never is not really far
away from here, by the way, never meaning the way things are, as you consider today. But it
doesn't mean that we can't just bring up certain descriptions of the credit system. So because
that ties in a lot with technology. Typically, you ever notice how the newer technology always
costs a little bit more, you know, because it's a little better, supposedly. So whenever you bring
up anything like that, how the transactions are being mitigated or done these days is through a
credit-based economy. And people are still saying that it's debt-based. Well, because some, maybe
they were told that it's debt-based. So they just say that it's debt-based. But do they spend five
seconds looking at its credit? No, they don't. Why should they? But hopefully the four listeners
that we've got maybe will. And I think they're beginning to realize it. So that, you know,
many things, again, I think somewhere it was written that money could pretty much solve all
things, right? Or many problems can be solved with money, paraphrasing. We'll be more in the
intralinear version. But I would say that maybe could it be because there's no money and many
problems aren't being addressed. They were preemptively done through the credit-based
economy. And by the way, as we before, you know, we're almost done with the first hour here,
but I'd like to just say that you couldn't, let's just say underscoring with the financial
community is reliance on technology. They go hand in hand. And you have people that are so
oblivious to anything real that they're still discussing wiring money. Have you ever heard of
someone saying that the money's being wired? Yeah. It's like, yeah, we're going to call the
restaurant, Seth, you know, I'm kind of hungry right now. Maybe you are too. And I'm going to
have you a sandwich or maybe some hummus wired over to you. Does that sound about right?
Wonderful. That would be wonderful. Thank you.
That sounds about right, doesn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. Wait until people, well, no, they're not going to find out how it works, but
yeah. And by the way, they talk about still, let's just throw this in there. I'm not
in defending the Federal Reserve or apologizing for them, which by the way, defend and apologize
means the same thing. It's redundant. Yes. Yes. They're just brokers. The people are being screwed
by their own local bank branch, right? That was bass backwards, but yeah. It's where you, the
little shop that they call a bank, it's not the Federal Reserve. They're the ones that are doing
the funky stuff, right? And they're acting independently. They're all little trusts that
have certain regulations. And if you maybe unregulated to a certain degree. Yeah. And by
the way, there is no Federal Reserve Bank that was shut down in 1933. What's being operated as
the Federal Reserve system, right? Yeah. It's a system. The system of the signature is where
the credit is garnered from. So for example, if you go down and see common folk on the street,
they throw litter on the floor. But if you, let's say, tell the common folk, I want to take a pen
and sign the name that you use on the litter before you throw it on the floor. Does it change it?
And they're all going to say, no, it's still litter. It's just garbage, man. So what? I
signed the name on it, right? But here comes a limousine with a bankster in there. And if he
sees someone sign the name on a bubblegum wrapper, they tell the chauffeur to slam on the brakes and
grab the bubblegum wrapper, put it in the pocket because that is worth a lot of credit.
You see, that's why people will never understand how the money system works. That's why you got
to tell them little stories like the parents do. It's debt-based, man. Or it's going to crash every
month. Yeah, every month. Just keep telling them it's going to crash. The dollar is going to crash.
Yeah. Yeah. But fortunately, it never is not too far away. So, yeah.
That happened like a hundred years ago, wasn't it?
Well, yeah, about 33 for sure. 33 to 39 for sure. There is no dollar. The interesting thing here is,
you know, we talked about instant communication. It seems to fall apart when anything
validatable comes up because that was over 80-some odd years ago,
and yet people still haven't noticed. So, we could accurately and very precisely say there
is an 80-year time delay when it comes to comprehending how the credit system works
with people. So much for instant communication. All right. We'll be right back.
Yes. And with more instant communication in a few minutes, folks.
Welcome back to Uncommon Sense here at American Freedom Radio on Americanfreedomradio.com.
You can find contact information for the program here, the broadcast, at uncommonradio.com.
If you'd like to email us, the Greek and I, or get into contact with us or find easy links to
past broadcasts and things of that nature, that's the place to start. So, uncommonradio.com.
Yeah. And the current chat and Ustream are easily found on that uncommonradio.com,
www.uncommonradio.com. It's easier to put in the .com and the www because that's a very common term.
And if you do a general search on the browser, you'll get many other things. We
kind of have that set up just as a calling card, because years ago, people asked you,
you did something. I said, you got a card? And you're like, oh, no, I don't, man. Well,
yeah, you just go to a printer and get some cards. Now, today, if someone asks you,
where can I find out more about this? Say, well, do you have a website? And you're like,
well, no, I don't, man. Well, you also, yeah, we don't say that. We say, yes, we do.
The only reason the website is up is we're not asking for subscriptions. So we get beer money,
and we're not asking for this or whatever. And there's nothing secret. There's no secret area
in there. It's just a common courtesy. If someone asks, what's the site? There it is.
But speaking of getting beer money, we are being broadcast through American Freedom Radio,
and they are relying on donations and things like that. So you know what to do, folks.
There are, I want to thank a few folks out there that do it. Because of Uncommon Sense,
the Greek and Seth Michael, there are a couple, I think, that consistently donate because of this
venue here. You know, they know for sure they can tune into Uncommon Sense and American Freedom
Radio and have a dummy load, two hour free dummy load per week sonic experience. And of course,
for the rest of the week, you can be dummy loaded, you know, but you know, for at least they know
for two hours a week, there will be no dummy loading. And yeah, it's pretty and they do
appreciate it. And we appreciate you for helping out the crew at American Freedom Radio. Yeah.
Absolutely. If you would, we've had a couple of people express interest in,
I guess, donating, giving us a little bit of something just as a thank you for broadcasting,
things like that. If that's something you're interested in doing, just email us.
Yes. I can. It can be done with relative ease. But yeah, so just email us. You can
uncommonradio.com www.uncommonradio.com. Like I said, I do this because I enjoy the conversation
and it's a conversation. Whereas even if we were talking about some of the same subject matter
that is being discussed elsewhere, it's certainly done in a different manner and with different
content. You don't hear the things being discussed the way that they're discussed here anywhere else.
That's part of the reason why we do it publicly. The Greek and I have had conversations, many,
many conversations broadcast and the relative privacy of not being broadcast over the land.
I enjoy the conversation, the ability to learn, to contemplate and to talk about things in a way
that is just not available elsewhere. And seemingly you don't need, I mean,
as long as it exists, you don't have to have many saying these things. You just need them said.
There's an old saying, perhaps that, I think it was one of the, I think it might have been Socrates.
He said that a fool has to say something, but the wise have something to say. So if you tune in,
by the way, anywhere at any time, you'll see there's a lot of people that have to say something.
Have you heard that before? We have to do something, man. We got all these problems. We
got to do something. It's like, uh, yeah. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yeah. How's that working out for you?
And there's a lot of interest in the problem, right? But there's very little interest in the
solution because once the solution is given, you can't philosophize the problem anymore.
Oh, I'd say it's, there's a lot of interest in the symptoms of the problem.
Yes.
Talking about the problem, whatever that may be. There's many, many symptoms that are discussed,
sort of like treating the symptoms in the, what they call the medical community, things like that.
If it's not, you know, for immediate trauma care, I recommend avoiding them.
Yes. And the trauma care is information and technology or skill that has been gathered
for thousands of years from the battlefield. By the way, folks, you can do that on your own.
And yeah, yeah. The avoid, and the most of these entitled classes, we kind of harp on them,
deservingly so. All of your entitled classes pretty much are there to be self-serving and
to pretty much keep the greed and gluttony and vanity of society at bay or in check.
Absolutely.
Yeah. If you look at the scientific, religious, medical, legal society or education societies,
they're just pranking you. And, you know, I'm kind of being known as the guy always just talking
about the pranksters, you know. But yeah, it's a prank. There's a lot of people out there looking
for quote unquote medical solutions from the medical society. You're not going to get that
because they're not there to do anything but prank you. You're not going to get solutions
with the legal society because they're just pranking. You know, same with the scientists.
I came on to the AFR chat before the show started and I want to say hello to Dylan
out there if you're listening. Hello, Dylan. As he said hello and he said Dylan posted
before we came on. Ninety eight percent of all science scientists or science is false
and 95 percent don't even know it. And there's some wisdom, folks. Thank you, Dylan.
Yes, that is pretty accurate, pretty correct. The numbers may be floating around a little bit,
but yes, pretty much the majority of it is bull. Yeah. And by the way, if anyone wants to
investigate that on their own, that infinite bastion of information, the Internet, there's
quite a few articles or commentaries, I'd say things being written about scientific fraud,
by the way, and not just from critics or people deciding to throw rocks or being stoners, by the
way, behind the scenes, I was once in a conversation with some other radio hosts and I said, I'm just
doing the radio show to throw stones, throw rocks. And someone said, you're a stoner. And I'm like,
no, I'm not. I'm like, oh, yeah, that was a real good one that got me.
And speaking of stoners, by the way, I just kind of like here's a pop curry.
There's a lot of talk about the legalization of cannabis, right? I bring up the stoners.
How many of them actually research what they're talking about from an objective point of view?
Well, if you said none, you're correct. Actually, there are a couple. Yeah. Up in the northwest,
but a couple meaning like the four or five listeners, right? A few, very few. But most
people are hinging on the legal society. And if you actually go and study the legislation
regarding illegalization of certain things or prohibition of certain things, you'll find that
it's in almost all cases, it doesn't apply to those that are outside of the administration and
or it's been repealed. So all this crying about legalization of cannabis is just
a typical human tripe against that. I think it's the perceived the perceived
persecution or prosecution of the pranking of such things. Yeah. There are a Greek guy. Yeah.
A Greek guy had all this. That's their job is to prank people because of that stuff.
Yes, exactly. Yeah. I had all this pot, man. And the cops came in and beat me up and took it.
What do you do about that? You know, it's like, well, they're they're not operating under
any law. Anyone. There's this is interesting. I'm not going to give too many specifics. I don't want
to sound pedantic, but there is several companies, local companies. And you could find on the
Internet, you know, like a local pizza shop, for example, or whatever. And sometimes on the website
they say, well, hiring. Right. And then you go down there and say, you know, application, click on it.
And they give you a little caveat. They say, well, the hiring is done according to this code,
right? U.S. code, whatever, whatever, you know, Right to Work Act, whatever, whatever.
And then you click on it and start reading that code. Oh, no, no. He's telling us to study. Yeah.
Just five minutes, folks. If you start reading the code, it actually tells you that in order to work,
you need this type of paperwork or whatever the attorney general finds to be acceptable.
That's a really big or who the hell is this attorney general guy making the decision?
And if you don't have the quote unquote paperwork that they list, which by the way, by the way,
if you research that paperwork, it cannot be used in the way they're telling you it should be,
by the way, by their own definition. But who is this attorney general guy? Go, go say,
well, I don't have that paperwork. I'm going to go talk to the attorney general.
Do they ever want to talk to you about it? No, no, they don't. This is all pranking, you know,
all of it, not some of it. And I just gave I'm not going to be pedantic and give the
codes and all this. Right. But go, go research the right to work acts and things like that and
start reading it just a little bit. I know you don't want to. You know, most people hate that.
They don't want to look at what things mean and they don't want to look where things come from.
Right. Because whatever reason I don't want to get into why it's because we just talked about
the pathos of it. But, yeah, you'll be you'll be scratching the head and you're wondering,
what the hell is going on? Well, we're discussing here on Uncommon Sense what is going on
objectively, which most people don't want to hear. If you've been subject to pranking,
that's all you know. That's all you're going to resonate with. For example,
if you make a tuning fork from scratch to resonate at a certain frequency,
when all the making is done, that's the frequency it's going to resonate at. So, you see, and how
would one do that? I'm never mind. I'm sorry. I almost digressed. Well, you know, you could take
a block of aluminum, a block of sheet, some aluminum stock or metal stock and start cutting
it away. And, you know, you know, the tuning fork, right. It's a typical kind of image when
you say that it's length and how would you find that that that a four thirty two or or, you know,
four forty five. How would you use something? Yeah, you'd use something else. There's another
way to have a reference, right? Yes, exactly. Measuring reference. And in this case, it would
be Hertzian, right? You know, the sinusoidal form, things that kind of convey that in an analog
manner that you can interact with. Right. Because some people can just hear it and they can't
objectify it. Right. But if you have, you know, I could hear it like if I had a tuning fork and
then went to make another one, you know, or something. But I would have to have that note
to begin with in order to like even if it wasn't a visual thing, like I would have to hear the sound
and compare the sounds as it was being done. And I don't know how accurate, probably within a cent
or two of accuracy. But from scratch, I couldn't I couldn't make a tuning fork from scratch.
Yeah. Well, unless you made the first one and then you would spend a lot of time referencing
what it did and then anything else would be measured against it. Right. Yeah. Now,
that'd be an interesting project to set upon making a tuning fork from nothing.
So, yeah, I digress. I'm sorry. Or some stock, metal stock, let's say metal is pretty good
for a quality. You can make it out of any material, but it won't react the way that we
commonly discuss a tuning fork. But the interesting thing is right now, people are acting as if
everything is just new and nothing. There's nothing old, old is discarded. So they really
don't know. Just like the tuning fork. Right. But here's the thing. If you've been made
socially, culturally, mentally, spiritually, in your family, in your society, whatever,
to be subject to pranking and the pranking is good or the pranking is the way that it is.
Right. And you're motivated by penalty. That is what you resonate with.
And that's very simple. And this is the common trait that you find.
One thing that we like to discuss is that pretty much people are now motivated through penalty.
You know, if you ask people why they do certain things other than like touching themselves and
things that feel good, right, eating when they're hungry is because if I don't do it,
you know, X, Y, Z will happen. It's usually X, Y, Z is something bad.
And they're motivated by penalty. And they've been pranked.
And if you ask them, they've been tuned. That's what they they are tuned to resonate with. That's
sounds proper to them because that's they have been like an instrument, a string, a note,
anything. They've been they've been tuned. Very. That's an enlightening way of looking at it,
I suppose. Good. That's a good analogy. Yes. Yes. They've been tuned to resonate
with the lie and the prank. So, you know, so I don't know where these guys in alternative media
or mainstream or these people that want to make things better are using as their launchpad or
their reference, because until you start looking at the nature or object of the way things are from
an objective point of view, removing yourself from it and admitting that you're in a sick state in
the society, meaning any society, doesn't matter if you're in Russia or Iraq, South America,
let's say Venezuela, U.S., Canada, doesn't matter, China, Korea, you're all sick. Pretty general.
Yes. Speaking of which, by the way, we got I got a lot of crap on a quote unquote Skype group.
One guy came on and he said, where do you get off, man? You talk like you sound like you know
everything. Right. And I said, well, wait, hold on a second. Hold on a second. You know,
how do you know that? Did you hear the show? And he's like, oh, yeah, yeah, I did. I did. I did hear
the show. I said, well, then if you heard the show, then how could I be the only one that knows
everything? Now you do, too. Right. So it's not good to play with humans. I mean, they're just
silly creatures, but you see the point there. So, you know, yeah, this is funny. Well, if you heard
it, you know, you know it, too. Now you're it, too. You're it. Yeah. You got the cooties now,
too, man. Yeah. Anyway, people are just. Yeah. So just don't don't make fun of them. Yeah,
it's just it's kind of hard. It's not. Well, the thing is, you've got to have fun
because they get so ramped up and, you know, they like to they have this.
Well, it's what they're tuned into. You know, you've got a strong adds new new meaning to the
concept of being high strung as well to give an analogy within an analogy. OK, you have someone
who is tense all of the time, right? There's an. Yeah. Yeah. These are all armored tuning.
It can be, you know, it can be felt, it can be heard, it can be seen. I don't know about tasted,
but yeah, they're tuned into it and they cannot return without great difficulty or inconvenience
to the mind. They by the way, folks, if you're this is more addressing the four or five listeners,
but you ever notice that when you speak to your average surface dwelling earth inhabitant,
those that are enlightened or awake, if you start wanting to discuss the or bring up the points of
what things are really based on, you know, reference things that are tangible or validatable,
they try to discount it by telling you, oh, that's an opinion or that's your opinion. Right. So that
somehow makes it go away. Right. Or and the other thing that they like to say, by the way, this is
a caveat to the four or five people out there. The other thing they say is, well, I don't agree
with that. Like for some reason, because they don't agree with it, it's not true.
This is the kind of stuff you have to put up with when you're dealing with the average. Yes,
look up what the word average means. Surface dwelling earth inhabitant, the typical psychopath
or whatever. By the way, again, I just want to bring up something that was brought up in
conversation recently, talking about also people making excuses when you bring up how things are
the way they are, because they can be easily referenced and explained. People jump out of
the woodwork and say, well, well, it doesn't you see what people have been so preconditioned.
I'm like, yeah, yeah. So what you're making excuses for them. Are you like the attorney
for the human race now? Whether they were conditioned or whatever is irrelevant. We're
explaining what is going on, you see, and what is going on right now. People are talking about
they've been conditioned and dumbed down. Well, again, here's your time delay, folks.
The dumbing down ended a long time ago. You've been in the numbing down. And I brought that up
and someone in conversation recently said, yeah, got apathy. You know, you remember that got milk
ad, you know, it was a black background with the Gil Sands font got milk. I want to do the maybe
the shirts and the hats and put them on the website. And it'll just be a black cap or black
T-shirt. And it'll be, you know, the Gil Sands, you know, font is a got apathy question mark,
you know, can it can it if they're going to be on the website, can it be have apathy question?
Or have. Yeah, maybe. Yeah. I have apathy. OK. Yeah. So this is where this is where you're at.
You know, you know, it's an opinion, man. Or that's I don't agree with that.
All right. OK. It's the tuning bit. If you if you speak just one one note out of tune.
And if you look at if you know what we are able to exist, you know what we are able to perceive
before we look at that is how it's referenced, you know, as being a verse, right? A verse in a song,
piece of piece of music there. There are chords involved even on on a single instrument. You know,
if you have one one string that's tuned out of scale with everything else,
then it's going to sound incorrect. So the the concept and the idea of good information being
shared with and reacted to poorly by those who have been tuned to bad information,
you know, it's just it's a dissonant. Yeah. Yeah. It's become. Yeah. It hurt. It can it can
cause physical pain. You know, emotional pain is physical pain. You know, it can cause distress.
Old old wine and new wineskins, you know, kind of idea and retuning can be done. It can be done.
But you have to like I was saying, you know, I couldn't build a tuning fork
from nothing. I would need something to reference. So in order to to retune or to
tune to a different scale or a different note or a different chord structure,
you have to have something to resonate with to adjust the tuning. So it's just I don't know,
I kind of ran away with that analogy. But it's it's very I'm you know, I or access to a large
part of my perception of this plane of this world around me. And so having having that it's
something that I understand a little bit differently or comprehend a little bit differently than a lot
of the physical world and being able to translate a lot of what's going on in the physical world
to, you know, something less complex in my own mind, I suppose, to music that's very it's an
apt analogy. And it's it will come in handy in describing things to a lot of the people that I
that I talk to. So I like that. And chords also used in geometry regarding circles and things and
that can be rationalized mathematically or geometrically. Perhaps maybe what we're trying
to do is rationalize a certain type of thought that might bring some relief. Like, for example,
you'll never hear being discussed here to make the world a better place, because it Yeah, anyway,
we're not going to get into that at the moment. But that, by the way, is a big mistake for those
that have skill. If you ever noticed, by the way, anyone who, let's say a discoverer or inventor,
that publicly goes out and says, we have to make the world a better place, they meet a very bad
fate very quickly. And that is because of the divine nature of things as well. So if you are
skilled in as such, and you can make the world a better place, just do it, don't say it publicly,
and don't promote it as such, but you will be flattened out like a bug. If you do, you know,
cosmically meaning of the world and from the divine as well. Here's the thing, folks, and this
is the best thing for the young. Today is a little bit worse than yesterday, but not as bad as it's
going to be tomorrow. Think about it. Okay. It's very gradual, like the frog being boiled in the
pot analogy, right? If you turn up the heat too much, he jumps out. But now let's follow through.
If he jumps out, now you have to put him back in the cold water. All that time that was spent prior
has to be, you know, thrown away and you restart. So if you're like five minutes away from boiling
him, and it took three hours to get there, if he jumps out, you can't just put him back in the hot
water, he'll jump out again, you got to start all over again. So yeah, so today's just slightly worse
because if it was much worse than yesterday, everyone would stop and address it, you know,
and you're not getting anything that's going to be this is an assurance, folks. When you tune
into alternative media or mainstream or university, or all your little funny stuff you guys like to do
generally, you're not getting anything. All that discussion is tripe, folks. I mean, it's just
wasted time dummy loading hamster wheel stuff. You know, that's why when you speak to people that
are in the business, mainstream and alternative, they're like, if you bring up the question about
how come this stuff is so dumb, like, oh, it's just entertainment. Okay, there was actually
a court case regarding this in conversation, I didn't get all the details. But there was someone
being sued or suing Fox News. Because Fox News apparently said this person did such a thing or
was bad or whatever. And they repeated it several times. And the person, I guess, lodged a suit
against this media company. And the judge ruled in the favor of the media company saying that
because they're a media company, it's all entertainment. So you don't have a case against
them. So from that point of view, when you tune into anything that you're tuning into, folks,
and this is a general broad brush. I mean, there's some good things on the internet, like,
you know, I have several conversion websites, like I want to go to Fahrenheit to Celsius, let's say,
you know, where I want to look at water vapor or like seismic reports, or, you know, maybe a
periodic table of elements. Yeah, there's some decent things you can do instant telephony and
internet, you can do emails, you know, but your articles in your media. It's resonating, by the
way. So yeah, so what the reason we get together? Yeah, we might sound a little arrogant, a little
haughty to say this. But when you come to Uncommon Sense, you're going to get two hours. Troy,
you're going to get two hours. And we try to sweep the floor clean of all that other crap
that is available. And hopefully, we're delivering that to the four or five listeners,
and whoever else who might randomly come across and get really upset on hearing what they're
hearing because they don't resonate. And yes, by the way, if you listen to us, and you think
that we know everything, well, guess what? If you heard it, you do too. So it's kind of like the old
radio and heavy artillery have in common. Oh, once you hear it, it's too late. That's right.
So, you know, you're going to come across many things that you like, but it's just remember,
you're being entertained, and you're going to get whipped up into a frenzy whipped up into a
lather. And you're just going to walk away saying, you know, I very often see on various chats all
over the internet, I hear a lot of the stuff that's being discussed. And the people put in
great show after that. And I'm like, really, I'd hate to hear what a crappy show sounds like.
But anyway, so this is I mean, two hours, I think is enough a week. If we could get just a few
people to hear it, even though it might be too late for most if they do. Yeah, folks, just look
around you and look at trying to figure out what things are based on. And by the way, speaking of
what things are based on, you've got to know how many times we discussed time, right? There's many
ways to discuss the same thing. It's just series of events. And what we call time is just nothing
more than the recordation of those events, past, present and future. The present is very hard,
by the way, to discern. Because you can, you know, the moment is very difficult to grasp.
That's why a lot of this sets, correct me on this. Is it solipsism?
Solipsism, I don't have the etymology pulled up. But the concept is viewing oneself as the
universe, essentially, like you are viewing the entire ever all of existence, only through how
it affects you directly, I think. It's like the concept of is this all a dream? Versus is this
all my dream? Like my dream would be solipsism. That's where the people that come in that say,
well, it doesn't really matter. It doesn't really exist. That's your opinion. Or I don't agree with
that. This is not the type of place that you will get that kind of stuff. We speak about things that
will direct the mind hopefully to do a little bit of study and study as a noun and a verb. By the
way, I was looking at that because I tend to look at that. And by the way, people hate studying,
meaning looking at what things should be, or what they're based on or validating things.
And they hate knowledge and they hate the truth. And why do I say that is because I take really
good notes when I go into conversations with people. And I find in person that they either
gloss over or have the you know, beyond the the initially when you start discussing what things
are based on, they have the deer in the headlights expression look. But if you continue, then they
have the expression of a baby seal right before it gets clubbed look. You know, like now I'm lost.
And what are you doing? And why are you doing it? But I don't know what you're doing kind of look.
So there is a point in history, by the way, because by the way, how many times have we
mentioned that there is another intangible society, intangible meaning, physically many
levels known as the gods, right? And they have a hierarchy. And that aspect and by the way,
folks, when we talk about the gods, and we're using that term colloquially, what so we can
communicate, we're not discussing any of the ridiculous religions on the planet at the moment.
And ridiculous meaning that accurately, because fortunately, the gods of ridicule,
yes, worthy of ridicule, absolutely. But they're just accommodating the people, right? Just like
when you see a big service station or a gas station in the middle of the desert. It's because there's
a million cars passing by. They're accommodating them. If those that highway is closed, that
station has to go because you know, coyotes and scorpions don't aren't going to serve it and go to
that business very much. But anyway, when we discuss this, we're not discussing it in any of
the context that most people are familiar with. We're not talking about Santa Claus and all the
other ridiculous stuff that people worship. Yes, you do worship it, even though you're kind of
schizophrenic and psychopathic to say, we all know it doesn't exist, but we do it anyway. Well,
that is the mark of a true sick person. Brief aside, what is worship? That's a that's a word
that is commonly used, and I would say rarely understood or comprehended. Let's look it up.
Let's bring it up. Isn't it mean to give something to or perhaps so let's let's look, look at it,
would bring it up. Admittedly nation, I'm gonna have to bring it up. Yes, let's see.
I have, you know, held a conceptual idea of what it is, but the history of the word itself comes.
The verb comes from the noun Old English water keep condition of being worthy, dignity, glory,
distinction, honor, renown from we are worthy. Skip a reverse supernatural reverence paid to a
supernatural divine being. It's first recorded in the 13th century. That's interesting.
Some years ago, check this out. In most cases, the divine beings that people are quote unquote
worshiping, if you push them into a corner, they will tell you it doesn't exist anyway.
You ever noticed that? In most cases, not all cases. Like I know in the Western society,
during the darkest time of the year, they worship the Santa Claus.
Cats. Well, Greg, that sounds ridiculous. We don't worship. Oh, really? But I'm not looking
at what you're saying. I'm looking at what you're doing. Right. Actions speak loud. Yes. Yes. Which
is really Moloch, the revival of the human sacrifice. You know, that's why you put the
child on the red, red hot creature, you know, make a wish of prosperity. Ask him what he wants.
Yeah, pretty sick bunch of people. Psychopaths. Can anyone say that? Psycho meaning it's all done.
It's all done in parody now, like it's not, you know, the I'm yeah, it's all done. It's all done
in parody. And it's the parody is not acknowledging of the history. It has to. It's something that has
to be kind of dug into to actually find where these customs and these traditions come from
and what they're actually saying. I don't necessarily recommend the idea of doing it.
It's been. You won't. It's not one of those things that will make any friends. No, no,
you won't make friends. Yes, that's why. That's why I recommend getting a furry little friend.
Social upheaval at home and in public. Yes. Yes. That's the other thing at home. See,
the thing is, when people come together, I think we've discussed what love is to a certain degree.
And folks, you don't know how to love. You don't even know what it means. You don't know what it
is. You have to learn how to love, by the way. And yes, a lot of people do take offense to that.
And by the way, could it be that if someone is offended, they're not seeking the truth?
The truth of the matter is, you're a subject to external input. And what you think love and hate
is, is what you've been told. You should think it is. English is a horrible language for discussing
such things as well. Oh, yes. The limitations. And unfortunately, it's the only one I speak
with fluently enough to think in. So it's yes. So the thing is, you know, I speak to younger
people, they mean relationship. And I'm like, what, what do I do? What's this about? What about
that? I was like, learn to love each other. You have to learn to love. Because if you look at the
would you say malevolent entities, see things that are malevolent and fraudulent and untrue,
and harmful, potentially always present themselves as being the real deal or not. So
I like very rarely can someone take a crayon and a dinner napkin, and write 100 on it and say it's
a banknote and go to spend it. They have to go through great lengths to mimic what you see.
So what's going on is regarding love, by the way, and we won't make friends.
Yeah, you can have to learn how to love. I've kind of discussed that a little bit in parents.
You've got to have to learn how to love children. And this is what I tell, by the way, the biggest
mistake an inventor, let's say, quote, unquote, inventor, and a parent can make is to fall in
love with their invention or their children. I've seen inventors fall in love with the invention,
and then they can no longer objectify it. And I've seen parents fall in love with children,
and they can no longer objectify what's going on. You know, and as a matter of fact, they can fall
in love with children to the point where they favor one over the other. You might have heard of that.
They referred, I think that the reason they call it falling is because it is disorienting.
Yes.
For anyone who has ever experienced it, it feels like you were,
like the ground has been removed from under you.
Yes, yes, exactly.
It's very strange.
Yes, and yeah. And when you understand the displacement of things, how things change,
we're discussing things about how change is required. It kind of keeps life going.
You know, don't be rigid. But by the way, we just wanted to mention, when we discuss these things
and what they're based on, and the parodies going back to the worship of this Moloch creature,
Moloch, M-O-L-E-C-H, I believe, you're not going to make friends, familial or ordinary people.
So look for things where you might get an unconditional attention, what you consider love,
feeling good, which is a little furry friend, maybe a cat or a dog.
They tend to have short attention spans. They tend to develop vocabularies. Most,
for example, dogs or cats can develop 50 to 100 word vocabulary and recognition, right?
Come, sit, food, eat, no, yes, bark, don't bark, right? These types of things.
So if you're going to pursue some of the things that are discussed on Uncommon Sense,
I recommend getting a short attention span furry creature in your presence.
Absolutely. That's solid advice right there.
That's right. We do give advice as well. So yes.
I would say that you'll find some people will be tolerant, but it's discordant to a lot of
people, places.
Yeah. And you don't want to press the issue, by the way, any topic matter. Yes.
And any topic matter, any subject you can look into and find out what it was based on the history
of the thing and how do you validate it. If you run into your average surface-dwelling earth
inhabitant and start discussing it, they might get a little disoriented or discordant, right?
But if you keep pushing the issue, you can actually, if you can read one's body language
and facial expressions, you're going to have to stop or get away from them because there are
precursors that you could recognize where they actually want to bring physical harm to you for
continuing on such a discussion, by the way. And I have seen this in person, that if you,
many people want to engage in debates or discussions regarding certain things.
And if you stick to what thing, the history of the thing or what it's based on and how it can
be validated, if you pursue it, they do want to bring physical harm to you, right? And this is,
you know, could be familial or friend or just ordinary occurrences, you know, in public or
whatever. So you have to be very, very careful. You got to understand, we also say the earth is
a very dangerous place. It's a very violent place. And the level of order that people are enjoying
is just that. There is a level of order, so you can have enjoyment, you see, you know, and some
peace. But I want to go back to this kind of brought up all the gods, the gods don't act in
futility. And what you will be getting, and this is a little bit of the current events, right,
we brought up some kind of European Union thing going on, maybe with England and such.
You're going to get a perfect society in the next decade or sort of around that time.
Because later on, this way, you'll be without excuse, the last thing the gods want to hear
is a whining human. We never had a chance to have a perfect society or world peace and
knowledge, freedom, prosperity. So you'll get that for a short time.
Yep. And you're gonna have to watch the seasonal aspects of it as well.
Things are planted in the spring, they grow in the summer, and they are torn down in the fall.
So, you know, right now for the certain part of the world, geographically, it's summertime.
So when you look at the quote-unquote current events, you will find that
it's a growing time. The events that are put in front of you are things that are being,
agendas that are growing, expanded on. And soon after this season will be the fall,
will be a tearing down time period. And by the way, folks, regarding things that
are discussed, the real stuff is always done in quiet. Where the noise is, typically,
is a distraction. So the stuff that's being brought to you and discussed both
mainstream and alternative, that's just echoing the noise, the distraction.
So when you start to look at how things are, what things are based on and referencing things,
you will see that the truth is still very, very, very quiet.
Like an example would be kind of like harping on the financial commentary.
Whenever you hear someone discussing what's called financial or economic or money,
keep in mind that it is a credit-based economy. So look up what credit-based economy means,
and then contrast that to the entertainment that you're being, that's being thrust upon the ears
or visual. And you're going to have to laugh, and you're going to have to realize that you
are being entertained because it's bogus crap, all your financial commentary.
Now, when you listen to the quote-unquote medical community regarding health
on your whatever media you might so choose, you ever notice it's all chemical-based, typically.
I shouldn't all, but yeah. And how many times they discuss that you should
pretty much eat seasonally or the food hasn't, the quality of the food has an effect
on the body based on the environment, seasonally very, almost none, almost never.
How many times are you told in discussions of health and from the medical society,
mainstream alternative, that the body absorbs things, this ridiculous thing
could be said about the body, like you're a filter bag walking around and
hopefully you're not leaking everywhere, like things are leaking into the body,
ridiculous stuff. So yes, it is entertainment. You're being entertained. And I hope you're
being entertained. But I call it just being dummy loaded. A lot of people go and I see
what they call the pagan weekend or the Pope's work schedule. There's lines around movie theaters.
It's like, what are you doing? You're just sitting in a chair, paying about 20 bucks these days,
15 bucks, 10 bucks to sit there and be dummy loaded for two hours visually. Yes, it's dark.
And there's pretty pictures on the screen. I found out this is what people like. They like
being entertained. They like tuning in. Yeah. You ever hear that? Tune in, right? To what?
If you have a group, you've heard the reference to someone changing their tune, right?
Yes, yes, exactly.
Changing the narrative. There is a question here, speaking of entertainment for nothing else,
in referencing something that we spoke of last week. And that is,
I have a question for the host. They have the time. In the last week's show, you talked about
the realm of the gods. My question is, do shamans go to the realm of the gods or are they simply
hallucinating due to the fact they use psychoactive plants or different methods to put them into a
trance? Thank you. So there's a question. What of shamans, Greek?
Interesting. That's a real big one. Let's look at the quality of it. Use and contrast the
economic commentators. They go on there talking about financial collapse or this or that or the
other. Do they ever bring up it's a credit-based economy? Never. Almost never. On the other hand,
when you look at these shamans, do they actually introduce what they're doing from a more than
relativistic point of view, but from a referential point of view that they are dealing with,
let's say, non-cosmic forces or divine forces and there's a hierarchy. Do they ever talk about
the hierarchy? Do they ever talk about the quality of what they're doing? Very rarely.
You ever notice that? Yeah, most of what's described that I have come into, that I've
heard or read the description of, tends toward the idea of the lower imps and whatnot, just kind
of messing with people. I've heard the stories of people that have had life-changing experiences and
stuff like that at the direction of such people, but I have no experience with it other than the
secondhand. And like I said, I can only comment on what is reported as it's not something that I have.
Well, I've met people who have been in what's called an automobile accident and had the head
go through a windshield and told me that was a life-changing experience as well. Certainly.
Typically, let's go back to a lot of the discussion. If people are resonating with
the prank and the lie, if the shaman comes up with something that's true or beneficial,
will it resonate? The answer is no. It will be dissonant. So they're going to have to, again,
accommodate. Now, I'm not saying that all the shamans are like that, but yeah, as a general
rule of thumb, the ones that I've encountered that are self-proclaimed shaman or whatever,
yeah, they are dealing with things that they don't even know about. Just like your economic
commentators or the people in the legal society or people in the medical side,
they don't know what they're doing. There's many gods, right? Many, many gods.
Yes. The thing is here, it's the quality of the issue. There's very little discussion regarding
quality these days. When I say these days, I mean, why should there be? Because we have all this
technology, right? We're so technologically advanced. No, I hold that in very low regard
because they don't really give you anything that is, would you say, fundamental? Perhaps
if you run into these quote-unquote shamans, it's taken for granted that it's something good,
let's say. How many times have you ever heard that in conversation? I'm a shaman,
or I went to a shaman, oh, that's good. Really? What? So, no, personally, I hold that very low
regard. I don't even regard it as much. But on the other hand, yeah, do they know what they're
doing? Probably not. In most cases, no. Are they accommodating the audience? Absolutely.
Do they have, most of these people, quote-unquote shamans and gurus, do they have a need for food,
clothing, and shelter? And do they wonder how they're going to get the means to provide food,
clothing, and shelter? Yes. Do they charge you what they call money for it, usually? Yes.
Yeah, some of them do it for free or whatever, but so what? You've got to look at the whole
picture here. By the way, if anyone is interacting with a shaman, these people are
so spiritual, oh, man. Ask them to define soul and spirit. Watch their eyes roll in their head
like a Vegas slot machine, right? Typically. Yeah, don't, off the record, everybody cover
their ears. Don't poke fun at stupid people. Yeah, leave them alone. But yeah, I would say
it's a very, very difficult aspect to engage in. But what they're doing is they're engaging in the
realm of fiction. Here, I'll leave you, maybe we have a few minutes left or maybe three-quarters
of the way through. There is a fictional realm that is there for entertainment. There's a
fictional realm that's there for pranking. There's a fictional realm that's there for,
that could create general inquiry. There's a fictional realm, again, for entertainment, right?
What's going on very much right now with the discussion and the conversation is using words,
using time, and just concepts, concepts and ideas and things, but nothing much gets done
because you can see, don't listen to what's being said, look at what's being done. And you can see
there's a lot of stability in it. But I wanted to bring up, there's a campfire scene, right?
And there's a, they're out in the desert, people, some people are called cowboys and the other ones
are called Indians, and they're fighting each other. And it's nighttime, and they're sitting
around the campfire. And finally, they said, let's take a break from fighting. And the cowboy tells
the Indian, he says, Well, you know, I'm getting tired of fighting you guys, I'm going to get a
battleship and come out here and blow all you guys up with the battleship. They're sitting out there
in the desert, right? Campfire. Anyway, then the Indian says, Oh, really? You're going to do that
with a battleship? Well, I'm going to get a submarine and sink the battleship. Cowboy looks at
him, he says, Well, where the hell are you going to get a submarine out here in the desert? And he
says, Well, the same place you got your battleship. Right? So this is basically the nature of most
conversation that is going on right now. What will happen is a topic is brought up. And it's
unfounded, typically, and it's based on nothing, of course. And the discussion begins. And usually
the host or the guest or whoever is starting the discussion is pausing and searching to see what
kind of agreement they can get from their audience. And then the audience gives a little bit of
feedback and from all the nonsense, and then the discussion continues. And that's what's called a
great show. Anyway. Or a great conversation, or a great movie, or a great whatever. So you're being
baited into this very stable, you're in a very stable condition, by the way, on what's going on,
if you understand what was written about this time from the past, you will see that it's very stable.
Everything is the way it should be. So did we mention, did we ever mention set that there's a
coming Middle East Union? I seem to recall that. Yes. Yes. Right. And what does that mean? By the
By the way, oh, yeah, it's just words, man. It's just it's your opinion. It's your idea. Well, you
know, when you organize a most powerful, let's say power base, culturally, economically, judicially,
religiously, that the world has ever seen in throughout known history, in the near future,
there's a lot of things that are going to be changing. But you know, it's gonna seem very
natural when it comes across, by the way. So and the reason bringing this up is perhaps if you look
at the quote, unquote, date of this show, or whatever, and the current events, supposedly,
what they call England is no longer part of the European Union. So yeah, well, why? Well, if you
look at events, and you comprehend fully, that the entire Western world and Asian world, you know,
meaning East Asian, is going to play second fiddle, or be second in importance to the coming
Middle East Union, things start to make sense. And there's not many surprises. So consider that,
folks. You know, I had gotten maybe one message in three years that someone once said, well, you
know, it's really exciting to know that there's going to be a Middle East Union, I could see it
now. And I'm kind of looking forward to its coming, even though it's going to be end up very
horrifically, for most, I should say, even though while it's being while it ends up horrifically,
most people will see it still as being good. Sounds kind of complicated. But yeah, there are
very few that want to acknowledge these things. And you must know the past and you must know the
future. And you will, if you listen, and do a little bit of research. And there's different
types of pasts and different types of futures, meaning how at what level of veracity do you want
to go into these things? Again, we just stated, not recommended, because you will not make any
friends. People don't want to hear this. They want to be entertained. Absolutely. Yeah. Yeah. So the
thing is, by the way, folks, learn to provide, learn to be happy, provide meaning food, clothing,
shelter, you know, be comfortable. Have a you have a body, you're animated through the body, the
spirit and the is animated through the soul and the body. So you want that to be in fairly good
shape and not putting discomfort on you. You want to be safe, the earth is a very violent place.
You want to be able to recognize that your typical surface dwelling earth inhabitant is not doing
very well. And you want to provide help when possible, but set yourself apart from them
as much as possible as well. Because they are very full potential of great danger.
So and well, coming in that danger comes through pranking, by the way, because if you look at the
reason why people do things, they really is no reason at all. So bring comfort, be set apart,
consider there are things that there's more than meat that meets the eye. Consider that
everything was not created 10 years ago or 100 years ago, there was a little bit more going on
back then. Consider that there's things to learn. Good food, good drink, good company,
good conversation. I recommend all of those things. Yeah, things in moderation. Yeah, good sonic
experiences, good visual experiences. Now we're not going to say that uncommon sense is a good
sonic experience. I mean, it could be good for some and bad for others. Fortunately, not many
people are listening. And unfortunately, not many people are listening either way.
I just recalled a question that one of the emails that we received that uncommon sense
was asking about dreams. And I know we don't have much time left in the broadcast, but
someone was asking specifically what they think that they're being shown things by a couple of
different entities in their dreams and just curious as to what they think they are. They're actually
bidding. We pull it up right this second. Well, that's five weapons in the head that basically
are they aware getting from an external source that's typically messing with you?
Are they? I mean, that's I mean, I'm kind of answering with a question,
if you know what I mean? Yeah. Typically, when you find out what dreams are, you stop dreaming,
folks. Yes, you do. A lot of the in paganism, by the way, which just means ignorant.
They stress dreams a lot because see, they don't the typical pagan mindset does not
considered quality discernment. So discern quality, folks, and I guess that's it.
Uh, for this week. Thank you all for listening. Thank you, Seth. Thank you, AFR. All those in
the chat. Uncommon radio.com. American freedom radio.com. Thanks for being here and listening.
Yes. Thanks again, folks.