It is close to the end of the month.
I was looking at the wind-up toy for reference there and yeah, very close.
About the 30th, I'm reckoning, of the fourth month and of course right there we lost everybody
but four people when we say that but that's all right, it has to be said.
Also, another contact way is www.uncommonradio.com, www.uncommonradio.com, that is just a simple
way to contact the Greek or Seth Michael and a lot of little convenient things you can
click on perhaps and yeah, that's just another way and also you will find a link to the chat
and a link to Ustream without having to go longhand.
So, it's uncommonradio.com and it's a common term.
If you just search uncommon radio, there's quite a bit of it being brought up by the
search engine so that's why I mentioned the www.com part of uncommon radio.
Also, speaking of which, four or five listeners, we got an email regarding four or five listeners
and maybe we'll start off with that a little bit.
Of course, keep it anonymous and I want to thank the people behind the scenes that do
a little bit of administrative work including yourself and listen and watch the contact
information so we do get it and we do like to answer back.
So, just a moment, I thought I had just hit something and it went away.
So, let's just bring it up in a moment again.
But yeah, so this is going to be a long month by the way.
It seems an extra observable long month.
It looks like the moon won't be coming around again for a day or two again.
So, very interesting how that's working out.
Yeah, one of the emails that we received was, I like to mention when we talk about studying
old texts and things like that, one of them that I like to recommend to anyone who is
trying to study such things is Kohaleth which is better known as Ecclesiastes.
The word just means preacher.
Or Ecclesiastes means the assembly or the group.
In English, sorry.
Yeah, Kohaleth being.
They stretched Kohaleth into meaning assembly or assembler.
But go ahead, yeah.
It gets complicated, doesn't it, Seth?
But go ahead.
Yeah, so I'm just going to basically read a little bit of this email.
It's very short and I'll leave any names out to protect the guilty, I suppose.
It's a great show.
I'm really enjoying it.
I did read Ecclesiastes, Seth, and seemed to get a lot out of it.
What I found interesting was that it confirmed a low opinion of the concept of karma with
the statements, I'm paraphrasing, about the wicked living long and prosperous lives and
seeing good men whose lives were cut short and how time and chance happens to the good
and the bad.
Thanks for recommending that in the audiobook version.
What was confusing was the previous book of Proverbs seemed to say the opposite.
Again, paraphrasing, wicked will be punished and their lives will be cut off, etc., and
the good men will prosper.
Am I missing some context for Proverbs?
Do you think you will be putting up reference section with suggested reading?
That would be great.
So that's something we might look into.
I was looking at the word idle and I want to I'm going to stick with the Ecclesiastes
and just kind of read very short.
I kind of I was I don't have a lot of time to sit at the computer and answer emails,
but I did feel I this is this was my response.
It said Vanity, a coleth Ecclesiastes preacher book written by one who is considered wise
about wisdom.
And so the question I asked this this guy that sent the email is what did it say is
good for one to do or bad for one to do?
And yeah, so that's as far as that goes.
You know, it's one of the things in that book that is repeated and and studying such
things, you'll find a number of ideas, concepts repeated.
And it seems like a way of emphasizing a point.
If you're going to go through the trouble of repeating it, you know, perhaps it's
worth the consideration taking note of.
It underpins it underlines actually emphasizes and underscores the thoughts of those that
know the secret.
You know, I say the secret, it's not there's not only one secret, actually, by the way,
Seth, anything and everything in Scripture is still secret, by the way.
But that's another discussion that we've brought up.
So, yeah, it does even a cursory view of the of that section or that book, let's say,
because it is a book, does give one maybe, I don't know if it's a sense of relief,
because in this case, it raised a big fat question mark.
So, well, and it's I think that part of the question is picking one idea or concept
out of the book that's mentioned.
And the, you know, it's saying in Kohalath where it speaks about, you know, the wicked
living long and prosperous lives and seeing good men whose lives are cut off short time
and chance happens to everyone.
It's that in and of itself is underscoring or underlining the, you know, the vanity.
And the repeating nature and the repeating nature of things, because you see that repeated.
Yeah.
Well, here, I want to just throw in something, tie this in, folks.
And if you want to hide something, put it in the public library.
So if you want to keep a secret, just say it on a minor Internet radio station, right?
So let's just do it this way.
All right.
How do we do?
This is one of the secrets.
There is a primary society known as the gods, and there's a hierarchy and the chief god
by the way, very few people know this.
And I don't mean people as in the common way, but the people that the people go to,
you know, the religious leaders.
I mean, not the schmuck down the street that's got a circus or a church or, you know, a synagogue
or a temple or whatever, or a mosque.
Not those guys are completely, you know, the street sweeper class talking about the
guys that are running those guys, you know, like way up at the top.
They don't even know because they're so busy with their stuff.
So that's why I keep saying society is pretty much lost at this point.
But this is it, folks.
You ready?
There is a society that controls the society.
And there is, they're known as the gods in English, the Elohim, right?
The El, the emanators.
And within there, they have a ladder, basically.
And it goes all the way to the top.
And you have the chief deity.
And what makes them the chief deity, folks?
You ready?
Ready for this?
Ready?
Not subject to death.
All the other gods are subject to death.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know.
Right.
Okay.
Lost everybody right away.
But we still got to say it.
Now, the interesting part is this particular manifestation of reality is the height of
creation, their creation.
Why?
Because what they have done is they have animated material with spirit, mind.
And they've also animated the mind or the spirit through material.
And when this was proposed to be done a while back, there was a division in that society.
They're like, no, no, no, no, no.
A third of them said, don't do it.
Don't do it.
Because when you do that, it'll be full of corruption.
The material gets corrupted.
Any other group said, well, got to do it, man.
It's the highest form of our art so far.
That's the secret, folks.
Very simple.
So when you read about that, tie that in with Ecclesiastes and Proverbs, how the wicked,
right?
Well, actually, you know, we don't even have the text translated.
So it's kind of hard to discuss.
But you have to know what is delivered to the people can be discussed to some level.
So yeah, wicked, corrupt.
Yeah.
This was already proposed and known prior to all of this coming together.
Kind of like, yeah, you know, remember the Ford Pinto?
They knew the gas tank was going to explode.
But they put it on the market anyway.
I don't know.
It's not an experiment.
Oh, boy.
Here's another secret.
The what you call the Bible or the text, anyone starts explaining it to you, they're full of
crap.
Unless they first start saying that it hasn't not been translated to this date and you have
to go back to the languages of preservation.
So that's one thing.
And the other thing is what you have delivered as your version is not even what's loosely
called the version.
It's really poor.
On the grading system, it would get an F.
And not only is it poor in meaning, but the books are not even in the right order.
But it doesn't matter because you're living in a society that is 100% pagan and or heathen
or whatever you want to call it.
They're into these little charms and talismans like a rabbit's foot.
You know, they carry something.
They think it brings them good luck.
So if they touch the King James Version, they think it's something.
Yeah, they take those into the Temple of Justice even.
Yeah, just touch it and you'll be fine.
Swear on it.
Touch it and say this.
Yeah, I mean, this is ridiculous.
I mean, we're talking about but this is the corrupted spirit in material form at this point.
You know, there's an old saying that miners like to use.
It's fix it or blow it up.
Well, you know, anyway, so that's the interesting part.
So those are some of the secrets in terms of secrets, plural secret of a grab bag.
You know, we like to bring these out.
And by the way, these things are anything anyone can access.
I just want to throw something in.
It's not ignorance.
And don't and I tell people don't make excuses that people have been dumbed down or they've
been conditioned.
I've gotten a couple of messages, you know, you're kind of harsh calling everyone a moron
or an imbecile.
You know, they've been, you know, conditioned and ignorant.
I said, let's let's get away.
That's that's you're making excuses and taking sides.
Where's the objectivity?
You know, if you see a piece of burnt toast and it's, you know, burnt and unedible, you
get, well, you know, they left it in the toaster too long.
Well, no.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well, yes, or whatever.
But the fact of the matter is this is a piece of burnt toast.
That's objective.
Now, how it got burned, why it got burned by who or what is irrelevant at the point.
So at this point, society is irrelevant in terms of their excuses that are made for them.
So that's why the message that is why what makes this uncommon and why we do state that
there are only four or five listeners.
Right.
There's a difference between hearing sounds and listening.
So.
Yeah.
Anything else you want to touch on that with with the books of wisdom, I guess you'd call
it, which which are dubbed only not only not subject to death, but in the in the same in
the same words, death is subject to the most time.
That's right.
And what's interesting is the double negative aspect is in the future, death will be put
to death.
And when death is put to death, that death is dead.
So if death is dead, there's only.
See now, believe it or not, this might sound incredible, but it's actually in the fashion
that I just mentioned being objective.
I was in a conversation yesterday with someone.
We'll keep it anonymous.
And they actually had told me I think they caught themselves.
Maybe they didn't.
I don't get my knowledge from a book.
I get it from first hand experience, from experience.
I don't need a book.
I was like, wow, well, what if it's on a USB?
What if it's a book is just a communication, right?
We can put it on a drive.
We can put it in electronic form.
We can speak it.
Now, here's the interesting part about the mind.
I was going to badger this person, but it wouldn't be good.
I said, look, man, I got this book on how to do magic tricks and how to saw a woman in
half, you know, put her back together on stage.
You know, everyone will believe that.
And right.
And then everyone, you know, I'll lie.
And everyone in the audience watching me saw a woman in half and put her back together.
We'll swear that a woman was sawed in half and put back together.
That's what they saw through their experience.
I got it all from book.
I got you all fooled, right?
Yeah, I mean, this is this is the level of, oh, man.
Yeah, the spirit corrupted in the material sense.
There's a lot of discussion about the mind, right?
But no one ever connects it publicly to what's called the spirit, which is exactly what it
is.
So, all right.
So how about how about we toggle and do this other one?
I'm going to paraphrase because it's kind of long and I'm going to take out the yours
and these and mines and kind of paraphrase.
It says, just wanted to drop a line and say that I love the show.
I heard you.
I heard you mention that you only have five listeners, question mark.
I wish there were more people out there that tackle the topics in the same style that you
use.
I did major in philosophy, so I'm grateful for that from the institution, quote, unquote,
I paid, quote, unquote, money to for a work permit, basically.
Now, this person is getting it here, right?
Or they got it.
But that institution never taught me the things I have discovered during my own research.
Do you have any reading suggestions, subjects of law or religion?
Thanks for giving me some truths and thanks and all that, right?
Now, religion just means something you do regularly.
Now, in subjects of law, that's simple.
That comes from your deity.
That's not something that anyone can really escape.
They can try to rationalize away what law is.
But when you bring up law and religion, those are societies within society, just like there's
a medical society, scientific society, educational society.
You're going to have to be paramount in exercising objectivity because the people that work in
there, all of them, bar a small group, are pranksters.
They don't know anything about the fields that they're purveying to be giving instruction
on.
And that small group that I'm mentioning are people within these societies that realize
what's going on and are looking for an exit strategy, which normally takes anywhere between
two weeks and two years.
In other words, you will not find anyone in the medical community, except for people working
in emergency medicine and nurses emptying out pee pans or poop pans, or anyone in the law
community or anyone in the religious society or education society that has any integrity
and is not operating as a prankster.
Now, they don't know they're doing it, but they're doing it, or they know that they're
doing it and they don't care.
Now, the people that are not part of that group have discovered that it's all a prank
and they had bought into it.
And now they're scratching their head and they're like, uh-oh, I got to get out of
here.
But I got a lot invested and also I'm getting a lot of credits for doing this, so what am
I going to do?
There are quite a few people.
It could be as high as 10% that are in a pickle.
I've met quite a few, well, I should count them on your fingers, quote-unquote doctors,
lawyers, people in the religious fields that actually don't talk about working in that
profession.
I met an assistant district attorney and she said she quit.
She was kind of embarrassed to say she did that.
And I said, well, why did you quit?
She said, I found out what it was about.
Same thing with a doctor.
I went to someone and they were not working and they were working in import-export and
they actually had a degree as a doctor.
And I'm like, what happened?
So I don't really like to talk about it, but I found out what it was about.
I met someone who was a Catholic priest once and he was working in a totally different
field and mentioned that and he says, well, why did you leave?
I found out what it was about.
So yes, this might sound general and specific and maybe condemning to a certain degree,
but it's just a judgment call and not being objective.
You are being pranked.
So to tie this back to, yeah.
Yeah, I was going to say, you know, prostitution is frowned upon generally in society.
And yet the systems that are in place, what they call like the justice system or the
medical system, things like that, these large portions of society are, it's very, I mean,
it's the same model currently as prostitution.
You get what you pay for, essentially.
So with the justice, perhaps you're paying them to, you know, not screw you, to be euphemistic,
whereas prostitution would be a little bit different.
But at the same time, it's all.
Right.
And justice is also the religious system.
It's the revival of the ancient goddess religion.
Sorry, folks, you may not believe that or want to believe it, but that's not.
That's you're going to have problems in your life if you think justice has anything to do with law.
So anyway, but yeah, they're there to screw, you know, but even prostitution gets complicated.
You know, there's a lady, she was working in that field and they take her to she's suing
one of the Johns, one of her clients and for rape.
And they put her on the witness stand and ask her, how did you know you were being raped?
She says the check bounced.
And so anyway.
Yeah, but the problem right now is not really a problem.
If you objectify it, it's just the state of affairs.
People are always talking about all these problems.
If you I posted in the in the chat, I said the persistent dummy load got you down.
Well, there's two hours of relief at the top of the hour by the wind up toy known as the clock.
Right.
Meaning this show.
And yes, you're being dummy loaded.
You are in a hamster wheel, folks.
The thing is, but we're done with our treadmill.
Yeah, all of your media at this point is not worth reckoning.
All of it.
That's some of it.
And all of your systems that have been put in front of you, informational systems are
easy to reckon as just filler.
You're going to go across the board looking for information and it's all a dirty pond.
Now, better than a dirty pond might be a flowing stream.
But even better than that is the spring where it all comes from.
So what that means essentially is be persistent about going to the source and seeing what
it's founded on.
Right.
Regardless of what it is, you know, like, let's you know, the religious community is very
easy to badger and they should be and they will be by society and the gods themselves
in the future.
Extremely so.
But they are pranksters.
Like, for example, if you look up paganism, they define it or they look at, you know,
look up religion.
The true religions are Christianity, Islam and Judaism.
And if you're not that, you're pagan.
Well, that's like saying here, have a seat and there's a thumbtack on it.
You're being pranked because all those are extremely pagan.
So at this point, you're not going to be able to really reference anything.
And if you don't think Islam, Judaism and Christianity is 150 percent pagan, you haven't
done your research.
Pagan meaning just ignorant and whatever.
And then you go ahead to have a discussion with someone in medical school.
And once if they introduce themselves as such, say, oh, you like to heal people and they
kind of look at you all bewildered.
Like, what the hell does that mean?
Right.
Or you run into an attorney and you say, well, you know the laws because not the law, the
laws, because there are many.
And they look at you as well.
You know, I kind of just represent people and right.
You know, they don't know anything.
None of them do now, except for the small group that we qualified and quantified that are
looking for an exit strategy.
But here's the pranking.
You know where it starts.
I had a discussion about it yesterday with the parents.
How so?
Children are all talk to parents and say, hey, or, you know, people around children
and their parents say, you know, the education system is stupid.
You don't learn anything at all for 12 years.
You know, and the parents will say, yeah, I did it because I did it.
The children have to do it.
OK, so now you got pranked by your own parents, folks.
Sorry.
So wherever you look, you're going to be pranked.
It's this is the age of the prankster.
Maybe we're saying that we're not we can't qualify or quantify it.
Maybe for the sake of discussion, Seth, that's a pretty good way to maybe overall get away
from the debates and the discussions.
People look at the minutia of the ridiculousness of the things they discuss, you know, and
meaning that your your media is junk at this point.
If they're not talking about genetically modified octopus or purple tomatoes that are going
to eat you or little space aliens that are going to get you.
They're talking about stupid things like liberty and rights and legalism, right?
Or this religion versus that religion.
You know, that's like arguing you're at Disneyland.
I want to ride the teacups or Thunder Mountain or whatever, you know, what are you talking
about?
It's all fantasy.
But yet it's a fantasy that is very dangerous.
A lot of these pranksters are armed, folks.
They're armed with all kinds of things.
Poisons, projectiles, words, institutions, bad information, bad information.
You're dangerous right there.
Bad information is a dangerous weapon.
And people don't know where to go because they're taking up space.
And we've discussed this very much.
If you look at anything that's been created, it's always in large numbers.
All of creation is in very high accountability to quantity.
And there's qualities there.
Are there qualities?
So when you hear about 100 people or 7 billion people or all the people in society, it doesn't
mean jack shit.
And I'll use that term.
Has nothing to do with anything.
Don't have to make an excuse for anyone.
What you're looking for is what's right and what's wrong.
And that comes from your God.
Your God.
Not God, but your God.
So you choose what level you're going to operate on.
So anyway, this sounds dogmatic to the ignorant.
You know, there's an old saying that says, never talk about politics and religion because
you're going to offend the ignorant.
By the way, anyone who pursues the truth cannot be offended.
Let me think about it.
Maybe that's why when you go to court, they consider it an offense.
And here's the thing that people don't understand.
They're talking about government, right?
The buildings exist, but the offices are vacant.
Legally and lawfully.
And there's small groups of people in government that are waiting for people to do something
about it, not in the sense of revolution, but in the sense of acknowledgement.
And in America, they're doing an election and people are going to vote.
I don't know what you're doing voting at an election.
That's like going over and emptying the waste bin.
What are you doing?
You're vowing.
When you vote, what you're doing is a blanket vow that whoever the electors pick, you'll
stand behind.
And they're voting for a leader of an entity that no longer exists.
I mean, this is so twisted and bizarre.
And also, if you have a fair assessment of society, who the hell would want to lead a
society like this?
That person would have to be suspect and questioned in the first place.
And what I mean by society like this, just walk out your door, stand outside where you
live or walk for five minutes.
You want to lead these people?
Anyway, OK, let's let's get let's get happy.
Go ahead, say something happy.
Something happy.
How about you mentioned in the couple of minutes before we went to broadcast, you had some
news stories or some articles that you you wanted to comment on.
And so if you have any of those brought up, that'd be I'm I'm interested.
Yeah, what's interesting, I brought that up because that came to mind.
I tend to have been doing a fast from what they call the Internet, other than using it
as a glorified telephone book and a telephone, because, you know, back in the days, you know,
I grew up at a time when the phone hang on the wall and if it rang, it was really important.
You know, it's not, you know, so I've been trying to use it for communication purposes,
but just browsing the Internet.
Obviously, there was an event that happened last week regarding a shooting and it's just
twisted and stupid in the way that it's being viewed again because people are that way.
So but nonetheless, looking at several things, one article, this is on Rents.com.
I'll scroll down to it.
The war on stupid people.
Well, good subject, right?
It's by the Atlantic and it says American society increasingly mistakes intelligence
for human worth.
It's a July, August 2016 issue.
What they call that is written by David H. Friedman.
And it's an interesting article because when you go down the article, it's pretty lengthy.
I don't want to read the whole thing, but it kind of starts off something like as recently
as the 1950s, possessing only middling intelligence was not likely to severely limit one's life
trajectory.
IQ wasn't a big factor.
When you're married, where you lived or what other things or what have you, the qualifications
for a good job, blah, blah, blah.
That's all slave talk.
But basically, it talks about how people that are not considered smart or regarded as stupid
have become automatically disagreed with, right?
And it brings up Darwin.
It brings up all these things in media.
But it also brings up as a reference point, who is smart and who is stupid is the reference
point of who is smart or those that are educated by the conventional education system.
So what happens here, there is no discernment, right?
It's basically backing up the pranksters.
It's another prankster article, you see.
So it talks about college boards and university educated people versus those that are not.
So it's implying that unless you have a university education or formal education, 12 years of
nonsense, that you're not smart.
So right here, people are going and reading articles thinking that, oh, yeah, I'm noticing
the trend of that, you know.
But they're not reading it.
They're not noticing that it's another prank, okay?
It's basically supporting the pranksters.
That's why I keep saying these pranksters are accommodating the people because if you
got rid of all the pranksters, which is about a third of the people on the planet, the other
two thirds that are left will immediately subdivide themselves into three groups again
and they will assume the level of prankstership again.
There's no changing it, you know, at this point.
The other thing, there was a couple of other things that shot by, let's say, the conscious
of looking at what's in the media.
Oh, yeah, another one I'll bring up.
There's a group that likes to do international news, several of them, and they have several
articles.
This is just a general.
I will not get into the article.
Like I said, I would maybe tell people how to look at or describe what they're really
saying if you're looking at it objectively.
But there are several international sort of news type groups.
One of them is regarding retired military, which I affectionately like to call the cartoon
network.
But anyway, they're discussing about what the hell's going on in the Middle East.
And believe it or not, I've had some communications with some of these particular news people
and laid it out for them, but they dare not touch it.
And the actual people that are bringing stories, that's what they are, let's say, lack even
the most basic intuitiveness to even indirectly mention the coming Middle East Union.
They won't touch it at all.
They want to blame it on certain groups, the Jews, the Zionists, or all this other stuff,
or religious people are generally peaceful.
No, religious people are generally stupid.
So this is the thing.
Maybe we'll digress from what I mentioned about going through some articles.
But the thing is, what maybe looking at it generally is when you folks are looking at
what's called the news, mainstream or alternative, and a special alternative because we're along
that line, I don't feel like I'm criticizing any colleagues because I'm not a team player
and I don't have any colleagues in the alternative media whatsoever, not even close.
And if anyone thinks there is, they're not listening.
The point here is this, what you're being told is not only misinformation put out by
disinformation is unintuitive, it's just downright unintuitive, which makes it even harder to
explain.
Now, you see disinformant is someone who knows that they're giving poor information just
to direct the crowd mentality.
The misinformed are those that actually latch onto that and believe it and speak it as if
it's they're reporting on giving a good report.
But all of it, whether it's disinformation or misinformation is just downright unintuitive.
What I mean very quickly is listen to what's being said and spend just a few minutes looking
at what's being said.
You hear things about talking about debt and the economy.
First of all, that is unintuitive because everyone knows, I'm saying this in a way,
that when people go to the store, they have in their pocket a plastic card.
Is that a debt card or is it a credit card?
And I didn't say debit, I said debt.
It's credit.
It's a credit-based economy.
So right away, any discussion regarding money, just like any discussion regarding the biblical
text, whatever, if you don't preface what you're going to be discussing because it's
contrary to what people think and discuss normally, you're talking crap.
You are a coprofago or coprofagia, which is not only talking crap, you're eating crap.
So any discussion regarding economic activity or whatever, if it's not brought up that you
are in a credit-based, not debt-based economy, you're listening to junk.
The other thing that's unintuitive, I'm saying this is intuitive because it's very
simple, credit score, credit card, credit base.
The other aspect of it, of alternative media and mainstream, is this thing called liberty
and rights and legalizing.
What the hell?
I'm not even going to go into that, folks.
Just look up what those words mean.
Privilege, you know, all this stuff.
This is just downright unintuitive.
I mean, it just doesn't make sense.
Now, I don't know if it's what they're putting in the water, right, quote unquote.
We are always threatening to do a water show.
And by the way, folks, I hope you're keeping your water dark and cool,
cool meaning 39 degrees Fahrenheit or 4 degrees Celsius, and keep it in the dark.
Yes, we are threatening a water show, which will come one of these days.
So you're going to throw that in.
So how's that water doing?
Just keep it cool.
Yeah, we're not talking about water on Mars or some super hyper water or some ridiculous
tripe that you hear everywhere.
I mean, everywhere.
You have more power than you think or believe you do.
Learn how to keep your water cool.
Learn how to keep the water dark and out of absence of light.
But again, just to go back to this mini rant, Seth, and everyone else, the four listeners,
five people listening, let's say, is that not only is the information just poor all across
the board, it's unintuitive, unintuitive.
And I'm not going to touch on the aspect of rights and liberty and legalization,
but go look up what those things really mean.
You know, but here's the thing.
You're dealing with a spirit in humanity right now that will discount information.
They hate knowledge and they hate good information.
As a group, humanity functions in that modality.
They actually hate the truth.
Go figure.
You know, if they don't like what you're saying,
the first thing the moron says is that is an opinion.
You ever notice how they do that?
So it's very...
Science has become its own faith.
Yes, the law society...
Science no longer means knowledge.
It means what is academically, what is the working academic theory currently.
That's science right now.
Let's do a...
Well, off the top of your head, the definition of academic means impractical,
theoretical, never leading to a conclusion.
And here's the thing, again, about the media.
You ever notice when they have a host or a guest or whatever and they introduce them
based on their academic credentials?
Folks, that's when you hit the red button or the X and you close the thing and you go away.
Because everything that's going to come out of this person's mouth or head is ridiculous
or it's academic or impractical, theoretical, never leading to a conclusion.
Now, I'm not saying everything because they might use the word the or is or was.
But this is the state of your media, folks.
And I say your media because you're claiming it.
Now, there's a lot of good media.
For example, there's streaming music and there's audio books.
But right now, the people that are talking and supposedly bringing you stuff,
and if it's not in the realm of entertainment in your mind or in the mind that you use,
got nothing else to tell you, folks.
But anyway, you're not getting it.
That's the point.
But they are getting it.
If you look at the lack of support in alternative media, the starving artist syndrome,
I think that kind of shows how ridiculous the whole thing is.
But anyway, we get off that topic for now.
Because it does, you know, why go down to the realm of the ridiculous?
But here's the thing, folks.
It's just listen to it and do a little bit.
If you do a little bit of research on what's being said on mainstream and alternative,
not some of it, but all of it.
If you do a little bit of research, you'll find what's being said,
not only ridiculous, but unintuitive.
It just doesn't make any sense.
That's why we call it the dummy load.
People dedicate, they have energy, they're energetic beings.
People generally dedicate X amount of energy every day or every week or every year in term of time
on learning things.
They want to find out, hey, what's going on today or yesterday?
What happened this week?
And that's energy that you're dedicating.
And what do they do?
They go to the internet.
Very few people buy newspapers and things.
Actually, they do.
And what they're doing is they're being dummy loaded.
It is a load that is being put on you, a treadmill or a hamster wheel.
And it's taking all the energy away that you could be using and doing good founded research,
basically not reading what someone else wrote about something else,
which wrote about what someone wrote about something else.
But what is it based on?
You will find you are being served junk across the board.
And then you will find it unintuitive.
How the hell can we be listening to an economic commentator talking about debt when it's a
credit-based economy?
This is unintuitive.
It doesn't make any sense.
Yes, silence is golden.
But anyway, what else you got, Seth?
What else you have on the mind?
Someone in the Ustream chat says, as the credits roll, so does the slow reveal.
Sandy Hook hoax 9-11 conspiracy election fraud project paperclip,
quote unquote, conspiracy theory is being passed to the people via alternative
and primary media sources.
Why do you think this is?
Do you think conspiracy theory, quote unquote, is being released as data and a paranoid mindset
on purpose and with purpose?
Yes, it is.
Things will be exposed.
People won't see it.
But the reason why things are being exposed is so people are without excuse later,
like a real simple thing.
Here's a way to really massage the thought, OK?
I may not go direct.
I'll just massage the thought for a moment.
You ever notice people that profess religion, whether they grew up in it or new founded,
and they're enthusiastic about it, and I mean that word literally, right?
They're very enthusiastic about their faith.
But if you discuss anything with them right away, the source of their problems are political.
So they all of a sudden profess faith in a higher power.
But all of their problems are caused by human agents solely.
They abandon their God, right?
So this is the other thing.
Theory, the conspiracy theory came around the JFK, right?
That was coined to kind of sidetrack, right, like a theory.
But on one side, theory is bad.
But on the other side, they like academics.
They're good.
OK, all right.
So it doesn't make any sense.
Now, things like JFK, the reason why you're not going to find out who killed JFK in reality
is because they hired the right people to do it.
And what makes the right assassin, the right group of assassins, the right assassins is
they do not get caught.
If they got caught, they were the wrong group.
Duh, that's why you're never going to find it.
And it's also cosmic.
It has nothing to do with JFK's political stance.
It was a cosmic stance while he was taken.
In other words, these gods are behind it.
The gods don't abandon these situations.
They have a very heavy hand in it.
OK, maybe it had to do most likely with no one is discussing is JFK's faith, believe
it or not.
But anyway, with some there was some very in just in, you know, what I have read on the
matter and things like that, the timing and place that those things happen were heavy
with symbolism as well.
Yes, because there are certain, you know, there's layers of entities, there's geographic
ones, cosmic ones, and then there's a command group, you know, a hierarchy.
Now, 9-11, you shouldn't know what happened on 9-11 because it'll scare the living
daylights out of you.
And it has nothing to do with space weapons or something stupid like that, or nanothermite
or micro nukes.
Yes, you know, I'm not going to get into it.
It's not that difficult right now.
I mean, it's out there.
It's very practical.
It would be irresponsible to discuss 9-11 with accuracy because it would be like crying
fire in the theater.
People are too motivated by panic fear.
Let me just say this, and I'll say more than I've ever said.
There are structures that exist today that are occupied, that have the same type of situation
or scheme that brought down those towers.
And if you discuss what it is and how it works and why it's there, it would be like crying
fire in the movie theater because there are other structures that entail that same scheme.
It would be irresponsible to discuss it.
Yeah, and if it was discussed with accuracy and that knowledge became widespread, that
would affect what they call the real estate market fairly dramatically.
Yeah, and again, this is just all, you know, but it's a dummy load and people are going
to academics, you know.
They'll be shunned in the future, by the way, but nonetheless, maybe we're a little ahead
of the curve.
But 9-11 is irresponsible.
Now, most of the other to discuss publicly because, you know what, folks, you don't
deserve the truth based on the way you behave, right?
You don't go out and buy a fine leather couch and put a baby, a six-month-old baby without
a diaper on it unless you want to soil that couch.
And when I say you don't deserve the truth, I don't mean you're not deserving of it,
but at this point, absolutely not.
You're just, you're acting, the general population is just acting in a severely inappropriate
manner.
Even I'm talking about from their thoughts all the way down to their outward behavior
at this point.
And yeah, I know people don't appreciate hearing that, but, you know, clean up your
act, things might start being cleaned up around you, but that's not going to happen.
It will be, well, it will be cleaned up and you will be going into one hell of a society
next decade that you will appreciate, but it's going to be a big fat lie, even though
it'll be real at the same time.
The real part will be that there's going to be a Middle East Union where things are
going to be based out of and you're going to have pretty much a peace on earth like
you want, prosperity, what you call liberty, education, prosperity, all these other things.
And you're going to be promised that this is going to last a thousand years and you're
going to believe it.
It's only going to last a few years.
And when the glitches come, that's why I say it's only going to last a few years,
you're going to be told you have to do all these things to get back on track and you're
all going to believe it and you're all going to do it and you're going to follow through
on what is going to be hell on earth.
It has nothing to do with some despotic government, police or military.
You're going to be doing it to each other.
Yep.
So there'll be more details on this coming in the next couple of years.
And then after that, no one will be able to discuss the reality of it.
So it's going to be quite interesting how that's going to work.
So OK, so being intuitive, being unintuitive, misinformed or disinformed is pretty much
the question.
All of that can be taken away.
These shades of gray.
If you start looking at what things should be based on, what things are referenced for,
in other words, source material, be objective.
I don't think that practically people are capable of that at this point in mass.
I'm not promoting Gustave Le Bon.
Gustave L-E-B-O-N is a book called The Crowd and talks about the nature of crowds, crowd
mentality.
You ever run into someone who likes to go to protests or political activism?
People like to talk about conspiracy theories.
Religious groups, educational groups, movements.
I'm not talking about bowel movements, but nonetheless the same.
All of these require sort of the objectivity that Gustave Le Bon brought up.
It takes a certain type of individual to join a group like that.
And when you join the crowd, obviously you're not set apart.
So with that in mind, I think we'll have Seth here in a moment back again.
I might want to go and do a little recap on that because there's something about repetition.
There's repetition.
There's saying the same thing in different ways over and over.
Perhaps maybe that's how learning is done.
And now we're not here to maybe teach, but we're maybe here to share.
That's another way to think about it.
So let's see if we could pull up Gustave Le Bon, the crowd, the nature of crowds,
just for a one minute relief here.
This is an interesting thing.
I think this might be it.
And let's see how it comes off.
In this video, we will provide a summary of Le Bon's classic work.
In particular, we will investigate his insights into the nature of crowds,
look at the role ideas play in influencing crowds,
examine the religious sentiment of crowds,
and discuss the psychological and emotional benefits one derives from joining a crowd.
What is a crowd?
Le Bon defined a crowd as a group of individuals united by a common idea, belief, or ideology.
The idea which unites a crowd is not chosen by a process of clear reasoning
and examination of evidence.
Instead, as we will discuss in more detail later,
crowds accept beliefs and ideas superficially
and utilize them as fuel for revolutionary action.
When an individual becomes part of a crowd, according to Le Bon,
he undergoes a profound psychological transformation.
That is, he ceases to operate as an individual.
He is no longer himself but has become an automaton
who has ceased to be guided by his will.
With such a psychological transformation,
an individual no longer lives for himself
but instead becomes a pawn who sacrifices his own personal ends and goals
in favor of those of the crowd.
In a crowd, every sentiment and act is contagious
and contagious to such a degree that an individual
readily sacrifices his personal interest to the collective interest.
As was mentioned earlier, Le Bon maintained that a crowd forms
when an influential idea unites a number of individuals
and propels them to act towards a common goal.
These influential ideas, however, are never created by members of the crowd.
Instead, they are brought into the world by the minds of great individuals.
Well, as I said earlier, maybe not so great,
but this is a small excerpt at the one-minute mark
from a video called Gustave Le Bon, The Nature of Crowds,
put up by Academy of Ideas.
If anyone is ever interested, don't necessarily buy the book.
I'm not saying don't buy the book, but perhaps do the audiobook,
which is on that illustrious thing called YouTube.
And of course, it's true if it's on YouTube, right?
But nonetheless, get familiar with some objective reasoning
regarding these groups.
And this is something that is brought up over and over and over
that we're bringing up on Uncommon Sense
is because typically, when you get together on a media format,
such as radio, internet, chats, all this other thing,
a crowd is formed, believe it or not.
Now, define the crowd.
Well, who knows?
But the characteristics of the crowd can easily be defined
when you look at what Le Bon had written about it.
It's easy to perhaps, how would one say,
objectify what is going on or simpler to objectify.
So perhaps someone will do their research
and find out something else and message us
if there's any more details on Gustave Le Bon,
because it's a good sense of objectifying
what is going on with people.
And again, just to go back to what's uncommon,
because this is discussing things of uncommon sense in nature.
What is uncommon is just basically the faculties and qualities
that mankind has been endowed with.
Okay, basically, you have a mind and most people have an able body,
or if you don't, you have people around you that do.
And using things to their highest and best use is really uncommon.
It seems like there has been a just rolling around, taking up time.
And that is the truth of the matter, by the way,
if you look at it cosmically, you're in a waiting room,
a waiting period or a curing time.
But it doesn't mean that the slightest bit of realization
can make one operate on a higher level,
which is the highest and best use of what they can do.
You know, it might be known as economy of movement,
or killing two birds with one stone.
I don't think anyone should be killing birds.
But, you know, these things where you're using high efficiency in your life
and avoiding the dummy load, unless that's what you want.
A dummy load, for example, is expelling energy
just for the sake of expelling energy.
You know, and putting it out there in a way that doesn't do anything
is generally beneficial.
But technically, a dummy load, by the way,
is an electrical engineering term, is very beneficial,
you know, to test the system.
But nonetheless, what is uncommon is people operating efficiently.
And even when I say efficiently,
each one, each person has their own character.
Each person has their own way of looking at things
based on what senses they like to employ when they're looking at things.
But there are things that are common that all people have to a certain degree
that can be objectified, that could lead to a little more harmony
than what people are, I shouldn't say experiencing, but complaining about.
So what we like to do is bring you a point of view.
And sometimes, yes, I will say it goes on a little bit of a rant kind of idea.
Yes, it might be a little harsh,
but truly accurate to discuss humanity as a group of morons or imbeciles.
Yes, it's quite accurate, I assure you, if you look at it that way.
But nonetheless, the harshness aside,
imploring or asking people to employ objectivity in their lives
will lead to efficiency and actually using their intuitiveness,
which is granted to each individual.
One person might have an intuition based on something a little more
a different subject matter or perception than another.
And having this shared objectively, again,
perhaps this is where ideas and thoughts and things come from.
And these are all uncommon.
You know, when you hear people discussing the current societies
and the current systems in place, objectify it.
And you will see what is being discussed is absolutely worthless.
It is absolutely tripe and junk.
When I say worthless, I mean, I like to throw in the idea that
what you consider worthless,
one man's treasure is another man's garbage and vice versa.
I've actually discussed this with people.
Sometimes I get a little critical on what people are doing or saying,
but I kind of let them be because, yes,
one man's treasure is another man's trash.
So I think it's just let them do what they want
because there's a lot of trash collecting going on.
But welcome back, Seth.
So I think you're back.
So, yeah, I played a little bit of Gustav Le Bon,
the little excerpt on it because I believe that,
well, I believe, meaning repetition has its value
and repetition has its own way of,
let's say, setting in the mind the message that is being put out.
And the message is basically, be careful of what you do.
Be careful of information as it comes to you.
Learn to objectify.
You know, that's why very often we bring up,
you hear any biblical discussion,
if the first thing or within the first part of what they're discussing,
they don't mention that there is no public access to the text,
you're having a problem.
So this is our first hour.
We will be back.
Glad to have Seth back as well and take a break.
We'll see you guys at the second hour.
Welcome back to Uncommon Sense here on American Freedom Radio
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com as well as UncommonRadio.com.
My name is Seth and I am joined as well by the Greek.
Greetings.
Yes, yes, and welcome everyone.
Everyone, let's say four or five people listening.
And nonetheless, we keep going.
This is our second hour.
And, you know, Seth, I just want to tag on,
someone tagged on one of the emails here and on the Skype messages.
Can you explain the differences and relationships
between the physical dimension and the dimension of the gods?
And where are they if they never die?
Let's go backwards.
The gods do die and they can be put to death.
How clear that is to you?
I don't know, but it becomes very clear if you study.
But if you hate studying and you hate knowledge,
well, that's another thing.
So let's just say at this point, the gods are subject to death.
That's why there was a film called The Matrix.
And I found it astonishing how they revealed there was a section of the film.
And it's really sad, by the way.
This is a commentary that society, if you listen to Special Alternative Media,
they give a lot of movie references.
It's like, man, that just really proves what I've said a while back that,
you know, everyone thinks everything was created maybe a couple of decades ago.
But nonetheless, the movie, the film called The Matrix,
has said that one of the paraphrase here is that if you die in The Matrix
or you're killed in The Matrix, that you die in real life.
Now, that's how the gods operate.
Also, if you're a god and you manifest physically,
you know, meaning spirit animated through material known as aka a living being,
and that living being is slaughtered or put to death, you die spiritually as well.
You're put into disanimation, unanimated, right?
And your god friends on the other side will say, oh, he died, right?
And you might make some enemies if you kill a god,
whether intentionally or unintentionally,
and might actually start reading some ancient texts
and see how that's brought up prolifically.
But yeah, they do die.
And where do they go?
Basically, death is a state of unanimation.
People are still subject to the ridiculous aspect of what happens after you die.
The ridiculous aspect is, go talk to someone about what happens after you die,
and the majority of the people will give you something that is akin to the teacup ride
or Thunder Mountain or Mickey Mouse or something at Disneyland.
They are operating in a pure fantasy waiting room scenario.
What I mean about this is, no, do I have first-hand knowledge?
No, don't need it.
A lot of people say, do you have first-hand knowledge?
That is the most ridiculous thing to ask someone
unless you're operating as a prankster.
For example, all you folks out there who want first-hand knowledge about everything,
hey, I got a pretty good report that if you put the hand inside of a blender when it's on,
you're going to lose the fingers.
That report is good enough for me.
I don't need first-hand knowledge.
No.
If I stand in front of a car, on a speeding car on a highway,
that it's going to flatten me out and kill me.
I don't need first-hand knowledge of that.
Right.
So all you folks out there that are pranking or actually have,
like metaphorically being pranksters, can't address you.
Sorry.
I want pranksters.
I'll go to doctors, priests, rabbis, lawyers, whatever, politicians.
There's plenty of pranking going on.
But here's the thing.
When you...
You don't even have to go to them.
You can just turn the television on.
But go ahead.
Or the media, any media.
Now, here's the point.
It's a state of unanimation death.
It's just like being asleep without dreaming.
And we did discuss dreaming, not you and I, Seth,
but on a previous sonic experience or presentation.
When you're dreaming, by the way, you're being plugged.
Just like someone walking up to a dormant computer and putting in a USB stick.
Usually, it's a low-level spiritual entities that are messing with you while you're sleeping
so they can high-five each other watching you talk about it the next day.
It doesn't mean that higher-ranking spiritual entities or
gods will not also send their messengers to give you a dream.
But if you get a dream from a higher-ranking spiritual being,
you probably won't wake up.
Or you will wake up with severe physical trauma.
And they will also identify themselves.
Where the pranking spiritual entities make you think that it's your dream.
It's my dream.
I dreamt this.
I dreamt that.
I, I, I, me, me, me.
So, and they're just laughing their asses off at you, folks.
But once you understand that the purpose of sleep is to rest,
that's why when you look at these ridiculous religious ceremonies known as funerals,
the idiot that is conducting the ceremony
will talk about all this stuff, how you're with the Lord, or with this, or with that,
or going doing this, playing a harp, or going to Denny's for breakfast
on the other side, or whatever.
What do they write in stone?
Rest in peace.
Because you're going to be sleeping.
Death is the great sleep.
It's no animation.
There's no, here, here's, how about we throw in another little secret?
You know, there's a place, by the way,
where spiritual beings will be held captive on the earth, a physical place.
But they will know that they're being held captive.
So that means that they're not going to be killed.
They're being held captive.
And this is a place in the earth.
And if you want to figure it out, you can figure it out.
I'll give you, tell you what it's about.
The way you deprave or punish these spiritual entities is by sensory deprivation.
So it's kind of like being awake and asleep at the same time.
In other words, there's a place in the earth where these beings will be stored for a millennia.
And it's a sensory deprivation.
There's no feeling, no sensation, no light, no sound, nothing.
Quite interesting.
I figured I'd just throw that out there.
So, you know, you read about in the ancient texts how these
being spirits will be chained up for a while, right?
So I just thought I'd throw that in there.
But yeah, when they die, anything that's dead is inanimated.
There's no dream state.
You don't come back unless you're brought back.
And no one has been brought back except for the prototype.
So that was a long explanation around the second part of that email.
And some people might think that's dogmatic.
That's like the way it is.
Well, sorry, folks.
You know what?
It is.
That's a really good report.
Not because I'm saying it.
And here's the other thing I want to just say.
If there was anyone that was saying what was being said on Uncommon Sense,
even close, even 1%, I don't think we'd be doing this.
I think Seth enjoys conversation.
I do as well.
The Greek does.
But on the other hand, it's like looking at these matters that are
some of minor, some of great importance,
depending on your opinion, of course.
And no one is discussing them.
In other words, I've said before, the media, as prolific as it is,
is not being used even slightly to its highest and best form
other than a glorified telephone book or streaming music.
And I think it's about time that two hours a week,
something can be perhaps maybe dubbed as saying that the media
is being used for its highest and best reason.
But anyway, so the rest of it is the differences
between the relationship between the physical dimension
and the dimension of the gods don't know.
We know that what we do know that if the gods created everything,
that they are primary informative.
So the question there would be,
what do you know about primary informative conditions?
And what I can report that I've read on that is that
there it's not a difference of dimension,
simply a difference of perspective.
It's all in that mode of thought.
It's all one dimension, the dimensionality,
the idea of like the multiple universes stacked upon the one
is an inaccurate way of looking at it, I think.
I think that it's all, you know, our perspective is very limited.
Because some maturity as well.
Right.
Well, yeah.
And, you know, the location in that dimension,
I'd say that it's all right here, so to speak.
But there are physical differences in location, obviously.
But there are a couple of instances in, you know,
the old books that talk about brief moments of time
where an individual or a sizable group of individuals
was shown everything that's going on all around them right now.
And it broke them.
They, if I'm recalling correctly, begged for it to stop.
Exactly.
Yeah, it's not the fairy godmother and the wicked witch.
There's no, when you're shown that side,
it's all, how would you say, you might be dematerialized, right?
You're either rapidly or slowly.
So it's quite interesting.
It's quite a fearful place.
Yeah, not even to illustrate the awesomeness of it,
just to illustrate that, you know,
it's very possible that there is a lot going on around us immediately.
I mean, like in a room that you're in right now that is not being observed
and that cannot be observed because of the limited perspective.
Yes.
So thinking of it like that is kind of an abstract way, I guess.
But at the same time, it's about as tangible as the intangible can get, I suppose.
So yes, that's what I'd add.
It should be appreciated.
Now, what I mean should be appreciated is the realm that we exist in,
that we cannot comprehend or go there, should be appreciated, folks.
Because it's not what you think.
Hollywood is lying to you.
Your priests, rabbis, imams, ministers, the pope, your college professors,
everyone around you that is telling you about the,
they're all lying to you about this stuff, right?
Making it happy-go-lucky or it's just whatever you believe
or what you make it or this group says this and this group,
we believe this group says this and this group believes that.
Well, you pick and choose.
No, it's none of that ridiculous crap.
That's all it is.
It's coprophagia.
Coprophagia.
Look it up.
C-O-P-R-O-P-H-A-G-I-A.
So here's the point.
The point is appreciate it.
Stop taking things for granted was one way to look at it, you know,
and enjoy where you're at.
Be efficient and stop hating knowledge.
Stop hating good information.
And most people will not admit it, but they sure act like it.
You know, the people that came before you were not ancient primitives.
Why do you think so much energy, by the way, has been put into obfuscate,
twist, corrupt and not provide accurate information about the past?
Think about that for a moment, folks.
I'm not just talking about your geopolitical history or history of events.
I'm talking about all of it.
It's very important that people don't get a grip on reality, it seems.
Now, when I say it, I'm not saying that it is very important that it is that way.
But it is.
You know, I mean, in a good way.
Some of the loose discussions that I have is that
anyone that pretty much figures out the whole truth and nothing about the truth
dematerializes.
You're no longer here.
You know, you see no purpose of it.
You know, it's like you're plucked out or you some interesting stuff going on there.
You know, think about it.
So just be appreciative.
Going should go back to the we talked about Ecclesiastes, perhaps, you know,
what is it?
Good food, good drink, good convo conversation.
That's that's certainly one of the one of the things that I pulled from that text.
Seeking wisdom is repetitive in in reiterating, you know,
eat well, drink well, good, good company.
That's yeah, it's there's wisdom right there.
It's one of the reasons I enjoy, you know, when we speak about food.
And I think it's a good thing to talk about when we broadcast as well, because,
you know, it's that's important.
That's important to health, whether you think of that in a spiritual or mental sense.
And a physical sense.
And that's, you know, if you need that to go anywhere else, it's part of, you know,
the base of just existing in, you know, in this in this place and this time.
Yeah, that's another thing that was discussed in a previous sonic presentation was we called it
the container.
I think it was episode two talked about how the body works, not because of some scientific idea
or some quack, you know, quackery.
But by the way, still, I have to do this, by the way, so that I have to say it,
you know, when I convey in an engine driven wagon,
and I see like a medical building or a hospital, I have to pull over and stuff the ears with
cotton, because if I don't, the quacking is so loud, the ears are ringing for like a week later.
You know, and people are still anyway, that's kind of a joke, take it how you want.
But the quacking is so loud.
I mean, yeah, if you live about a mile, if you live within a mile of a medical establishment,
or so, I mean, can't you hear the quacking?
But, but we talked about how the body works up because based on what the ridiculous grunt,
now, they've done some good grunt work, by the way.
But we talked about how the body works based on how objective you want to be, you know,
using a lot of the grunt work, you know, that they've come up with, like,
if anyone researches how the intestines work, go look at the intestines.
I mean, don't look at a graphic bloody image.
But look at the diagram.
Some of them are fairly accurate.
Look at all the layering.
Nothing passes through that.
It's all hydrophobic.
It's not porous.
So when you eat food, you're telling you, you know, I was once on a call,
I think it might even be broadcast in another place.
There was someone there selling, I've got 30 years medical experience.
And you should take this because it's absorbed by the body.
And I'm like, what are you talking about?
The body doesn't absorb anything.
And I started going into the, you know,
supposedly they're 30 year professional in the medical field.
They didn't know that the intestines are sealed off.
And I mean, this is just ridiculous stuff.
I mean, there's prankster, obviously, you know, MD, doctor, whatever, prankster.
So this sonic presentation called The Container was, I believe,
pretty comprehensive in discussing some of the fallacies and some of the
actual points on what's going on and considering it,
considering what food is and what drink is and how the body works.
And that's fantastic in its way.
And I think like you mentioned earlier,
discovering the true nature of the realm of the gods would be,
as you mentioned, memorialized about a certain group of people
who were made privy to it said, stop, you know, it's enough.
We don't want more.
If you actually start looking into how headquarters,
the actual body that you're using works, you may not want to continue
because it is radically different than what you've been told and what you think.
So it's but on one side, that's an aspect that how it can be perceived.
On the other side, if the soul, the spirit and the body work together
to animate the being known as yourself,
then you have, let's call that headquarters,
the physical part being the building or the physical aspect.
If you're deceived about that, you're deceived about headquarters.
Don't you think that anything, if headquarters is full of deception,
what do you think will be allowed to come in?
Deception. And what do you think will come out?
Deception. And when was the last time you turned into any media?
Anyway, we'll dig again there.
But you see, there's a level of how much do you really want to know?
And you don't have to go far away to do it.
It's just if you stop hating knowing and hating information
and start being objective and intuitive,
you might actually make some headway and find out it's not what you think
and not what you thought.
I don't know. There's an old saying, perhaps,
maybe I kind of twisted it around a little.
You can bring a horse to water, but you can't make him think.
Speaking of horses, by the way, I want to interject a good report
that I got regarding a horse and maybe applying some treatment.
What do you think, Seth? Go into it for a minute or two.
Somebody that's in Europe has a horse that sprained the ankle,
got pretty swollen. And what do I do?
And I said, well, you know, that's lymphatic, man.
You got to wrap that as tight as possible.
And I mean tight and then let it release it every 15 minutes.
It's going to take a lot of work.
But in a day or two, it should go down.
The third day, 72 hours, roughly, should be gone.
Well, this person went out and did that.
And they were quite happy to report back that everything worked as such.
And typically a horse that has a problem like that,
it could escalate, it could get better.
But typically things don't get better on their own like that.
The horse was limping around and dragging around.
And after three days of just very tight wrapping and releasing,
the horse is as good as new.
So I just wanted to report if anyone is interested in understanding
how to promote healing in injury,
whether it's human-based or animal-based or whatever,
study lymphology, the lymphatic system.
And you'll notice when you start doing that
on that wonderful thing they call the internet,
you'll see how little information there is about it.
But yet whatever information is out there,
you will find that it is very helpful.
And intuitive.
So I believe one of the...
You've heard of blood testing,
you know, looking for pathogens and conditions and things like that.
Well, there was a particular health institute in Europe a while back
that didn't do any blood testing.
They did lymphatic fluid testing because it was far more effective.
So get into comprehending what the lymph system is,
not just the lymph nodes and the fluid itself,
but its effect on the physical being when it comes to injury.
And you will find you'll be able to do things
that might even be called miraculous to some degree.
So anyway, speaking of miracles, Seth,
what else would you like to discuss?
So we've got about 40 minutes.
I didn't really plan anything for the discussion.
We basically said we'd do some things and we didn't,
which was read news articles.
But in essence, I think just having a two-hour spot here
where we could actually are free and open to discuss things
that not only is not being discussed,
but no one else seemingly can't discuss.
So here we are.
Yeah, absolutely.
Talked about the email that was...
Or I don't even know if it was an email, actually.
The message that was, shouldn't call everyone stupid.
I'm paraphrasing, of course.
But it's not as if we are telling you or anyone else to hate anyone.
That's not it at all.
Just kind of looking at everything.
I don't know if rationally is the word,
but it is certainly rational.
Just making observations and stating those observations.
We'd like to get into the text a little bit,
but we're doing that in the same way.
Reading what was preserved and sharing that.
So, yeah.
Yeah, that concept is going to slam people
and they're going to take it laying down.
I mean, imagine right now,
just normally a brick wall falling on someone.
You know, the person's going to yell, ouch, right?
But something even bigger than a brick wall will fall on society
and they're going to just be like, oh, okay, fine.
Seem normal.
That is proof of a cosmic influence, you know, allowing it to happen.
And that will be where people will be going back
and actually referencing things.
And it's going to be a really bad day
for those that are in the religious community.
You know, the leaders, the preachers, ministers, priests, whatever.
The moronic leadership.
And it's also going to be a bad day for many academics.
It's going to be a bad day for a lot of entitled classes.
You know, bad day meaning days.
The one that people will start to spend more than,
maybe I'd say five minutes a week
looking at what things are based on.
You know, you may not have, like, for example,
the Western world may not have Moloch or Santa Claus
as their chief god.
Go figure.
So, you know, around that time of year.
I mean, these are things that probably we'll be discussing
to a certain level as time goes on.
Right now, you can't really discuss these things,
at least on the internet, radio as such,
because there's still, if you listen a little bit
to how people are bringing subject matter
on what they call internet radio,
they still introduce people that have academic backgrounds
and beliefs and things as being something good
and setting precedent.
So you've got to laugh.
And you still have children being told by their parents,
yeah, they know that they're not going to learn anything
for 12 years, but they've got to do it anyway
because they did it, right?
So that's still going on very prolifically.
Social conditioning, essentially.
But when you see it going on on such a level
that they're emphatic about doing it,
that it's not time yet.
But when you see that falling apart,
you know, when you see people trying to bring on
guests to discuss things, and they will start
to not want to bring people who have
academic credentials, you'll see that this thing is cracking
and people are coming to their senses.
And when you'll see parents saying,
no, we're not sending you to this ridiculous institution
for 12 years, and then you see it's cracking out,
you see the time is coming now.
It's time to come out now and maybe discuss things
in a more clear and objective fashion.
But right now, it's clearly not.
It might seem like 100 years away,
but it's not, folks.
It's only a few years away before the cracks
in the system start to arise.
So it'll be quite an interesting time.
And then there'll be a short time to discuss
these things openly, and then it's kind of time
to put your head down and walk away
because there's going to be quite a fervor
of revived things.
And actually, it'll be more than a few years
to discuss these things openly.
But right now is not the time.
But I think we've put out enough.
I mean, we started off the program
just saying, here's a secret, folks.
And truly, it is.
And there are many secrets.
And there's no mystery.
There's just secrets because mystery means no one knows.
And that's kind of leaving the gods out of it.
You know, so, yeah, on that.
And by the way, you brought up the term
of hate and stuff.
You know, people think hate is a bad thing.
Well, then love would be a bad thing
because it takes a lot of passion
to love and to hate.
The opposite of love may not be hate.
It's apathy, indifference,
because it takes a lot of passion and effort
to do both love and hate.
You know, look at, quote, unquote,
hate groups or hating on someone.
It's not, you know, it takes a lot of energy,
a lot of focus to do that.
It takes a lot of energy to love.
You know, the opposite of those.
They're both actions.
They're both like we're in the English language.
We're limited by the many ideas
that are conveyed with a single word.
It can be handy for art and poetry,
but for, you know, expressing
quantities and, you know,
or like that side, something tangible.
It's one of the peeves I have
with the English language,
which is the one that I, you know,
certainly know the most words.
And I don't know how well I speak it,
but it's, you know,
all of these very, very different concepts
that we express with these single words,
but in that some of the mechanics are lost.
Like, you know, the fact that love and hate,
those are things that are done.
It's not just an idea or a concept
that is held as something, you know, acted upon.
So yeah, and the opposite of that
would be inaction, you know, apathy.
Whereas just like you're saying,
it takes a lot of effort to hate or to love.
So there's a lot of what's done.
I, you know, I certainly hate,
I've said in the past in private conversations
a number of times that, you know,
music is one of the few things that people do
that actually like beyond that.
It's all kind of absurd when it's looked at
from a perspective that is not
very, very small and localized.
Like trying to see everything as,
if you look at all of humanity as an organism,
you know, a single entity,
a lot of what is done is absolutely absurd.
So I like music though.
Like I said, I still like people
and I like the music they make.
I don't like them in large quantities.
They tend to be less reasonable in large quantities.
I'm not sure why that is.
But the crowd, I think the crowd brought it up a few times.
Yeah.
He did a good job objectifying it.
But yeah, the music might be using human attributes
at a highest and best use is, you know,
is one way to view it.
And, you know, here's the thing.
Here's the thing we've discussed, you know,
like for example, reading was never done silently.
It was a pretty new phenomenon,
maybe 500 years.
It was always done reading aloud.
Like if you went to an ancient library,
you were given reading material
or picked reading material
and you went to something that looked like a little booth.
And if it was really long
and you had to read the whole thing,
you brought several people with you.
And that was the, let's say,
the inception of the conference room.
But, you know, the music,
when people were going to play music back then also,
it was considered a spiritual act.
You were interacting with the gods.
You know, go look at some of the writings that were done.
Of course, you know,
if you tell anyone to go back more than 10 years now,
it's like, oh no, none of that stuff existed.
All of that stuff, those were stupid people.
You know, everything sprang into existence
just 100 years ago.
You know, I mean, this is the level of humanity at this point.
But when humanity does go back
and look at how things were done,
it will be quite intuitive.
I mean, they might reject it.
Typically people say,
well, I play music because it sounds good and I like it.
But, you know, if you go back
and look at the history of it,
it was an interesting,
how would you say,
things were more directed or the conscious effort.
The conscious effort of making the music
was not just making the music,
was that people had a little bit more understanding
on why they were doing things, I should say.
Yeah, it's the natural,
I think that the natural element to making music
and the desire to make music
is certainly a spiritual one.
And currently, like in what is broad,
what I observe, you know,
I'm surrounded by music a great deal of the time,
all sorts.
And currently that element is still acknowledged,
but it's done so like most other things
that are acknowledged in parody.
It's done like all of the,
any type of music, just about any type of music.
There will be elements to it,
even in the way that it's marketed or packaged,
you know, in the tangible sense,
or even just a photograph associated with a song
on the internet, you know,
which is becoming more and more common way,
you know, as you were saying earlier,
broadcasting music, streaming it.
And there are elements that are undeniably spiritual
with any of that in any sense of the term,
colloquially or, you know, etymologically.
And, but it's all done in parody,
very tongue in cheek,
even if that's not the intention or the style,
just the way that it's done.
Sorry, I kind of rambling there, but.
No, that's fine.
Well, music is still used.
It's a food in a way.
In other words, it satisfies a hunger
or it satisfies a palate.
It satisfies a desire to listen, you know.
You know, people like music as generally they do.
There's something that is considered to be pleasant,
even the most unpleasant sounding music,
by the way, there are people who find it to be pleasant,
right, you know, there's,
I basically say, you know,
if it sounds good, it is good, you know, essentially.
And also combined with music,
let's not leave out the aspect of dance, right?
The physical interaction.
So, you know, these things, again,
are still being used quite a bit.
And, but the purpose of them has been sort of changed,
you know.
But the, it's, I'd say that it's
the perception of its nature that has changed,
not its nature itself.
Like, I don't think what music is,
has changed, has gotten better or gotten worse.
I'd say that music has always been music.
And it's the perception of that has changed.
There's, you know, a lot of,
you can look at things electronic and done on the computer
as being like a pseudo world,
like another reality within our own,
because of all that can be done with it,
just simply with the manipulation of ones and zeros.
When you look at it like that,
and you look at the building blocks
that we are able to observe around us,
the immensity of the hologram,
the whole image that we're experiencing currently
that we are in is,
it's kind of mind boggling, I guess.
I'm going off on a tangent there.
Oh, no, that's fine.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
I like that work to boggle.
Let's do a quick look up on that,
or boggling.
I've been looking up words.
Yeah, boggling.
Mind boggling, the boggle.
To start with fright, as startled horse does.
Shy, take alarm.
Middle-aged boog speeter.
Let's do, I guess, a bug.
Meaning to raise scruples, hesitate.
I guess that flips it around a little bit.
Boggled, but one who hesitates.
Or to start with fright, as startled horse does.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's accurate.
It's kind of frightful.
It's kind of startling.
Taking alarm, yeah.
Every once in a while, I'll use a word accurately
and not even be aware of it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so this is part of the, let's say, the discussion,
something as common as music and common as dance.
When people do a little bit of, let's see,
historical access to what it was about,
it actually fills the mind or the spirit
with a little more substantiation on why we're doing it
and it's okay.
Or when things are said to not be okay
and things that are said to be okay to do,
or fit and proper or whatever,
it's good to be able to fill in a little bit
of how things were done to understand where you're at.
One thing I used to say in public a lot is,
in order to understand a thing more completely,
you have to understand the history of that thing, right?
And once you look into the history of that thing,
it tends to put things in a more solid perspective.
And then, of course, there are many determinations
that can be made beyond that.
Is this something fit and proper
based on the way that I want to live?
Or is it not?
Or I didn't know that.
How many times do you hear that?
I didn't know that about this.
There's, again, bringing the best and highest use,
you always kind of harp and rant about
how the quote-unquote internet is not being used
at its best and highest use.
Not at all, very little is.
But one way to use one's energy
in the best and highest use
is when you're embarking on something that is new
or you have interest in, find out where it came from
or what it's supposed to be based on.
Now, this is not necessarily for one's overall benefit
because it will not benefit you socially.
Because what we mean by socially,
go back to Gustavo Bonds, the crowd, right?
Go to any group that is protesting or activism
or political or religious or whatever,
and you will see the objectivism that Gustavo Bond
brought out about these groups very clearly.
But when you start looking at what things are based on,
the crowd mentality will not favor it.
It's very difficult to go and discuss
with someone who is deeply ingrained
in the crowd mentality the nature of things
or how things are.
Like, for example, we brought up scientists
several times today.
And that's a fairly new term.
Prior to that, they were known as natural philosophers.
In other words, learning or wisdom about,
friendly wisdom to nature, I guess would be the way to say it.
That's right.
A fondness for the wisdom of nature.
Yes.
And the scientists were around
when it became more technocratic,
meaning the government's involvement
or the ruling class now using it as a tool.
And by the way, kind of like all over the place here,
but here, folks, this is something that you need to consider
and really consider this.
These entitled classes, people with degrees and diplomas,
or there's a fellow on the email called it working papers.
I mean, just, you know, they're entitled.
They're there as a buffer zone between those who are,
you know, the main pranksters and the people being pranked.
They like to have buffer zones, you know,
kind of like a median on a highway or something
so you don't kind of see the cars coming
the other direction all the time.
Kind of scary.
So it's for both sides.
So when the chief pranksters, the human authorities,
want to keep people away from discovering things or whatever,
they set up scientists, religious leaders,
attorneys, doctors.
So when some poor schmuck in the crowd,
like figures out, let's say a cure for cancer
or a free energy device or a methodology of law or something,
what they do is they sick these entitled people on them.
You know, like sick them, like a dog.
They're basically acting like junkyard dogs.
And if you could look at this as a tool of suppression,
that's not their whole purpose.
Their whole purpose is also they're pranksters themselves.
But if you actually look at the junkyard dog mentality
that is put on these people with quote unquote degrees.
Now, this is not because degrees are bad and all this stuff.
I mean, they're quite degrading
if you actually look at the system.
All of that could have been used properly
and could have been used in a good beneficial way.
But I assure you, it is not at all right now.
And these entitled classes, again,
the people with the prefixes and the titles,
they're really a buffer zone.
Again, so some poor schmuck in society figures something out.
They just sick these guys on them.
They say, well, if you came up with this medical device,
where did you get your medical degree?
Oh, are you a doctor?
No.
Okay, that means that everything that you do is worthless then.
And they discredit people based on these entitled pranksters.
And again, this might sound general,
but it's generally true that most of the people
that are using their degrees and entitlement in society,
it's a social rank.
They are pranksters, except for a small group in there
that is looking for an exit strategy
because they found out what it's about.
And this is really a bird's eye view
of human society at this point.
Now, there are some people that are in those entitled groups
that have done good work.
But eventually, when you do get to know
any of these people who've done good work
or look at more completely,
they are very wholly dissatisfied
with the institutions they adhere to.
This goes across the board.
Now, put the propagandists aside.
But here, give an example.
Yesterday down here, down by the university,
I spoke to no less than four people in a half an hour.
And they're all either involved or graduated
or worked with the university.
And they all admitted within conversation,
I kind of brought it up,
that it was absolutely worthless.
No, no value at all.
And yeah, and four...
Have you ever heard a doctor tell you something like,
no, I'm not allowed to tell you this
or something like that?
Sorry, small interjection.
Oh, no, no.
Yeah, they're pranksters.
I recently had a discussion with someone said,
man, I almost got pranked by a doctor.
I said, how?
And they went through the story.
I said, yeah, you almost got pranked.
Yeah, it's just social rank, folks.
This is about being on Earth.
This has nothing to do with what you believe in.
This has nothing to do what you've been told.
This has to do with being a...
Let's say in the mind,
imagine that you are traveling through the galaxies,
you know, like a Star Trek, Gene Roddenberry kind of thing.
Was it Gene Roddenberry did Star Trek as well?
Yeah, Star Trek, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
So you're going to all these worlds
and you lay down on a planet and you're like,
what's going on here?
Come back and report to the captain.
You can't start sitting there and say,
I like chocolate ice cream,
or I'm Christian or I'm Muslim.
I decided to believe in this
or I decided to believe in that.
Captain doesn't want to hear that.
You got to be objective.
You know, I really like this TV show.
That doesn't tell me anything
about what's going on down here.
Or, you know, are you political?
Who's your favorite political guy?
You know, you can't come back
to giving reports like that.
But that's all you hear.
That's all you hear from people.
This is ridiculous reports.
You know, there's even a report
that I'm not going to be persistent about giving.
There's people talking about
legalizing certain things, right?
Cannabis has just come out and say
it's the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard of
because none of that illegalization
or legalization has ever applied to anyone
other than the effects of the pranking.
Actually, if you go study all the laws
to all these things that are quote unquote
illegal or legal,
they're not being administered properly.
It's just a set of pranking,
you know, all of it across the board.
But here's the thing.
How many times have you heard in
loose discussion or firm discussion
about all these laws?
What are we going to do about this law?
Well, first of all, people, listen to this.
I don't really want to be a proponent of this.
How ridiculous you are and they are
and the whole thing is just ridiculous
is that according to the federal manual,
which is also used by states,
in order for a proposed law to become law,
it has to be read three times,
not once or twice,
but three times on the floor of a legislative body.
It doesn't matter if the law is one page long,
10 pages long,
or 30,000 pages long,
the entire thing has to be read
three times on the floor of the legislative body
in order for it to be enacted and passed as law.
Now, how many of those laws
that have been enacted in the past decades or so
do you think have been read in any legislative body?
How many?
Seth, you want to guess?
None.
Yes, that's right.
None of them.
And how many people are talking about legalization of this
or that or whatever addressing this matter?
None.
None. Zero.
Maybe one or two research.
He's not, he's very objective
and he has a very interesting point.
We might have him as a guest one day.
I don't know.
I mean, other than his research,
he might kind of find what we're saying to be very obtuse,
but nonetheless,
a person has come up with this
and I've confirmed it.
So here's the point.
So then what's going on when someone has what they call cannabis
and the cops come in and bust them for it,
take them to court and throw them in jail?
What is that?
That's all pranking.
Why? Because these are all pranksters, man.
They love it.
They love pranking.
I have seen quote unquote law enforcement in public
when there's a crowd,
they discern certain people.
You know, you'll have 10 people doing the same thing.
And let's say, I don't like you.
You're going to jail.
But no, you, you're okay.
You just stay here.
And they're doing the same thing, by the way.
This is all who they feel like pranking.
It's all about pranking, right?
And it goes on and on and on.
And this is what it's like on earth.
Not America, not Europe, not Russia, not here or there.
This is the state of affairs of the human condition
on what is known planet earth.
By the way, I want to throw something in about that.
There's some people looking for the lost Atlantis.
And you know why you're never going to find it?
Because you're standing on it.
That was the old name for earth.
But anyway, I thought I'd throw that in there.
Lots of little secrets, maybe, which are uncommon.
So yeah, we talked about, again, there's buffer zones.
There's pranking, a lot of pranking.
You know, one thing we haven't gotten into
is lawfulness and unlawfulness.
I think you and I have done it before quite a bit.
But until people figure that out, what that means,
which will be in the near future,
when you discuss what's lawful and unlawful,
law tends to be very objective.
And it tends to go after all, regardless of your title.
You know, there was an old maxim,
is Rex Lex or is Lex Rex?
Meaning, is the king the law or is the law the king?
Yeah, that was, yeah, that, yes.
That was a chanted in the streets at one time.
Lex Rex, Lex Rex, Lex Rex.
Law's king, law's king, law's king, yeah.
But yet, at the same time, they put their hand on the Bible
and they think it has some mystical, magical power
or a rabbit's foot or something.
So these people aren't really going anywhere.
Just like today, you hear about,
let's go protest this thing.
I'm like, you gotta be kidding.
You know, you don't know where you are, man.
You know, this is planet Earth, you know.
In other words, if you've got a lot of energy
to do that kind of thing,
activism, protesting and all this other crap,
and they let you do it, they meaning the other pranksters,
you know, the pranksters that have sharp objects
and projectiles and chemicals and buildings
with cages in them, they let you do it.
Yeah, go ahead, spin your wheels.
It's got nothing to do with that.
The gods are in control.
But yeah, and exactly, you know,
someone sent a message.
Man, I'm so glad you said about on the last program
or maybe the previous
that the people have abandoned their gods.
Yes, they have.
You're living in a,
by the way, the entire human society right now
is either outright pagan or outright atheist.
Atheist meaning without a god or denying it,
or just pagan, just ignorant, straight up.
This is your human environment at this point
across the board.
That is a very accurate statement.
And also lawless.
It doesn't mean you don't have any order.
You have quite a bit of order.
Fortunately, the pranksters are maintaining order
through pranking.
They do a good job keeping order.
You know, here in the US, what they call America,
they have a military base pretty much in every state.
You know, why?
Keep order.
It's got nothing to do with training anybody.
You know, so yeah, this is the state of affairs
on the planet.
It's very uncommon to discuss this, by the way, Seth.
What say you?
I think it's uncommon to discuss the reality of things.
Oh, yeah.
This program is this broadcast.
I'm just going to call it a broadcast.
It's not really a program.
There's no set anything we're doing here.
But I'd say that this broadcast certainly lives up
to its title.
Yeah, it's a bad object.
People hate it.
Now, recently, I'm repeating this probably the third time.
I found out it's kind of a hard thing to figure out
or come to the realization that people actually hate
knowledge and truth.
They have a hate for it, and mildly and not so mildly.
And that's why, you know, for example, places,
venues where people speak and the people know
that it's a question answer after the speaker is finished
or a quote unquote show or program or that has callers,
people calling in.
If you ever look at objectify what's going on,
most of the time, the people that want to interact
with the host or the speaker are just sitting by.
And what they're thinking is, when is this person
going to shut up so I can get the microphone
and I could tell everybody what I want to say?
Right.
This goes on and on and on and on.
So there is a you've got to also look at the character
of the of the society as a whole.
What what keeps the common base going as it does?
You know, and that's why there is not a lot of
progress on their own.
And that's why I keep saying it's all cosmically dictated.
And the best thing to be efficient is understand
cosmic cycles.
You have the agricultural cycle on the planet.
You know, you're locked into spring is planting.
Summer is growth.
Fall is breaking down.
Winter is an in-between time where you do things
that you couldn't do during the other three seasons.
You know, by the way, folks, this springtime,
we kind of discussed spring and the nature of it.
Right.
And now you're in summer here on this part of the world
and winter and the other part.
But watch what's going on in current events,
by the way, during the summer.
That is a growing process.
In other words, it's growing things that have been planted.
There was a recent event that happened somewhere,
what they call a shooting, let's say.
And that is growing something that was planted
a few months ago regarding a certain group
and their rights and things like that.
So watch that carefully.
You know, it's interesting, right?
It's also, yeah, summertime is when things kind of grow.
You know, they've already been planted.
They've passed the sprout stage.
So let's, lest anyone forgets what comes after summer.
Fall, that is a time where things are torn down
or harvested, brought in.
And you've still got another couple of months before that,
a couple of moons, I should say.
And at that point, watch the events
and you'll see that they are breaking down events.
And that's why at least there seems to be
a little bit more reason this year
than last year or the year before.
I'm talking about the pagan year that people go on,
you know, the Pope's work schedule.
There's not a lot of crying about complete financial collapse
this summer, by the way,
which is absolutely ridiculous, never happens.
So yeah, just be observant on the seasons,
seasonal changes, spring planting,
summer growth for fall breaking down
and winters in between time.
Time for travel, time for rebuilding things,
things that you wouldn't do normally.
Yeah, quite interesting.
I always found it very odd that people went on vacation
in the summer because that was a thing
that was always done throughout humanity in the winter,
you know, because during the summertime,
you were in the height of things, right?
Production or growth.
But maybe it shows that society has taken a cue
from people of leisure because people of leisure,
I guess, vacationed anytime they wanted.
And maybe if it was more pleasant in the summer
to get away from the heat, let's say.
But here's another thing about people that were wealthy,
people back in the day.
When you were wealthy or affluent
or high in stature in society,
you were a person of leisure.
What's interesting now from personal interaction
with people that are of high net worth,
credit worth or whatever, what rich people, as they say,
they have no time at all.
I don't know.
And even if you haven't interacted with millionaires
or billionaires or whatever,
you might've heard about it, quite busy.
They don't have any time whatsoever.
I find it to be quite interesting the flip on that.
So I'd throw that in there for a moment.
So we got any questions or anything
that we could throw in the mix here?
Oh, there was a question earlier in the chat
that I'm sure would be interesting to some.
And it was kind of, I guess, a personal question for you.
But it asked, who would you say is your deity
if one gets their laws from their deity and et cetera?
Well, let's be right.
I'll say it in a general term.
Why would you, if you were given a plane ticket
and it was free to travel or a boat ticket
and you could go coach business or first class
and cost the same, which one would you go?
Which one would you go for?
You know, if you were to eat at a five star restaurant
or a greasy spoon for free, which one would you eat at?
Greasy spoon or the five star restaurant, let's say.
I'd probably go to the five star restaurant
because I don't know that I've ever eaten in one of those.
And if it's free, yeah.
Yeah, it costs the same, let's say, or the effort's the same.
Or if you were to fly in one of these big things,
these big metal cans with wings,
would you sit first class business or coach for free?
You know, it costs the same.
Let's say it costs you a nickel.
What do you get for a nickel?
Where are you going to go?
Right?
See?
So very simple, right?
And how do you find out about anything?
Well, guess what?
We've been here for more than 10 years
or 100 years or 200 years
and everyone that's come before us
is not an idiot like today.
Anyway, I don't mean that that way.
But the things that were memorialized
a very long time ago and are still preserved today
are here today because they're important.
Think about it.
Actually, maybe some people do too much thinking,
they get into a lot of trouble.
You shouldn't do so much of that.
Yeah, that's right.
And here's the thing, folks.
You're not going to be making friends
listening to Uncommon Sense.
Are you sure you know that?
One thing I wanted to mention
before we end the program here,
also out of ecclesiastes,
is not only the good food, good drink,
but to not do anything to excess.
In the English, at least,
it says to not be overly righteous
or overly evil or to be overly anything.
It's kind of obvious knowledge or wisdom
that is lost on a lot of people.
People are gluttonous with a great deal
more than food.
Study is one of those things.
Be realistic.
That's vanity.
That's vanity over much of anything.
And remember, folks, nothing exceeds excess.
So again, thank you again for the past two hours, everyone.
And donate to AFR if you can.
And visit us at www.uncommonradio.com.
If you want to send us a message.
Thanks, folks.
See you again next week.