Welcome to Uncommon Sense. Hey Seth, go for it.
Greetings and welcome. Uncommon Sense here on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
My name is Seth and as well we are broadcasting with the Greek. Welcome.
Yeah, hi. You know, you said my name is Seth. Names are just sounds that people answer to
and if you're going to go to another language as written, it better sound the same.
In other words, names are exempt from language. So if your name is Tom,
no matter what language it's written in, when it's sounded, it better sound like Tom.
Otherwise, it's not the name. It's another name.
So it's very interesting how these things work.
I want to get into a few things on how things work or maybe how they don't work
and how they're working when they don't work. Got that?
One of the things, Seth, I wanted to discuss is how people get a lot of description but no explanation.
And it seems like when the explanations try to be brought forward,
everything gets lost because they're not used to it. They're used to descriptions.
So, for instance, you know, the cat is black. The house is red. You know, the sky is blue.
But when you get into why the cat is black, why the house is red and why the sky is blue,
you've lost everyone. When I say everyone statistically.
So I guess that comes with listening versus hearing things. Are you hearing things, Seth?
Yes.
Okay. Occasionally, right? Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. It's best to listen. So now that we're here, also check your audio, Seth.
You're a little fuzzy there. It sounds like you're speaking between some fuzzy dice.
So, yeah, this is another episodic sonic adventure.
And by the way, folks, if you want to contact Seth or the Greek, it's www.uncommonradio.com.
It's good to put the www in front of the Uncommon Radio and then .com after it
because Uncommon Radio on a regular browser search is very, very common.
No pun intended.
But, yeah, I was mentioning before we started the show that, you know,
partly when we did this adventure here on American Freedom Radio,
it was kind of like maybe structuring it mentally and, you know, sonically,
like the previous sonic adventure done here, making it kind of topical.
Discussing topics and things like that are edifying.
One can say they do help individuals,
and I'll give a long and a short list about what the future holds on this.
And, you know, discussing very specific topics.
But during the week of doing that, you know, this was weeks and weeks before,
I was listening to various forms of media, alternative and mainstream,
and just looking at what's on the Internet and even looking at print, you know,
going to a kiosk, going to a university library, for example, discussing with people things.
And the contrast between the mindset that's required to impart pertinent information,
contrasted to the mental state of humanity at large,
is so far that I decided subconsciously or without saying it, I'm saying it now,
not to be topical on many of the episodes because people have just lost it.
When I say people, I mean all of humanity across the board.
That's why I started off by saying people just want to hear descriptions.
They can't listen to explanations.
And before we get into any more of that, would you say it has something to do with discernment?
Would you say it has something to do with paying attention?
Would you say it has something to do with just paying attention or looking at what's obvious?
I mean, is it possible?
You know, give an example.
Lawfully, it appears to be the last week of the fifth month.
Now, I want to bring this up again.
I've been speaking about this for over a decade, but I don't even know how to keep time.
You are on, you, whoever is listening, have associated with people or in fact yourself,
have wholeheartedly accepted the papal work schedule known as the Gregorian calendar as a timepiece,
and it's not.
The same way you've accepted little pieces of paper as money when it's not.
The same way you've accepted little pills that you take as medicine, and it's not.
The same way you've accepted entitled classes to help you, and they're nothing but pranksters and predatory.
So here's the point.
I want to bring this because I had someone bring up a question.
Today, according to the Muppet World, Muppets and Puppets, it's July 16th, 2016.
Okay.
And it's what they call a Saturday.
Now, let's go back to what they call 2015 on Muppetdom.
And July 16th was on what's called a Thursday.
Okay.
Now, let's go to the Muppet year of 2017.
No offense to Muppets, by the way.
And let's see what they call July 2017.
The 16th is on what they call a Sunday.
All right, folks.
Let's just be reasonable.
No, no, no.
Actually, it's a lot.
Let's be semi-reasonable.
Just a little bit, incy-wincy, teeny bit reasonable, please, with sugar on top.
Just be a little rational, please, just for a minute.
By the wind-up toy known as the clock.
Let me ask you, is July 16th a Thursday, a Saturday, or a Sunday?
Nobody got an answer.
You know why?
Because there is no answer.
It's what you are told.
Anyone's old enough, you remember when the new year came around,
according to the Pope's work schedule,
we got to go to the harvester and get a free calendar,
or the card shop and get a calendar so we know what day it is.
Yep.
And you know what, Seth?
No one, and I mean no one, is talking about this at all.
It seems to escape everyone.
Obvious.
Now, why is it obvious?
Well, I just showed you why it's obvious.
Just five minutes' worth of research, if you could call it that,
which research means to search again.
So, you know, first of all,
most of the people today are so numbed and dumbed down that they'll tell you
time doesn't exist, it doesn't matter, that's fine.
That's why there are plastic brooms and reflective vests
and toilet brushes and things like that.
And, you know, there's lots of work that needs to be done to maintain stuff.
You should be doing it.
But those people that want to understand the structure of how things work,
not just by description or explanation,
need to realize that there is something called lawfulness and unlawfulness.
So this is just one example.
Just like the money system, many people talk about the money system,
but do you endorse it, right?
What does that mean?
I had someone ask me, what do you mean by endorse it?
And it's like, you've got to shake your head, you know.
So what's uncommon is the obvious.
The last thing for mankind to discover is what's obvious.
So how obvious can it be?
And what is the obvious?
Hey, what do you think, Seth, should we bring up what obvious means?
What is that, etymology online, that's the easiest one.
I'm not really happy at those folks, by the way.
But they do a good enough job, I think.
Like a lot of the Internet, it only has what it has.
Church is an interesting one to look up on etymonline as well.
Maybe we can get into that.
I did a little bit of that earlier this week.
But obvious, adjective, 1580s, frequently met with from Latin, obvious,
that is in the way, presenting itself readily, open, exposed, commonplace.
From obvium, adjective, in the way, from ob, which is against,
and vium, accusative, via, which is way.
So meaning plain to see.
Yeah, first reported in the 1630s.
Okay, so what's been memorialized as what that word means is not far,
I mean, the way we're using it is pretty accurate, I'd say.
It's not like the word average.
Have you heard of it?
It's just an average joke.
It's just average.
People think it's just like a median thing or something.
Actually, average means damaged, which, again, damaged merchandise or goods.
So in many cases, upon more critical, slightly more critical observation,
you would find that to be true.
By the way, when things come up during the week or so,
more than a couple of times I do mention them on the show.
And I've heard this, this is the third time I've seen and heard this saying,
and I've got to tell you, it kind of rubs one the wrong way.
And it's something about the only wisdom there is,
is that one knows that they cannot know anything.
Now, if that is not a prankster's motto, I don't know what is.
And that's all I'm going to say about that.
But I think that you just watch what people say
and what they adhere to without thinking at all, at all.
And I mean zero thought at all into what's being said or done.
Again, paraphrasing, it says the only true wisdom there is,
is to know that one cannot know.
Now, Seth, you and I have done a little bit of discussion
and research on what was memorialized before us, and it's all about knowing.
And we've also discussed or myself brought forward the concept of the pranking.
So if that's not a prank, I don't know what is.
Now, is it solipsism, where people say it doesn't matter, it doesn't exist,
it's only in your mind?
Again, there's lots of jobs and tasks.
There's highway medians that need to be swept.
There's windows that need to be washed.
There are farms that need weeds pulled.
There are bodies, vertical bodies with able hands, billions of them.
We're not talking to you.
We're not talking about what these people think.
We're discussing about what can be said, what should be said,
to a rational thinking, rationally acting member of this planet.
Or I hate to say member of this society.
You don't want to be a car – what is it?
The reason you don't want to be a member, perhaps,
is I wouldn't want to be a member of any club that would accept me as a member.
But you guys get the point.
No one is paying any attention.
We've given many examples on how no one is paying any attention,
neither do they want to.
Now, what is one to do?
Absolutely nothing.
But should one speak about it?
Absolutely.
I think it should be said.
Again, I think that doing a quote-unquote radio show
on a minor Internet radio station for four or five listeners is a bit overdone.
But nonetheless, we're here, and there are many things to be presented.
But, again, just to preface on what I mentioned earlier,
making each episode sort of topical in nature and to edify individuals
and then looking at the individuals and the mindset that they are engaging in,
the contrast is so great that just basically showing up here with Seth once a week
and trying to get the cobwebs out, just kind of shake people up.
There was a scene in a film called Moonstruck with Nicolas Cage and Cher.
It's a short scene, and he's going on and on about being manic-depressive or something,
and she just walks up to him and slaps him in a New York accent and says,
Snap out of it!
So we could slap people around for two hours a week and get you to just snap out of it, folks.
Snap out of it.
Pay attention.
I know it takes a little bit of work, but just like going to a gym,
you don't expect to go to the gym for the first time
and be in the Mr. Universe context by evening, do you?
Right?
So it takes a lot of work.
So maybe if we can get people sore between the ears here, Seth,
what do you think about that concept?
Are you sore between the ears yet?
That's a question for the listener.
Well, if you're not sore now, you're going to be later.
So how does one know?
What is knowing?
Knowledge?
Well, that's interesting.
There are several other words in other languages that we are used to when we bring up the definition,
and it's a functional thing, just like fear and love is functional.
You have to learn it.
Can you discern it?
In other words, can you know a lie or do you believe a lie?
If you know a lie is a lie, is that the truth?
Yes, it is, right?
So it's functional.
It's a functional characteristic to it.
Knowledge is something that we could look it up.
Shouldn't we do that?
What does the word knowledge mean and where it comes from?
Actually, I'll do that.
Let's bring it up.
Should we just look up know?
What do you think?
Because there's a lot.
There's gnosis, right?
We're speaking in English.
That's the other thing, folks.
When we're discussing things that have been memorialized in the past,
if we go back far enough, there was no English.
And I like to, if I use a word from another language,
I like to always discuss it in the language, Langua Franca, that we're speaking in,
so people don't brand you as being part of some strange group or something.
There's lots of strange groups I like to use,
especially Hebraic terms and stuff like that when they greet each other and things like that.
And I don't believe in switching languages.
I mean, kind of like stereotyping is brought in when you do that.
So I want to stick, when we bring up something memorialized,
jump around and discuss it in the language that we're speaking in.
But here, knowledge.
Oh, boy.
Gnosis.
Acknowledgement of a superior honor worship.
For first element, see no.
The second element is obscure, perhaps from Scandinavian.
Okay.
So to know, let's go to know the first element.
Oh, inside information in the know.
Okay.
Oh, that's the noun.
Verb.
It's a verb here.
Boy, there's quite a bit of it.
To perceive a thing.
I'm going to perceive a thing to be identical with another.
Also be able to distinguish, perceive or understand as a fact or truth.
Fact or truth.
Okay.
That's, you know, because fact or truth.
By the way, facts can, right, or truth are not the same.
Know how.
Okay.
Proto-dramatic, knew.
To know.
Okay.
Oh, boy.
Boy, do they get into it.
To have sexual intercourse with.
Well, that's what's in the King James, Old Testament kind of stuff.
When someone knew someone else, they're presuming that.
Okay.
To know.
I like the bottom one.
Know nothing.
Ignoramus.
That's the one that tells you that wisdom now is being an ignoramus, right,
because there's a saying that's come up that wisdom is to know that you cannot
know or you know nothing.
So wisdom equals ignoramus.
That's like war equals peace and ignorance is education and very Orwellian in that sense.
So snap out of it, folks.
Snap out of it.
Get the cobwebs out.
You know, get into the leg press or get on the treadmill and, you know,
it is a dummy load, but work the body, man, work that body, mind, body at least.
Pay attention, folks.
Snap out of it.
So what do you think, Seth?
How would you sum up know?
I mean, do you want to read all five paragraphs?
I don't.
Basically, it's kind of self-descriptive,
but it's not giving us too many outside references to itself.
But there's a term that's bandied around called gnosis, right?
And there is no knowledge in the gnosis.
Anyway, people that use that term,
I've studied their work since their groups and, folks, there's nothing there.
It's kind of like going to a bank, you know.
Here's one that is relative, I think, to the conversation of anything else.
Latin, seer, S-C-I-R-E, to understand, perceive,
it's the same basis, science, science, and nations.
Cognizeer, you know, to know, to recognize.
So Latin, know would be seer.
So that's pretty basic.
I would say that it's to comprehend, not to understand, and implying agreement.
Whereas comprehension is more to know, you know.
But like most English, it's a little bit obfuscated.
And the way that we use it colloquially can mean a number of different things.
Have you ever heard someone say, you know,
reference it in the biblical form as in intercourse, Adam, his wife.
Check your audio, Seth.
Okay.
Yeah, another Chaldean Hebrew is it would be, I believe, da'at or ayada, yada.
And also those letters mean things, and you'll see that the aleph is in there, the first letter.
And in one of them it's doubled.
So what is knowledge?
Okay.
Do you have knowledge of something as being there?
You know, for example, first have knowledge.
But then if a person can't describe what they've seen, what good is that?
I think when you discuss knowledge, there has to be a level of discussion within the word.
Is it knowledge that can be communicated?
Is it knowledge that cannot be communicated?
I've read in places, written in the past,
that people had seen and known things that they could not speak.
You see?
Again, that's why I mentioned earlier, it's one of these functional terms.
It's how are you functioning with the term.
Just to kind of loosen things up, we've discussed using the media as an example, but we have to,
because this is where people go, basically.
They're sort of here now.
Things that are thrown in front of people by those with microphones
and those that hear them with speakers on the other side, oh, that's fear porn, or that's fear,
or you've got to love and all that.
Again, those words like fear and love, those are things that do not come naturally
and are not comprehended naturally.
In other words, when I mean naturally, it's like when you see an animal being born in nature,
they're pretty much ready, most of them, especially the four-legged ones,
are pretty much ready to go within a few hours, and they have a preloaded operating system.
You see, mankind doesn't have any of that.
And at this point, knocking around terms like fear and love and knowledge,
without understanding the function and understanding what they're really set up to communicate is for naught,
and it just becomes anything else that you hear going on.
It's just a description, something that evokes a feeling, but there's no substance,
and there's no communication.
Here's something, here's a way to put it up that I've never put it before.
Most of the stuff you folks hear is not worth memorializing.
Think about that for a moment.
Most of the stuff you listen to is not worth memorializing.
What does that mean?
Something that you record so you can go back later and read it or listen to it again.
Unless you missed it, and then if you missed it and you pick it up on a memorialized event,
you're like, oh, I just wasted two hours, or it made me feel a certain way.
You get a lot of feeling touching yourself, too.
But anyway, functional, like love, for example.
You have to learn how to love.
Love is not what you think it is, folks.
Fear, fear are things that are based on one's strength of mind or spirit and their skill level.
The example I give with fear is that if you don't know how to operate a dishrag or a mop,
you're a lot of fear of a glass of milk spills over,
but if a glass of milk spills over and the person next to you knows how to operate a dishrag and a mop,
then you say, don't cry over spilled milk.
It's no big deal.
Look, I know how to operate a dishrag.
I can fix it.
So all this stuff about fear that you guys talk about, you know, and it's just like, yeah, yeah, fear.
Yeah, I said fear.
Fear what?
What are you talking about?
Get the cobwebs out.
Pay attention.
What's being said?
Now, most people don't care to know what words mean and don't care about how they use them,
as long as everybody and their friends and everybody around them thinks they know what they mean
or get some kind of a point across them.
What's the point?
There's no point.
You're just taking up time.
Stop taking up time.
Make the best use of what you've got.
So with that said, anything else about paying attention, Seth?
Maybe like what else is obvious that people can discover?
Well, I'd say that a lot of what we discuss is relatively obvious in any way that you'd like to take that word
colloquially or directly from the words that it's built from, ob and vm, you know,
because it's definitely in the way or against the way, ob being against and, you know, vm being the way.
This is definitely against what is perceived as being the way currently.
It's, I don't know, water, water, food, shelter.
Those things are all important.
Yes.
And, of course, people have lost sight of that as well and have accepted with apathy what there is.
You know, here, let's say we're visiting the planet.
We need to be objective.
We can't go back to the starship and tell the captain we really like, you know, strawberries.
He doesn't want to hear that.
He doesn't want to hear what we like.
He wants to hear about how things appear and what is going on objectively.
What's interesting is if you go to, this is regarding food, by the way, if you go through certain places,
especially the most active concentrated life force places would be like the rainforest, right, very dense.
If you went through the rainforest, you'd notice that the most colorful little creatures and things tend to be poisonous.
And what's interesting, then you go into man society where most of the civilized, quote-unquote, world gets their food.
You'll notice that in certain places where they have food on shelving, they're much more colorful than the others.
And you'll find that that is mostly the food that is promoted for the children, very, very colorful packaging.
And if you look at the ingredients, you will also discover it is also the most toxic.
Think about that, folks, how things run in parallel and no one is paying any attention.
So just a little commentary.
I think we've also discussed in commentary what would an ancient perhaps or presumably observe
and how we would react in this society today.
And I've always said it wouldn't be any big deal.
Most of the things that get over in about 15 minutes, a couple of days for a few other things,
and they would be probably in horror other ways.
So pay attention, folks.
What is really going on?
What is really in front of you?
And if you think that nothing matters, well, that's fine, too, because you're not thinking.
So there's a shake the cobwebs out.
I think coming here for 16 weeks, roughly, or I think a couple episodes were down, but they're on Ustream,
so it's roughly around the 16th time we've come around.
It's too bad we've got to come around and just kind of like shake people around.
Between the years, there's a lot to discuss.
And what will be discussed in the future, by the way, by the Greek and perhaps Seth and others,
well, let's just say Seth and the Greek, will be things more topical in nature.
But you're going to have to approach them with a very, very, very, very, very, very, very clear mind.
I want to bring up a comment, Seth.
We've talked quite a bit about dreams and talk about being topical or not being topical.
Well, we've gotten over that pretty much, pretty well, I would say.
I noticed a comment back two weeks ago, I believe, where someone was – this is not to put the individual in the corner,
but sometimes you have to.
The individual says, I'm tired of this, all this poo-pooing of dreams.
You know, Pharaoh and Joseph in the biblical text, dreams are very important.
There's an example of someone who's not listening.
They're hearing that we're discussing dreams and they're hearing certain things,
but the way they strung it together in their mind is not what we were saying.
I can just apologize or defend, say we've never poo-pooed dreams.
We're actually giving the origin of it.
Now, very often when you have a high level of misdemeanor or criminality, harsh language is required.
So maybe we were kind of harsh about bringing up that you're being plugged by lower level entities.
Yes.
The reason why it's safe to address the general public as such is because most of the general public is not Pharaoh.
Most of the general public is not in a high position.
And most of the general public is not in the position that Joseph was, as you say.
We're not poo-pooing dreams.
We're simply giving the origin.
And why the harsh language is necessary occasionally is because wherever you go, high and low,
and you will find the information to be not only inaccurate but untrue and so far removed from anything that's been memorialized.
Now, I've noticed there has been a very big trend in the past decade or so to reinvent everything and not look at anything that's come before.
So we've all been, I guess, created about 100 years ago and everything before that doesn't matter.
So we're kind of putting things together in a way where it might sound a little bit harsh because the level of stupidity that's out there is unusually profound.
If you want to know what it is, well, it's everything before everything that comes on after.
So here's the point, folks.
Learn to discern what you're hearing.
And also, Seth, I believe that we do bring up a lot of prefacing.
We do tend to preface things quite thoroughly before we discuss them and when we discuss them to the level of it can be done with the mindset that can be perceived in public.
I guess most might be semi-public.
This is not terrestrial radio.
But nonetheless, there are many, many things that will be discussed.
Just to tie it back into what we started with earlier in the future, matters of how the human body works and what you can do about it.
I want to throw in a little testimonial, Seth.
We've discussed things about the human body at some extent.
Recently, a few weeks ago, someone was wearing short pants and sandals and they got caught in the middle of a catfight.
And I don't mean the kind of catfight you hear about in biker bars and things like that.
I'm talking about a real catfight, you know, like a little furry creature.
Pussies, okay?
And the person got equal amount of claw tearing on the left of the left leg and on the right of the right leg.
And they were very adamant about telling me about this and showing me a week later the injury.
What they said to me was, look at this leg.
It's really scratched up and red.
Now look at the other leg.
You see nothing, absolutely nothing but clear skin.
And I said, well, why are you showing me this?
Well, they said that both legs had the same amount of injury.
The one that you still see the scratches on is the conventional way of treating it.
And on the right was the way that you describe on how to treat a wound.
And there was not one mark on the body whatsoever.
So these things will be discussed very, very simply.
I've been in a situation, for example, where I was holding a piece of plastic in the hand and the drill bit slipped.
The drill slipped and drilled into the hand.
Yes, kind of funny to do that, kind of like the cartoons.
You don't feel much while it's happening, but it sure hurts later.
I have a medical person, a doctor acquaintance, and a week later we met up and I told him about the situation,
showed him the hand, and there was nothing visible.
And the doctor said, funny that, that same day I was working in the garden.
And I caught myself and went to the hospital and got stitches, and they showed me the scar.
Very, very, very, very visible.
These are the things we'll discuss, folks, things that you can do, practical.
I'm not going to talk about politics, all the stupid stuff that you hear everywhere,
like what's going on with taxpayer dollars, because there are no dollars and there are no taxpayers.
I'm being pranked.
I'm not going to talk about Planet X or past lives or if you came from beta reticuli or purple enema juice
or all the stuff that you hear about underwater basket weaving and advanced nose picking
that will never, ever, ever, ever come from Greek and Seth.
So many, many other things will be discussed.
One of the things we might discuss is weather.
Mark Twain said that everyone's always talking about the weather.
When is somebody going to do something about it?
I remember once being in a place called Houston, Texas, and near the highway you'll see these international symbols,
and it was basically a white background with a blue dot and two curved arcs around it.
I guess it's the international symbol for a hurricane.
And I asked the people, I said, what is that?
He says, well, that's a hurricane, and the arrow means get on the highway and leave.
And I'm like, so, okay, so when you have a bad storm coming, you mean you all just get on the highway and leave, right?
That's what you do?
Did you ever try like laying down and putting brown paper bags over your head?
Maybe that works as well.
So we're going to discuss things about that.
The galaxy.
Yeah.
We put brown paper bags over our heads?
The Earth will be destroyed in 15 minutes.
Will it help if we lay down and put brown paper bags over our heads, right?
It's great.
They show them doing that anyway.
So if you have the urge to put a brown paper bag over your head, don't even bother, right?
We're going to talk about how to do food preparation, and we're going to talk about water preparation.
And what is water?
Because when you really discover what something is, you tend to not think of it the same way anymore, right?
And when you discover how things really work and what they are based on your own observation and rational thought that can be communicated and memorialized,
not all the tripe that you hear and are taught.
You will feel cheated, by the way, right, in many cases, right?
If you still think the word nice means something pleasant and you're a rational individual, if you look up what that word means,
you might feel slightly cheated, like no one ever told you, and you were made a fool of by using it,
but no one really thought of you as a fool for saying the word nice meaning something pleasant, because guess what?
You're all surrounded by fools anyway, so there's no contrast.
So if you're ready for a contrast, and you're ready to bridge into the realm of explanation,
you might want to stay in touch and keep tuning into Seth, Michael, and the Greek.
We'll also discuss things about machines.
No pun intended, Seth.
You work as a machinist.
I mean, I don't know how much of spinning metal at super high speed with razor sharp carbide tool bits will help people, but nonetheless.
It gives one a comprehension of precision at a very small level, very minute,
and how precision and just being able to apply those same concepts into communication adds, I don't know,
at least an idea of what being accurate is.
Like you said, a lot of preface goes before what is said.
We don't know if someone actually has a Bridgeport vertical mill in their living room or a hard edge lathe.
You never know.
Yeah.
I mean, look, I've seen people that are really into cars, car engines,
and when the engine is being worked on, it's on one of these engine dollies, and guess where?
They wanted to show me the motor.
Guess where they took me to show me the motor?
The living room right next to the coffee table.
So, yeah, you never, ever know.
But we will talk about machines and cars.
Yes, how cars work, how they really, really, really work, folks.
Yep.
And all those people in Detroit and wherever that design cars, they don't know how the engines work.
They're only there to design a certain part and move along.
How do I know this?
Because I've had discussions with them.
They don't know what's going on.
Just like people and your leaders in religion don't know anything about the books that they're supposedly based on at all.
Nothing.
Just like doctors don't know anything about the body.
Well, this is one thing they do know, speaking to dentists and other people in various medical fields.
If you push the issue on what could be done or should be done to the body, on a side note,
they are very forthright to tell you, well, the body will heal it.
Well, the body will heal it.
Right?
Okay.
So where's your research on that?
And how does it heal?
Yes, I know the description.
You know, it's funny.
If you ever bring an animal or someone to the doctor, you call up and you say why you want to visit, let's say,
a sprained ankle or an eye infection or whatever.
And upon presentation, the doctor looks at it and he's like, oh, you have a sprained ankle.
You're like, duh.
We told you that before we got here.
Because all they can do is describe things.
I've seen recently an animal being brought to the vet.
Told them the dog had an eye infection.
And this is, let's look at the animal, the dog.
And first thing the vet said all startled, oh, it has an eye infection.
Yeah.
Told you that.
But why?
They don't know.
Right.
They're just there to describe things, folks.
Give a little bit more than that.
Pneumonia is a good one.
You have pneumonia.
Hmm.
Yeah, you have.
Oh, yeah.
Told you that.
Yeah.
You have pneumonia.
What is it?
I don't know, man.
Yeah, it's just a painkillers, antibiotics.
Yeah.
Where'd you get your medical degree?
Huh?
Okay, folks.
We'll talk about going back to the cars.
Got stunned on that for a moment because it's so bizarre that how they really work
and what you can do about it if you're handy or if you have someone that's handy.
You'll be amazed what you can do with an automobile, just reworking what's there.
Yep.
Don't want you to know that.
Yeah.
just a reminder that I don't encourage people to just stop working and stop just hearing things
and repeating things unless you've got lots of carbon paper around.
So if you're tired of just listening to descriptions, you might want to stay in touch.
You notice we didn't bring up the dummy load and all the other stuff that prevails in society
and the pranking too much.
By the way, pranking, yeah we talk about the pranksters, you know who you are, but you
know what?
If you want to know who the first people that pranked you were in life, it's your parents,
folks.
Yep, sorry.
Not making it up.
So what kind of a start have you had?
Think about it.
Tooth Fairy, Santa Claus, Gregorian calendar, you got to go to school, I know you're not
going to learn anything, but I did it, so you got to do it too, yeah.
And all the motivated through penalty.
If you don't get a degree, you're not going to get a good job.
Oh, hey mommy, why do I need a driver's license?
Oh, because if you don't get a driver's license, you're going to go to jail.
It's your parents talking, folks.
Not all of them, but most of them.
Every culture, doesn't matter what culture you're in.
What kind of a footing is that?
So parents, be kind to children, because they are your kind, right?
That emotional crap, by the way, when you talk about your children, doesn't work.
People that are rational.
Oh, I love my children, I really do.
Yeah, right.
Can you please write that down and sign it?
That's as an IOU.
I responded to a post that an acquaintance had made in an internet forum recently.
It's not something I do often, but he was talking about current events in general, or
at least what the media provides as being those current events, and said, what's wrong
with, what did he say, peace, love, and understanding?
And I just took it like it was a question.
And so I answered it like it was a question.
I said, well, peace is stagnation, love is not comprehended, and understanding implies
agreement.
Those are, that's what's wrong with those three things.
So.
Very good.
Careful what you ask for, folks, especially when you're talking or writing the Seth and
the Greek.
Uh-huh.
Everyone, everyone attains peace, at least for a little while.
Or a long while.
Yeah, or a long while.
It's referred to as death.
Some cultures refer to it as hell or the grave.
Or sleep.
Yeah, sleep, rest.
Greek.
Right?
Yep.
In Greek, to chemise, chemise is the prefix for sleep, and tideo is a place of, a cemetery
in Greek is chemitidio.
It's a place where you go to sleep.
Chemitidio could also mean like factory or a place that purveys a certain thing specifically.
So the word cemetery in Greek, or chemitidio, it's almost taken from Greek, means a place
where you go to specifically sleep.
And you got 7 billion people trying to search for what happens after you die, and a percentage
of society pranking them with all kinds of bull about going places.
So anyway, yeah.
And he lived 70 years, and then he slept with his fathers.
Uh-huh.
And every culture tells you you sleep, but yeah, yeah.
But people, you know, it's funny, once I was on a public forum speaking, and after the thing
ended, a whole bunch of people ganged up on me and said, how dare you say there's no
such thing as reincarnation and being reincarnated.
All of the Asian people, they believe in it.
That means it's true.
I'm like, they've been pranked just like you have.
It's funny how the Westerners, I mean, it's pretty obvious that they've been pranked to
the hilt with Santa Claus and Easter Bunny and all that other stuff.
And I don't know, what's the groundhog and all the other gods that they have.
And they're running over to the East, Asian religions.
And boy, oh boy, this is one thing that I prefaced in private and I have said in public.
In the future, when knowledge is spread and things are acknowledged, the Western world,
Western man tends to take things in stride to a point where they're reasonable.
But in the Asian cultures, they get really upset, folks.
Like, give an example.
Like, you know how there's an issue with police here killing people now in the news,
which is total crap.
So what if they kill 1,000 people a year in cold blood?
The doctors kill 3,000 a day.
The police kill 3,000 a day.
At least half of that in cold blood.
I've been around them.
I've heard them talk about it.
It doesn't matter.
We have another one.
So you've got over a million being killed by doctors and no one's paying any attention.
So forget about the police.
Irrelevant.
But if you have police brutality in Asia, they don't go to the public square and protest
like the morons in the West do.
They know where the cop lives and they drag him out of his bed while he's sleeping
and club him to death.
This is how the Asians roll, folks.
Not all of them, but it is common.
In the future, when it's discovered, more than discovered and known,
that all the stuff that you've been taught in Asia by these little monks
that everyone thinks is, oh, so enlightened,
those guys are going to be facing a level of, let's just say, let's not say,
that you have never heard of.
They're going to skin these guys alive.
All you little monks think you're so spiritual.
Their own people are going to do this to them.
In the West, what will happen is your average minister, preacher, whatever, whatever, priest,
will just deny ever being in that field.
He'll just deny it, and people will approach probably and say,
hey, I saw you wearing the uniform or the clothes.
No, no, that wasn't me.
I worked in this profession, you see.
They'll just lie about it and get away from it.
Where in the East, it's really going to be a lot of carnage because of you.
Yeah, so anyway, this is going to be interesting.
I just have one of those faces.
That wasn't me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So this is not too far away, folks, about a decade or so.
And by the way, maybe on the second hour, we're going to recap what we've always been talking about,
which is the coming Middle East Union and what leads up to such a thing.
And something going on in the news actually over there.
Yeah, it's not yet.
Yeah, there is.
Yeah, it's just we'll preface it.
How can you have a union, not necessarily formal or informal, just a union?
Now, when I say union, how do you want to think about it?
Let's just say a loose confederacy of nations.
How can you have that when the alleged grouping of a group, let's say, is very nationalistic
and at odds with each other based on proximity or borders or policy?
Let's give Europe for an example.
How can you have a European Union if France is at war with Germany, Germany is at war with Greece,
Greece is at war with Italy, England is at war with Germany?
How are you going to have a union when you have highly nationalistic governments?
How can you do that?
You can't.
So all the teeth have to be pulled out.
Right.
So they can't bite each other.
So they all kind of go in the same pen together.
But this is going to be very, very different, folks.
And when it comes, when it comes, it'll be wholly accepted because you're being primed for it.
And you don't know it because it's obvious.
It's been memorialized for thousands of years.
It's rational.
For example, grandma used to say, all things go around, come around.
Right.
So we'll talk a little bit more about that perhaps in the next hour.
It's a good place to kind of maybe pick up a different topic or not.
But what you're witnessing and have been witnessing, by the way, this is a preface to what's coming as the Middle East Union,
won't be called the Middle East Union as such, but it will act as one.
What you're witnessing is a lot of fires to kind of tear things down there and keep tension going until the timing is right.
This is divine stuff, folks.
It has to do with the gods.
Yes.
We're not talking about Santa Claus now or all the other things you folks worship.
So we're talking about another society that controls this one.
And the rains will come in the next beginning, in the next few years.
They're going to put out all these fires there.
It's a metaphor.
And you're going to see roughly ten nations, which only nine exist at the moment, working together.
And that ninth nation, we've described where it will be.
We'll talk about it more in depth in the next hour.
We'll also maybe talk about what else to watch for.
And maybe a little bit about the Great Deception, which you're all going to fall for.
I can say that pretty accurately, all of you, except for a very, very, very, very small group.
Why?
Why can one say that most people will fall for the Great Deception?
Because the Great Deception is based around, say it, Seth, peace, love, and understanding.
Peace, love, and understanding.
Yes, and when you get that, you will be told that this is how it's going to be from here on in,
and you're going to believe it, because why shouldn't you?
It's self-evident.
You see it.
It's manifesting.
And when the glitches come in, we'll talk about it on the next hour, perhaps,
how horrible it's going to be on this planet, not only for the people, but for the bees, the whales,
the tigers, the caterpillars, the dogs, the cats, the squirrels, and the fish,
and everything that's alive, for several reasons.
That we will not get into detail how it will be and why it will be so difficult.
But we might in the future, let's just say semi-privately, perhaps.
Because, by the way, this kind of information is only going to be viable to be discussed publicly
for the next couple of years.
There's going to be a major change in public thought and the way things are transmitted, ideas,
starting in roughly the spring, summer, fall of 2018, that year,
roughly what you call on the Muppet schedule, 2018.
And no one's ever noticing what happened all the years before that.
And, by the way, if you start pulling that Anno Domini crap and the Year of Our Lord crap,
I don't know what you're talking about, because if it's supposed to be based on the biblical text,
it wasn't born on the year zero.
It's very specific, the biblical text.
I know most of you want to pull the hair out of your head and set yourself on fire
and start chanting to yourself, just an opinion, just an opinion, just an opinion,
like an attorney does.
But when the biblical Christ was born, it can be down to about ten minutes.
But how many people care to look into that?
If you said none, that's pretty accurate.
So, anyway, there's many, many levels to this.
And if you're, like I used to tell young children, if you're not disgusted with humanity,
you're not paying attention.
So learn to pay attention, and you'll get over being disgusted,
and you'll learn how to function in it.
And the best way to function is to set yourself apart.
So, with that said, we have a few more minutes before this hour is wrapped up.
And I think what we wanted to do is sum up why we've been showing up here.
Perhaps get the cobwebs out of your head.
And the intent was to discuss many, many things, but have not been,
because of just the sheer profound laziness, dumbness, and numbness that I see in society.
And that doesn't mean that it won't be discussed in the future.
We're going to talk about, what is it, planes, trains, automobiles, the human body,
and we're going to talk about, what is it, technology, food, history, things to come.
All these things will be discussed in the future over time.
But I think what we've done here so far is, for two hours a week, folks,
you can have the cobwebs wiped out of the head if you're listening.
Now, if you're hearing things, well, that's, I don't know what to tell you.
If you hear things, leave some music on in the background.
It might distract other things that might be taunting you.
But if you're hearing things, I've got nothing for you.
We're speaking for people who know how to listen and want to know what things mean
and are looking for explanations because they're tired of descriptions.
What do you think about that so far, Seth, for the first hour here?
I think it's a good preface.
Yeah, I think so.
It's warm here. I'm having quite a bit of a cool drink.
And if you guys hear that.
So here we go, the first hour, and we're coming up on the second hour.
We might get into a little geopolitics of where the human mind is going to be going as well.
So stay tuned, folks. We'll see you soon.
Hello and welcome back to Uncommon Sense here on American Freedom Radio and AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
My name is Seth.
That's the sound that I respond to most readily.
And the Greek will be with us momentarily as well.
I would like to remind everyone that American Freedom Radio does appreciate your support.
If you enjoy hearing this program, if nothing else, you can go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and donate.
They make it very simple, very easy to do.
Just follow the links through there.
You can find Uncommon Sense on the Internet at UncommonRadio.com, www.UncommonRadio.com.
It's basically just a calling card.
You can find an email address to get into contact with the Greek and myself,
as well as where to hear the broadcasts and previous broadcasts as well.
There's also a blog spot that someone put together.
Thanklessly or thankfully they did.
It just shows you that someone is listening and feels that they want to put some of their time towards what's being said because it's important,
not because it's being said by us.
And that is JustGreekSpeak at BlogSpot.com, I think.
I think the link was posted in chat, but we'll probably post that on the Uncommon Radio.
And there's also a site, there's also a YouTube channel.
I don't know how well that's going to do.
I'm not a big fan of that.
Because sometimes we do use quote-unquote copyrighted material even though we give credit.
There will probably be an iTunes and other ways.
There will also be a way to do semi-public, semi-private, however you want to do it,
discussions on serious topics that can help people,
not about some planet or you came from some other universe or you're going to be reincarnated as a butterfly
and all this other tripe and garbage that you hear.
And it's going to be real stuff that you will prove to yourself that these things work regarding weather,
regarding automobiles, regarding food, regarding the human body, regarding past, present and future events,
regarding the mind, regarding love, fear, knowledge.
All these things will be discussed in great detail in a semi-public, semi-private forum yet to be established.
Don't know how, don't know where, don't know whatever.
But we know why, because it's not being said and it's just sad, folks.
Just really, really sad, the condition that humanity is in.
You're going to be known as the society that had everything
and not only threw everything away but ignored everything.
And just to reiterate, I can't believe people are actually writing,
the wisdom there is to know that you can't know.
Now if that is not a prank for a bunch of morons, I don't know what is.
Stop being pranked. Learn how to recognize the prank.
Learn how to recognize you're being mocked.
And learn how to recognize that you're being overfilled with descriptions lacking any explanation.
And all those explanations can be provided by just, yeah, you guessed it, searching for what is obvious.
Just like, for example, when you heat or cool a room indoors,
you notice how the heat goes to the ceiling and the cold goes to the floor?
So you have a hot head and cold feet all year round indoors?
And you have a cold head and cold feet all year round outdoors?
But this is a secret, folks.
The reason why it's a secret is we're saying it publicly.
If I say it, promise not to tell anyone, that when it's hot in the valley,
it's cool up at the mountaintop.
And if you get in a plane or something and go towards the sun,
which is allegedly a heat source, it gets colder and colder.
Because in all natural living biological systems,
you have an ascending, rarefying cold, and a descending, densifying heat. That's why
if you call a medical person and say I'm not feeling well, they ask you why. Well,
you tell them my head is hot and my feet are cold. Well, you're not feeling well, they
agree. Well, wait a second here, it doesn't sound right because heat's supposed to
rise and cold's supposed to go down. By the way, you bring up this discrepancy
between a rising cold and descending heat in biological systems to someone
who's gone through thorough quacademic or academic pranking, you watch their
eyes roll back in their head like a slot machine because A, they're going to try
to describe, not explain, and then B, they will never ever ever ever ever ever ever
admit that they've been cheated and frauded by the quote-unquote system that
they have allegiance to. Just like most people can never ever ever ever admit
that they've been pranked by their parents. Sorry folks, you're a sick
society. Sick minds, as in psycho meaning mind and pathos meaning pain or sickness,
psychopathic society. Get over it. Don't have to be that way. Now, you're not going
to change it. Anybody, by the way, who says they're going to change the world or has
an idea or group to make things better is an idiot, a moron, and to be avoided
because it ain't going to happen. Everything's in a preset path at this
point and there is nothing you're going to do to change it. What is being
discussed or at least the conversations that I overhear or that I see pieces of,
there's, you know, the fact that it is sick, you know, all of society is readily
apparent and but what is what is going on is everyone is picking the symptom
of that sickness that they dislike to be vocal about and saying that something
needs to be done about this symptom of this sickness and the actual, you know,
the root causes are completely and totally ignored. They're not even, the
they're not debated. They're just completely and totally ignored. Speak to
an older person, folks, anyone over 50 about any of the things that you might
have heard or listened to here. You know what they tell you? Generally, 99%. Well,
you know, I kind of bought into these paradigms, too, you know. I mean, what are
you going to do? This is just how it is, you know. I'll tell you what you're going
to do, you old fool. You'll learn how to set yourself apart and start giving some
good information to the younger folks. You younger folks, by the way, are screwed.
Avoid older people. Been reduced to morons. You're gonna have to go back. You're
gonna have to learn how to seek information. But anyway, and speaking of
information, that's something that's been communicated, right? I mean, we could say,
I mean, information, if you discover it firsthand, you might communicate it to
someone else. Otherwise, it's just something that's inside someone's pea
brain. So when you say the word information, it's how things are being
communicated. So watch how things are being communicated. And one thing that
we've said before is that the real stuff is never happening where all the noise is.
The noise tends to be a distraction. And what I mean by that is the noise, when
you comprehend and understand and see that it's noisy, let's say over here or
over there, and it's by design, there's a structure behind it, whether it's
mainstream or alternative media or print or what people are gossiping or
talking about or getting emotional about is a distraction. It's they want you to
look there because where it's really going on is where it's quiet, right?
You could look at, just look at everything pretty much. You know, for
example, a lot of people think that they're doing well with the alternative
media. The alternative media is just piggybacking on what the mainstream
provides them. You know, basically the mainstream goes up.
N-I-C-H-E. Niche. That's what it is. It's just a niche of the mainstream currently.
It's not providing different information. It's just commenting on the
information that is provided. Now there could have been a good alternative
media. There could have been, if a wormhole opened up and some people from
another planet, let's say, came through every morning and left, you know, went
back home at night, and those people from another, people coming from, let's
say, a wormhole from another place were doing alternative media, I think you
would have something worth listening to, folks. But otherwise, just, yeah, okay, I
will get off the alternative media. So because this is an anomaly,
uncommon sense is neither mainstream nor alternative nor it's none of that. It's
an anomaly. It's like as if it's not happening. It's like you can't, I can't
believe what these guys are saying. Yes, if you're listening, you will find
there's lots of stuff to believe in because it's either stuff that's
happened or stuff that will happen. So, you know, kind of discussing again, what
is the explanation of these things? Can we jump into what we said we'd be
talking about on the second hour, which is the coming Middle East Union? What do
you think, Seth? Yes, let's. Yeah, I want to bring up something here, folks. I want to
show you how no one's paying any attention. I mean, no one. There's this
meme, this thing going on called terrorism, right? It's all terrorism these
days. Now, hold on for a second. These are acts of violence, let's say. Now, it
doesn't matter if they're staged or false flags. We know that they are.
Most of them are because there's an agenda and the agenda is beyond what
mankind can control at this point. But just think about it. These acts of
violence, think about this for a moment. If you've ever watched any of the
Warner Brothers, I think it was Warner Brothers, Bugs Bunny. Remember if you did
something to Bugs Bunny that he didn't like? He said, this means war. Remember
that? You take out a white glove and smack Elmer Fudd or whatever. He said, this means
war. Okay, so yeah. So all this, what happened to this means war? Now it's all
terrorism. Yeah, yeah. Well, by the way, folks, if you look at any of the ancient
texts, it does talk about a time where terror will be brought upon people, fear,
terror, things like that. And they will be running when there is no fear and acting
and emotionally reacting when there is nothing really to fear. The reason why
you have it called as terrorism, by the way, is because you're way beyond the
level right now where it's nation versus nation. You're in what's called a global
setting right now, a worldwide setting. And if anyone has, let's say, done any
research or studying about the credit based economy, the statutory laws and
treaties, you'll notice there are no more countries. They've legally or lawfully
been dissolved. I mean, lawfully, they sort of exist because the blood that runs
through the people defined as a nation is still there. But legally, they've been
dissolved, all of them pretty much. And the ones that haven't been are on the short
list to be so, like Libya that was, you know, for example. So you're in a
situation now that is worldwide. Forget about this nation thing, you know,
sovereignty and whatever. Because if you look at the way things are supposed to go
according to the ancients, first, you had events happen to a certain familial group
and then to nations. And then in the end, it's all global or worldwide. Sorry,
flat-earthers, by the way, if you don't like the word globe. You know, you're going
to have to wait until the next stupid meme comes up in society for you guys to
latch on to. But anyway, the concept of terrorism, the concept of Bugs Bunny
declaring war, the concept of all these things is part and parcel of there is no
more sovereign nations and you're being poised and set up for a world leadership
coming out of one group. And I'm not discussing the New World Order. That's
Muppet-puppet discussion level stuff. It has nothing to do with what you guys have
been talked about on and on and on for decades by all these other people that
pretty much got a lead on to what's called the alternative media. They're
known as the granddaddies of alternative media in the 90s and early 2000s. A lot of
New World Order talk, forget about that. That's already down the pipeline and is
ready to be spit out. There's a new New World Order that everyone is going to
welcome. And we'll discuss that and why in many other discussions. But what we
were going to do is catch up on the second hour is the Middle East Union. And
in order to really get the cobwebs out is why is no one discussing why
international incidents are now discussed as terrorism and not outright war? Yes,
there are some wars here and there that are called wars. The reason is because
wars are done to protect a particular set-apart group or an isolated group, a
nationalistic, sovereign-type body. But none of that exists anymore, in
wholesale, other than a small specific enclaves here and there. So it has to be,
cannot be called war anymore. It has to be called terrorism, you see, because
you're all going to be following a worldwide scheme. And that worldwide
scheme is very simply going to originate where it originated. And it's going to
end where it originated, just like a racetrack. If you look at a racetrack,
locate the starting line. Okay, got that in the mind? All right, where's the
finish line? It's the same, same position. So what we're doing here is giving a
little bit of the rationale, because we don't want to talk symptoms, right? So
very simple way to look at it is, even if you look at the behavior of society,
without, you know, staying on the description end of it, is the beginning of
society in what part of the planet? Is it the Middle East, sort of what's called
the Middle East? You might call it the Levant, it's the center mass of the
Earth. Even in your pre-programmed, pranking, mainstream schooling system,
they tell you that life of mankind's or society started around the Mesopotamian
region. So they've got a little bit of it correct. All of your other historical
records lean that way. Now, of course, we're not talking about the 99% of the
airheads that want to talk about, well, they believe it's this, or they believe
it's that. We're not talking about that. We're not allowed to make things up, if
we're going to have rational discussion. If you like to make things up, watch
little children, they make up little games, and they get very serious about
them, until an adult comes in and starts shaking them up. We're not here to be an
adult to anyone, but this has nothing to do with what's being discussed in public
right now anyway. So you're going to look at that part of center mass. If you look
at a map of the world as it's laid out flat, draw an X across it, and you'll see
that it pretty much intersects in the Eastern Mediterranean, west of Asia, sort
of northern part of Africa, southern part of Asia Minor, or Europe. That
general area is going to be the area of focus. What's been prophesied is ten
nations rising to prominence, where all economic, judicial, political, educational,
entertainment, financial systems, and military will be focused out of. Like, you
might have, let's say, a country with more military might, but it'll do the bidding
of that area. You see, if it sounds familiar to anyone that's American. Now,
by the way, speaking of American, they don't know what they're doing. Don't
blame your quote-unquote government, or you want to call them Satanists, or
whatever, whatever, whatever, or they're incompetent, or it's about money, or it's
about oil. And I mean, you can't blame them. I mean, they already have contracts
to use the credit that the people are not supposed to know about, to make very
expensive single-use items known as weapons. I mean, you'd all do the same
thing. Don't say you wouldn't, because I know you would. If you had access to
unlimited credit, you'd use it also, and you wouldn't be sharing. Yes, yes, I know
it sounds kind of judgmental, but it's a pretty good call. So, the Americans don't
know what they're doing, by the way, but they're doing it. Is it possible to do
something and not know why you're doing it? You know, let's say, an overall large
reason? Yeah, absolutely. Happens all the time. Are they being pranked? Yeah,
possibly. By cosmic, beyond cosmic elements? Yeah, that could be another
discussion. You know, people want to be nationalistic that are in America, but
you're gonna play second fiddle to the society in the Middle East. Sorry, folks.
The sooner you realize that, the more at peace you will be with what's happening
around you. It's better to know what's going to happen before it happens, and
trying to rationalize it while it's happening, even though it's biting you in
the ass. Let's say this is the same for Europe. Europe is going to be playing
second fiddle to this, politically, economically, judicially, and everything.
Now, there's another thing that has to come up before we get into any more
discussion about the Middle East. It's the thing about Islam. Get that out of
your mind, folks. In the future, all of the mainstream religions in the world are
going to be kind of put aside. For what? For something called the truth. Yeah.
Simply finding the truth is simply beginning to read and study the text
that your religion is based on. Oh, but I don't need to study, I believe. Yeah, you'll
see. So, there's no way you could call yourself Christian if you read, or do
what Christians do if you read, the biblical text. No way, unless you're
insane or evil. Same goes for Judaism, the same goes for Islam, if you read the
Koran. There is no way you will do what the people that call themselves a Muslim
do. I'm talking about moderate, extreme, or anything. The same with the Buddhists,
the same with the Hindus, on and on and on. Right? This is very simple fact. It's the
truth. It might sound dogmatic to someone who is unstudied and looking to
be a prankster. You know, you start talking to an attorney about law, they
get very upset because inherently they know they're doing that field to be a
prankster. They don't have to do anything and they get all your money, let's say.
Same with the doctors. You start discussing their field, they get very
upset. That's how you know you're dealing with a prankster. So, don't fall for the
mainstream religion causality. And by the way, folks, I've also heard in
passing, oh, it's the Crescent versus the Cross. Okay, well, first of all, if you
read the biblical text, there is no crucifixion. They could use the word a
hundred times, but rationally there isn't. If you read the text and
understand, the biblical Christ was brought to Pontius Pilate and he
demanded, Pontius Pilate that is, that Judean law was used on him. There was no
crucifixion in Judean law. So anyway, but if you're dabbling in what's
called the New Testament, you will know that's like getting a four-year-old and
showing them only graduate-level physics books. It doesn't matter if you hold it
right side up or upside down, you're going to get the same out of it. Nothing. Anyway,
so there is no crescent as such. If you go look at the symbol of Islam, you might
describe it as a crescent, yes, because it looks geometrically alike. But if you
really look at that image, it's an image of an eclipse. It's a dark body eclipsing
a lighter body. Look at it. It's one circle superimposed over another. It's
not a crescent as you would see a moon being partially lit or a sphere being
partially lit. Are you paying attention? Yeah. No, the answer is no, you're not.
And you're not supposed to because you're not going to have any friends if
you pay attention, by the way, and your family won't want to talk to you. That's
how you know you're doing it right. You're pretty much rejected across the
board to some degree on most things. So there's a mindset that needs to be put
in place or realized, and everyone will realize what they need to realize in
their own way, let's say. Most people won't realize anything. But I mean, those
that want to listen and actually do something. So you can't jump into a
Middle East discussion, especially a coming Middle East Union, without
understanding why things are called terrorism, what the mainstream
religions are, and how Islam is irrelevant in its cause in this.
It's not a religion versus a religion. It's a society, perhaps, versus another
society. Just like we've disclosed here, there's no such thing as a Bronze Age or
an Iron Age or a Stone Age or a caveman. There's a complete lie put out to you by
the quackademics, academics, pranksters. You might have a stone-type
society that is parallel to a bronze society, to an iron society, just like you
might have a society that's all wired and one that is wireless. So on and
so forth. But all these things exist in parallel. So why is there terrorism? There
is no more nations. It's all some kind of semi-unifying, semi-worldwide
causality. Not the New World Order that you guys hear about and want to talk
about. No. It is a New World Order, but it's sort of along those lines. That's
why it's all being called terrorism. And the mainstream
religions have nothing to do with it. It's traditions and customs. You also have to
understand there's no money. You're in a credit-based economy, which, by the way,
you will never understand, according to what's been memorialized. But fortunately
or unfortunately for you, never is not too far away. So to go back into the Middle
East Union wholeheartedly, just discussing what's coming, I believe, is
not enough without discussing the type of thinking and perceptions that should
be made or can be made about it. So I'm going to take a – that was a long-winded
thing there, Seth. I'm going to take a break. Anything you want to add or take away
to the rationale that might have to be put in place before one can rationalize
or have a good discussion on the coming Middle East Union without getting into
any specifics at this point? It comes back to, you know, another topic
that we've discussed. You brought up dreams, but even going a little bit
further than that, just, you know, thoughts and where thoughts come from.
And if thoughts are not simply, you know, machinations that are coming from the
internal and are actually something more that's not really
discussed in a rational manner anywhere as coming from without as opposed to
within, then it leads, you know, directly, the consequence of thought being action,
that these actions that we are seeing on all levels are not simply as they are
described. They're not simply as they seem to be, as they are broadcast
through the television or through the Internet or through the radio. That what
is going on is going on at a level that is, the level is not actually discussed
anywhere with any rationality. No, it can't. Yeah, it can't, because people lack the
maturity. And I'm not talking about just an age. And by the way, folks, if you want
to see what an eight-year-old mentality is like, run into your average grandma
person, granddad. They haven't developed more than eight or nine years old. They
may look older. You should respect them, at least socially, because they've been
around. They've gone to the bathroom a lot more and they've brushed their teeth
a lot more than you. But other than that, they've ceased to mature. So anyway,
there's a lack of maturity on many levels. And by the way, folks, when you've
still been plugged in a bad way with this King James stuff, and these memes
and sayings and cliches, like God is within you or anything is within you, go
look at that. That's not in there. That's not in the text. They put that in there
for you. I was on a discussion once, and this fellow liked to reiterate a quote
from, I think it was King Henry, when the King James Bible was out. He says,
the people must, I'm paraphrasing here, the people must understand that the King
James Bible is under license, and it is only to inform your conscience. Remember,
it is under license. What are they telling you? So all this stuff about you
have something is a joke, and you've been pranked. And don't be a prankster, folks.
It's all you're receiving and you're transmitting. And memory is like a cloud,
by the way, and you do need the equipment to access it. But here's the point. When
the gods come in, just to intersect this, because we were at an intersecting point
when, you know, it's not discussed, it's the gods with accuracy. And whether you
are dealing with a benevolent or benevolent god, by the way, it is a
frightful thing. If people tell you they've had this soft, wonderful feeling
and they saw a god, they're making stuff up because they want to sell YouTubes or
whatever they do these days. Yeah. Anytime you deal with anything legitimate from
the other side, overtly, unless you're being pranked by them, they'll present a
very soft image for you to go and tell your friends and then they'll high-five
themselves, we got another one of these stupid humans. The concept of
discussing the gods is beyond most people's pay scale. And it will be, all
the way to the end, because they will be pranked by others that are going to be
putting on quite a show. And there will be a legitimate influence from certain
entities, let's say, to do so. But yeah, there is. Yeah. It's not just black and
white. The wicked witch wears black and the, what is it, the good witch wears
white. It's not like that. Any god that you encounter, you will be, if they're
not very careful and you are not careful, you will be dissolved out of this
existence. So there is a very strong influence of that on this world. But
yeah, the mindset, again, just because you have religion, what they call that,
you've been pranked. That's like saying I like baseball, or strawberry ice cream,
or advanced nose-picking, or underwater basket weaving. It means
absolutely nothing. It is there to prank you. All those funny hats and funny
costumes and revived sex temples that you call whatever you want to call,
places of worship, that's what they are, folks. Do the research. So irrelevant
stuff. I mean, you know, it's like when did the Yankees come in, you know? When
did the Mets? Hey, how about them Mets? How about them Yankees? You know, how
about that Islam? How about that Christianity? Same stuff. Sorry, guys.
Buddhism. Again, just keep in the back of your mind, folks, when the Asian people,
in general, Asiatic people, find out that they've been pranked with all that
stuff they put on them. Oh, boy. So let's get into a little bit more of the
Middle Eastern Union with some specifics, perhaps. You know, I hate piggybacking
on when it's noisy, but let's just say it this way, folks. There was a lot of
noise being made roughly in the past day period or so about an alleged military
coup in Turkey. Irrelevant, folks. Wouldn't say irrelevant, irrelevant, but
irrelevant on what we're talking about. It's just more noise and more
information going towards what we've been discussing, which is the Middle East
Union. And what we said in the past hour to preface this is how can you have a
loose confederacy of nations if they're all nationalistic and ready to pounce on
each other with policies and things in place that discriminate or create
disparity amongst countries that are tangent or parallel with each other. You
can't have that. So I would say the easiest way to look at what's going on
is to understand time, which we've kind of given a little bit of understanding
on how to be lawful in it. Understand that things build up in the, things that are
planted in the spring build up in the summer, torn down in the fall. If you
look at any event being a summertime event, these are all building up events.
So if you've been looking at some of the quote-unquote acts of terror, we've just
explained why things or everything is called terror. I want to throw this in
there, by the way, before we get to the Middle East Union. If you ever notice,
especially in the Western world, the authorities, municipalities, states,
federal government, whatever, is very anxious to brand something a terrorist, a
terrorist attack. And in order for it to be memorialized or branded as one, it has
to be done in the media, has to be done legally on paper, and it has to be
discussed as such. Do you know why they do that? And it's a monetary reason why
they do it. Because after 9-11, what they call 9-11, a terrorism insurance was put
in. I don't know how big the claims are, but if you're working in a municipality
and you have, let's say, a robbery, the municipality might be able to draw a
little bit of insurance on it, maybe. But if you can brand that robbery into a
terrorist act, now you tap into the terrorist insurance fund, and that's huge,
folks. They're chomping at the bit to call everything terrorism because of the
insurance companies. And by the way, all of you idiots are being told that all
the money is on Wall Street, and it's not. It's a couple of blocks northwest where
all the insurance companies are. Don't believe it? Look it up. What is the
largest industry in America? Yes, you guessed it, insurance. So the other
reason you're hearing, because they're motivated by a credit, is they have
terrorism insurance. So there's another motivation to bring that up. So when we
say these things, we're giving you the explanation why, you see. We're not just
saying, oh yeah, they're calling it terrorism. If you've ever been in a
Homeland Security office, they have a poster to the employees. To the
employees, and it says the purpose of Homeland Security is to regulate
commerce. Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. Uh-huh, you heard it right. If you know
anyone that works there, they will tell you. Tell them to go in the employees
lounge. You have a poster explaining what they're there for. So it's all about
issuing and dispersing credit, folks. But that's just the explanation side. The
description that we could get into again is the event that recently happened
in Turkey. That is nothing more than, if you look at it in the summertime, it's a
building up event to what? Breaking down. What happened? There was a coup. Okay, what
does a coup do? Well, the actual coup itself is a breaking down period.
There are several, quote-unquote, I know a guy runs over people with a
truck, it's terrorism. I just told you why, right? Cash in on it. So, and people, by
the way, your lives are regarded as nothing, by the way. Yeah, no matter what
you, your innocent lives. Do you hear anybody saying, these are innocent people
that were killed, that is a mark of an idiot. Because there's no such thing.
You're all target, you all got targets on you, right? So anyway, the events that are
happening now, you see in great succession, they're breaking down events.
Things being blown up, torn down, people killed, this, that, and the other. These
are breaking down events, man. And this is going to continue. We have another two
years of it, roughly. We, whoever we is, this is the breaking down period. And then
the building up period starts. So what else you're going to see? This is the
most that can be explained about what's going on in Turkey. Yeah, they're going to
recuperate and bounce back, but they're not going to be like they were before.
Now, why is Turkey important? Is Turkey going to be part of this Middle East
Union? No. They're not. But they're going to have a loose alliance with Greece and
Cyprus. And let's say places like Libya, Northern Africa, that whole Mediterranean
rim, North and South, not the Levant, but this northern part of the Mediterranean
rim and the southern part of the Mediterranean rim, like the Northern
African countries and the Southern European countries, predominantly Turkey,
Greece, and Cyprus, are going to be a loose alliance around this Confederacy,
right? So, and things are done backwards sometimes, so you're going to see a
softening up there. What you're going to actually see that's really going to be
bringing in the main push or the crux of the matter where things
will start to rotate like the hub of a wheel is the formation of a new country
in northern Iraq, which is also going to take some land from Turkey and Syria.
Now, I wrote about this a long time ago, that Turkey and Syria will be in the
news and so will Greece, probably making an exit based on economics and things
like that. And I was told I was crazy. And I don't know if I should thank the
people for it. I guess crazy is good. But this country called the new Assyria,
which is going to form in northern Iraq, is also going to be borrowing a few
kilometers into Syria, more than a few, just a couple, 10 maybe, and Turkey.
So, it's being softened up. People, you know, can do research in that area.
They'll see there's a lot of activity. I'm not talking about the Kurds and all
these other groups. I'm talking about the Assyrians. Not Syrians, Assyrians.
So, that's where we are so far. And, Sefa, you could back up. We've been saying this
and many other things regarding that region with great accuracy for quite a few
years, you and I have, at least in public. I'll be back in about a minute and a half.
So, take it on from here, Sefa. I'll be right back.
All right. Loose confederation. Ten nations coming together. It's interesting.
We've, as Nickery said, we've been talking about this now for three years, give or
take a few months. And it's, a lot of it just kind of takes away the surprise of,
I'm certainly no longer surprised by just about anything that I see come across
media in any of its forms. A lot of head shaking, I suppose.
But, you know, it's all, the people that are presented as being in control and or responsible
are, for the most part, just as in the dark as those who they are claiming to be in control of
or responsible for. So, it's not as if, except on very, very small level, it's not as if they are
willfully even pursuing what we are talking about.
It makes for really easy descriptions. He did it. He did it. You ever watch the news and say,
we don't know who to blame yet. That's what they say. They actually tell you that.
This event happened, but we don't know who to blame yet. You just want to, remember those
cartoon gloves, you know, the really big four fingered glove where they slap them back and
forth, you know. It's like, what's wrong with you people? Not the people. You got to remember now,
when you're listening to alternative or mainstream media, they're saying all the
stupid shit they're saying to accommodate you. So stop being stupid. I can't believe it. Like
sometimes I find myself yelling at the television, let's say, if I turn it on or
the computer, if I tend to land on someone talking about something,
and then I have to catch myself and say, wait a second.
There are people that listen, they tune in to hear this stuff.
You can't fault those that are dishing it out. There's a reason why lemonade stands are set up
in hot weather. There's a reason why there are gas stations on the side of the road in the desert,
because there's a highway there. But if that highway closes, the stupid stuff goes away.
So anyway, the description part is so easy, the blaming mankind. But if you're a god,
and you don't want to show up overtly, why don't you just affect a group of people to do something,
or make a riverbank overflow, or throw down the company car?
Or company car is kind of an inside joke for what a tornado or hurricane is.
Yeah, you could even write down in relatively plain speech that you were going to do that.
Yep, and when and how, and no one, everyone ignores it.
They want to talk about Anunnaki, Planet X, and that you came from Planet Reticuli as a baby,
or something stupid, or you're going to be reincarnated as the Dalai Lama or something.
Yeah, or blame it all on the CIA or the intelligence agencies.
Folks, I don't think you guys know anyone that works in the intelligence agencies
to be talking that way. These people don't know anything. They're there because it's a yob.
Y-O-B. And they won't hire you unless you're extremely bought into all the pranking.
That's a fact. And also, by the way, we do base a lot of this stuff on what's called
the biblical textbook. You know what, Seth, we've never, well, at least I have, I could say,
never recommend anyone go and read the biblical text. And this is sarcastic, folks, but it's true.
You know why? Because you're not going to understand anything in it.
You're going to get the, is, or was out of it, or day and night out of it, but you're not going
to be able to piece it together, because you're going to have to learn to read out of things.
If you go and approach any ancient text, and you say, oh, this is the part that I saw in the movie,
you're going to start reading into it things that are not there, because Cecil B. DeMille
put it on film for you when you're still in short pants, and you no longer had to wear a diaper.
You saw the repeat on TV, because it was probably done 40 or 50 years before you were born.
Yeah, I have recent experience with, like you said, you know, and I second that, that
never really encourage anyone to do that. But at the same time, I'm often, with regularity even,
encourage people that seem determined to do it anyways, that they go and read the book
Ecclesiastes, and even in doing, I've received responses back where it's like, that book is,
it's kind of repetitive, but it is, it has what I would certainly consider wisdom in it,
it's kind of a book about wisdom. Right, and knowledge. Yeah, wisdom and knowledge.
But even in that, something that is, it's written, it seems to be on a higher perspective
on a lower grade level, to borrow an analogy. But it's, because it's very, it's repetitive.
It says what is important over and over and over. And I received a response after, you know,
recommending that to someone publicly, that they had done just that. They had taken this,
they'd taken one line out of it and used it as a sort of justification for a previously held
opinion about another like religious group or sect. And, which is not what was being spoken
about in the text at all. It was just being, it's very, very basic, written to just about,
it's just from a certain perspective. A human perspective. Yeah. Yeah. Assisting the human
situation. And speaking of which, we did bring, this is a segue, we're also going to talk about
the deception. And let's just give a secret. What a better place to give a secret than a
minor internet radio station on a show that never is not supposed to be here.
Someone mentioned in the corrupt KGV, the Antichrist is supposed to come. Let's, let's give
the secret regarding that. By the way, folks, whenever you hear the term the Antichrist,
it's not in the biblical text. It's instead of Christ, right? Well, a Christ figure is someone
who's anointed, someone who is supposed to assist you to the next level, let's say, right?
Right? Or to prove something out. If you're thinking about that long hair, nailed to a cross,
wearing a diaper, sorry. That's Mithra Serapis. So, but, but here's the point. It's all secret.
But here, let's give a secret. Now, for those of you that understand and comprehend and listening
that today, whatever you call whatever date you communicate with is the papal work schedule.
And the papacy, Catholicism, Christianity, the Pope, the Vatican, all that stuff has got nothing
to do with anything. It is a social mechanism. It has nothing to do with spirituality,
other than the spirituality that is defined as the mind. You see what I mean?
The secret is such, if you know how to keep time, we know pretty accurately that the, instead of
Christ, let's use the Antichrist character that is going to come on the world scene, is roughly in
his 19th year, right? And what I mean by that, again, to you folks, that regarding timekeeping,
when you have, let's say, your 18th birthday, that day, the next day, that next extra day
is from your 19th year. So when you become 18, you're in your 19th year, right? Because you're
not using time from the previous, you're using time from the current, which has not been memorialized
as being finished until it does. So when you become 19, you're actually in your 20th year.
You see? It's kind of like backwards the way the legal society does it, but either way,
that's just a little secret again. But this fellow, contrary to all the stupid stuff that
you are exposed to as a society, the Antichrist, I use that term because it's common, the instead
of Christ that is prophesied to come, he's going to be a highly, highly charismatic individual.
Everyone is going to like him. It's not going to be this bad politician, or this evil guy,
you know. Actually, all the way through, even when he's doing things that are, quote-unquote,
evil. And what I mean by that is because what people consider to be good is actually evil,
but to the gods, and what the gods consider to be good, people consider to be evil. So when he,
this person starts to administer a worldwide government in an evil way to the gods,
but in a good way to humanity, even then, he will not be viewed as a bad character. So
all this Hollywood crap, and there's people writing books about Antichrist, and YouTubes,
and movies, and it's all false, all of it. And you know what, folks? That may not sound rational,
but if some of it wasn't false, we wouldn't be doing this. I just say, hey, by the way, Seth,
and everyone, go check out this link. This is good stuff. Sorry, guys. That's why this is the
show that's not supposed to be a show. And what a better place to give secrets on that.
It has nothing to do with what you believe in, unless you have the information. And by the way,
how can you believe something if you're not informed about that thing? Think about that,
folks. So right now, this person, and should we give a little bit more secret on that,
Seth, or just hold off for the future? Maybe we'll hold off. Let's just do that.
But that's, I think, enough, his age right now. So if some moron next to you – hopefully we're
not addressing morons directly, so I'm not going to call if you're listening to a moron – but
if a moron next to you says, look at this guy here. They say he's the Antichrist. Well,
if he's older than 20, roughly, past his 19th year, currently, around there. Nah, sorry.
Another Easter Bunny, Chase, Santa Claus, Tooth Fairy, whatever, whatever else.
Maybe they told you that at the circus. I mean, church, circus, whatever, same thing.
You folks are in really, really bad shape, and no one is saying anything.
It's really sad. It can't be that the entire population is that, and much in the dark,
or that much immature that they like to make stuff up and go with it. Could it be?
It's like a dream. Yes, you will find that to be true if you do study.
I had once someone say to me, I don't get any knowledge from a book. I get it from experience.
So if you're dealing with that kind of mindset, folks, you're in really bad shape.
So what a better place to give out a little secret like that, Seth. I mean, what say you?
I think we'll just leave that secret right there. So we're looking for someone right now.
We're not going to give – there's more information to give on him, quite a bit more,
and to identify him, not necessarily needs to be identified directly at this point,
because if it's not meant for him to be identified, you will be blocked severely.
But what's wrong with knowing? Oh, we're not supposed to know. Okay. It's really confusing,
isn't it? But that's the secret, folks. It's a, yeah, confusion, war, war to bring into confusion.
Yes. Now, war in Greek is polymos, poly meaning many, and polemic,
like that's where you get the word meme from, you know. So, yeah, yeah. There's a lot to come.
Another secret is one we've been giving away, which is watch for the rise of Assyria in northern
Iraq. Yeah. Another secret to give, let's just give this secret, and we'll see who's listening
by who we get in touch, who tries to get in touch with us privately. Did you know that Israel has
about four prime ministers left before it's turned around into a monarchy or a pseudo-monarchy?
Did you, here's another secret, folks, about the Middle East. Are you ready? You ready? Did you
know that when, around that time, that Iran, Persia, will be more unified as it's becoming,
and will form a very strong financial alliance with what's known as Israel? Did you guys know
that? Now, here's another secret, folks. Did you guys know that the monarchy in Jordan will be
expelled, and that country will break up into several jurisdictions? Here's another secret,
folks. Did you know that what's known as Lebanon, the coast of Lebanon, the cities of Tyre and
Sidon, are going to rise to incredible financial prominence in the near future? Did you know that?
That's another secret. Yeah. And all these can be underpinned and explained in great detail,
which they will be in the future, in a semi-public, semi-private way, perhaps. I don't know. Well,
actually, I do know, but we don't know exactly how it's going to be done at this point.
There's a lot of secrets, folks. We just gave you a handful.
Here, here's another secret, folks. There's no money. You're under a credit-based economy. I
wanted to just bring that up, just to throw this in, because this does tie in, just so I could give a
lengthy definition of why you're being told everything is terrorism. One is because it
actually witnesses that there is no sovereignty anymore, like Bugs Bunny. You know, when you
did something to Bugs Bunny, this means war. You won't hear that that much. You have war-like
behavior. And also, there's a big insurance for municipalities and local and national governments
to get from when they call, like dropping a cigarette on the floor terrorism. They could
cash in on that much more on the credit. But here's another secret, folks. There is no money.
And the reason why you're not being told there is no money is because – you see,
when you go into a casino, you have to get chips to play. When you're born into a country that has
a credit-based economy – and by the way, if you don't know that it's a credit-based economy,
how come they don't call those plastic things money cards? What do they call them?
Credit or debit cards, right? But anyway, the reason why you're not told about how to access
or why you should be able to access the treasury or, let's say, credit line that you're issued
at birth – you want to call it the all-caps name or the social security number and all that,
all these other agencies that dip and dab into that, right, when you're birthed – and birth
has nothing to do with being born, by the way. These are all secrets, by the way.
You know, it's not that these things are secrets, but the way I'm stringing them together is.
What happens if you understand what's called public policy, all the statutes and codes and
things regarding money and law that each corresponding government or whatever nation
you live in uses – the reason why you're not being told about this is because the people that
are in government have term limits and they understand that if they create policies and
things that give people access to it, they're not going to be able to profit once they leave
the office. So when they're in office, they put up the game that there's debt and there's all
this stuff and there's money. So when they get out of office, they have friends and family that
could work in what's called the secondary market, which is called debt collection and loans and
all these other financial products. By the way, banks don't have money. They have financial
products – a mortgage, a loan, a card is a financial product like hot dogs and hamburgers
are at a restaurant, let's say. So the reason why you're not being told this by your entrusted
leaders is because they have plans for the rest of their lives and their friends and families
when they do get out of office, how to take advantage of your ignorance of the lack of money.
And that is the secret. Just as car insurance was, there was no car insurance per se. That was a
requirement back in the day, but the senators said, why don't we start all these penny stock
insurance companies? And then when we get out of office, penny stock insurance companies,
and we'll pass laws or make laws, alleged laws that people should have it. And when we get out
of office, we already got a head start and we'll do really well. Our family will do really well.
So for just a small group of people to line their pockets, the rest of society has to go ahead with
it. So these are little secrets, not the things themselves, but how they're strung together.
So we have one more episode to go and we will see you folks next week. In the meantime,
you know what to do. Go to the American Freedom Radio homepage and do the right thing for them
and stay in touch with us if you can. Thank you, Seth. Thank you, everyone.