Greetings once again and welcome to Uncommon Sense with The Greek and Seth Michael, when Seth
Michael can make it. And hello everyone. You can find us at AFR, which if you are listening to me,
you are probably on AFR at the moment, or on UStream, which could be found at uncommonradio.com.
That would be www.uncommonradio.com, and you will see the appropriate places to click on to listen
to this stream, whether it's AFR, American Freedom Radio, or on UStream. Now, being on
American Freedom Radio, of course, this is a, let's just say, listener-sponsored venue, and
without you guys, there is no AFR, so you know what to do. You should be able to figure that
out by now. On the homepage, you will see there is a way to contribute. So again, hello everyone,
and this is Uncommon Sense, and why are we doing the show? Why are we calling it Uncommon Sense?
Simply because we don't want to be common. Well, what is that? You know, why are we discussing
things that are uncommon if we don't want to be common, and who's we? And why do we want to be
uncommon? Well, you know, let's just say it this way. You know, sometimes I've been in discussions
with people, and they bring up the Greek philosophers, and the great religions of the
world, or science, or in scientific advancement, and all this other stuff, and I have to say,
hold on, hold on, hold on. Okay, if this stuff is so good, all right, it's so great, and such a
wonderful achievement, how has it served us? How has it served mankind? How has it served society?
Not well, has it? So maybe an examination about what people are noticing or calling with prestige
to be so wonderful is not so wonderful at all, maybe because it's commonly accepted to be such.
Anyway, speaking of uncommon, anyone know what day it is today? Yeah, if you're on that thing
called the Pope's work schedule, known as the calendar, yep, yeah, probably lost all the
audience right now, just by saying what day it is. Yeah, but there's about four or five listeners
out there that kind of know what talking about. You know, you can't keep time with that thing
called a calendar. And I keep repeating the same thing over and over. Why can't you keep time with
it? Well, very simply, you ever notice how if you kind of acknowledge a day on that thing,
comes on a different day of the week every year. But anyway, enough said about that. But
if those of you are interested, kind of reckoning it's the third moon or the third month, and it's
roughly around the 18th day because it's past noon here, it might be the 17th day where you're at.
But roughly, I'm saying it's perhaps around 17 or 18. Close enough. And, you know, one of the
topics that can come up at this time of the year for this part of the world is springtime,
kind of dedicated a couple of hours more than a few, few four hours or so previous to springtime
thoughts. And what's interesting, again, about what's manifested in the spring is quietness,
except for the baby lambs that are running around, maybe with a little fledgling birds
and things like that. It's a time of quiet. And one little bit of heads up to folks,
you know, speaking of quiet and the opposite might be noise. You know, wherever the noise is,
by the way, is where the distraction is. Okay, the real stuff is going on where it's quiet.
You ever walk through a forest, or go deep sea diving, or in any of the completely, let's say,
engrossed natural environments, you'll see there's a lot of quiet. That's where all the growth takes
place. When you're sleeping, and the body grows and recovers, it's pretty quiet and you demand
quiet. In other words, formative energies, things that form things and grow are quiet.
So from a social point of view, because typically most people that tune into things like this,
basically broadcasts or sonic events, are interested in social things, social commentary,
telling them what to think. I remember being much younger one time, someone said,
don't read Time magazine, because it tells you what to think. And I kind of kept that in the
back of the mind. And I wondered, isn't everyone trying to figure out a way to find something
that's going to or someone else that's going to tell them how and what to think. I was kind of
found that interesting. But people kind of tune into these various media formats. So they could be
told what to say, but well, not necessarily what to say, but how to think, you know, they have a
certain amount of energy to dedicate to learning things that are quote, unquote, new. And not only
are they partaking in various formats, written, internet, sonic, visual, as in video, and they
look at what's called the news, and they got television shows and radio shows and alternative
media shows called the news. Yes, they're just shows. And very often they get noisy. You know,
you have people discussing things in a way, look here, look there, you know, and this is not where
it's at. The real stuff is happening where it's quiet. You know, so again, we don't want to
necessarily lean to social commentary and things that are about society. But this is, for example,
a sonic event like this, or why people do tune in is to hear about social things. You know, there are
some ideas about perhaps doing a cooking show or discussing how the body works and how other
things might work in certain specificity. But typically, people are curious about social
things. And which brings me to perhaps a comment I had a listener contact me, and
thankfully, to the Greek, he said, I had some people in the Jehovah's Witness protection program
come and knock on the door. And they kind of left bewildered scratching their head based on things
that I heard you say that I used on them. And I was like, Well, okay, well, thanks for letting me
know. And I was wondering what he had said that had never really come across in the message. But
what's interesting is perhaps it was interesting experience because he said the people in the
Jehovah's Witness protection program kind of walked away, scratching their head. So it might have
been maybe something uncommon. What's interesting about this when you interact with people that
join certain groups, well, albeit a quote, unquote, religious group, because that term is not being
used properly. But let's say a religious group, or political group or any other group, what have you,
there is something called the crowd mentality, which I like to refer to by a book written by
a man named Gustav Le Bon, L-E-B-O-N, at the end of the 19th century. All right, well,
hello, everyone. I don't know how, how I managed to do that. Apologies.
Says he's busy, he might still be on the call.
Okay, am I? Can you guys hear me? Yes. I just got word. Great. I just got word that,
for some reason, I dropped or was lost. Okay. So we are live. Great. Okay. Great. I just took a look
at chat real quick. So yeah, okay. So just maybe I'll do a recap. I don't know for how long I was
gone. But it was pretty much discussing and welcome, Seth, by the way. I was kind of discussing
just general social sentiments towards media, because people go to media, to hear things that
are socially based, you know, they might go to a cooking show or how to fix your car or whatever,
listen to music, you know, private interests, but generally, their public interests, you know,
in large interests, that people attend certain forms of media or all forms of media. Right.
So it kind of brought it brought that point up. And in order to understand, perhaps maybe
where one can come from, from an uncommon point of view, is typically people are discussing
things with prestige, oh, the wonderful nature of the great philosophers, or the true meaning of
these religions, or how wonderful and advanced scientific research is, you know, and I'm like,
well, hold on a second. Okay, well, that sounds real good. But you know, how well is that served
society, all that stuff that you guys think is so great? Right? How is it served? Has it served
as well? I would say not. And it's still commonly discussed, as if it's something wonderful.
So and just kind of tying that in, I'm reckoning roughly, it's the third week of the third month,
to put it loosely. You know, and of course, right there, we're going to lose pretty much anyone who's
tuning in, except for four or five people that have realized that you can't keep time with the
Pope's work schedule. And, yeah, I wanted to also bring up, you know, again, why people tune in,
you know, it's for social things for to hear about what they've been, what they're being
told is going on. So they know how to think about it, right? Even things that they that are far
reaching and far away from their personal location. So I think it's interesting how,
how, how the how and why people tune into, let's say, even, you know, what we're doing,
or what anyone else is doing, or that show called the news, you know, and maybe giving a little bit
of a truer perspective. But not based on truthism, by the way, because by the way, folks,
this word truth has been hijacked. And anyone who uses it is highly suspect at this point.
So when I say anyone, I mean, generally, you have something called the truth movement,
and it's really truthism. It's, yeah, it's, you know, billions of billions are served,
right was the golden arches and billions, billions, yes, are served. Yes, with this truthism.
So yes, you're not going to do well. So with that kind of stuff. So yeah, I like going back to
Gustav Le Bon's The Crowd. And because that is a I would say it's a good ref, objective referencing,
let's just put it that way. You know, if it's objective, and it's rational, and it's clearly
communicated, and well defined and accurate, why not write stuff? Absolutely. And, you know,
I want to just discuss something regarding the crowd every time I come on, and I was thinking,
instead of doing that, that there's a fellow on YouTube who put together a synopsis of the book,
and he did a really good job. So it's going to play a few minutes of that maybe three minutes or so.
But I wanted to bring up also a listener, I don't know if this came out through the air earlier,
who kind of thanked the Greek, he said, Well, thanks, you know, I had some people in the
Jehovah's Witness Protection Program come and knock on the door. And I discussed some of the
things I've heard on common sense, and they walked away scratching their head. And I just
wanted to bring that up. I don't know what he said. But, you know, listen, folks, just just
by the very virtue that the letter J was invented around 500 years ago is a good way to kind of keep
the chronology accurate. You know what I mean? Right. Yeah. And names, by the way, are exempt
from language, right? So Seth, right. If you were to move to China, and they wrote your name in the
Chinese script, if anyone that just only spoke Chinese read that script, it should sound like
Seth. You know, that's correct. Yes. So regardless of what the name is, or the sound when it's
communicated, it should retain that sonic character or quality to convey that communication.
It's, you know, I had someone once said, Well, that's my Chinese name. I'm like,
well, okay, that's accurate. But that's not your name and written in Chinese. That is the in other
words, you have been renamed, you know, so. So, yeah, my favorite is a woman. It was an Asian
woman or Chinese woman that worked in a food establishment. And she had a name tag Jane,
J-A-N-E. And I'm like, that can't be your real name. You know, she barely spoke in English.
And she says, Well, my name is Tsane. So phonetically, it'd be T-S-A-N-E. And I was
like, wow, that's a really good phonetic approach. So Jane and Tsane, her name being Tsane in Chinese,
and Jane is really a very good, so a good phonetic approach like that is still retains a good amount
of precision and accuracy. So it can be pulled off. Yeah. So maybe should we go right into the
audio perhaps that I've just queued up about Gustave Le Bon? What do you think,
Saf? Any other thoughts on that? Or should we just go ahead? Okay, so with that said,
let's give it a roll. Yeah, let's do the audio. I kind of hope it comes through well. And this is
just to give a little bit of credit on this. This is on YouTube. Man, I feel smarter already. I
watched two YouTubes today. It's the channel, the channel is Academy of Ideas. And the thing is,
you know, when people ask me, I said, Go look it up on the internet, go do a video, because
sight and sound, you know, you show me and tell me, you know, works well. So it's called the
channel's Academy of Ideas. And it's Gustave Le Bon, the nature of crowds. And let's see,
we're going to start it at the 59 second mark, we're going to run it to about four minutes,
four and a half or so. And it's Gustave Le Bon, the nature of crowds on YouTube. So if anyone wants
to hear the complete synopsis, or that was put together by this gentleman, it's around eight
minutes, 41 seconds, I'm going to be starting at around the one minute mark going to about four.
So enjoy, folks. In this video, we will provide a summary of Le Bon's classic work. In particular,
we will investigate his insights into the nature of crowds, look at the role ideas play in
influencing crowds, examine the religious sentiment of crowds, and discuss the psychological
and emotional benefits one derives from joining a crowd. What is a crowd? Le Bon defined a crowd
as a group of individuals united by a common idea, belief or ideology. The idea which unites
a crowd is not chosen by a process of clear reasoning and examination of evidence. Instead,
as we will discuss in more detail later, crowds accept beliefs and ideas superficially
and utilize them as fuel for revolutionary action. All right, I'm going to pause right there.
Seth, isn't that interesting? No evidence required, right? So all right, let's continue.
When an individual becomes part of a crowd, according to Le Bon, he undergoes a profound
psychological transformation. That is, he ceases to operate as an individual. He is no longer himself
but has become an automaton who has ceased to be guided by his will. With such a psychological
transformation, an individual no longer lives for himself but instead becomes a pawn who sacrifices
his own personal ends and goals in favor of those of the crowd. In a crowd, every sentiment and act
is contagious and contagious to such a degree that an individual readily sacrifices his personal
interest to the collective interest. As was mentioned earlier, Le Bon maintained that a
crowd forms when an influential idea unites a number of individuals and propels them to act
towards a common goal. These influential ideas, however, are never created by members of the crowd.
Instead, they are brought into the world by the minds of great individuals.
Since those who compose a crowd are by their very nature mediocre, they are incapable of
understanding these ideas in their original form. Therefore, in order for an idea to unite
and influence a crowd, it must first be thoroughly simplified. Ideas being only accessible to crowds
after having assumed a very simple shape must often undergo the most thoroughgoing transformations to
become popular. It is especially when we are dealing with somewhat lofty philosophical or
scientific ideas that we see how far-reaching are the modifications they require in order to
lower them to the level of the intelligence of crowds. However great or true an idea may have
been to begin with, it is deprived of almost all that which constituted its elevation and its
greatness by the mere fact that it has come within the intellectual range of crowds and exerts an
influence upon them. For example, a great philosopher could extol the nature of liberty
in an 800-page masterpiece. However, the crowd, incapable of comprehending such thoughts,
would require the concept of liberty to be thoroughly simplified in order for it to
stimulate revolutionary action. Le Bon proposed that this is where leaders come in, for it is
the leader of a crowd who communicates simplified ideas to the crowd and in doing so unites it
together and stimulates it to act. The majority of men, especially among the masses, do not possess
clear and reasoned ideas on any subject whatever outside their own specialty. The leader serves them
as guide. In the modern day, one can see how invigorated and rejuvenated crowds become when
they hear a leader pronounce that a cause is being fought in the name of freedom, peace, or
prosperity. Once these words are proclaimed, the members of the crowd nod their head in blind
obedience to whatever else follows from the leader's mouth, completely ignorant as to the
corrupt purposes that may be the true guide for the leader's actions. As Le Bon wrote,
How numerous are the crowds that have heroically faced death for beliefs,
ideas, and phrases that they scarcely understood.
Okay, we'll leave it at that. And how many times have you folks heard the ideas evoked in this
past three minutes of this fellow on this YouTube that I just played, repeated, let's say within the
but not being brought forward. You see the concepts of, let's do this, let's do that. And the actual
people that are partaking in these groups have no real perception of the depth of the
statements being made, or the concepts behind. And just tying that back to the fellow who had
communicated that some people from the Jehovah's Witness Protection Program came to the door,
and he spoke to them uncommonly, and they walked away scratching their head. I think I responded
something like maybe they should have been scratching more than their head. But
nonetheless, whether you're looking at a group as such, or any group, folks, whether they're
activists, whether they're reformists, political groups, religious groups, as such, you will find
the followers of these causes and crowds are pretty much adorned with the most superficial
and what you say, unfounded aspect of the reality of the formation of the crowd or the cause of the
crowd. So I think there was a statement once about if you want to learn about voting,
have a five minute discussion with a voter. So and you'll figure that out. The same with all
these things. There's a lot of stuff going on right now that people think is new, but it's being
done in the same old way. And there's no objectivity that's employed by the crowd, other than being in
the crowd. You know, if I Yeah, I was gonna say there are hints in language as well, specifically,
rhetorical language or the rhetoric, which I guess is kind of redundant. But just like,
how often do you hear the word revolution being used? And that, that in and of itself, just the
word, you know, it means to, you know, spin around, it would imply a cyclical movement,
you know, a movement. Yeah, a movement in a in a circle. So you're going to get absolutely nothing
new from a revolution, you can you can look at history, and see, you know, see the effects of
the many different types of revolutions. Things may appear to be different from the starting point
on the circle that you're that you're starting from, but you're essentially just moving, moving
around in a circle. So if you would like a revolution, stand up, spin around, sit back
down there, you have, you've taken part in a revolution, and it will get you it's, it's less
likely to get you injured. Well, no, actually, it could get you, it could get you wrapped around
the axle, man. That is very possible. Yes. And also, when I said RPM, I kind of meant revolutions
per millennia. Yeah. Think about that for a minute. Yeah. Social revolution, political revolution,
activism. Yeah. I have some yeast packets, you know, for baking, you know, leaven. And it says
active, you know, activism, every time I see it, you know, I want to I want to do one of these
parody shirts. You know, I've got activism right here. Yeah.
Fermenting revolution. Fermenting. Yeah. Yeah. So when you hear these activists or
reformists or political commentators, and it branches off, by the way, into the
what you say, quote unquote, scientism, astrophysicism,
quackademia ism, economic ism. Yeah, and it's just right now, what's being put out wholesale
to society, whether it's macro or micro, it's just still using this same structure,
where can we say stuff like we've been saying for a long time? It's debased as well. Yeah,
absolutely. There is the basis for the even the ideas in, you know, that are espoused by
those that would consider themselves political revolutionaries. The you hear a lot of catchwords
and catchphrases and things that get your attention and are, you know, designed by the
people who originally espoused such ideas to elicit emotional reactions, because people don't
think as clearly when they are emotional. And when you get people, you know, that agree and tell you
that, yes, you're right, and things like that, then it's it it adds a a fake basis, a ground
of sand to stand upon, made up of many, many little rocks, rocks we don't generally think of
as being, you know, intelligent. And the smaller they are, the less, the less useful they are for
the foundation, be it of a building or of thought. So, yeah, I wanted to go into,
you just evoked something that we commonly do in the uncommon sense venue here. By the way,
while you were speaking, it kind of jumped out and it's a we kind of try to dispel a cliche.
And maybe we'll display to cliche dispel two of them. Because they tend to be like a spell,
by the way, these cliches, you know, you know, like, you know, what came for you how people are
coaxed into thinking there's any value in the paradoxical quality of certain things, like,
for example, what came first, the chicken or the egg? Chicken? Yeah, the rooster and actually the
chicken farmer, because the chicken as it's known today is heavily domesticated and bred to be as
such. Right. But nonetheless, it's the the animal itself came first, because there are very various
animals that produce eggs. And because people are sort of coaxed into believing that this is
an accepted paradox, they tend to believe it. Also, that's another part of the crowd mentality,
where the emperor has no clothes is another part of the crowd mentality, a lot of the biblical
cliches. And the thing that brought this concept to mind was when you were mentioning building on
sand. And what's interesting is, you know, there's just paraphrasing here. There's a cliche
that, you know, who can build a tower on sand and will it stand right now, most people think that
people would go out when you hear that cliche is like, you know, when you're on the beach,
not necessarily like a sandcastle where the tide comes in, but just loose ground that you build on.
And then you come back and you have something that might look like the Leaning Tower of Pisa
or worse, right? Right. What's interesting when you study when this was written, places of study,
I think that we've mentioned before ancient libraries, there was reading out loud, there
was no silent reading. And I'm going to kind of go around the block on this concept here,
and we'll tie it back together. So if you were to visit an ancient library, you would pick up your
reading material and you would be if you were alone, you would be seated at a booth and you
would close the door and you would read out loud. So if you walk into a library, you hear all this
murmuring and rumble of everyone reading things out loud, even if you're in your personal space,
alone, you would be reading it out loud. That's why very interesting if you watch an old film
where someone opens a letter and they're reading it out loud. You might think it's for theatrical
or film purposes, but it's actually quite accurate to do so from that era, let's say 500
years prior. Now, other than that, when people had gathered, let's say in a conference room,
they have these whiteboards or blackboards or chalkboards. They had them as well. But what
they had also produced was things called these sandboxes. So they would have a table that you
would sit at and it had a large sandbox and you would have a pointer or a stick. And when you had
an idea, or if this was an engineering topic, you would actually draw out what you wanted to build
in the sand. It was like a sandbox on the table. And people would take notes on things called
Pinaxes or Pinax. It would be like a small piece of slate that you carried in a purse or a bag
and you would use a form of chalk or soapstone, like a white soapstone type thing to mark it.
Right. So it would be more indelible than just plain chalk. And by the way, these little
miniature Pinaxes that were used back then resembled the tablets of today. You know, those
five by eight or seven more, you know, they call them like 10 inch tablets or tablets. Yeah. So
it's really interesting when you look at that. It's a revival and no one is making the connection
because they don't know about these things in the past. So just to go back around the block here,
when the tower who can build the tower on sand is not necessarily on one hand, yes, you don't want
to build it on an unstable ground. But it also means that you have to take action because once
the tower is designed or its idea is incepted on the sandbox, right? It needs it needs further
action. You know, in other words, if you look at, let's say, the biblical cliche on that it states,
do you have the wherewithal to build it? Right. No one sets out. Why should you even set out
designing it if you're if you do not comprehend how are you going to get the wherewithal to build
it? Right. Is an interesting thing. So I just wanted to throw that in as a little tidbit of
uncommon history that people could look into the sandboxes that were used to draw on and also the
Pinax tablets that people used to carry around to take notes. If you look at what's called the
New Testament, there's several areas there where the scribes had when the Christ was speaking,
they had pulled out their little Pinaxes and had written on them what he was saying. And
even today, a board that one writes on in Greek is known as the Pinakos.
So that's one of the cliches, perhaps that is not necessarily dispelled, but perhaps we gave a
little more background into maybe we could say. So the thing that I want to dispel is someone
had once sent me recently, not too recently, but let's say recently, a made me aware of a group
that was supposedly discussing things biblical and historical in that in that text. And I said,
well, they're not really that accurate. Some of their points seem to be on point. And so I
are accurate, but they tend to have fallen away. And let me just throw this out. When you approach
any of these divine writs, if you put too much energy into them, too much zeal, and you focus
on just one thing, you will be rewarded with distraction, and you will be spun off. And then
you will be focusing on things that are not even in the text. I'm just going to repeat that for a
you will be rewarded with distraction. Is there a is there a mechanism here, either in thought or in?
Yes, greed and gluttony. A lot of people, a lot of people jump into a bit of information and try
to reveal it, which may be truth to help society. If anyone that embarks, by the way, and this is
might sound dogmatic, but it's too bad if it does. If you figure something out, and whether it's in
a discovery, materialistic, mechanistic, or spiritual, or whatever concept, an idea,
and you start promoting it heavily, as being the answer to saving the world, you will be rewarded
with should we call them rewards, you will be sent down a path that will ultimately lead to
your destruction, if not physical, at least destructive causes. If you look at anyone
throughout society that says this will save the world, or we have to make the world a better place,
if they push the issue, they will be quickly stomped down. Sometimes not necessarily quickly,
it's not because of the malevolent forces, but also the benevolent forces. And we've discussed
this in some detail, we might pick it up in the future again. But just to go back to what this
information was regarding things biblical, this person had sent me this. And one of the comments
on the comments of what these people were saying, because we're speaking about the return of a
certain biblical figure known as the Christ, and the comment was, was no one can really know.
So this guy's full of crap. Now, what they do is they typically cite a verse in Matthew,
which is no one knows the day or the hour. Right? Well, that has nothing to do with his return. If
you look it up, I believe it's in what's called Matthew 24 area of Matthew 2426. Something like
that, I believe, I'm just paraphrasing in that area. If you look at when the Christ is asked,
and he says, well, people tend to extract that and say, well, no one knows the day of the hour,
they think it has to do with the return of a biblical character, it has nothing to do as such.
It has to do with the question that is asked prior that he is answering with that answer,
which is when will the earth and the sun and the heavens wither away or go away,
or wear out, and he says, no one knows the day or the hour. It's regarding the entropic
wearing away of the heavenly bodies. Isn't that interesting? Has this ever been brought up to you
personally, Seth, by the way, in context? I mean, no. Sometimes you and I can have a personal
discussion or private discussion on air. Everyone can just. Well, in day and hour, day and hour are
relatively specific as well. Yes. Apply the week or the week or the year. Yeah. Or the month. Yeah.
Or the month. Yeah. But the whole point is it doesn't even have anything to do with what people
think it does. Right. And it's seemingly tying that back in with the crowd audio clip that
was played. It ties in perfectly again. What I'd like to just say with that is that pretty much
anything and everything that I'm seeing right now, mainstream or alternative, is really following that
crowd outline. As you know, not to be overreaching, but it is quite accurate to say that that's spot
on. You know, the other point I wanted to bring up today is the other. Well, actually, the two
points. One was the crowd. And if anyone wants to look into it, of course they can. Gustave Le Bon.
But the other two things I wanted to bring up, which are large subjects or how people are addicted
to really low quality stuff as a general rule, as a general consensus, as a general application,
wholesale application, not necessarily specific because there are still some quality
things in the world. But the general majority of the people at large are addicted to low quality
stuff. Again, we mentioned what is it that was we could say golden arches, billions and billions
served. Right. Even having a conversation about that earlier, actually. Yes. And then a lot of
cheap goods at low prices, you know, which are actually, you know, fine with a couple, a lot of
sayings about what happens when you buy things that are cheap at a low price. You know. So,
yeah, this whole thing, also the information that's being put out. It's like the low hanging
fruit. That's it's not only low hanging fruit. It's just rotten. It's just decaying. It's past
its freshness, way past its freshness. But, you know, you could say that about the quality. But
and then, of course, within that quality would be there's no accuracy, no precision, and there's
actually no truth, even though it's expounded by those that are part of the truthism movement.
So these things are not necessarily frustrating, but it's just interesting to discuss. Not too
much, because if you want evidence of it, just tune in anywhere and everywhere, whether it's
mainstream or alternative, and you will see what we had just brought up, quality of a low ranking
or low quality addiction to stuff. And it seems like the less accurate, less precise and the
lower the quality of the information, the more subscribers you get and the more donations you get
and the more people discuss it. You got to be really excited about it, too. Yeah. And it tends
to create excitement as well. You can you can yell at people. You can. Not that they shouldn't be
yelled at. They should be. Yeah. But maybe with with some maybe with something with some substance
behind it. Yeah. And the other thing I wanted to bring up are the concept of the pranksters. Now,
like, what's a prankster? You know, well, it's interesting. I haven't looked it up etymologically,
but I think at one point I meant to do harm or against the will of another or something like
that. And when I when I say the pranksters, I'm talking about a third of you wholesale humanity
that are partaking in this and the other third are supporting it. And the other third are just
scratching their head, wondering what the hell is going on, either poised to be victimized by it,
because when I say victimized, yes, because there are spiritual entities behind it. And what I mean
by the pranksters are your entitled classes, you know, like your legal society, your medical
society, your political society, your scientific society. Even those offering services are
pranksters, you know, like car mechanics tend to be pranksters as well. You know. Yeah. And not
to actually put them down as a group. But, you know, there's once I saw a thing where they took
a car to be fixed and they were charged several hundred to replace a part and they did not replace
the part and they had to put like a secret marking on it. You know, this is not to get off
as a car mechanic. But let me to bring us back to the word prankster. It comes from prank and stir.
It stirs a suffix one who does. Yeah. But prank is a ludicrous trick. 1520s of uncertain origin,
perhaps related to obsolete verb prank, just decorate or dress up from the mid 15th century
related to the middle low German prank, which is to display or display a comparer,
also Dutch pranken, German pranken to make show or to strut. And the verb in the modern
sense is also from the 1520s. So a ludicrous trick is from decorate or dress up.
There's there's the etymology. What about the thumbtack on the seat?
Yeah, that would be. Well, let's see what's ludicrous.
Also spoke of spells earlier just before we get too far away from it. And that's one of those
words that's interesting because it means exactly what it says. We all spell. Right.
And words have, you know, there is I don't know if power is the right the right word to describe
what it is that words have. But there is a lot that can be done with them,
obviously, from giving someone direction and having that direction carried out. You know,
that's one very obvious, you know, use or power that words have.
Like sand.
Like, yes, absolutely.
Like sand on the sand table.
That's right. And if you throw enough of them into a bag, you have a makeshift weapon, right?
Enough grains of sand, enough words, right? Yeah. Quantity is certainly not greater than
quality in power as far as that goes.
Just to interject, folks, don't be impressed by large numbers because this is how the cosmos works.
The formative beings that created everything like big numbers, the cells in your body,
the cells and the atoms and the molecules in the room.
Yeah, pie.
Sample.
Look up at the sky at a clear night. They like big numbers.
Don't be impressed by them. The numbers are not large to impress you.
They're there because that's how things are done.
But when we speak about quality and quote, unquote, truth and things of this matter,
that we're actually directing it towards the very few, like four or five people
on the planet, maybe, you know, really stuff we can get into a discussion,
which is very short in the future.
They're about 7000, which is the one out of the million deal.
You know, 7 billion or so.
Don't be impressed by 7 billion people on the planet and you have to save anyone
or get anything different to happen because there's more than that.
More, more cells than that in your body, perhaps, or who knows, right?
Or molecules in the room.
Don't be impressed by 7 billion at all.
There's always been a very few and there will always be a very few for the interim.
Let's say for this interim.
So, yeah, the pranksters and let me just can I give an example regarding pranking
and the legal society, by the way, I'm just going to throw this in.
I was listening to a recorded court conversation yesterday,
and this was from a federal court case.
And without giving what the case was about, the person who had made the defense,
the victim, the defendant showed clearly how the prosecution was way out of bounds
and unfounded with their charges.
But the prosecution couldn't address that.
All they could say was, well, he had signed a plea.
And according to the plea agreement, he could not appeal it.
And because he got he agreed to a plea, he received a benefit.
So now he's operating under a benefit.
So this is pure pranking, you know, what you what you see in here,
this the same thing with the medical society, you know.
Well, you know, you agreed, you know, you came to me, you know, for it.
You know, you were given a list of the side effects, you know,
even though it's like one point font, right?
And, you know, the scientific community is pranking you folks.
Pretty, pretty good, too.
I mean, we don't need to get into how they're doing it.
But I mean, just I think I gave the example last week of how
alleged the alleged magnetic field of the earth is caused by molten iron.
Go look up how magnetic molten iron is.
It's not, folks.
Curie point is way below that means where it loses its magnetism.
So you're being pranked all around.
Now, when you combine that concept of being
would you say people are being led by pranksters?
I would say they are.
I will say certainly putting on a show.
Yeah.
And the pranks, are they harmful?
Yes, because, for example, going back to what the legal society did
to this individual, they had him in the can in jail.
They said, if you don't sign this, we're going to keep you in here for 20 years.
So they use threatened arrest.
The same with the medical society.
I've seen certain medical technicians and they say, well, legally,
I can't tell you, you know what to do, you know, regarding that treatment.
But I legally I can tell you this, which tells me that the legal society
controls medical society.
And also I have run into an attorney or someone who worked like as a
paralegal type that was editing scientific textbooks.
And I said, well, what the hell do you know about scientific textbooks?
As I don't.
And he was part of the editing department.
So anyway, the level of pranking, the same if you look at what they call people
sitting at the pulpit or people that have degrees of divinity, degrees.
I mean, you go and you just bring up a five year old, let's say an eight year old.
Let's give him that because five year old would be too humiliating.
Let's say an eight to 12 year old.
Bring to anyone who has a degree in or speaks from the pulpit of any religion,
by the way, anything in the text that they allegedly subscribe to and what
they immediately shy away and say, well, see, it doesn't matter.
It's what you believe in.
It really that stuff doesn't matter.
You know, so pranksters, again, in the religious community.
And by the way, spiritually, the pranksters or socially from the cosmic perspective,
the pranksters in the religious using that term in air quotes, for example,
community are going to be held at higher regard than mass murderers also, by the way,
because a mass murderer is not taking up directly the representation of a spiritual being
where the religious culprits are.
So, yeah, folks, so I had an email question.
What happens to someone, for example, in terms of judgment, you know,
like a Mother Teresa versus an Adolf Hitler?
I just answered that question, I think.
So anyway.
Yeah, the three aspects of combining the elements of Gustav Le Bon's The Crowd,
humanity's wholesale addiction to low quality stuff, let's say stuff.
You kind of look up what that word stuff means.
Kind of it sounds it sounds good.
And it's got it's one of those phonetic words like slush or fluff or stuff.
Stuff to furnish with.
By the way, this is on Adam online.
Stuff a verb to furnish with goods, provisions or reinforce or troops to pad,
upholster, fill out from a stuff, a toffee or a toffee or a toffee.
Probably also part of stuff to fill, create a cram full fill with food, drink or gorge
to clog with padding.
Interesting.
Cookery sense.
OK, so yeah, it's to furnish with.
OK, so it's a verb.
Yeah.
And the noun is quilted material worn under chain mail.
Interesting.
Under chain mail.
So I wonder if it's so specific that it's quilted material worn under chain mail,
because chain mail is a form of armor, let's say, right?
Chain mail, meaning like armoring, you know, not like that, not as a chain or.
You keep going with that when it gets better.
OK, to equip or stock with, according to French sources from old high German stuff
fun to plug stuff or or from related Frankish where to stop.
But strong objections to this.
OK.
All right.
OED has strong sense extended to material for working within various trades.
Matter of an unspecified kind, meaning narcotic dope drug is attested 1929.
The stuff.
OK.
Slang to no one's stuff.
Have a grasp on the subject recorded from 1927.
And by the way, since we're going on a little etymological tip here.
How many times have you ever heard of?
Someone saying I'm an academic, you should listen to me.
They don't say this directly, but I'm an academic, right?
So it's prestigious, right?
By the way, English professor or not an English major.
I'm sorry, not English professor, but an English major.
Let me know that he was an English major the other day in conversation
because I started talking to him about words and his I can quote him.
Did you know that you're talking to an English major?
Did he say academic club?
He did not say academic.
He was that was.
Yeah, where I was going with that.
That was what he said to imply that I asked him if he knew what the word nice meant.
He did not.
No, of course.
Yeah, because, you know, the more education you get, it's kind of here's another prank.
The education system is a prank.
Anyone that's gotten more than eighth grade education in the public or private school
system has you could generally say has suffered almost what could be known as irreparable damage.
And it would probably take you more than double the amount of time to clear yourself of it.
And then you have these people that actually progress through beyond the eighth grade and
are proud to say that they have gone to undergraduate graduate studies.
It's a prank, folks.
You've been pranked these.
And by the way, we're going to read the definition of the term academic.
And if you think this has any prestige to it, and we're going to tell you it doesn't.
And now that I've told you, it doesn't.
If you have the look on your face like a baby seal right before it gets clubbed.
Well, here it comes.
Relating academic on the item online relating to an academy collegiate scholarly from Latin
academic us or the or of the academy from academia, meaning you're ready.
Here it comes.
Theoretical, not practical, not leading to a decision.
So for all you academics out there, sorry to hear it.
Well, I'm not I shouldn't be sorry because I didn't make them do it.
But talk about wholesale low ranking addiction and pranking.
Oh, man.
And the crowd.
Oh, how many times have you heard in public someone say, well, this person or especially
guests that are introduced as having these high degrees and things like that as being
something good?
I mean, talk about the crowd mentality.
Yeah.
Oh, this guy is.
I was on a recent discussion saying, well, I talk to people are from MIT.
I'm like, I mean, morons in training.
But anyway, so the idea of the of the low ranking wholesale, low quality addiction, the
pranksters and the crowd mentality all thrown together is an uncommon way to view what the
common existence is about.
Yeah, let's repeat that for a moment.
Most people have a common existence, even in their timekeeping.
I think B.C. is before common era and a right and Anno Domini and all these things.
The work schedule that they're on is even common.
It's based on the crowd mentality, the addiction to low quality stuff and also being led by
pranksters and the pranksters you will find in your entitled classes.
You know, which which is not difficult to surmise in summary that they are pranking
you, because if you approach anyone that's a specialist, a publicly specialist and that's
part of a society that's known as such, they're simply pranking you.
So, you know, people are going out discussing, how are we going to fix the world?
And how many times have you heard it based on some religious group, right, or some evil
oligarch?
Right.
I assure you that even if those groups did not exist, you would still be subject to the
crowd mentality and addiction to low quality stuff and the pranksters.
So at this point, you know.
This I could surmise and say this is an uncommon commentary on what is common.
Now, if that didn't lose most of the people, I don't know what will.
But Seth, you still with us?
I did not lose me.
I'm still here.
Okay, great.
I would say that's a very accurate, broad brush stroke of the common reality.
Those three aspects, the crowd mentality, again, the addiction to low quality stuff
and being ruled by pranksters.
Taking a little pause there, let it settle in for the five listeners we have.
But nonetheless, yeah.
All right.
So we've covered the pranksters.
Somewhat, somewhat.
Yeah, yeah, it's the aspect of the the pranking.
Did we mention also when I say, well, somewhat we yeah, we covered them broad brush in general
point of view, but there's so much specifics that could be gone into, right?
We didn't mention the financial society or the current, you know, what they call financing
that higher society.
They're pranksters also.
In the there's another way of looking at it, and it involves just a little bit of etymology,
I suppose.
But we're currently all aspects of society.
You mentioned it earlier that, you know, medical textbooks are edited by attorneys, by lawyers.
Here comes our music.
Yeah, we'll get into that after the break.
Yes, Uncommon Sense.
We'll be back in a few folks.
Greetings and welcome back to Uncommon Sense.
Hello, Seth.
Are you with us?
OK, and Seth will be joining us momentarily.
And we were discussing just before the break.
What were we discussing, Seth?
We were discussing the society or at least the society that we're all experiencing right now
wholesale that we've been talking a little bit about pranksters and how we are.
Let's say that those that lead us, whether we're being ruled by them is
another another matter.
But certainly those who are leading us currently or at least pretending to or
have that pretension are pranksters.
Pretty much.
To illustrate that a little bit further, I figured you had mentioned earlier in the conversation
medical textbooks and how they can tell you some things legally and legally.
They can't tell you some things and that their textbooks and their operations,
what they can and cannot do is dictated to them by attorneys, by lawyers.
And that's just medical textbooks, certainly, but not just medical textbooks.
All textbooks, all textbooks are are edited by lawyers.
They must pass through that.
That's that's how things get published.
I would go further than that and say just about anything that is published
for mass market distribution has some level of editing done by
legal staff, attorneys, lawyers, et cetera, not just books.
What we can say to each other in conversation, what we can wear,
what we can eat, what we are told is healthy, what we are told is unhealthy,
what we how we are allowed to travel, where we are allowed to travel.
All of these things, all of these things are dictated, enforced by varying agencies.
But the dictates all come from attorneys, from lawyers.
There's a word for that in another language.
That most of you will be familiar with on one level or another.
And that's how she done.
That's the word.
That's that's where in English we get the word Satan.
The originally in the language that we take it from the Hebrew,
or at least what is healthy and it's as well today.
Yeah.
Is is how she done the adversary?
The hawk being the and shut down being where we get the word Satan, which just means adversary.
And there are a few passages where it is specifically referring to
a particular adversary, but it is used in the text often to denote any adversary.
And so in in the courts, in in Hebrew speaking countries, Israel,
they they refer to the the lawyers on either side of any case is how she done as the Satan.
And we're currently so you can take that.
And very, very literally, we are currently living in a society in a society that is ruled
and governed by the Satan's hashtag on.
Yeah, no, it's interesting.
Just to comment on the ridiculousness of what one can call information gathering
is there's a lot of people more in the alternative.
Actually, I don't hear it much on the mainstream other than in Hollywood,
dubbing people Satanists because they have revived
certain minor deities from the ancient world of Egypt and Canaan.
These people are not Satanists.
They're simply it's actually in a lot of their temples.
They use the name of the ancient dark lord or deity that they have revived.
You know, but because of the crowd mentality,
you have people that come out and say this is satanic or yes, it is adversarial,
you know, but but they call them Satanists.
What's interesting about that is, again,
it's the addiction to low quality communication or low quality information.
And the crowd mentality, but but here's the thing, you know, earlier, Seth to mention
how I mentioned one third of the humanity right now are clearly in the prankster mode.
The other third are clearly supporting them and the other third is waiting
pretty much are subject to it as well.
What's interesting is a lot of the people that are actually coming out
trying to make commentary on Satanists and all the bad ruling oligarchs,
you know, and, oh, corporations, you know,
they are actually taking on the form of pranksters themselves.
The activists, the what would you call them?
People coming out and trying to discuss these matters to inform society
and the alternative community are actually taking on the the characteristic of a prankster,
because I've noticed very often if you try to approach,
which many of them are approachable in the alternative community, let's just say,
regarding the accuracy of their statements,
they take on immediately the typical defense that a prankster does,
which is immediately try to reduce the information to the level of opinion
or discredit or discount the validity of it, even though anyone can see it.
So I just wanted to throw that in there necessarily as a dig to the alternative media community,
because it's not they don't need.
I mean, anyway, there's an old there's an old saying about a fool being presumptive,
you know, that it's not proven that they are such until they start speaking.
But nonetheless, we also wanted to bring up the point that
when people do use that term, what it really means.
And I think, Seth, it doesn't really mean anything sometimes to bring up
what something really means, because it makes their whole venue go away.
You know, venue, you know, meaning whether they have websites about it
or they get a lot of hits on YouTube, man, you know,
I think YouTube will pay a thousand bucks for a million hits.
So, yeah, you're really putting out a lot of rubbish information for pennies.
But but but nonetheless, you know who you are out there.
Pretty much. Well, anyway, the whole idea to bring forward things about
that are being discussed with precision and accuracy will not only make you unpopular,
not only will you have no listenership other than four or five people.
But but the thing is, I believe it's something that should be done.
And when I say I believe in it, meaning that if we bring up the definition of whatever,
we're using a good reference that will not only hold as its definition currently,
but it did hold its definition in the past, but also will hold that definition in the future.
So these things tend to be unpopular and that's why it's called uncommon sense.
So Seth, I also brought up the concept of
the economic society or the finance society as being pranksters.
You know, the other day I was listening to someone saying that they were
concerned about money being transferred and the banking or financial institution
was delaying the transfer of the funds. And I just had to laugh my ass off, as they say,
you know, because banks cannot transfer money any more than electronically or by wire any more
than you can transfer a tuna fish sandwich by wire.
You know, this is still part of the addiction to the low quality thought
by put on to the crowd by the pranksters and the people in the media, alternative and mainstream,
are still parroting this information as well as the information about making the world a better
place. How are they going to make the world better when they're rank and floating well
above their heads? They're way below the waterline in junk quality information.
So, and of course, locked into the crowd mentality. There is no solution within
what is being put out right now, wholesale across the board, mainstream or alternative,
other than the suggestion would be to set yourself apart from it. There's nothing wrong with being
familiar with the ridiculousness that's being expounded out there or being put out.
But other than being familiar with it, being the familiar out, maybe too much coffee,
I can't say that word, being familiar with it is there's no value in it at this point.
The only solution that can be granted would be to set yourself apart from it and focus on
food, clothing and shelter as being of the highest quality you want to afford.
And on the information side, if you had a filter for what is inaccurate,
you would pretty much go to any venue at the moment and it would be silent. It would pretty
much filter out everything that you're listening to, except for the or is or basic terms like that.
Again, just to tie that back into something that's very important, which is the economic
society or the finance society is not only paramount in the prankster explanation of how
society is being governed or provided with, but the people that are supposedly giving out good
information are also subject to it. Why? Because I had heard an individual discussing that there
was perhaps potential controversy because the banking institution was delaying the transfer
or the wire transfer of money. So there is no such thing, by the way. And this would lead
into a discussion of how the economic system works. And I've been threatening that for a while,
discussing how finances or how the credit based economy really works. But Seth, I hear an echo
on your apologies, but it's OK. But nonetheless, it's just a threat at this point,
because it's so simple. It's almost in the sub sensible realm, because when you discuss the
credit based economy, people all of a sudden think, oh, we're discussing finance. It's debt based.
It's debt based. There is no debt if the credit is not based on any substance.
So you're not given something on an IOU, folks. Yeah, debt is based upon something and their
debt being the lack of something and that something is nothing.
And yeah, there is there is no debt. A hundred percent. A hundred times zero is still
zero. Correct. So but the thing is, when people but the thing is, again,
let me just do this is not to condescend, but I'm going to just say it anyway. If we're not
Seth, did you know that if we're not putting out low quality information,
we're not going to get any listeners? Did you know that? I do.
If we put out high quality information, we lose the listenership in general.
Statistically, yeah, there might be one one or two left. Someone I mean,
someone's bound to turn it and tune in on accident. So.
Yeah, there's got to be four or five, which I would suggest. It seems to be consistent.
There's four or five people out there that can stomach, you know, the idea of quality
information, not not because we are putting it out that it's quality. It's that we are putting
out quality information not to tout anything and not to be arrogant about it, not to condescend
or anything. But if someone drives up in a Ferrari, that is a quality car, regardless of who
is behind the wheel. You see, fortunately and unfortunately, let me just this might get us
in trouble somehow, but I might just say this is the only place that I know of that puts out
quality information bar none that I've run into. There's got to be others as well, but I haven't
run into them. Hence, then, maybe the indirect necessity to do what we call in common sense.
But just to tie it back to threatening to discuss how the economic system works,
let's just do it in tidbits. I think we'd bring up the economic side of things every time we meet
here. But let's just say this. I'm going to say it a few times here in different ways,
maybe the same way. Financial institutions do not wire money. They cannot wire money any more
than a restaurant can wire you a tuna fish sandwich or a steak or a pizza or a vegan salad.
Think about that for a moment. Actually, don't think about it. You'll get yourself
into a lot of trouble. But listen to what is being said here. Financial institutions
cannot wire money, do not wire money, period. Just think about that for a moment.
Well, what the heck is going on? We'll discuss that in the future. But you have to keep in mind
anything economic is going to be discussed based on the definitions provided on what is known as
a credit based economy. And of course, no one wants to look at that, right? Just like no one
wants to look at anything anymore. Actually, you do want to look at things if they're low quality
and they're based within the thought process known as the crowd mentality that has been put out by
pranksters. Think about that for a moment. Well, it makes sense. And the fact that if
you've ever tried to find the foundations of thought or ideas that are currently taken for
granted as being accurate by different groups and individuals, and then you start to realize that
the foundations aren't really there to be found, if you'll forgive the overuse of the word found.
But then it kind of makes sense like, oh, I get it because it's all a prank. It's all a show.
And everyone has just found their part to play. And those that are confused about things
have just not found their part to play. Well, the thing about the show is those on stage are
lying and those in the audience are swearing to it. You have a man sawing a woman in half on stage
and putting her back together and all the people in the audience will swear that they saw that happen.
You see this on how information is being dispensed. But you know, you have to realize,
though, from a single point of view, that the material aspect of the body, you know, the carnal
flesh, toes, head, blood, breathing, that carnal side enjoys emotional stimulus. Right?
You know, there's no reason to be a robot. There's emotions for a reason. It ties in with
the biological functions quite well. And they tune in and if they hear information,
that gives them stimulus. In other words, they can they recognize the information because they
have heard it from memory. They recognize it because it's in their memory of something they've
heard prior. Like, for example, radioactive material, you know, oh, that's bad. That's bad.
Okay. And then they will gravitate towards listening to hours of tripe that is completely
inaccurate. Or they will hear about, oh, some very wealthy oligarchs are going to destroy mankind.
And they from memory bring up and recall they heard something about that before and they fall
into it and they feel emotionally charged by listening to the low quality imparting of
information again regarding that subject. Why? Because they have admittedly or unadmittedly
fallen into the crowd mentality, which is if the information is not superficial,
it doesn't quite resonate, let me just say, with them, right? Because they've tuned themselves,
just like a tuning fork resonates to its corresponding frequency with other tuning forks.
They've sort of tuned themselves, humanity at this point, and wholesale. There are a few people
that are not, let's say a few, meaning a couple of few left on the planet. Most of the people
have tuned themselves into this low quality stuff, just like what I might call a corrupted palate.
People that eat a lot of junk food tend to have a palate for it. And when they are presented with
something that is more wholesome or pure, they tend to not recognize it as such. The palate is
sort of corrupted or overwhelmed and desynthesized. And this would be the commentary on what information
is, because this is an information-based sonic experience. I mean, otherwise we could play Bach or
YouTube or some other recorded information, or maybe Seth can play a live guitar.
This is a sonic experience, and what we're trying to do is sonically impart some uncommon
ways of looking at things, where someone that is listening to what is being said here, perhaps
can maybe retune if it's up to them, or use it as a contrast, because there is no contrast. You see,
when there's no hot, there's no cold. You have a polarity. And what is going on,
and what has been going on in wholesale, and will, is this crowd mentality is moving people
into this amorphous globule mass. And because there's a lack of contrast when the crowd is formed,
there is lack of seeing the difference if something is good or bad or true or not,
or unfounded and superficial versus based on something. So in essence, trying to provide
information that is based on something or founded or lawful, you know, this is something, Seth,
we haven't been bringing up often in conversation, but one simple way, and by the way, people hate
the term lawful because they don't want to, well, anyway, that's another. Now I'm going to get into
like a personal commentary on humanity, but ask yourself, is it lawful? What I mean by that is,
if you see a triangle, it should, having three sides, and 180 degrees as the sum total
angle of the interior would be a lawful triangle. If someone shows you something with four sides,
it is not a lawful triangle. You see, there are things that are lawful and things that are
unlawful. And right now, the majority of society in what they're engaging in,
even in the very dispersal or dispensement of information is unlawful.
Meaning that, for example, when you tune into a particular
venue that is giving you information or commentary on something, regardless of the topic,
if it's going to be opinion based, it should be reminded or should be discussed as this is
strictly an opinion or disclaimer should be given. And in many cases, what I do hear often
being put out there to the public sonically or in print, should basically have a disclaimer and
almost for every other few things that are being said, because people are walking away,
listening to things that are unlawful. In other words, not based on what the subject can be based
on or should be based on, and memorializing that in their minds in memory, as something viable or
something usable. So what that means, in essence, is this is like the anti crowd mentality, what
are you using the faculties, what we've been given as people, you have a mind that can
properly rationalize things, and it's not being used. It's pretty much basically taking in
information as an emotional experience, is what you're hearing in concordant with previous things
that you've heard, that make you feel good, or not necessarily make you feel good that get you
agitated. And somehow guided the mind to say, Oh, yeah, we have to do something about this,
because it's a bad thing. But if you look at what's being discussed about what should be done
about it is, and the thing itself that is bad, there is no basis for it. In other words, the
basis for it is not there. It's again, fiat. No. So how does one get away from that, and
not necessarily that one should most people are tend to have a level of freedom of choice,
let's say, they have a free will, and they go about their lives doing what they believe they
they choose is right for them. And who is anyone else to tell them what's right or wrong.
But that's why I believe one of the outlines of today, coming together on Uncommon Sense,
discussing the three various aspects, a general outline would be the crowd mentality,
the addiction, the wholesale addiction to low quality stuff in general, and being ruled by
pranksters is a general is a very good general outline to explain what is going on. And this is
across the board, folks. There is nothing really going on right now, even though there is because
we've kind of discussed it's this part of the world is springtime, the other part of the
world is fall. On one side, it's a planting. And on the other side, it's a harvesting.
Let's say part of the season. And when you're looking at the planting or the springtime,
from a social aspect of planting things, you'll notice that it's fairly quiet. And just to tie
it back to the beginning of the first hour, discussing that people come to these information
type venues to get information that are socially based, even though I'll be at you might tune into
a cooking show or how to fix the car kind of thing or something specific or reference material.
Generally, people go to media in general, to hear social commentary, what's happening in the
quote, unquote world, what's going on, right. And the best way to make things sensible is obviously,
where the noise is, is not really where it's at. Right. And not even when the dust settles,
because then the picture kind of changes again. It's always where it's quiet. And I believe
you know, most people tend to gravitate towards various forms of media to see and hear about what
is in the news today. And they tend to take it in daily or weekly blocks, or sometimes seasonal
blocks, even though they they fail to refer to what is going on to the seasons. Like, for example,
I think there's still a little bit of talk about a financial collapse coming next month regarding
the US dollar, which is a complete joke on every aspect, because financial next month now. Yeah,
again, let me just put it this way. This is an open challenge. If anyone out there is a
commentator on economics or economic matters, I dare you and I challenge you to get in touch with
us at uncommon radio.com www.uncommonradio.com and we will bring you on air and we will tear you to
pieces within five seconds. As a matter of fact, Seth in the Greek will not do it. We will bring an
eight-year-old on that we will coach for no more than 40 seconds before you come on air and you will
be discarded immediately. Any financial commentator out there, it doesn't matter who you are. You know
who you are if you're listening, because all of these financial commentators bar none are basically
discussing things as if there is still a substance-backed economy. If they don't discuss
in that realm, they bring up like there's any relevancy to a country's currency.
They don't understand anything, but here's the thing. The more they threaten
financial collapse or financial doom and gloom, the more people tune in and the more subscribers
they get. Why? Because it's the crowd mentality and people are addicted to low-quality stuff
and all these guys that are commentating on economics are strictly taking their information
by watching the pranksters. In other words, the pranksters are lying to it and the economic
commentators are swearing to it. What are they lying about? That there even is a possibility of
financial collapse because you are under a credit-based economy, folks.
How do we know? Just go read the codes and the laws. Oh no, he said I have to read, I have to
study. Oh no, that's horrible. Why can't I just pay someone to do it for me like I can go to school
maybe? Is there a meme? Do we have a meme for this yet, Gregg? Well, the thing that we came up with
is truthism is the new movement now, right? It's the truthism. Yeah, and there is no truth in the
truthism movement, folks. But anyway, it's so simple to demolish what humanity is basing their
reality on. It's not even worth demolishing. It's kind of like you can knock it over with a feather.
There's nothing really there that's in their minds, but yet they're being guided with what
they want to afford to be guided with. What I mean by what they want to afford to be guided with
is they actually dedicate energy into taking in junk information because wholesale, humans are
typically addicted to low-quality stuff at the moment and it just tends to be the reality of it.
It's an easy thing to objectify. But in essence, going back to the financial reality, I like to
rant about the financial people because money is almost like a cure-all in a social setting,
by the way, right? And we've in part discussed what money is and in part discussed maybe what
credit is and things like that, but maybe one day we'll dedicate two hours to it and really lose
the crowd, quote-unquote. But in essence, it is springtime. It is slow and it's planting and it's
quiet, supposedly. But one thing that you will always hear the Greek and Seth discuss, perhaps,
is what is coming. Yes, it is possible to know the future. Anyone and everyone that does things that
last more than a moment or so expect something from that action, right? And that expectation
is based on something rational, right? If your hands are dirty and you walk up to what's called
a sink and you turn on the faucet and grab some soap and properly dispense soap on the hands and
let the water run and you move your hands under the water, your hands will get clean. That is
a simple action to define that the reason why people approach soap and water with dirty hands
is because they know in the future, in the short coming future, their hands will be clean. That's
why people engage in action, because they have a sense of the future event that will come if
they engage in that action. And this is how pretty much everyone operates. But again, just to tie it
back to coming together to media, why people come to or go to media is to hear what's called the news
based on social socialism or truthism, to hear about what is going on today or a week, because
they seem to have no more than about a week attention span, by the way. If you are wondering what is
coming when we've again, just to tie it in with what we've discussed is what you're witnessing in society
right now is the precursor to a Middle East Union. So, if that helps, this is a very tall general statement
to make, but if anyone can take that to heart, we'll very soon realize that the true explanation
behind what's going on, you know, when they approach media, and they see and hear what is called the news,
you know, because you will see, especially for the past decade or two, or three, there has been
tremendous focus in that part of the world. And why? Very simply, if you look at a racetrack,
where is the starting line? Same racetrack, where is the finishing line?
It's exactly what is going on, folks. It's really simple. So, when you understand and comprehend and see
that the soon-to-manifest future events will be focused in the, quote-unquote, what's called Middle East area.
Now, when I say Middle East, if you took a map of the world, and you looked at the main landmass,
and you, let's say, eliminate the concept of the Suez Canal and such, you'll see that the entire continent
of Africa, Asia, and Europe are all connected as one mass. If you draw pretty much a diagonal through
that landmass, you will find the middle part of that landmass is in that general area we're discussing,
from the shores of Judea, going all the way east, perhaps even as far as to India, and is perhaps
north as Turkey, and a south as, hmm, would call the Negev and beyond, maybe the west coast of Africa,
or a bottom of Saudi Arabia, is that general area, that general central region. And also, what you
will be witnessing in the future is the southern Mediterranean, or let's say, northern Mediterranean,
or southern European rim countries like Turkey, Cyprus, and Greece, and northern, quote-unquote,
African countries, forming a loose alliance as a satellite group to this Middle East Union that's
going to be coming in the next decade or so. And the reason we keep bringing this up is because
we're getting closer that this time period, which will be ending in roughly two years,
will be the next seven-year time period where you will see the building up of this Middle East
Union. So you still have about two more years of the same stuff that you've been experiencing for
the past five or so, which is this repeat of events in the Middle East, but a repeat of this weekly
cycle of what's in the news now. And of course, let's put in another dig to our economic commentator
idiot friends, that of course, you will always, regarding the economy, be hearing of an impending
doom just about every month, which never comes, by the way. What you will see is a restriction of
credit. And of course, what the hell is credit? No one knows, right? Yes, you can find out if you
go and study the laws that are put together for which corresponding country you might be living
in. But of course, that requires study, and no one wants to do that, of course. Why do that? We
have YouTube, or we have wonderful hosts and internet shows and things like that, that'll tell
us and I assure you, you're getting no information. So anyway, you know, with that said, just kind of
wrapping up the idea of why people go to the media and whether it's mainstream or alternative is to
find out generally, what's going on in the news. And other than looking at the daily or weekly cycle,
it tends to be still this irrational disconnect that people are wholly relying on this sonic
stimulation of what or visual stimulation if they're reading on the topic. And fortunately,
for the psyche or the mind, it has it perhaps a built in what you might call protection mechanism,
because you'll notice that a lot of the things that they're reading about or discussing in the
news are unfounded, debased. And the protection mechanism does not allow for that to linger much
more than a week or so. That's why, for example, you know, if you look at the previous news cycles
that people discuss, especially in alternative media, is you have a missing plane, you have a
threat of an economic collapse, corrupt politician, and something is going to destroy the planet.
And then it repeats after a week or two or three or four, a missing plane, corrupt politician,
economic collapse, something is going to destroy the planet, and it just keeps repeating. The
reason why it repeats is because people have installed or pre installed perhaps a safety
mechanism not to remember or to kind of like numb themselves out to what they're perceiving,
because they know it doesn't make any sense, but they don't want to look into
what does make sense about it, finding out what it's based on. So, but that's it.
Yeah, good. I've read a quote from was it was it Morgan or was it one of the presidents
who said that if the people knew how the banking system worked,
there would be riots in the streets the next day.
So, yeah, yeah, well, essentially here, here, let's throw this out real quick. Essentially,
it's a credit based economy. So when you're when people are born, they they're pledged by
their parents into their bodies and everything that they're going to do into a quote unquote
system, whatever it is, it's a monarchy of socialist communist capitalism. And by the
way, capitalism just means that when you're done using or building something, you destroy it,
so no one else can use it after you. But anyway, when you're when you put together a
credit economy, you basically get everyone to put everything that they have everything they will
have into the system. So it works. And you have this giant trust that's put together and it's
being managed by the legal society. Oops. pranksters. So there you go. That's it in a nutshell.
All right. Yep. So yeah, so people, you know, tend to ask questions like there's one in chat,
how do you save a house from foreclosure? That is really a big question. It's actually a small
question. You're dealing first of all, you're dealing with pranksters. The definitions need
to be looked at. You're not saving anything from a foreclosure. There's there's many aspects to it.
And, you know, and that, at this point, I would not direct anyone in a form of advice on
how to deal with that. But the more you study, the better off you're going to be.
And don't be emotional about it. With anything that's critical, like for example,
there was a couple of situations brought up, whether it's, you know, cliche or whatever,
where it's difficult for a surgeon to operate on someone in his family. Right? They tend to
have someone else do it because they're emotionally attached. You know, when you do
things that are critical. So the more the more rational you are, the better off you'll be in
any situation. But but by the way, Seth, we didn't bring up which we tend to bring up very often.
You also illustrated earlier how the legal society or these level of pranksters have engaged in
almost every aspect of society today. What we have brought up before, and at least the Greek
has been saying for over a decade, is the legal society is nothing more than the priesthood for
the revived goddess religion. What does that mean? They operate under what's called a justice
system or a justice department or whatever. That is the revival of the ancient goddess religion.
And if you're really want to bring up something that's obvious, I mean, it's right in your face,
kind of tell you, you know, it's all about justice, people want justice. But no one,
when I say no one, I mean, statistically, actually investigates what it is. And if you do it
objectively, you will discover that it is nothing more nothing less than the revival of the ancient
goddess religion. What do you know about ancient goddess religions? And if you answered nothing,
you probably answered right, because most people don't know anything about
ancient religions, and their and their revival. And this is exactly what you are in right now.
And why? You know, if you objectify the formation of societies and into nations,
they tend to adopt what's called a patron, or in this case, a matron deity. All nations have them.
I'm going to stop there and pause for a minute. All nations and all countries and societies have
a patron or matron deity. Think about it. So what is the most prominently featured
deity in Western society? It's a statue of a woman. She's blindfolded, holding scales or
some variation thereof. And how many people are questioning its origin, its function as such?
None. And if you do, you will discover that is nothing. It's a liturgy of this
revived goddess religion in a loose sense. It's done in a modern sense. At least the ancients
were acknowledging this, where the quote unquote, moderns are not because it's not because
moderns have been dumbed down. They've just strictly been numbed down. The dumbing down
ended a long, long time ago. The numbing down has been turned up. So you get it. Will that numbing
down wear off? No, it's going to get stronger and stronger. Can you actually acquire good sound data
or information while you're numbed out? Well, that's up to you to decide. But if you're going
to look at the legal pranksters running the entire show, right, sawing a woman in half,
putting it back together and everyone in the audience swearing to it, you're going to have
to find out what their patron god is. And you will find out that it is a revived goddess religion. And
again, what do you know about the revived goddess religions? And if your answer is nothing, you're
in good company. But that is exactly what is going on. It is an oversimplification of a lot of the
reasoning and social ills that you will see, but yet fail to recognize as such. So with that said,
I hope we are fulfilling some uncommon sense here. Now the chances of being able to go out,
oh, let's say, or go in, or acquire other individuals to have a sensible, rational conversation based on
the things discussed herein are next to nothing. So if you are within the sonic reach of what we
are discussing here, or what you are hearing, take good notes, you could always find it in
archives. And if you go to www.uncommonradio.com, you will see there are links there either to the
or to American Freedom Radio, which American Freedom Radio has provided a very well-organized,
well-placed, easy-to-access archive of these programs. And again, American Freedom Radio is
listener-supported, listener-sponsored, and actually here for the listener. I'm sure that
those that have put American Freedom Radio together did not do it so they can listen to
themselves. They did it for everyone else. So you might want to give them some support.
As a matter of fact, you should support them in some way or another. You know how to do that
by simply going to their homepage or anywhere on there and inquiring on how to provide some form
of assistance. And it is simple to do and it should be done simply because of the service
they provide, at least for what is being said here in its archival form and its ability to
be broadcast or sent to you live around this time every week. So I just wanted to throw that in
there because you folks know how to do it and you know what to do to support AFR and the folks
there. And let's just say it this way, or again as it might be condescending to some, simply because
they have uncommon sense here with Greek and Seth is a good enough reason to go ahead and sign over
your entire bank account or whatever is left into it. But anyway, so go ahead and donate something.
I'll just go out and say it. So please help them out. And I'm saying please meaning politely.
So Seth, are you with us again? Okay, we have Seth has a little grounding problem there. Okay, so
basically fulfilling this week's mission on the uncommon sense is just to reiterate again
because repetition does bear one of the elements of learning is what we want to do,
kind of evoke and bring forward is that the three parts that can be used as social commentary
for your typical surface dwelling earth inhabitants these days is Gustav Le Bon's analysis of
the crowd, the perpetual, seemingly perpetual low ranking thought or low quality addiction
of humanity at large. And also considering that the level of prankstership and the level of
pranksters that are dominating human society as being those three being the simple elements,
not the all the be all end all but a general brush stroke over the entire planet right now.
And what is going on here would say that is very founded and very accurate.
Meaning that what we've based on describing human society as being part of Gustav Le Bon's
description of crowd thinking, the humanity being again addicted to low quality stuff
across the board and also being run by pranksters can be founded. If you do a little bit of research
on these three aspects, you will find that it is a very good more than single category description
or outline or let's say a description which underpins human society at large today.
You would find that if you did a little bit of homework on these three aspects, the pranksters,
humans, addiction to low quality information and things and the crowd mentality, you will find that
to be true, not being true within the realm of this truthism that's being put forward today.
Because the idea of being common is not much of an idea anymore. It's just difficult. It's not
difficult to do. Just walk out your door and look like everyone else and think like everyone else.
We're not here to tell anyone that the world needs to be saved or changed.
Into what? You see, but the idea of being uncommon and learning how to set oneself apart
from the realm of the common might be the goal. Now, is it really a goal? Well, you know, it's
is it a be all end all? Is it something that you will achieve? No, because you're born and you die.
But it's about what you do in between. And all you have in between is time. And by the way,
if anyone says to you, I don't have any time, they're kind of delusional, because you're born
and you die. And in between, all you have is time. So if you want to translate, when someone says,
I don't have any time, if you translate that into translate that into a rational communication,
is what they're really telling you is that they don't know how to manage their time,
or they don't want to dedicate time. Right, that is the, the actual translation of that
into rational communication. So all you have is time, folks. And what you make of it, or what you
observe of it, or how you operate within that time that you have, you have a choice to either be
common or uncommon. And what you will discover is when you discover the realm of the uncommon,
you will see that what is being thought by the commoners or what is in common, it's best to
leave it all alone, and set yourself apart. And what I mean by set apart, it is not necessarily
a form of quarantine, but it is a form of if you're setting yourself apart, you don't complain
about it. You don't, you don't put your energy, or your thought into hopeless things that are masked
or described as being hopeful, or hope, a general hope, or a general faith, and things that are
unfounded. And that's all you pretty much see and hear everywhere today. As you hear things,
we have to make the world a better place or to have hope or to have faith, or to hope for a better
future. And there is absolutely no specifics. Let me just say it again. Absolutely no specifics.
Why? Because you might say, well, Greek, that doesn't sound reasonable. This person said,
if we do X, Y, and Z, or A, B, and C, that'll help us. Well, yes, they did say that. But if you go
look at the sea, what it was founded on, or if it's based or baseless, you will find it to be
unfounded and baseless, pretty much across the board. This is the state of humanity at this
point. So it's going to be very interesting. Well, actually, it's not going to be very
interesting, because it's very easy to see what what people engage in, what they are engaging in
last week, last month, last year, what they will be engaging in a week, a month or two or three or
four or a year or two from now, it's pretty much going to be the same that they're doing in now
uselessness, the same stuff. Well, it's going to take on a different form a little bit, at least
for the next couple of years. Yeah, there's not much going on, folks. Other than realizing the
and objectifying and seeing what's rational, and setting yourself apart. Again, it just means the
easiest way to set oneself apart is when you hear about something, or engage in anything,
is it lawful? What is it based on? You know, if something is being brought forward, let's say of
historical reference, or of scientific or medical or social or legal ref, you ever notice how it's
being discussed in a way that is to grab your emotions, or some du jour topic, but the actual
foundations are very rarely discussed, or what it's based on, are very rarely discussed.
You know, whether it's hidden away or sequestered from public reality or public mind is irrelevant.
You know, if you listen to what is being put out right now, through humanity at large, and we're
talking about the halls of deception known as university all the way down to, you know, click
away on a favorite place that you go to get information on the internet, from you're being
entertained or used, or it's being set up basically in the mainstream by a set of pranksters,
in the non mainstream, it's basically there to grab your emotional and garner emotional response.
So when I say this, of course, there's not completely absolute, there are some things
out there that are founded and based, you know, but when you start listening to a topic being
discussed, whether it's in university or all the way down to alternative media,
just don't jump right in and take it for, you know, let's say what's being presented as the
be all end all as such as if it just sprang into existence. You must understand its history or what
it should be based on. Is it lawful? In other words, again, when you hear of an economic discussion,
is it ever discussed that it's at least preface that it's a credit based economy and the
information herein is a discussion of it? Never. If you hear of anything regarding any political
discussion, is it ever being discussed in a way that actually is based on the laws of the country
or the patron deity of that country? Never. If you hear of anything scientific,
is it ever discussed on anything found in the real in the real world?
Never. Typically, some x, not an explanation, but a description of something. Of course,
science is very good at giving descriptions, but never explanations, of course, because,
you know, for all, I mean, we already know that electricity is nothing more than electrons going
down a wire, is it not? You know, I'll tell you, if you do this experiment safely,
if you cut a live wire, you don't need a dustpan. You won't make a mess because you won't have
electrons jumping out of the wire running, falling to the floor or floating in the air,
because there's no such thing. But is anyone bothering to check? You know, still people are
revoking this intellectual giant known as Einstein. But by the way, if you have a society
of mental midgets, it doesn't take much to be a giant, just like if a society is blind,
the man with one eye is king. But nonetheless, has anyone ever gone and researched what Einstein's
work was based on? Has anyone researched anything beyond that? Not really. They still like to parrot
all this stuff. When you listen to comments on things biblical, has anyone ever read the text?
The answer, if the answer is no, you're pretty much correct. Everyone says they have.
But go check up on it, you'll find they haven't. So you have a lot of things, you know, is it
lawful? A lot of things being discussed and is what being discussed, is it lawful? You know,
there's a lot of discussion to be found, a lot of information to be imparted. Is it lawful?
You know, I think last week we did bring up a reference to a man named Frank Chester. If anyone
has gone back and viewed any of his work, credit must be given to him that when he does bring up
any kind of geometric form or any idea that he's bringing forward before he proceeds, he says this
works because you could see here it is lawful. Lawful in the geometric sense, meaning that if
it's got four sides, it's a square. If it's got three sides, it's a triangle. That is a lawful
discussion. What you're hearing, folks, is that three sides means it's a square. Four sides means
it's a pentagon. And one plus one is five. And no one is paying any attention. Why? Because again,
the emotional stimulus to be garnered from tuning in to whether it's a visual experience or a sonic
experience anywhere that you go seems to trump people's rationale. Why? Because you have most
likely a mechanism of protection in your mind that has to also be in there if you're going to be in
the crowd mentality, addicted to low quality things and ruled by pranksters. How can you be aware and
how can you be perceptive and objective if you find yourself in the crowd mentality, addicted to
low quality stuff and ruled by pranksters? There is really no answer other than to numb yourself out
and go by emotional stimulus. And if you ever wonder what I'm talking about, look at how much
stress is being put into right now, into the stimulants and things like that of a certain
variety, by the way. So yes, humanity at large, you're common. We are here to bring up what's
uncommon. And if anyone other than the four or five listeners comes across this program,
and you don't understand anything that's being said here, it's fine. It's normal. But what we
try to do is be objective, be rational. And until the next time we come around, folks, remember,
be uncommon, or at least in your mind, be lawful, be rational. And in the meantime,
enjoy yourselves and all the best. And we'll see you again soon. Thank you.