Do you want to jump into it, or would you like me to?
No, I'd like you to.
I just wanted to say also there is www.uncommonsense.com.
It's Uncommon Radio.
Uncommon Radio.
Uncommon Radio.com.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Uncommon Radio.com.
And use the www because there's a lot of other things you'll find in the searches when you
do Uncommon Radio.
So use the www.uncommonradio.com.
Thank you.
And you will find links there or on that page, the simple calling page where you can just
click and find archives directly and the Ustream directly and everything else.
So, yeah.
Do you want to go into the names or perhaps we were discussing or should we just carry on?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, sure.
Let's go for it.
I was going to suggest something uncommon that I've been thinking about.
As I put it earlier, just kind of kicking around in my own mind this week is perhaps
the importance of names as a kind of as a hint to a lot of the things that we've discussed.
I know last week predominantly we were discussing food and water and cooking and such things
and I think that we're going to get into that a little bit more later on as well.
But I wanted to suggest the importance of names and them being something that is relatively
and keep in mind that I'm using the word relatively here, but it's relatively easy to research
as far as scripture, old texts go, is names.
And just one example is the name Elijah.
That's how it's pronounced in English.
KJV?
Yeah, King James Version, any sort of text based upon that which most of what's in English
is what it's based upon if it's not that itself.
So that's a biblical character that's known as Elijah.
That's right, biblical character known as Elijah.
And the name, it wasn't Elijah when it was being spoken.
He wouldn't answer to the name Elijah.
It's in common colloquial Hebrew, in common translation or untranslated even.
And by the way, Seth, I don't think anyone ever answered to that name before 1500 or so.
So anyway, go ahead.
Yeah, precise.
But it's Eliyahu.
That's how they would pronounce it today.
Now I wasn't around when he was walking.
So I don't know if that itself is perhaps even a degradation in pronunciation.
It's possible because there was a period of time where part of that name was not used.
It was forbidden actually for the people speaking the tongue from using that name.
Let's just say what it means.
It means that Yahweh is Elohim.
Yahweh is my El.
That's what it is.
And there's a lot of hints in just that phrase
because it's suggesting, one, that there are more than one of these Elohim.
More than a suggestion, I guess, but yes.
Right.
Eli is what roughly into English we use the word God.
It's inaccurate.
But that's roughly Elohim being God's plural and El being God's singular.
And Eli is likened to the God of me or my God in English,
although the E is what denotes that it's a possessive belonging to one.
That's why they have a specific name.
Very often these things are taken for granted.
And the meaning and the definitions are, let's say, perhaps listened to, heard, understood.
But what is the common thing to do?
Just go back to what everyone else is doing, right?
It doesn't matter.
But what are you going to do?
Set yourself apart.
You're not going to go around making corrections.
You're going to sound like a real outcast at that point.
I don't think it really needs correction.
It's just something that's – well, it needs correction for accuracy.
But I don't think commonly it can be approached as something to be corrected until a later date,
until it reaches the top.
The inaccuracy and lack of precision and loss of meaning and all the other things
that go along with things that are degraded go out of vogue.
It seems to be in vogue to allow heaps of degradation and corruption in almost every aspect of the human –
humanality, if there is such a thing in man's existence.
It seems like there's no lower limit to how much inaccuracy and precision,
corruption, or just taking for granted can be allowed.
I think the names can be inclusive in that.
One thing we've also mentioned, Seth, in the past is names are exempt from language, right?
Absolutely.
It's a sound that denotes an object, a person, meaning man or woman or a thing,
and it's exempt from language.
But I found that especially in the entitled classes now, whether it's scientific, judicial, education, legal society,
I should say because there is no judicial system anymore to be recognized as such by definition, let's say.
But what they're doing is they speak in verb and adverb and pronouns.
They don't use many nouns anymore.
You ever notice that?
There's no substance even in the language.
Yeah, it's become very commonplace for those that are loquacious to actually not be saying anything at all.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, okay, the name.
Interesting.
You know, there's a lot of talk in certain study groups, by the way.
You know, like I mentioned, study groups regarding legal matters and such about the use of the name.
And when I ever do any correspondence, whether it's sonic or written with anyone,
I always preface and I state that, you know, any legal matter that you might consider in today's world is actually a prank.
You do comprehend that, right?
You're being pranked.
There's no law that they're using or anything.
And so actually going after a particular aspect, there's many people that are considering the importance of using the name.
But, yeah, this is another thing that's commonly regarded, again,
is people think that a lot of the institutions and things that, let's say we call the entitled classes,
you know, people with social rank, doctor, attorney, professor, scientist, these ranks,
they think that these entitled classes now are holding any kind of information that is, let's say,
people approach them from a sense of convenience because they don't have time
or don't want to make the time to study these things on their own.
And they really shouldn't.
And there's an element of trust that man has bestowed on these classes of people known as the entitled ones,
the educated ones, the elite, let's say, the professionals, right, the experts.
People have taken for granted and have lost the ability seemingly to many extent of checking up on what is being put out by these experts.
And this is a time period, folks, that will be coming in the future.
People will be dedicating a little bit more time, like a minute a day,
into seriously considering what they're being told about things that they have not delved into
because they have their own lives to delve into.
So, you know, an example of that is if you are a baker and you bake bread all day for a living
because you're good at it and you like doing it, notice I didn't say the word job,
and you want to know something about astrophysics.
Well, you know, you're going to go and maybe today with the electronic convention, look up on the Internet,
you know, what your interest is in astrophysics.
And majority of the stuff that they give you there is bunk, you know,
or you might want to understand something about the human body or let's say the medical sciences.
What they're providing you with is bunk, so on and so forth.
You know, the legal society, you want to get some legal information.
It's bunk.
So right now it's just fascinating how the level of quality that mankind is operating on is so low.
Have you ever heard of the old comedian Henny Youngman or Kenny Youngman or Henny Youngman?
He says, I looked high.
One of the things he says is, I was looking high and low for you, but obviously I didn't look low enough.
Right.
So this is the state right now.
And this is meeting on a qualitative aspect.
And what makes it even worse really is let's just say,
could this society in the future be known as a society that had access to everything,
but threw everything away?
No.
So, I mean, look at the level of persecution, by the way.
Let's just go back.
Since you brought up the name concept and kind of narrowed it on the Eliyahu Elijah concept there,
you know that whether it's urban myth or not,
there's a lot of good evidence to suggest that several hundred years ago,
if anyone did any research or study, they were heavily persecuted.
Right.
I think, isn't it Don Quixote, that writing where he spent time in prison because he did a public reading of the biblical text?
Maybe anyone else familiar with that story?
Okay.
So you're in a time period now where you have so much access to information,
albeit it has to be sifted through and discerned, but it's just not looked at.
You know, one of the notes that I was putting together mentally was, you know,
the previous sonic project that I did here on AFR.
The first episode was kind of like a primer or preface to what would be discussed.
And the things there are like no one's really paying attention, right, and no one's really being objective.
When I say no one, I mean statistically most people.
And also that we're subject to external input.
We're unlike the creatures, other creatures that are pretty much born and ready to go with an operating system.
You know, I always give the metaphor of if you had a six-week-old puppy raised by a family of gorillas,
if you adopted that puppy as an adult, it would act just like a dog, would know the difference.
But if you had a six-week-old human baby raised by gorillas, if you invited him over or her over to your presence as an adult,
guess what they will be acting like?
So just like gorilla.
Gorilla.
So the interesting part about the external input is when you look at the bottom of the barrel scrounging for so many hundreds of years,
you know, the low-level quality of the mind that's been indulged in these low-level, you know,
aspect of thinking for so long that someone just researching a little bit on something that is, you know, a matter of fact,
all they have to do is a little bit of study and then just go out and profess this interesting factoid that's easy for everyone to access,
and they kind of build a career on it, whether it's an alternative radio or mainstream,
or they write treatises in university or papers, and they rarely consider furthering the study.
So even there's a lot of sources of sort of unique little factoids and subject matter that can be researched,
but it's – I'm not saying it should be exhausted, but there's still no depth.
And it doesn't mean that the depth should be arduous and long-lasting and, you know, just a little bit more.
And in other words, I think it's laziness, spiritual laziness or laziness of the mind, you know.
So I guess that ties in with names quite a bit.
I mean, would you say it's kind of laziness also that, you know, people kind of just don't care?
Maybe is it because they – you know.
Laziness, distraction, I'd say.
There's a lot of pretty colors being broadcast to people, a lot of pretty sounds.
You know, I'm setting it up for something else that could be a reason that I've always discussed.
It's something called cosmic censorship, being censored by the gods or, you know, the Most High, let's say.
It's a real interesting concept.
And by the way, censorship just means to block or redact or prevent, I guess, the flow of information,
whether it's visual or sonic or whatever, literal as well.
And if you do notice that someone, let's say someone here, versus something is censored cosmically,
there's nothing you can do to make them see anything else if they're censored about that particular thing, let's say.
You know, you hear that often when you bring up certain facts in society and people say,
well, I really don't see it, I don't understand it, and it could be as simple as a popsicle stick, right?
So that's one of the things of discernment.
If you run into anyone who's cosmically censored about a subject and the subject could be really simple,
don't even bother continuing.
There is nothing you can do.
Now, it doesn't mean there will be a time when the censorship is lifted,
which is actually going to be coming around the corner here.
Roughly what you call 2018 is going to be an interesting time for the lifting of some cosmic censorship.
So anyway, these things are to be discussed in greater detail, perhaps.
But if you don't know, if you can't grasp what cosmic censorship is, by the way, guess what?
Chances are you're censored as well.
It's one of those things.
It's really simple, but it's difficult because it is pretty rigid.
And sometimes the censorship can be lifted.
Again, it's cosmic, and I don't think anyone can really do it,
but it appears to be lifted when certain realizations certain people have,
and let's say those realizations become what's called life-changing.
You've heard of that, right?
So that could also be attributed to some of that censorship being lifted on a personal level.
But yeah.
Oh, another thing I was thinking of, a mental note.
We speak often, you know, if you're going to come to Uncommon Sense,
you're going to hear definitions of things that are not just like, ha-ha, look at what this word means,
but things that are very practical.
We always tend to bring up the concept of soul, spirit and body,
defining them, and by now I think if anyone's frequented the show,
pretty much knows what we're going to say.
But if you haven't, the soul is your breath.
It's a very physical thing.
The spirit is the mind, and the body is the body.
Let's say the carnal, the flesh, it can be defined many ways as well as material.
Now, it's interesting about the mind, and you ever hear about people being spiritual?
Like, some of this guy's really spiritual, right?
I'm familiar with that brand.
Right.
It's supposed to be something good right off the bat.
Well, it's the mind.
You could be of a good mind or of an evil mind, let's say.
Let's just keep it real basic black and white.
Spiritual doesn't necessarily always mean good, but here's the other thing.
There's a quality that I've noticed, and I've really never said this publicly on radio perhaps,
but let's just try it.
What do you think?
I don't think you know what I'm going to say, but let's go for it.
Anyway, on this end.
What I mean by that is you ever hear – well, before I go into it,
there's a level of – someone who is considered spiritual on a qualitative level
doesn't use the word or the terms me, my, or I very often.
It's interesting when you read a lot of the ancient texts,
and you listen to people who are sort of elevated on a better, higher quality of operation.
You'll notice they don't use me, my – like my hand, my finger, my car,
my kid, my money, my house, my wife, my show, my this, my that.
When you hear that often, that is someone who is on a lower elevation of spiritual development
or spiritual awareness, by the way, folks.
And I know this might sound kind of harsh and cruel and say, wait a second, Greek,
what's wrong with saying my kid or my computer or my –
I'm just making an observation here, and I'm giving you something to objectify.
So when you hear people speaking, and they start using me, my, myself, or I very often,
you're listening to a lower level or lower quality mind.
Now, let's just back this up.
Obviously, the Internet is going to be around.
I shouldn't say obviously like that, but it's going to be around for a while
because its purpose is not what people think.
It has nothing to do with information even though it purports to.
It's just a means of communication like the telephone was with audio and video.
That's easily available to anyone in the world pretty soon.
So if you go to these promotions that they give on browsers and things,
you notice they always say click here to claim your thing or this is my Yahoo or my whatever.
They use that terminology.
They're baiting a certain mindset.
It's very interesting because, by the way, if you really are a spirit animated with a soul and a body,
I would call it the container in essence.
The container is animated by the soul, and because of the life force,
then the spirit can be animated.
It's called consciousness.
Is it really yours?
Anyway, I think we can kind of keep going with this,
but I just wanted to put it out there because it seems like from feedback we've gotten on e-mails and such,
people like coming and listening to You and I Speak Seth.
It's basically a conversation we're having, and they say that they learn a lot of stuff sometimes,
and sometimes they look at the stuff as what we're saying as advice.
So that's why I thought I'd bring that up.
So, again, folks, if you hear people using this is my stuff or my whatever, me, me, me, I, I, I, I, me, me, mine,
you're listening to a lower level of mind quality or spirit quality.
Very interesting.
So just to top it off, if you ever go back and read any of the holy writs of the world or ancient texts,
people tend to refer to themselves in the third person.
So this is just something I figured I'd bring up because, you know, it's very common to hear that, right?
My kids, my car, my hand, my foot, my head, my computer.
So when you hear that, you right away know, yeah, Big Mac, French fries, Diet Coke.
So anyway, all right.
So keep rolling on.
Any more thoughts on that, Seth, or keep rolling?
No, no.
Yeah, we'll just keep rolling.
Spirit and soul is one of those things I think that bears repeating because that's one that's actually difficult.
That's kind of why I offered up the concept of names and, you know,
not them just being something that is referring to an individual,
but also possibly as a description and as a word that is a little bit easier to trace the history on
and find out its usage, its pronunciation, what the various parts of the word mean.
Whereas spirit and soul are actually, at this point in our recorded history,
especially in the language that you and I are using, have been obfuscated so much that it's like going back
and instead of being able to easily pull up where these words are defined with accuracy,
we actually have to go back to the text that they're used in and take them in the context in which they are used
and then those words being translated or versionized into English in the manner in which they have,
you know, applying the definitions as they were used in context in the actual text
as opposed to actually just being able to punch it into like edamonline.com and come up with an easy description.
So names are a little bit different and some of them have been well preserved
and in that the information is transmitted easily, you know.
You can get into studying scripture and start just with the very first verse that is offered up in the King James Version
and get into that. I've been looking at that single verse for three years with what I would consider to be new eyes.
Do you mean the first verse in the first chapter of the first book?
Yes.
Okay.
It doesn't say in the beginning God created the heavens and the earth.
No.
Not even close, really. I mean, yeah, it does include, it has some things inclusive.
But here's the thing. If the first verse in the first chapter of the first book is in Hebrew,
it is just blatantly incorrect. What do you think is going on?
I mean, you're at a major handicap. I mean, you're thrown into the meat grinder right there and spit out the other side.
Yeah, interesting, isn't it?
It's very interesting.
And one of the more interesting things about it is even with the horrible versions that we have available to us in our language,
when it's taken as a whole, there is still quite a lot of information that makes it through.
I think it's in spite of the poor version that we are offered.
But they do tell you. They do tell you what's going on.
I had a brief discussion with someone a little while ago about the Gideon Bible and they read the preface.
And the preface, I'm paraphrasing here, was as such, this version taken from the original tongues, revised and amended.
And initially to the person who said this, it sounded fine. I was like, what?
That means that, wait, revised means to change and amend means to change.
So they're telling you twice they've changed it.
And you will find in any unabridged version of any of the Holy Writs, by the way,
they're telling you they're not giving it to you, right?
It's kind of like if you go and buy, let's say, a bag of rice, right?
And it says rice on it and you turn to the back and it says ingredients and there's a long list of stuff.
There's a chance that it's something that looks like rice, right?
Big difference. So, yeah, I find that, you know, and by the way,
this has nothing to do with any religious or dogmatic reaction or discussion or approach to what's going on in society,
which is absolutely ridiculous. It's just one huge dummy load at this point.
I think we've discussed why humanity has been dummy loaded.
But again, it's not that difficult to access source material.
But I think we bring up Gustave Le Bonde and the crowd mentality.
Most people are still locked into the crowd mentality, you know.
And it's basically it's the imbecile.
And this is a term used often by Gustave Le Bonde that is attracted to that, you know,
a simple idea that attracts people into being motivated into some sort of crowd or group.
Now, if you go around the world, meaning man society and look at alternative media and mainstream university,
all of your sciences and legal societies, they are typically two or three or more people united in a group or united.
If you ask them what they're doing, they will always bring up some very oversimplified idea, which is nothing wrong with.
But if you examine what they are stating, the purpose of their grouping together a little further,
you will see that it has now changed and morphed away from what it was supposed to be.
So it's in name only. You know, how many times do you hear about activism?
You know, I know that too. Yeah, we've got to do something.
And like, OK, sounds good. But if I start looking at what they're discussing, oh, man, they missed the mark.
But, you know, they maybe the food is good. You know, they go out in the streets and they shout.
Maybe they're I don't know. Maybe they've got something we don't know about.
It's an animated culture, you know, or it's just a group of imbeciles, you know, or you could be animated.
Yes, exactly. So you could look at this across the board.
So I think it's let's go back to the what we call the biblical version.
It's just accommodating them. You see, you see, in order to be successful in any venture,
you're going to have to be able to accommodate your audience or patron or your clientele.
Right. So I think these things have been carefully crafted to accommodate.
But then then you see, then it's a self-consuming situation.
There's no right. Things don't get better. It promotes stability, obviously,
because if you've got a lot of ignorant people and you accommodate their ignorance, there isn't much change.
Right. There's no difference of potential. So everything is calm and steady. Right.
So it's a pursuit of peace. Yeah. But so from that notion,
is it possible to still have peace and have radical change where you just have to look clearly at what's going on five feet in front of you?
And I would suggest it is. It's just not happening at this point.
So it will soon it will begin soon, by the way. Absolutely.
As you said, you know, it's not a religious group thing or a dogmatic approach to anything.
It's just looking at the text as it has been preserved and and making observations on that.
Speaking of religions, by the way, the Medical Society for over a decade,
been saying there's no such thing as a virus and no one that has any integrity in the medical society will say that there is a virus.
You know, they just they just present things, you know, graphics and things, you know, meaning as defined,
as people think in their minds, what a virus is. Right. And what's interesting, Seth,
is lately I've been looking at some of the media mainstream and some of the products.
For example, there's a commercial for a disinfectant and actually saw it on a shelf.
It's a spray disinfectant starts with an L. It's been around for a long time.
So, OK, and they used to have prominently in their ads and on the on the container itself kills ninety nine nine nine point of bacteria and viruses.
Now it doesn't say viruses anymore and neither do they promote it as such.
So it seems like they're quietly redacting or quietly just pulling back a little bit from the virus thing slightly.
It's interesting. See, it's kind of like.
Yeah, yeah, I think we'll pull that little piece of fiction away. Maybe we won't make too much noise there.
I think that has a lot to do with the time that we're going into.
It's better to start retracting the BS before people get to the point where they can see it clearly.
Right. Because there may not be so peaceful about it.
I just thought I'd bring that up because I brought it up with several people in the know about this.
And they said, yeah, you know, I've noticed that as well.
They're not using they meaning the established societies, the media are not using that term as much as they did before.
And I find that to be interesting how things just what is it called going away quietly in the night or something like that.
Uh huh. And by the way, since we're on the subject, if anyone looks up what viruses are and virology, it's a branch of toxicology, by the way.
Toxicology. Yeah. Which is toxins.
Yes. Waste products. Yeah.
So and I think we've discussed that. And it all ties in, by the way, with the food concept.
You know, what you're doing is you're feeding the body, you know, I guess.
Yeah. And the quality thereof affects the rest of it.
In a previous sonic project we discussed, we did an episode called the container and we kind of went through many of the aspects.
But again, the basic things are the integration of one of a being in its environment is the thing that needs to be considered first.
You know, from a holistic point of view, meaning, you know, how are you placed into the environment and the effect of the environment on the body or the container?
And the thing that we've always brought up and have been saying for many, many years is to eat seasonally or cross latitude.
Right. And because could it be that what you're taking or passing through the body is changing the body according to the environment or the source and the source environment where the plant or the thing came from?
Let's say the fruit or the flesh will adjust the body to the corresponding environment where it was sourced from.
So, for example, if you're living in a hot climate or there's hot weather, middle of summer and you eat a piece of fish that is sourced from the Arctic, that will, let's say, use common terms, act as a blood thickener, change your body chemistry to living in the Arctic and you will not be able to cool down, you know, and vice versa.
If you're living in a cold climate or cold season and you're eating food that was sourced from the tropics and grown in the tropics, that food could adjust your body to living in the tropics and you will not be able to stay warm.
And this is one of the most basic concepts of the relationship between the material world to the material world crossed over by energies and things that you can't see in a microscope, but just make sense.
What about, and I know this is kind of getting into things we've already talked a little bit about, but things that always come to mind, what about when food is preserved, like in a can or like we've done for millennia with, you know, milk and yogurt and cheese?
We'll just look at it. It's different, isn't it? Doesn't it change it? It changes radically.
So if something, if you have two cucumbers, let's say, sourced as cucumbers, one is living, just picked, and the other one is preserved in salt, brine, and vinegar or whatever spices and it's several months old, it doesn't take much perception, whether it's visual, olfactory, or taste to see that they are completely different.
And once you look at it from using the senses directly that way, guess what? They are completely different.
The energetic quality or the quality that it will imbue on the being that is passing it through their body will be different.
That's why traditionally, for example, crops that were grown during the agricultural season, spring, summer, harvested in the fall and preserved, whether they were dried or canned, canning meaning pickled as well, you know, with other constituents, brines and vinegars and things, changed them.
So they were more fit for consumption off season.
And this is something that can be proven out using good science.
By the way, speaking of science, I was in a conversation with someone about a week ago, very adamant about how science is the savior of mankind, you know, in parentheses there.
And I said, Well, that sounds good. But if you know, he was touting the scientific method, right, and how objective it is.
And I said, That sounds good. But right now, none of the sciences that are promulgated and put out into society would pass their own scientific method of objectivity.
So again, if it's a religion, can we go back and say that there's not a religion on the planet that's doing anything that they allegedly subscribe to?
Oh, yes. Are they beginning to deify science? That's a whole other plan.
I mean, I don't like I don't know, I don't like to speak ill of the gods, but we'll just say cold.
How about how about that? Does that work? Cold goddess.
And I can I can only imagine. I mean, I'm I'm actually well versed in some of the what they would call, quote unquote, scientific approaches to solving what is seen as some of the symptoms of humanity's problems.
And they're they're not pleasant for those who want to continue walking around with, you know, mind, body and soul.
Yeah, they there are some very well documented groups, actually, that, you know, we're sitting around in in prominent universities here in the States, you know, openly discussing how many people were going to have to be eliminated for them to be able to make things better.
So I don't know if I would I would call science even deified as as a savior of anything.
Well, each religion tends to centralize each religion tends to centralize their their key, let's say, notions as being in saviorship of some sort.
Yeah, but yeah, it's you know, what we say about that, you know, there's a there's a thing about overpopulation, you could reduce the Earth's population to down to less than 100 people, just 100 on the entire planet.
If you include a rabbi, an attorney, a minister, let's say a scientist or a doctor in 40 years, you're all going to be exactly in the same shape you're in right now.
The number of people is irrelevant. It's the quality of how you're operating.
But, you know, here's the thing, Seth, it's it is almost mandatory to know the future.
And in the future, the God that is behind what's called science is not going to prevail over other gods, by the way, that are going to let's say one of them, could we consider the adversary of God?
Or I would say he was an Elohim, but he's more in the of the angelic venue, I would say, as an as a messenger.
That's his duty. Yeah, they will not prevail as as people think they do.
You know, yeah. Would it be what is it? What animals have a very short attention span? Is it a cat? I guess a lot of them were fish.
Oh, the shortest would be the fish, perhaps. Right. Right. Interesting.
Yeah. The age of the fish. Yeah. But what do you think? We're sort of a little bit halfway point of the first part of the show.
Should we touch on food a little bit? Are you OK with that? Yeah, I'm fine with that.
Before as a brief aside, I suppose the Greek and I were speaking for like maybe a minute and a half before we began the broadcast.
And I asked him to wait for the speaking on the food because I haven't done that yet today.
Right. But yes, I'm fine with it. And we have made bread.
You know, that's something that I make with the fair on a fairly regular basis in various forms and stuff like that.
As an unleavened bread, flatbread, let's say. Yes. Yes. Rapid. Rapid.
When I do if I do leavening of any sort, the only stuff I keep in the house for that really is eggs kind of act as a as a rising agent when you use them.
So I made I made I'd say that I made waffles a couple of times, but that would be inaccurate.
I mean, I made fried bread and it was the shape of a waffle, but I don't really follow any recipe for it other than just making making kind of a sweeter bread and then frying it on an iron.
But it's very quick. Well, I think a true waffle has yeast in it as an active, very active yeast.
Yeah, it would be right. And I don't I don't I don't do that. I've I've done it recently with was actually missing a few.
I didn't have any eggs. And I've you know, like I said, I'll just fry bread like that and put a little bit a little bit of sugar in it.
I always put oats in with it as well. A simple thing to do, by the way, if you're a fan or not, is mayonnaise.
A good quality mayonnaise mixed in with flour, a pinch of baking powder or baking soda and maybe an egg and some salt, let's say, will yield a pretty good biscuit, by the way.
Yeah, the mayonnaise. I haven't done that, but I've had it.
I've had it. Yeah, I haven't made them, but I've I've eaten them.
And they're pleasant. Yeah. Yeah. It doesn't use the the whatever you're using it in with the flavor of mayonnaise.
It just mayonnaise or it's mainly, you know, eggs to begin with. So, yes, yes.
It's a good roundabout substitution. And by the way, since you brought up bread, that was one of the things I was mentally thinking about was almost true to that recipe of laying out flour, adding an egg and some moisture to make the flatbread.
It sends the fat, let's say the butter or anything like that. You can roll that out and really thin or not so thin, if you so prefer, and using the extra amount of flour and slice it very narrow in a noodle form.
And if you have some boiling water going in a colander, just about a minute of that same mixture for making flatbread will yield a pretty good noodle or pasta.
So I have to try that. I haven't. That has not occurred to me. It's the same thing.
If you're late, just exactly just imagine you got your flatbread piece ready to go. Right.
Well, instead of instead of baking it, why don't you just cut it in a narrow form?
You're going to have to use a lot more flour, though, within the layer.
Obviously, you don't want it to stick together where if it sticks together when you're rolling out, let's say, a flatbread, you can mitigate it.
Right. Right. If you start cutting it, you might and it sticks together. You might have to start all over.
But go ahead and make a flat noodle out of it and immediately drop it in some boiling water for a minute or so.
And, you know, you know what to do once you've got noodles and pasta. You can top it with just some oil, butter and garlic or sauce or however.
You're going to need some fat so it doesn't stick together afterwards. When I say fat, meaning, you know, oil or butter or something.
And now you've got a fresh pasta.
How does how do how do the grains and breads like that?
I mean, obviously, you know, in the process of making bread, it'd be significantly different than just eating like, you know, the wheat kernels.
But how does that fit into the eating seasonally and things like that?
You mean whole grain?
Well, yeah. Well, flour, more specifically. Speaking of bread, because that's one of the things I eat all year round.
Here's one that's great, because that ties into an email we got regarding, let's say, the toxicity of refined foods, meaning he didn't use that term.
I am the sugar sugars. OK, I want to tie that in together.
Flour is a processed product that's removed from its natural state of balance. Right.
Right. And anything that is in that state is is is, let's say, prone to rapid oxidation and degradation of quality.
That's why a lot of oils, you know, nut oils or just any food that is like an oil, an oil or a butter, a nut butter or even seeds like sesame seeds.
Things that you have in storage flour are good for, I would say, about a season, a season or two.
You know, if you get it in the spring, you should have it eaten by the fall.
Don't let it last too long because it loses its efficacy. Right.
Now, let's just put aside that most of the products that we that are bought today are bleached and heavily modified and denatured before we even get them, no matter how fresh they are.
The general rule is don't start a food museum. Right.
The key is good rotation and don't overbuy.
So you things go bad. Right. Things go rancid.
And and even considering that, I mean, they have best by dates, you know, best if used by, you know, on almost anything now. Right.
It seems like because people, especially in the Western countries, have created food museums.
I go to people's homes sometimes when they ask for me to prepare a meal and I go through their cupboard and it's so jam packed and they're constantly just replacing what's in the front.
And I would reach in the back and there's a bottle of something from what they call 1998, you know, that should have been eaten in what they call 1998.
So, yeah, don't don't start a food museum.
But just to go off on the thing about the question about sugar, I think one of the comments was it should be listed as deadlier than cigarettes.
OK, without getting into how the body digests, because, by the way, you don't absorb anything.
Things are created in the body as they pass through the track.
When you, for example, take something like sugar that exists, let's say let's talk about cane sugar.
And by the way, if you do go out and buy sugar these days, if it doesn't say cane sugar, it's probably made from something else.
It's common.
Yeah, sugar beet or other things mixed and matched to get the chemical constituents that they would classify it as sugar.
But let's say you have sugar in a cane.
When that material is in the sugar cane, it's connected to mineral and water and starch.
And when the sugar is presented to market, all of those other things are stripped away.
And when you pass that refined product through the body, it doesn't only have to be sugar.
It could be oils.
It could be flowers.
When it passes through the body, the body recognizes it as a refined product and tries to compensate for its deficiency.
And it would actually then has to lose energy, let's say, or borrow from other parts of the body.
So if you have refined sugar going through the body, all of a sudden the body needs to supplement it with mineral, starch and water.
And that's what causes a lot of the decay and illness in the body.
Where if you have a whole sugar, it would just be considered as a sweet constituent, you know, a food, not something refined.
So this refined concept, that's why there are some sugar substitutes that are so far refined that cause so much damage.
Because they're so far over that the body needs to create so much of this other stuff to bring it to balance.
So this is just the interesting concept of anything processed.
But it's really the quality.
See, highly processed foods were always considered fine foods or fine products because they were considered fine.
You know, like a fine cake.
Like you make a cake out of fine cake flour and it's a very pleasurable cake versus a whole wheat, right?
But it doesn't mean you'll be eating cake every day.
Very often I run into people that say, well, I don't want to eat this meal because it's too rich.
And I'm like, when was the last time you had a meal like this?
It was two years.
Well, if you have this event, enjoy it.
You're not going to be eating like this every day.
So it won't have any health problems, you know.
Like some people, though, would decide to remove certain foods from their diet altogether.
And through an act of discipline, don't even want to partake in a single event.
And that's fine as well.
But if you're not clear about why you shouldn't partake in a particular food event, by all means, if it's of quality, partake and enjoy.
That's what we're here for pretty much.
I think we've mentioned before one of the words of wisdom is to have good food, good drink, and good conversation.
So I think it would be wise to consider having a good food event.
So I want to go back to what you asked, Seth.
Please rephrase that about the flour and the grains.
Well, just how we've spoken relatively at length about how eating seasonably might be beneficial to your health and your comfort.
I've shared that orange juice is something I don't – when it's cold outside, I don't go for orange juice anymore
because it was uncomfortable. It made things worse.
Or tomatoes when they're not growing or bananas.
Well, and tomatoes, that's another thing that I eat year-round but not fresh.
Preserved.
Preserved. Turned into a sauce, cooked in oil and herbs.
But that cheese and bread, preserved tomatoes, cheese and bread, that's actually a relatively large part of my diet all the time.
And cheese is not milk, by the way. Obviously, by looking at it, it is a milk product.
Yeah.
But going through that, yeah.
Absolutely.
Absolutely. So how does bread specifically – and obviously, I myself am curious and there's probably others out there as well,
maybe at least one or two interested in how does – do grains and not, as I said, whole grain flour perhaps,
but I'm specifically talking about what has been processed in turn, refined into flour for bread or cakes or waffles or anything like that
as well as how does that fit into eating seasonally?
Oh, what's interesting about that is most grains that are consumed are no longer in the state that they were in when they were alive.
So they've changed radically.
Preserved in a way.
Yeah, exactly. Going back to the pickle, the sandwich pickle versus the cucumber.
It's the mildest, most evident form of alchemy, by the way.
One thing that I suggest about that is that if onions or the onion, the general class of what's considered onion and garlic,
if those vegetables or roots were difficult to grow, they would be considered an expensive delicacy.
Think about the transformation that they go through with heat.
Take a bite of a raw onion or raw onion and then have it cooked in fat.
And what happens to it? Caramelized white Vidalia onions are probably one of the most delicious things,
if you go that way, as a complement to many dishes, roasts and things.
The incredible transformation, it's the most evident and basic form of alchemy, is cooking an onion.
Right. Going from this offensive, sulfurized kind of presence.
Absolutely. I despise onions that are raw. I avoid them.
You need them to be transformed for your palate.
You're looking for that absolute transformation.
And that's why I always suggest if they were difficult to grow, they would be considered a delicacy.
You know, so again, we're taking these things for granted to some extent.
But again, with the grains, I've had fresh grain and like a wheat berry type thing.
Right. Very delicious. But from from the objectifying, the perspective on that question would be since when have can anyone encounter a living piece of grain these days?
It's always processed or cooked or dried or milled. And you see.
So it's changed pretty. Rolled rolled oats are pretty common.
Yeah. Yeah. And yeah, an oat berry is is very different from from.
Yeah. So that's one of those things that go into almost into immediacy are transformed into something else.
The thing that I still can't get over is for thousands of years, bread was considered to be a daily commodity.
Like, you know, day old bread is heavily discounted, isn't it? Right. Traditionally.
But yet I in many of the shops that I go through and look at, they have breads in bags.
Yeah. And they're dated, you know, weeks out and the price doesn't change.
You know, that's not really bread any longer.
They've added. So there is such a long list of ingredients.
Calcium carbonate, which is plaster and glycol, which is antifreeze for the car.
I've noticed those ingredients. I found very expensive and I've found very inexpensive tortillas that are made without lard or aluminum.
So probably three ingredients like corn, water, flour, salt, maybe.
Yeah. Even those things tend to be made. That is a corn based or flour based flatbread again.
Yeah. I've been including consumption of tortillas right in there with bread.
I'm not a fan really of corn tortillas. I guess in chip form.
But even then, I prefer, I much prefer flour. If I'm consuming corn, I'd rather have it in bread or in, you know, kernels.
Or fresh corn, maybe. Absolutely.
Yeah. What's interesting about this also, there's been this aspect of gluten free.
It's like there's always some form of, I call it bioterrorism by the scientific community, by the way.
Bio meaning biological things that are sometimes good for you.
And then a decade later, they're bad for you and then they're good for you again.
You're being terrorized, folks, by these communities.
But nonetheless, this whole thing about gluten has to do with quality, not the gluten itself.
So, yeah, here's an hour of Uncommon Sense with the Greek and Seth Michael.
And we're going to touch a little bit more on food when we come back.
Greetings and welcome back to Uncommon Sense here with the Greek and Seth Michael.
This is hour two. And this episode perhaps is a little bit of a mishmash.
We were revisiting a little bit of some of the cooking discussion we did on the previous episode,
which would behoove anyone to listen to just to kind of maybe reconnect to the second hour.
Absolutely. I'm here. I would like to, before we go get back into what we were just speaking about,
I would like to remind everyone that you're listening to us on American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio appreciates and requires the support of its listeners as well.
So to find out how to help keep American Freedom Radio on the air and broadcasting
and by such assisting with the broadcast of Uncommon Radio, Uncommon Sense,
you can go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com. It's easy to figure out from there.
And if you would like to get into contact with the Greek or with myself,
you can do that easily by going to UncommonRadio.com
and following the contact link there and send an email. That's the easiest way to do it.
You can also listen to us on Ustream. There's a chat on Ustream that I try and keep an eye on there.
If you have any questions or want clarity, you can do that.
And it's Uncommon Radio on Ustream.
Ustream.tv forward slash channel forward slash second hyphen foundation is the channel that we broadcast on.
So yeah, I just wanted to say those few things there.
Cool. And speaking of clarity, I've been told in the past in private Greek,
man, you got some good stuff, but you really got to dumb it down.
You got to dumb it down for the people. I'm like, no, no, no, no dumbing down what we do.
We'll speak simply. We speak in a very simple way that hopefully is clear.
But I think we mentioned in the first hour, there's so many variables, cosmic censorship, the crowd mentality.
You know, most people that listen to things, it has to be super oversimplified
and almost they won't resonate with the concept unless it's removed from reality
and promotes the forming of a group.
You know, this is what I define as the imbecile, the average human on the planet right now.
Unfortunately, you know, fortunately, people will find out that from a creation point of view,
animating a spirit in a material world, you know, animals, insects, people,
and people are not animals or insects, but they're very unique as the fortunate aspect.
The unfortunate aspect is the duration of time that mankind has to go through
just to prove that this thing can, meaning spirits animated in a physical body,
can semi-automatically reproduce and conceive and keep reproducing over a long period of time to us.
And, you know, that's the fortunate part.
But the unfortunate part, again, is just the censorship that's on humanity at this point
where they just can't see and appreciate what's going on, which is fine.
It will be better understood as time goes on, and definitely in the future, way down the future,
it will be reckoned and realized for what it was then.
So, again, speaking clearly is important, yes, and simply is important.
But I don't think at this point, because it's called uncommon sense
and because there's a pursuit of accuracy and precision,
I don't think accommodating the crowd or group mentality or what's considered
concordant thinking or conventional or plausible thinking is worth doing.
But I assure anyone listening that the pursuit of speaking simply and clearly
is what uncommon sense is about.
Yes, absolutely. The crowd is catered to elsewhere.
That would be common or uncommon.
There's 166 hours around the two hours after, you know.
In other words, we'll be on again roughly 166 or 167 hours from now again.
And if you want to know what the crowd mentality, the imbecile mentality is about,
well, you've got 166 hours to partake and then revisit us again in a week or so.
So to have something that is not on the crowd mentality.
But anyway, it might sound kind of harsh or arrogant, folks, but sorry,
that's just about being objective.
Objectivity sometimes is kind of harsh and arrogant sounding, but not meant to be so.
But speaking of harsh, we were speaking about food.
And one of the things we brought up also was just having gratitude and realizing
what's going on.
And the comment that I brought up was the onion,
how something could be seemingly offensive transmutes essentially into something
quite pleasant by, you know, preparing it with heat.
And we were just discussing, you know, maybe doing a little bit more about food.
And maybe a lot of these things are very basic.
We're not getting into anything that I hope will challenge anyone's skill level
who is already partaking with some cooking skills.
So we also mentioned, I think, the things, Seth,
which might have been a slight surprise to you was perhaps crossing over
and using the flatbread recipe as a noodle recipe.
Yeah.
I think that you actually mentioned that in the past,
but it's something that had slipped my memory.
So revisiting that.
Yeah, because you've got it made.
In other words, if you're looking for inspiration and you do prepare the flatbread,
which is the flour and some cold water and an egg and some fat,
and you've got a lump of dough in front of you,
well, you might be inspired to make flatbread, you know, in a pan or in the oven.
Or you might be inspired to dunk it in some boiling water and make a noodle dish.
You can go either way.
So I think that's significant for the concept of variety at this point.
Absolutely.
And it's one of those things that is readily available and easy to acquire,
meaning that it's affordable.
And it's fresh.
And it is even after it's made, you know,
it's one of the things that can be preserved for a few days
without losing any of its efficacy and flavor.
In fact, sometimes flatbread is even better the next day.
Yeah, after it's cooked especially.
So the other thing I was thinking mentally that I didn't bring up
was we discussed, you know, cooking various starches,
perhaps touched a little bit on the meat products.
But one thing that I wanted to bring up also was pot cooking.
You know, when you're cooking something in a pot, a stew, a soup, beans,
things like that, what's interesting is sometimes I've noticed comments
on people, let's say, cooking beans.
And there's a colloquial or cliche about beans giving people flatulence or gas.
Okay.
Well, it's not only that.
It could be other foods that can do that.
And typically that's the body telling you that the food is producing gas
when it shouldn't be, right?
And they're like, don't eat that again.
But here's an interesting tip that if anyone is making, preparing,
let's say, a soup or a stew or beans, right, whether they are from scratch
or canned, yes, a lot of people do partake in pre-prepared meals
that they quote-unquote reheat.
One thing I've noticed, and this is a repeated practice,
and it's for many years, but I've never really been discussing it
with people until recently, is that when you bring a pot of a liquid,
you know, mixture, whether it's a stew, beans, or a soup,
to a simmer or a little bit more aggressive than a simmer,
you will notice that there is a foam that develops on the top of the pot.
Skim that foam off.
That will be removing the agents, let's say, that would promote gas or indigestion.
So I'll say it again.
Let's say you are making a vegetable soup or stew or anything, or even beans,
whether they are from scratch, fresh, or from a can,
when you bring the pot up to some heat would be considered, let's say, a simmer,
where you see, you know, a very mild boil, bubbles rising to the surface.
You'll notice that a foam accumulates on the top.
And sometimes it's a very mild foam, like what you would see,
like small soap bubble-looking kind of foam.
And sometimes if you're doing, let's say, beans from scratch that are dry,
you can have something as a very aggressive, scummy-looking foam,
almost like a sea foam that washes up on the beach and stands alone,
almost like a shaving cream consistency foam.
Remove that.
Skim it off the top.
Now, typically, if you're making a, let's say, pre-prepared dish,
let's say a can of beans,
and add about a quarter of a can or half a can extra liquid to it, water or broth,
and that will give you a little more leeway when you're skimming off this foam
that appears on the top.
And this is done traditionally.
It's never really discussed, by the way.
If anyone is ever partaking in any kind of a chefing event,
which would be, let's say, a finer restaurant,
the making of soups and stocks and stews were always reserved to the most skilled
in the kitchen because there was timing on when to, you know,
remove some things from the dish on its initial simmer or boil.
And I've noticed these things were never discussed,
and that's why I'm bringing them up now to perhaps save some grief from those that do food
preparation of pot dishes, meaning a stew or a soup or a bean dish.
Now, unfortunately,
you will not be able to induce this kind of event if you have what's called a crock pot, right,
these slow simmer things, which I don't like, by the way,
and this is a personal preference, and I'll discuss that why.
That will not get hot enough to bring up this foam,
or you won't get enough of a rolling simmer to allow the separation for you to remove the top of this off.
And the way you remove it, by the way, is with a good-sized spoon or ladle,
and you don't dunk it down into the liquid.
You just try to skim it off the top and have a pot with a handle handy next to you.
If you use a bowl or something and your finger is in the bowl while you're skimming off this hot liquid,
you might burn yourself, so be careful.
If you don't have an extra pot, you know,
make sure there's a towel or something around and be prepared for some spilling, you know,
so take precaution on that.
But I want to go back to the crock pot mention.
You will not get this type of aggressive heat, an initial reaction to create this separation,
which also you will not get, even though in what they call the States or America,
they're quite popular.
I noticed that food that's cooked in these little slow-cook electric-type things is not as flavorful
as foods that are cooked over a standard range, albeit, you know, let's say gas or such,
but even an electric one, let's say, where you can modulate or change the temperature.
And the reason why is very simple.
There seems to be a natural order through the history of mankind.
Imagine a time outside of this where you have gas or electric piped to the range, the stovetop,
and it can be consistent.
Imagine a time where you had to manually deliver fuel to the fire, okay?
So let's say you had a pot, whether it was an indoor hearth or a campfire outside
or an indoor stone oven or anything.
You were typically burning some sort of wood or coal,
and that fuel would eventually lose its ability to continue cooking,
so you have to introduce more fuel.
So when the fuel was introduced or the fire was initially introduced under the pot,
it was hot and consistent and higher in heat.
Then it would diminish, and then you would install more heat, and it would go up again.
So an inconsistent delivery of heat to a slow-cooked meal tends to yield a better flavor,
maybe because there's an expansion and contraction in the pot that releases more flavor into the liquid.
Perhaps that might be a good suggestion,
simply because if anyone is into making sauces or certain stews,
you'll notice that they almost always taste better the next day,
especially whether they were sitting on a stovetop or reheated out of the refrigerator.
As a matter of fact, I had heard there are quite a few restaurants
that pride themselves in their quality of preparing delicious dishes,
and one of the mandatory things is when they made tomato sauces and other vegetable sauces,
it was mandatory that they go into the fridge overnight
and then reheated to the patrons the next day or the clients the next day.
So it might have something to do with this expansion-contraction,
or it might be just that the old way of doing things yields a slightly better, more palatable product.
So again, you're not going to get that with a consistent crockpot slow heater,
but you will get it on the stovetop.
Again, the purpose of bringing this up and the mental note that I made
that I wanted to bring up in the first episode was these are tips that will make not only a better dish,
but maybe in this case save some grief from flatulence or being gassy.
So this also works, again, any kind of a liquid pot cooking method.
Anytime you bring it to a simmer, try to bring it up a little higher.
You'll notice a foam that develops on the top.
Skim that off.
That tends to be one of the constituents that leads to this indigestion or gas
or flatulence when people eat certain things.
So I just wanted to bring that up as a cooking tip,
because even though we're speaking about food and cooking,
you may not consider yourself proficient in that.
Well, you might want to investigate it,
and at least you've heard some things that are very basic that are very different,
even though they're very common.
We've discussed about preparing common things like various starches,
like maybe potato dishes, whether it was potatoes for a potato salad
or mashed potatoes or making a perfect rice or, again,
skimming off any kind of a foam that develops on top of a liquid when you're doing a pot cooking.
These are things that I believe I've seen for a long time being done but not discussed openly,
and I think that it would help anyone in any of their cooking endeavors.
And there you go.
I think I don't have any other mental notes on what I wanted to bring up regarding the food,
but that was just maybe about 15 minutes of this hour just to recap,
I guess, 15 minutes in the last hour and the previous episode.
I just think that food is an important thing to consider and food prep.
I was muted.
I was agreeing with you, but you couldn't hear me because I was muted.
That's fine.
Yeah.
So there you go.
And, again, just to recap on the removing skimming off the top, again,
just people get intimidated by when we brought up the concept of fear.
What is fear?
Well, if you lack skill, you're susceptible to fear, right?
So if you're not a car mechanic, you're really afraid of a car breaking down,
where, you know, even if you're a car mechanic, you wouldn't want it to break down,
but you'd know how to handle it.
You wouldn't be deathly afraid of it.
So there's many people that are listening, especially in the modern Western world,
that are not into cooking.
But I believe that many of the things that were said, when I say I believe, I mean, you know,
it's up to whoever is hearing it on the receiving end if they do anything with it.
Even if you're heating up a can of beans again, just, you know, how do you prepare it so it's the best,
making the best of what you've got.
And I feel like that was a really good endeavor on our part to delve into the food or the, you know,
cooking aspect of it for the two hours plus now that we've done, you know, the previous episode and now as well,
and especially from the feedback that I've gotten in the past week about it, even albeit minor.
And you notice we haven't gone into many of the health, what's called healthful or health aspects of it,
because I think there's been a panic in that direction.
You know, what is causing us to be sick, you know, right, kind of thing, you know.
Is it the food? Is it this? Is it that?
Well, it's all of it, you know.
And the thing is a robust organism can take a lot of punishment
and be very tolerant to toxins in the environment.
So those that did have the questions regarding the food and health,
I think those have been discussed over and over and over again about the seasonality of things.
We did bring up the process nature of things, how they do deplete in order to go back into balance.
So that's where the whole food aspect is more balanced.
And also the having skill and preparing it.
So because look, if it tastes good, you're going to feel better.
And if you feel better, then, well, you're feeling better.
But there's an aspect of the mind also where people have been weakened spiritually, meaning of the mind.
And of course, if you when I say spiritually right away,
people go to a lot of the new age bullshit talk that you hear,
and also a lot of the conventional religions of the world.
Those are there to weaken you, folks.
And the reason I'm saying that is because, again, like we've always said,
there's none of these groups are doing anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
And I've also caught in flag from saying people we don't Greek.
We don't need text to know this stuff. Oh, really?
Okay, well, you know, go off on your own.
You're a perfect imbecile.
You know, find a crowd to join.
This is the this is the idea of when we discuss the crowd mentality.
People tend to have an aversion to pursuing any form of knowledge that leads to accuracy and precision
and actually can be used as something that something is founded on.
Right. So, again, the the the discussion about health, a robust organism.
You know, here's the thing.
The mental and spiritual weakness, which is the same mental and spirit or mind and spirit, has been put on people.
It's the acts of terrorism that are put on humanity by the entitled classes, meaning, you know,
the experts and the professionals that you're going to are terrorizing you.
In other words, they're instilling fear and uncertainty where there shouldn't be any.
So the the how does one recommend to another being or a man or a woman to be strong and have, you know,
fortitude, you know, in their mind, in their spirit. Right.
And indirectly, the way we say this, by setting yourself apart from the rest,
because the moment you get dragged into one of these crowd mentality things or one of these cause mentalities,
not that there aren't good causes to to follow or pursue or put your energy into.
But I assure you that when you start seeing what's going on out there,
either mainstream or alternative in the causality range, it's unfounded.
You know, the idea sounds good initially, but if you look into it a little bit more,
it's drifted away from what it's supposed to be, not because I say so, but because they say so.
And you will say so when you investigate a little further.
So, again, just tying back to the causality of health and people, when you bring up food,
it's really a robust and strong mechanism or organism, I should say, is resistant to disease and unhealthy
and unhealthful situations. You know, I want to bring up just because we're a little bit on the health topic.
There's a man named Wilhelm Reich and a lot of he's very misunderstood and mispromoted, by the way,
in the alternative media and on the Internet. But if you study his work, what he had written,
he basically got into a lot of the non measurable or difficult or non material evident causes of things.
And he was one of the first people, let's say, in psychiatry, the field of psychiatry,
to discuss that emotional state is very important for physical well-being.
And that basically has become main mainstream since maybe 20 or 30 years now,
where people who were physically ill all the way from mild illness to, let's say, cancers,
were asked to consider their stress level. Right. This is mainstream.
And this was not even considered back in the days of Wilhelm Reich.
And the reason I'm bringing him up is because I'm tying this up with the concept of if the mind is strong,
then the body can be strong and a strong organism. It would be more resistant, let's say.
To disease and discomfort and other illnesses.
So, again, just to round about recap, we've been talking about food and food preparation
and a little bit of wisdom, good food, good drink, good conversation.
Ecclesiastes, read Ecclesiastes people. Yeah.
And anyone who is interested in scripture at all, I recommend start there,
even if you're just reading what is readily available in the closest book to you that has it in there.
And you might understand some of it. Right. Yeah.
The reason, by the way, I never recommend people read these ancient texts
because it's almost like setting them off on a futile mission.
They typically never understand anything in there. Typically. And I mean at all.
There's a lot of repetition in Ecclesiastes as well.
It's like it could be summarized in probably two sentences, but it's.
Yeah. So read, read Ecclesiastes. I pulled.
We've been speaking of food and drink and it always brings to mind that book.
There's a typical there's a message that I've gotten repeatedly from several individuals about saying,
should we stay away from the New Testament, just read the Old Testament?
Well, I just want to get into that just for a moment here.
Either way, here's the thing. There's a progression.
It's if that's why I'll use the term Christianity.
So it's really when you say Christianity, by the way, that is a secular term.
People kind of brand it with a religion.
But if you look in the secular historical nature of recordation, this is known as the Christian era worldwide.
OK, so it's also beyond it just shows you the state of man.
So if you if you shouldn't say we should blame it on that.
But, you know, you could you could and be justified.
But here's the thing.
Most of the quote unquote Christians or Christian era markings are that quotes and cliches and things gotten out of the New Testament.
And is that good? Well, it can be.
But I'll tell you why it's not.
When you've progressed that far down into the text, it the New Testament lightly refers to things that were gone into heavy detail in the Old Testament, let's say.
And if you don't know those details or have the maturity to comprehend that you're way down the line, you will not get anything out of it.
And if you don't believe that, just look at what's going around you and have a conversation with a Christian, by the way.
But here's the point.
The metaphor to this is by the time you get further down the text, since it's cumulative, it will consider it just as a metaphor, college level physics.
So if you have no knowledge of the biblical text and you and you are only talking about the New Testament or study it on your own,
it is no different than getting a someone who is a kindergartner and putting them into college level physics.
And, you know, after a day, an hour or a whole semester of of this, you ask them, do you have any questions?
And they raise their hand and they say, yeah. Do you have any candy?
Right. And if and if you don't think this is going on with Christianity, have a conversation with a Christian regarding the biblical text.
It is that asteroid. They know nothing. And the reason why I'm not knocking them,
I'm just saying that if you are, let's say, consider yourself to be Christian and you do study the biblical text holistically,
you will not consider yourself Christian at the end of the day after your study or Jewish or Muslim with the Koran or in the Hindu or Buddhist or whatever.
And this goes back to stating that there is no religion on the planet that is doing anything in the text that they allegedly subscribe to
or any of the things that it was supposedly based on. It's kind of like the money, how it's fiat based on nothing.
Some people like to say it's based on debt. So if we're going to carry that over to the religious matters, what kind of a debt are they creating?
This is not one particular religion, folks. This is all the religions are like this and all of their followers.
So beware of people that profess a certain faith, by the way, publicly or privately,
because if you are one of these people that pursue things known as knowledge and truth and accuracy,
if someone proclaims a particular faith, regardless of its Eastern or Western,
go ahead and do like a 10 minute study on the faith that they're professing or their religion,
and you'll come back and realize they know nothing. It's just one of the most phenomenal things of the state of mankind at the moment.
It's just it's just pathetic, really. But anyway, let's let's keep the conversation lively.
Or a question from a question from chat. Does eating the muck foam harm the body?
Talking about the beans. I just saw it in chat. So I wanted to. Oh, cool. Define harm.
I would say you would if you're here's the thing. When I started speaking about it,
it was attached to the concept of being gassy or having some indigestion or having flatulence.
Let's say being uncomfortable. Yeah. So if you're one of these person, people that are super tolerant of things,
you may not know or it may not matter. But the thing is, if it does appear in preparation, skim it off.
And not only will the food taste better, it will digest more readily. Right.
Many people I've noticed that don't know about this, stir it back down or just leave it alone.
And then after, you know, something like a pot, a stovetop pot cooking dish over a matter of time,
it will dissolve back into the liquid, you see. So you want to remove it on the initial simmer or initial boil.
Will it harm? I don't think harm is the term to use, but it will not yield a fine or better product if you if you don't do it.
And again, I've shown this to people, you know, just camping, you know, where, you know,
you're in the most rudimentary, inconvenient conditions typically when you're camping.
And they would, let's say, open some cans of beans or even have sometimes had soaked beans for the day.
And when they're cooking them, let's say in the evening, I just walked over there and started skimming all the top off.
And they one person once got upset. They were like, why are you doing that? You know, so you're wasting the food.
I'm like, no, actually, this is going to yield a better dish. And they all agreed.
Because the last time I was also told that the individual who had, let's say, resisted skimming it off,
they didn't like eating their cooking because it always gave them gas.
And this was the first time this person had prepared something that did not give them gas.
And lo and behold, see, so it's a matter of comfort or just a better quality preparation.
This also works with like chicken soups, preparing, let's say,
if anyone has ever experienced a Vietnamese dish called pho.
Pho is how it's pronounced in Vietnamese. It's spelled P-H-O or pho, typically,
as Westerners, but in Vietnamese, it would be pronounced pho, is a bone marrow soup.
And that develops quite a bit of a scummy foam, meaning a very robust foam,
almost like a whipped cream type consistency that floats on top of the pot that should absolutely be removed.
Now, if you're doing a soup that's been or something that's been treated with spices and herbs,
you'll notice they will also float to the top and you will lose them when you remove the,
not lose all of them, but whatever is in that zone of skimming will be removed.
So you might want to have, you know, an extra bit of those spices or seasonings to add back in, if you so think.
But by the time, if you're using dry spices and herbs, by the time the initial simmer comes up,
most of those things have released or imbued the flavor into the pot anyway, you know, the oils and things.
So, yeah, this is something to be considered because very often, well,
once I had someone say, well, look, we're skimming off all of the oregano, you know,
and the rosemary off the top. It's okay. I'll just add some more.
I would rather lose that little bit of seasoning and not have the foam, you see.
So try it and I'm sure maybe I'll get some feedback if there's anyone out there that's going to proceed.
But again, the feedback has been thus far, Seth, that gotten several perfect rice responses.
Yes, you did make perfect rice and several responses regarding potato dishes being absolutely delicious.
Wonderful. I haven't I haven't actually tried either of those yet, but I look forward to it.
Yeah. So we would jump from the discussing a little bit of the biblical text and the state of affairs of humanity back to food again.
So it seems it's interesting maybe maybe just a strict cooking show is in order.
That would be an interesting thing. But I think that's would be.
I wouldn't say challenging without the visual, but it can be done by just sonically.
But that's another that's another project, perhaps because there's things that could be prepared.
There's almost an infinite amount of combinations or dishes, let's say, within the season or across latitude that can be done in any case.
Right. I mean, we do have the ability to do video on the Ustream side as well.
Yeah, we'll set up a what do they call a test kitchen or a model kitchen, that would be.
And it's not it's not near as bandwidth heavy as one might think.
I've actually successfully broadcast some some video programs without any problems.
And part of the inspiration, by the way, about doing food is when it did partake in what they call cable subscription.
There is a plethora of food channel, food shows, food, even with the airwave HDTV.
Now, I think there I think it's petroleum broadcasting service or it was a PBS or whatever.
They have cooking shows. And I've been watching these for years and years, more than a decade or so.
Not not specifically and diligently. But when I do come across them, I always I always shake the head and say,
you're not going to learn how to cook watching this stuff. They're missing so many points, you know.
And that was always kind of a point of contention.
I was like, you know, people just need to know some real basic things that they can add,
you know, repertoire of things that could add to what they already know.
And when they get good at that or make what they're making the best it can be,
even if it's a can of beans being reheated, let's say,
then they can view with confidence expanding their horizons, let's say, into more things
or perhaps giving people the ability to partake in the kitchen a little bit more with ultra simple things like the flatbread,
which I believe you've taken to very well.
And, you know, there's some people that enjoy making rice and making a perfect recipe,
cooking the basic starches, because most of the time when cooking is involved, a starch will be involved.
Right. Typically. Yeah. Very rarely does anyone eat a slab of tofu or a slab of meat by itself, you know.
Absolutely. I'm I'm fond of the things that are inexpensive as well.
And the starches are inexpensive.
Well, because they're inexpensive, you could actually seek out really a better quality.
Yeah. Contrast. Yeah. Yeah. So you don't. Right. Because they're by nature inexpensive.
You can spend just a little bit more and get something that is more than just marginally better, but much better.
And, you know, same with like if you I like to eat sweet things occasionally as well.
And I've found very, very inexpensive, minimally processed cane sugar for just a few pennies more a pound than the heavily refined, you know.
So-called sugars. Yeah. Very bright beet sugars that are commonly available.
Like it's and I don't I don't eat enough of it to where, you know, a few cents more a pound is affects affects it that much.
So it's yeah, there's it's just kind of being aware of things like that and not to mention the flavor is just significantly better.
You don't have to use as much of it. It's got a more of a kind of a richer flavor.
It's not that I've kind of got a distaste for the heavily refined sugar, at least in what I'm cooking at home.
Mm hmm. Yeah, it tends to not have a good finish to it.
And I've explained to people before, you know, there's when you say salt, you know, well, it's salty.
Right. You maybe use I guess how, you know, you shouldn't use the same word to define the word, you know, but let's say if salt tastes salty.
Right. That's really difficult to to go to escape that one.
But when I when I started mentioning that people seek out higher quality salts and like, you know, if you're used to what's called a commercial iodized salt, which is toxic, by the way, no matter what they tell you, your body needs iodine.
It doesn't need that kind of iodine. And but then again, you know, it's part of, you know, if you're on planet Earth, you know, this is about being pranked.
But anyway, with salt, I mentioned to people when you start seeking out higher quality salts, whether it's the source of the salt or how it was harvested or however, seek out better quality salts.
You will notice that when you initially encounter it on the palate, it's obviously salty.
But and that initial quality may not be like a jolt, you know, like a buzz.
It might be maybe slightly more mineral like or slightly more metallic and very, very salty.
But typically, high quality salts have a sweet finish to them.
In other words, when you put some on your palate, let's say touch the finger on the salt, touch the palate, the tongue or on a piece of food or something.
You'll notice the saltiness in the beginning of varying degrees.
And it should always have a almost like a sweetness, not not sweet like sugar.
But it changes again on the finish of the palate, you know, after you taste it or consume it.
Right. That's one of the marks of a good quality salt.
It has a complex flavor and it changes.
And now most of the granular salts that people get in snack foods like it's typical to have a visual assault of salt on, let's say, what's called a pretzel.
Right. Have you ever seen salted pretzels?
They have these crystals distributed and stuck on the surface.
That's like visually there.
Typically, you won't see salt in a dish.
Right. I know it's not a pun, sea salt, but sea salt is one thing to pursue.
Right.
But you won't really visual.
You won't do it.
You don't know that it's there until.
Oh, that's a very salty dish.
It tastes salty.
But typically on something like a pretzel where you see the salt crystal is more of a sensation.
And that's typically not a good quality salt.
That is a good example to show the contrast of not typically not a good quality where if you do taste those salt crystals, they're just like salt from the start.
Salt to the finish.
Right.
It's kind of like some some are more mellow, some are more metallic, but it doesn't yield that sweet finish that a high quality salt would do.
And not to promote various salts, but typically the the there are sea salts are promoted very heavily, but it's also how they're harvested.
There's an ionization deionization process that takes place when salts are harvested using metal, especially iron tools.
Some of the most prestigious, let's say, best salts in the world are, let's say,
harvested during a certain time of the year and they don't use any metal, whether it's in storage or harvest.
And that kind of keep retains the energetic value of the salt.
And there's the Himalayan salts, which are more, I guess, land salt.
So if you pursue if you have just a little bit extra gumption to pursue a slightly better salt quality,
you will notice that salts do taste different.
Also, there are some salts that retain a lot of moisture and clump together.
And it's not something that has people are used to as being convenient in a salt shaker.
Right. In some traditions, it's typical to put some dry grains of rice in a shaker type thing.
If you have salt in the rice constantly absorbs the moisture.
But if you're getting something like a Celtic sea salt, some of these are 30 to 50 dollars a pound.
Those are very wet consistently and those are best kept in a bowl with a lid.
And when you're going to cook or salt, you would pinch it, you know,
use your fingers or a wooden implement to remove and add to whatever you're adding it to.
And might usually refer to grinding it further.
If you have a small mortar and pestle type thing, you know, weight a pound or pulverize something finer.
So that's the little bit of the I guess the the contrast to the sugar statement you made, Seth, about the salt.
I don't have the budget to spend 30 dollars a pound on it, certainly.
But, you know, here's the thing. You might be able to get a small package for like five.
Right. And that will last you about six months.
So it might be worth it again. Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah. And it's the labor that goes into it of maintaining its quality.
You know, the handling of food, by the way, changes its quality to the palate as well.
So, yeah, very important on that aspect. But, yeah, we were sort of drifted away again.
But the food is, again, very important, not necessarily because we did bring up some other subject there.
We talked a little bit about the crowd and a little bit of, I guess, a biblical reference,
understanding or comprehending a lot of these ancient texts.
But there is going to come a time where things will be comprehended a little bit better and a pursuit of quality also will be there.
You know, just to bounce around a little bit more, Seth, you know, before we started the show,
I kind of went on the Internet and looked at the news, world news.
I just typed in world news and looked at what was being offered.
And if anyone wants to do that right now, it's the end of spring.
You'll see it's very quiet still.
There's just a ridiculousness, you know, like some boat turned over, an American tourist in Thailand.
And, you know, someone lost a toenail on some highway and, you know, just ridiculous stuff.
There's something about an election, just absurdities.
Yeah. But nonetheless, it's still a quiet period.
And so seasonally, I just wanted to bring that up because we do discuss these culturally based matters.
I just find that to be very reassuring.
Absolutely.
Yeah. And, you know, upside down the other side of the planet, they're going into the opposite season.
So which would be winter, I guess, which would be harvest for them.
Yeah. Here it has actually been very spring like.
The where I'm, you know, where I'm at, the seasons tend to change rather harshly and dramatically with maybe a couple,
three or four weeks of what would be what would feel and look like fall between the summer and the winter.
And, you know, just a few weeks of spring as well.
And over the past couple of months, it's actually been relatively pleasant and in between.
You know, so that's lots and lots of rain as well.
Probably more than is normally useful or normal.
Yeah, certainly. I have certainly more than it's been over the last few years.
But I'm someone who is very fond of rain.
So I've been enjoying it more than some, I suppose.
All the flowers have to grow.
Yeah, absolutely.
One of these days we'll discuss more on the on the concepts of weather.
One of these days, perhaps, maybe not.
But, you know, what's interesting is the states, America, let's say, and specifically the states,
the central part is very unique in the world.
You know, guys, by the way, 75 percent of all tornadoes that occur on the planet occur there or, you know, in other areas.
So it's a very interesting phenomenon.
And this is on a planet. It's unique to the planet.
Very interesting.
Coincidences, physical coincidences and ethereal coincidences that lend to the weather patterns that you that are witnessed in the plains of what's called America.
You know, the tumultuous weather, I guess, of, you know, tornadoes and things like that and bad storms and perhaps even hurricanes and such.
Yeah. So but again, I guess the weather we may not.
But I assure you, folks, what you're being told about it is not accurate, but it's accepted.
You know, weather is not thermodynamic, as as explained.
And, yeah, it's one of these things that I think mankind is not ready to discuss openly,
even though there tend to be a lot of venues, especially in alternative media and mainstream.
Believe it, believe it or not, where they do speak of what's called weather engineering and such.
And I assure you, most of it is misunderstood, if not completely misunderstood and not applicable to what's going on.
But, yeah, I think the weather bears its own discussion because it's the same type of forces that allow you to stand up from your chair and walk across the room.
If you're able to do that, that is powering the weather.
It is not thermodynamic.
Thermodynamic is just secondary aspect of it.
So, you know, the weather might be an interesting thing.
And I did have I did a. On AFR, I guest hosted a few years ago and I had as a as a guest, Trevor James Constable for two hours.
And I don't have that archive.
But I think that was a very interesting interview who has since passed away about two months now at about 90.
So everyone's I did not realize that that had happened.
Yeah. And what they call by the Pope's work schedule, March 31st, I believe so.
Right. Yeah. He should have been a household name. But either way.
Yeah. Everyone's talking about the weather. When is someone going to do something about it? Right.
That's I think Mark Twain, Samuel Clemens.
But yeah, hopefully, you know, again, based on the feedback we've gotten,
I kind of feel good about discussing the food and the cooking aspect.
Typically, when you come to uncommon sense, we will be discussing things uncommon or maybe an uncommon approach on things.
And the very in you will be a lot of repetition for several reasons.
One is there might be someone new, there might be a fifth listener or sixth listener.
The other thing is typically the people that do adhere to listening to the side,
the sonic event, a repetitious of their questions.
So perhaps maybe we should be repetition on the statements and answers.
So I don't find the repetition to be, let's say, wrote per se.
But it's almost like an indirect necessity.
It's I think like you mentioned earlier, Seth, when you read a lot of the ancient texts,
especially the biblical texts, there is a lot of repetition.
So there's something to be found through it.
Yeah, I'd recommend paying attention to that repetition as well.
Yes, it's because it's not always the same.
Seemingly, seemingly think something is repeating, but it's just slightly different.
That adds a little bit more nuance or a little more information and more clarity.
Yeah, it's kind of important.
Like I wouldn't be surprised.
Like we'd like to keep all projects must come to an end.
Limited here.
I think when the next few episodes we might start, if not the next episode,
start revisiting some of the topics that were discussed in the previous sonic experience called Ocelli and the Greek.
If it's all right with you, Seth, we could perhaps even since they do exist,
maybe do an outline and you and I can in private refer to it and discuss perhaps offline or off air what can be revisited,
maybe filling in a little bit more because I have gotten a lot of.
Absolutely.
That's and I would like to go through and review those myself, because even even as I listen,
you know, there are questions and comments that I would like to throw in there.
So I'm I'm certainly not opposed to that idea.
Doing it like that. Yeah.
Yeah. Because there's things that were brought up like, you know, how the body works.
Not because I say so, but because if you listen to what's being said, you will say so.
And it's this is not some crowd oversimplified, ridiculous idea.
This is just using the faculties in your own perception and rational thought, whether it's what to eat,
how to keep time, we've discussed.
We've discussed various mildly political things known as the foundation of, let's say,
the states known as the Constitution of their laws pretty much discussed the condition of humanity.
I call it the dummy load. They're being dummy loaded.
That's pretty much like the hamster wheel or running on a treadmill.
A lot of energy being expended, but nothing really going anywhere.
Just, you know, events occurring.
So time can pass. Right.
Many of these things in that respect that were brought up on the previous sonic show, let's say,
was commented on, questioned on.
Perhaps some of the comments were this is excellent.
Some of the comments were this is you start on a point and then I would like to have heard more on it.
So maybe that will be the aspect that we will rely on.
How about just a little bit more filling in?
We discussed what dreams are.
The education system.
Those are things that could easily be expanded on because even if you spoke on those things for eight hours a day,
you would never run out of things to discuss.
Absolutely.
The nature of the gods also we bring up.
And yes, it's gods, folks.
Sorry.
It doesn't matter what you believe in.
Your faith means absolutely nothing when it comes to the gods.
And within the realm of that spiritual realm, there is a hierarchy.
And the level of idiocy on the planet right now referring to a god meaning God or not God or whatever is just ridiculous.
There is an entire realm there and it is far more, I would say, in contrast, complex and evolved than the material realm that we see,
but not unlike it in the way we, meaning humans, have set many things up.
The hierarchy in your military, the hierarchy in society, the forms of exchange, the forms of thought and things are very similar.
And it's not because I say it.
It's because we're adhering to things that have been more memorialized from the past and looking at them and seeing if they're a good report or not.
And that's another thing.
People on, let's say, this base level of opinion that they have failed to this point to be able to discern what's a good report and what's not.
How many times have you heard, Seth, people bring up, well, that doesn't resonate with me.
So that means the opposite of resonance would be dissonance.
Something as a psychiatric term or psychological term called, what is it, cognitive dissonance.
When you hear something that is not in accord with what's previously been heard, it's rejected, let's say.
Here's the interesting concept.
What if people have been bred for a very long time and through their culture and traditions to only resonate with untruths and inaccuracy?
The minute they come across accuracy or truth, it doesn't resonate with them.
In other words, yeah, it's opposite.
Yeah, that would certainly explain quite a bit.
Yeah, but it's the most basic thing.
So the thing is also there is something called we are modern, we are advanced, right?
Yeah.
So everyone that came before, especially if they've gone through efforts to memorialize a good report, see, they're ignorant and primitive.
You see, they didn't have the Internet, right?
They didn't have automobiles or airplanes.
So we have to discount everything from them.
They're just primitive, stupid people.
The interesting thing, this is the general consensus, by the way, of humanity at this point.
And those that do adhere to some kind of, let's say, quote, unquote, religious faith or whatever, again, very simple.
It's got nothing to do with the text that it's allegedly subscribed to, to that faith or religion.
And if you don't believe that, have a conversation with someone who claims to be faithful in any particular discipline or religion,
and you'll see exactly what we're saying here.
And it just boggles the mind that it is on such a vast level.
The third word, the third word in the text, the third word.
I'll tell you, the two major religions, Islam and Christianity,
if you back up a Christian into saying, like, why aren't you doing what's in the text?
Actually, what you're doing is in the don't do list.
Nine out of ten times, if not always, what they do is they start discrediting the text.
No matter how faithful they are, they say, well, who wrote that anyway?
Who cares? I could believe without knowing any of that.
They discredit the text.
In Islam, what they do is they say, well, that can't be in the text because the Koran was written to be simple.
And what you're saying is not simple, so it can't be there.
And they refuse to look at the text.
So people are so predictable.
Yes, and you can judge a book by its cover, folks.
If someone dropped a thick book with a yellow cover at your feet, guess what?
That's a telephone book.
Very easy to recognize.
So the people that are on this planet right now that are adhering to these religions,
also these societies now formed in legal society, scientific society, medical society are also religions.
They don't know anything about what it's supposed to be based on, just like economists don't know anything about money.
It's the strangest thing.
And this is something that is repeatedly brought up as an issue on uncommon sense because it's prevalent.
And I mean prevalent.
It's everywhere.
And it's fascinating at the same time.
It is fascinating and simple.
It is relatively simple.
There's a lot of it.
A lot of something simple could be viewed as something complex, I suppose, but that's not really the case.
You've got to understand, like we've said, who you are, where you are, and when you are.
That's like the three-part formula to getting a good roundabout idea so you could relax and look at things objectively.
So with that said, we just did another episode of Uncommon Sense.
And this is kind of a mixed bag of stuff.
Hope you folks enjoyed it.
And we'll see you guys again in about 166 hours.
So again, thanks, Seth.
Thank you.