Welcome one and all this is American Freedom Radio at Americanfreedomradio.com
And this is the Greek with Seth Michael
And we're going to be working on a project called Uncommon Sense. So welcome everyone who's listening out there and welcome Seth
Hello, Seth
Hello Greek
All right, and we're here
We're calling it Uncommon Sense. This is a project. We're calling it a project because
There's a purpose
and we're
thankful to American Freedom Radio to give us this time
and
You're going to be hearing us meaning the Greek and Seth
For as long as it takes for this project to perhaps either come to a completion or somehow
Be perpetual in one way or another
and again, it's called Uncommon Sense and
Why is it uncommon?
Because maybe
It's time for something like this
There's an ancient Greek philosopher
That talked about things being uncommon
And maybe we're going to go beyond philosophy and talk about the practical
And things that anyone can attain or observe
So with that said
Yeah, you perhaps heard the greek speak before
And you've heard Seth Michael before as well
And yeah, Seth you you have some
Expertise of your own as well people know you as being sonically rich in one way or another
So if Seth want to say a word or two before we start getting into what we're going to do
On this project Seth you want to just maybe say a few things?
Yeah, i'd like to let everyone know if they would like they can visit the website
It's currently just sort of like a calling card, but it's uncommonradio.com spelled just how it sounds very
Straightforward and should be relatively easy to find
uncommonradio.com
Eventually, you'll be able to find past recordings of the program there
We may end up doing a small bibliographic section just for
Possible references for some of the subjects that we talk about
and it's going to be
Relatively
This being the first episode. It's kind of an introduction
Um quite literally and etymologically even
That's a an accurate way of describing it. So
We're going to just kind of have a conversation
and
For those of you that are new to well, everyone I suppose will be new to this program
but uh, we'll we'll do you know, we're not just gonna
jump in
To the thick of things without a little bit of a a primer for those who haven't
Heard these topics discussed before and honestly if you haven't
heard
the greek
Or myself or heard us speak, you know with each other on the different programs that we've done. So
It will be
Something that is is certainly uncommon. I think that uh, i'm I like words and uh their meanings throughout
uh history i'm kind of a
a an etymologist of sorts
and
Uncommon is is a an apt title for for this program. So
Um, yeah, let's let's get into it. What would you like to discuss? Well, you know, there's a perspective
that one can take and um
it's called the the object the objectivity of a matter or the objectiveness of something or the perspective of
Uh something being a little more clean or pure less tainted or corrupt
and uh
We found that
I say we whoever the we is incorporated in that is that there's a there's a a social
Undertone about this is a society of corruption. It's a society of
just bad things happening and you know, everyone sort of accepts this as being common, but
But why you know, is it?
Are we just discussing the symptoms as a collective?
Are there specific reasons? Is there a history involved? Is the perception involved?
Is uh, is there something called the psychology of a crowd?
You know, I just want to introduce
Someone named gustav lebon who wrote a book called the crowd in 1895
And it's the psychology of a crowd and what happens when people get together
And typically it's not very positive
But there are positive things that can come out of it if it's done
And let's say a fit and proper or lawful way
So we're going to start looking at things here. Um, partly because uh, there's an unspoken need for it as well
You know seth many times I turn on what's called media whether it's mainstream or alternative
And I might be alone and I find myself yelling at the speakers or the device that i'm listening to
And i'm like, I can't believe this is being said and accepted
You know how many times have I think you and I have mentioned that in private?
And it goes across the board seemingly with almost any topic that's ever discussed whether it be religious
governmental judicial economic scientific
I'm, like wondering and saying what are they saying?
This stuff is
Unfounded
It's completely debased
so there there's a search that some people want to want to
Embark on which is to find out what things are based on
and of course
Like i've said before
You're not going to make friends doing this because people like to be part of the crowd. You will have some interesting conversations
Yes
Yes as well, you know the thing with that is occasionally
People that have strong beliefs in the things that we just brought up as being unfounded
you you have to be very careful with them because sometimes they start to put on a face that
Implies that they're ready to bring physical bodily harm to you
You have to be very careful on how you approach some of these subjects
Yes. Yes, um i've found
uh in talking with
Just specifically with the history of words and
I guess kind of a small primer on
my perspective of what words are and my own kind of
involvement and
intrigue
you could say with
The specifically the english language just because that's the one that I you know am most familiar with
Is that words are
are
It can be very very useful. Um, and that's because in
the very very basic
It's they they're tools. They are tools and we use them. Yeah, we use them to communicate with one another
Uh, we use them in in song in verse
um, and that's you know
has been
We've used them for for quite quite a while now we being, you know service-willing earth inhabitants
um
and
I when I was younger I read
um
a a few a handful of books that had a
Probably an unintentioned impact upon me, uh by ursula le glean
um
and
They they were you know novels. It was fiction, but the the way that words were used
As uh, what could be described as like a plot device?
Um was kind of eye-opening for me at a at a relatively young age, um, and
That's so i've i've always had
uh this
You know like we all do like the that feeling that something just isn't right and when you start getting into
uh language
and
you realize that
We take words from other languages and apply our own meanings to them
Specifically english speakers as it means perhaps. Yeah. Yeah as we we will change
What is being said and as someone who?
Uh likes to read old books
And study, you know old writings and things of that nature
Knowing what the words meant when they were first used in these writings
becomes something of importance because we live in a time where
These tools, you know, these words are used
not simply to build things but also to
tear things down and to alter them to change what is
Being built and not only not only written but spoken i've noticed
Perhaps there's a qualitative issue there, you know people can be wordy
Many things can be written and said but on the quality issue perhaps
Um, I like saying do you say what you mean and mean what you say?
You know like the issue of people describing their offspring as kids
Is an interesting concept to dwell on just for a moment because um
People will say my kids this my kids that and I said well that's going to be really rough having that many goats around
And they're like, well, you know what?
I mean, i'm not talking about goats and i'm saying but you said kids 15 times in the last 10 seconds
So a kid is a baby goat so you don't say what you mean and you don't mean what you say
So we have a quality issue here. Hmm
So because intentionally
One can just sit back and say i'll let them use the term kid
Because I do know what they mean in this particular society, right?
But what that tells me about that certain person man woman individual let's say
Is that there's a quality issue here, right?
They're not
Looking at the quality of what they're saying
whether it lacks specificity or accuracy or it also tells me a lot about the person that they
Are very readily prepared to fall into the social norm of the day
you see and
You know, and by the way, you mentioned about looking at ancient and old books and writings and I just want to say this
out loud
uh
Is that many people today have an aversion to bringing up the topic of things old?
I've noticed that and it's increasing
Uh, and and what I found looking at things that are old
Is that when you one studies, uh, let's say these heightened civilizations in the past, you know
Ancient babylon ancient greece ancient rome and so ha and so far even some of the ancient cultures right before their fall
They considered themselves to be modern
And if and I guess this society today does consider themselves to be modern as well, don't they
And you've heard that history repeats itself. I don't think it does because history is just a record
I believe that people repeat it
um, there's a level here of quality again if
One doesn't care about the outcome whether it's positive or negative and they just seem to just go ahead with something
Just to go ahead with it
There seems to be a major issue of quality
So it's the quality of things I think that we will begin to broach on and discuss
Further and further as time goes on
yeah, and the
um
I've i've heard it said and I cannot place the quote
That history does not repeat but it does rhyme
right and you will see uh throughout
Even just what is easily available to us through specifically, you know
right now
with uh the access to
All this information whether it's good or bad or true or false, you know is
something that we will get into further but
the the access that we have
currently is
uh without precedent in
You know academically accepted
History be careful with that word. Yes. Yes, well, uh with intention. Yes, let's uh
Whether it's been you know, whether we've had uh ease of communication
uh worldwide in the past is something that is currently
uh
speculated about um, there have been you know, a lot of
recent findings
that
would suggest that
the
the ability to communicate globally
um
Has you know is not something that is actually new and though it may not be, you know, exactly history repeating itself
Um, it seems to like I said, you know, right?
So yeah, well here here's here's maybe a thought that will probably set the tone for things uncommon
Um, it could it could be dubbed the information age right might have heard that we're in the information age
And now let's look at a little bit of history and I know people cringe because you know, we just kind of established from
Sensing, uh some feedback not not from all but from many people don't like discussing things that are not
Modern, but let's not get too old. Let's just talk about have you heard of the industrial age, right?
This was late 19th century or so
um and and um
Then you know, what is what is how did that end up?
Um, a lot of planned obsolescence toxicity and and proof of that is you know, I like going into
um chiding, uh
New car dealers, you know, I walk in and I say to the car dealers. I say well, you know, is this the new model?
And they say yes it is and I say is it different than last year's and say oh, yeah it is
I said could that be because you guys haven't still figured out how to make them, right?
You know, uh, I bought a hammer 30 years ago and if I go buy a hammer today
It seems to be relatively the same almost indiscernible
Might be a different color might be a different color as such but but here's the thing. What is the industrial age brought?
A lot of things that people are not really so happy about but don't want to discuss
I mean in in the americas you have what's called the rust belt in in united what they call the united states
Uh, and there's there's just an interesting just tastefulness
That lingers when you say industrial age now, let's go maybe bump around a little bit
And then came what's called the space age, right? That was the space age, you know when they're in 1950s 60s 70s
We're in the space age. How did that how did that work out?
Uh, we had jumped the gun on titling that that age
Yeah, I think they were talking about the space between people's ears, but but nonetheless
Um, here's the thing and and i'm going to say this emphatically you you're not going into space
You know, you were promised flying cars at the world's fair in the 30s by the 1980s
You're promised jet packs. I know the jetsons supposedly took place in the year 2200 or 2100 or something
But you're not going to the moon. You're not going into space. Sorry folks
And there's a very simple reason why because if you go out into space
There is no way you're going to be come back and tell people what you saw because if you're in space things are not
As you've been told
And the people that's why there are so few going into space and coming back
And you don't go into space unless you accept
The truth that you will give the report that you're told to report on what you saw when you're out there
Fascinating, but what happened to the space race? What happened to space age? No, let's not talk about that, man
Right. So now this is the information age. Oh boy
Need I say any more?
What information what information
Well, there's plenty of information. It's it's uh,
You know, it's validity. It's convenience is is
Questionable. Yes and yeah convenience. Absolutely. I mean here here's the interesting part about it
There's something called about the best and highest use of something
and um, uh
You know what let's just be truthful about this if the internet or alternative media had
Anything that was in its best and highest use in terms of uncommon sense we wouldn't be here
I would just privately be messaging people go listen to this
Go hear that
And it's not to say that there's not a lot of good stuff, but it's really difficult to find it
And is it a needle in the haystack? Absolutely, but you know the easiest way to find
A needle in the haystack is with a magnet
That's right
Yeah, and there's a lot of we could say the term bulldung or bullshit and there's a lot of it everywhere
But you know what? It only takes a little shovel to move a big pile of it
So it's going to be very interesting. So henceforth this project
You know, uh, there's it's all about perspective and point of view
You know, it's uh, what vantage point
You know, and again, I encourage anyone to pick up gustav lebon l-e-b-o-n the crowd and just to preface on that
What's going on still?
is
Gustav lebon wrote about the crowd psychology. I don't fully endorse everything that he said, but it's really a very neat and tidy package
um to look at
And just to boil it down for people
In order to form a crowd or when a crowd forms they form under an idea
And typically the idea has to be simplified and often oversimplified
So everyone in the crowd can accept it
and when these ideas and concepts that the crowd unites under become
Simplified and sometimes if not mostly
Oversimplified they no longer represent the original concept or theme
And now we have a big diversion and what ends up being a mob very often. I mean
A very simple way to look at it is look at uh,
alternative media
What do they call activism?
or protesting
Or movements or they call it truth movement and such, you know, I mean
Has that yielded anything?
um
You know, I mean is it yielded anything really other than youtube hits for people, you know when there is you know
um, I I would agree with what you said at the very at the very beginning with
Listening to media in all of its forms
um
and I suppose that it's easy for us to pick on, you know alternative media in particular because
Uh, you and I are you know
Relatively familiar with it and have been for a number of years
And have listened to a lot of what is out there and not just
Okay, so we will seth has just maybe lost a little bit of contact I hope i'm still available
But uh the picking on the alternative media is not the be-all end-all but it was probably
One way to say folks you've got to start thinking about what is the highest
Use the highest and best use of this and it's first communication second
information and third entertainment
And very often what i've heard from many is that they just like listening for entertainment
And the subject matter can be very very serious to the trivial and what's interesting is when we get serious
you know
One thing that I come out and say very typically is hey, does anyone know what day it is today?
And that ends up always being one of the most interesting topics that people like to ignore
You know keeping time
Keeping uh
a basis for things that
You might want to function in what is that based on? You know, what is your faith based on?
What is the science based on you know, and these are the subjects that we're going to try to perhaps
Grab by the tail one by one and continue to open and show people. Hey
There's no reason to be frustrated and if you are it's really your choice because everything is commonly available
And when you show things as being commonly available, it seems very uncommon because not all the other
people or
Children in the class want to do that
So it's going to be a very interesting ride here. So as we're
Continuing we lost seth for a moment. Hopefully we'll get him back in a moment. Uh, so
I'll just continue with some of the concepts that people might want to
Say is called greek speak
you know, uh
i'd say
one thing to start with is
What day is it really basic and uh might sound kind of shocking
But do you know that you can't keep time with the pope's work schedule? What?
Pope's work schedule. Yeah
Do you know the thing you call the calendar?
Do you know that you can't keep time with that?
It's not a time piece, but wait a second greek. I go to work and do all kinds of things
Well, it seems like we dropped
Lost the web coming back
Oh, we're all we're still on we just had a glitch there technical
Glitch, uh, it shows that we don't have the radio, but I hear that we're still speaking. We're still on
so, um
Let's see if uh, we are I don't have a way to monitor this, but we'll just continue we did we did lose you
uh
Yeah, and we shouldn't be on because american freedom radio is uh,
Showing that we're offline, but I don't know if we're online. Maybe i'll uh, just take a five second inquiry here
I'll be right back. Okay. Well, I think it's just you and I uh, I think we got dropped
I don't know if uh, danny is I don't know. I don't know if we're on right now
Um, let me just go into chat and see what happens
Oh, it says we're still on. Okay, great
We're still on I just got a message. Thank you. Thank you, uh steve
uh
So, you know seth I was going into a little bit of a monologue there before you
You know, we were trying to recover you is and that was about keeping time. Isn't that very interesting?
One of the most basic things
Is learning how to keep time?
And I brought up the subject that you know, you can't keep time with the pope's work schedule and that sounds really strange
Huh? What?
That thing you call a calendar is not a time piece
Uh, that's something we could start at in
Wondering, you know, what is going on?
Could it be possible that the entire planet?
Is not paying any attention
and they've
Basically gave up on keeping time for a work schedule put out by the papacy
You know, I I think starting uh, and
Answering the question. What is time?
Would be a good place to start with that. Thank you. Yeah, because it's such a broad subject
I mean, it's a big it's like a large elephant
Which side of it you want to look at?
And interesting time can simply be defined by the recordation of events
And that kind of goes in the face of time travel you hear a lot about time travel
And you're not really traveling in time if you if anyone
Supposes to have done that you're actually traveling to past or future events, but time itself
time itself is uh
Are you still getting an echo?
No, i'm not getting an echo
Neither am I
So maybe just on the monitoring end, yeah, sorry about the technical difficulties, um folks will bear with us
But uh, maybe we'll just keep rolling along and seeing uh, kind of feedback we get from the studio
Um, but but timing the recordation of events and maybe there's a lot of nonsense thrown into science fiction
That can actually travel through record events
Perhaps it's the
Event itself that people are listening that either there's something from the past or the future
But in essence, uh keeping time and then to start back that you can't keep time with the
Pope's work schedule is an interesting concept as well
um
i've heard
uh, i've you know, i've
a lot of
anything
a lot of anything in this in this plane is
uh, very subject to
uh perception and
One's perspective where you were perceiving things from so I imagine that from
a uh
a higher perspective
There would be
a
A completely and totally different concept of what we would be familiar with this time. Whereas
Uh, you know, we are experiencing this
through our own very limited
um
perception and if there is a
Another point of reference another
point actually not point of reference but point of
perception
That things could be viewed actually
as
nothing existing
Outside of now and I don't mean this moment as relative to you and I but I mean
all moments as relative to
a perspective
that
might be if not difficult to
attain certainly difficult to
comprehend
with the you know, the limited
Interaction that we have with this world through our our meat puppets, you know our
But but but but again just to revisit the concept of time
It's a form of communication when we show up when we meet when we do things
and to see that uh, uh
It's such a simple form that maybe we can say there's lawful time keeping and there's
the
Could we say unlawful? Would it be fair to say unlawful?
You know, uh, in other words what i'm trying to
Is like if anyone observes a certain day
On what they call their glory encounter, you notice how it's a different day of week every year
How could it be and no one's paying attention to this?
Because you know could it be that there are actually mechanisms that are lawful for keeping time that are being ignored
And actually might become the norm in the future as they were in the past
You know, certainly like just throw this out, you know, uh today appears to be the sixth day of the second month
I'm, not making this up
So, uh, we'll still have a little
A bit of a technical problem. Let's see folks just bear with us
So we might just reset this and be back in a moment
And we're waiting for seth to come back
Apparently there was an echoing problem technical problem here
Which hopefully will be mitigated some way or another
Addressing some technical issues
So
But I do believe that we are back broadcasting live again, this is american freedom radio
And you are listening to
Seth and the greek
on uncommon sense
This being our first broadcast like this we are
Dealing with some technical issues, but they're being addressed. So we do appreciate your patience
I think I can speak for the both of us on that at least
Okay
Yes. All right. Let's see. We're back now. We have a little bit of technical issue
But I hopefully it's been resolved and i'm relying on some feedback from anyone that's monitoring to see how we're doing
Okay, so I hear that we're all back to normal. So, uh, yeah, so seth, uh, let's try this again
There's something about this timekeeping thing that we uh, just can't seem to bring that properly and I hear that we're good
Okay. Thank you. Uh steve. Thank you everyone else for uh supplying the uh,
quality
feedback here
Uh, but seth in short, you know, how many times have you and I discussed even publicly and publicly, uh on air about um
the pope's work schedule and no disrespect, of course because
You know through certain covenants one might say that you should never say anything bad against the leader of a people
But what's interesting about that?
Is very often there's a lot of
Hmm
Conspiratoriality or let's just say bad mouthing of the papacy
The vatican the roman system
And what's really interesting about that is you approach any of those individuals and ask them what day it is and you know
What they always say something between january and december and monday through friday
I just got to shake my head and walk away and say you've just admitted with your own mouth that you're the pope's subject
By the way, you keep time
How do you think the rest of your active
Activism or protesting the papacy is going to go for you. It's not going to do very well
so
You know, how how can one set themselves apart without acknowledging what they're doing? That's another concept as well
But you know, I think we can go over time keeping but maybe just rolling along with some of the concepts that'll be brought up
You know the concept of being set apart perhaps
Do you think we're moving along on too many subjects here seth, how do you feel about it?
No, I think we're doing just fine
dealing with
What we're dealing with. I think that I think that time is a good
a good, uh
Basis, um and having it it's recordation actually based upon something
Uh that might be a little bit more
Than arbitrary or a yeah a methodology that is easily referenced
uh
for you know
certain localities
Um, but well beyond that as well for you know anywhere on on on the face of this
Planet that you can see the sky
because from
the earliest
Records that we have available to us and again by we I just mean, you know service-willing
earth inhabitants
Um, it seems that
The stars and the other celestial bodies have always been used
uh to keep time because it is
those are things that
um
If they are arbitrary, they are arbitrary on a level that makes the term
Uh moot
Yeah, exactly from our perspective. So with that we have
uh
a system of reference that is can be you viewed if if not universal certainly
colloquially universal to
You know surface-dwelling earth inhabitants you can look up and identify
The you know the difference between the what we call the moon
And the sun
Then you have uh
You have all of the tools necessary
uh at the very least
to tell
what day
of the month
Uh, what day of the month not what the date is, but what what day?
it is
uh using
Which is say one more time say that one more time
Please there's a difference between the day and the date where a date is something used on a document based on a system
That's accepted
For the let's say nomenclature of that document
Or that society but it has nothing to do with the day. Yes continue, please
Yeah, so we are
uh dealing with uh
Subtle differences, but as I said, you know words are our tools and how how they are used
It has an effect upon the world around us. Um and our interactions with it. So being aware
That's
Uh things it's not just that things
Feel as if they are not right is actually the things
In general are not are not right. We're living in a time. That is incredibly arbitrary. Um arbitrary just means
um spoken
It's very very basic uh an arbitrator someone who speaks generally on another's behalf
but uh, it's literally, you know spoken so
the the date, um, which
What the
They would call it
uh by the by the work schedule
um, the papacy today would be
The third month and the what 26th day
Uh-huh
2016 and I wonder what happened over the other years, but go ahead, right? Yes, certainly. Um, even
even uh skeptics
I don't think that year, you know, the the zero year is when time began
Uh, that's just oh, yeah, and it's a it's it's significantly arbitrary and once you realize that
at the very basic things of what we use
uh to
Orchestrate our lives and to plan things
Um is completely and totally arbitrary. That's one easy simple easily referenceable way
to acknowledge and
Be aware that
Yes thing something is not right
right many things are not right this is
uh, and it's something that's it's
uh, very rarely discussed
at least in this manner and
um for
people all over all over the earth, that's
Reckon certain days to be significant
For one reason or another what those days are has been impacted greatly by
Um
By this work schedule and it is functional as a work schedule
It's good for a building plan if you have a work that needs to be done
It works very well for that
But it works well for organizing the subjects and by the way, it just does a footnote here. We're not poaching any subjects here
We're not asking anyone to consider what we're saying for their reality. Let's say
So yeah
But it is it is you know, i've heard of certain corporate campuses where they had 10 day work cycles
And the days were either given letters name, uh letters or colors
Yes, and the people rotated on the on certain cycles
And and what's going on right now is the entire planet has pretty much adopted that like, you know
Can we give a quick example today is what they call here where we are saturday the 26th of march
Do you know that last year it was probably a thursday or friday and next year it might be a sunday
So let me ask you is march 26, uh thursday or friday a saturday or sunday
It's neither and no one is paying any attention to this at all
you know, so
What else are they paying attention to you know, it's quite interesting
How about how about instead of um, I feel like we might be leaving a little bit of a vacuum
Maybe just show a little historic
reference
uh, perhaps uh
Let's just maybe discuss the concept that if anyone does a little bit of history
They'll notice that uh, it was traditional in ancient societies that they settled their debts with the full moon
and isn't it
Interestingly apparent that today you're sent a monthly bill
Your debts are allegedly settled with the moon
Or but even though they're not following it and what's interesting is you ever look at the?
pope's work schedule that the
Beginnings of the months tend to align more with the full moon
Than the middle dark moon interesting just something to think about
and and also because you got to remember all systems whether they're
Accurate or arbitrary still have there a parody on something that was lawful or based on something you see
Now the other interesting thing is if when the day starts if we look at ancient texts we see
That the day started at high noon
Whether it's biblical or secular
And what's interesting if people are old enough
Do you remember if you went to a banking institution and made a deposit afternoon they counted it as the next day?
Yes, um, they still I i'm not
uh
Incredibly well versed in in
current banking practices
But it is I I believe that it is still the case
um that
The you know, the banking day, um does still
uh
Begin and end, you know, uh midday, you know, yeah, and and what's interesting is
Uh those that are I guess older film aficionados. Remember the wild west films the the papacy didn't chase them down
into the
the nether parts of the western americas
And they would hold court during day and uh the executions of hanging someone what what time did they start?
What when did those happen high noon?
Yep
Interesting, right
uh, so so these things now are something
that
Is the basis for time keeping and why why is it important to have a basis for things because guess what when you have?
The basis of it. You don't have to buy anything you ever notice that
When you start going into things that are based on something that is tangible
it sort of
Eliminates a need to have commerce being involved
you know, uh
So if you're using the celestial bodies to keep time, which is the lawful way or it's the basis you don't have to buy anything
I remember, uh
Growing up and the parents and the people around me said oh it's near the end of the year
We need to go to the hardware store or whatever and get a free calendar. So we know what day it is next year
right
Yeah, now it's done through the electronic conventions through the devices
So it's interesting how it transferred from print
To electronic it's and by the way, I just want to throw something in there you ever notice how
you bring up a bit of information, let's say in a text or a chat or
Online and what do people ask for they ask for a link you have a link for that
And i'm like, wait a second this link thing. I mean, it sounds reasonable, but there's something funny about it
Oh, I see aren't chains made of links
But anyway, I just wanted to
Yeah, so so this massive chain of links
Is being built and no one is paying attention to the fine points on what anything is based on
you know, another thing
maybe we could bring up is
temperature
Again, we mentioned something about quality. No one is paying attention to quality. It's all about quantity
You know when we discuss temperature we kind of talk about
The mercury rising or the mercury falling and by the way, you know mercury is toxic to us by the way
That's mostly
Yeah, okay. So it's interesting that was chosen. Yeah, I'd say well greek, you know was chosen. It's fluid. It's easy to work with
Okay, okay. Okay. That's not the point just an interesting observation. Remember just visiting here taking notes, right?
But what's interesting is the mercury
Or let's say the temperature quantity
Strictly limited to the expansion and contraction of mercury now. Hold on a second here
If you're wearing let's say a short sleeve shirt at sea level
At 70 degrees fahrenheit you might say you're comfortable
But if you go down below sea level at 70 degrees fahrenheit
with the same article clothing
You might say you feel a little a touch warm
But if you're at a mountaintop
At 70 degrees fahrenheit with the same short sleeve shirt, you might say you're a touch cool and you might need a jacket
But wait a second
It measured 70 degrees according to the mercury at all three locations. But how come you feel different?
Because it's the quality of the temperature that's not being discussed and where are the young
People let's say the brighter minds. Let's just say what people like to say about it
Why aren't they taught in these quote-unquote educational institutions to come up with devices that measure quality?
hmm
You see how important is that? How is how important is it to comprehend that just because it's 70 degrees flat
at sea level
Below sea level and at the top of a mountain you feel quite different
And it's noticeably felt
And there's no way to measure that quality
And how come there's no discussion about that?
It seems like quality has gone away. I want to lead into one other thought how many times have you heard
of
overpopulation
The earth is overpopulated man too many people
Oh, is that a quality issue or a quantity issue? It seems like oh, it's again. It's a quantity issue, isn't it?
So I throw out something here for folks
Do you know that a combustion engine your average size combustion engine you combusts more air in eight hours than an average person does in a year
So if you figure out the amount of combustion engines that are on the planet right now
Not only automobiles motorcycles, but generators and machines
And you did the long hand math on that and i've done this and I don't need to
Put this load on people's minds technically
If you did the math the amount of air that's being consumed by these motors
Or engines I should say is equivalent to a thousand billion people on the planet right now
So, where's the quantity problem?
But here's the thing i'll recommend and this is an opinion which I give very shortly
If the earth's population was reduced down to less than a hundred people
If you threw in one rabbi one priest one attorney and a scientist
In 40 years, you're going to be exactly where you are right now
Sorry
Not to offend anyone
And let's just take this around the block maybe and come back to where we started you ever hear people say that offends me
I have a thought for them
If you're if you're pursuing the truth, how can you be offended?
If someone if someone calls if you're pursuing the truth
and
Someone calls you an a-hole
well
Okay. Well, let's examine that we'll say well, uh, this person just called me that
uh
Is it true or not?
Well, if it's not true, it's not true. So it doesn't matter and if it is true, well, they just perceived the truth
So where's the offense?
Where's the offense truth is often dissonant. What if it really is?
What if the lie is resonant now again for the people cringing these guys are talking about ancient languages and ancient books?
I can't stand it
Right. I can't I hate that stuff because i'm modern i've got an ipad and I declare i'm modern and I know
Yeah, I know
Uh-huh
Yeah, uh, so
Here's the interesting part about all this right? I don't want to go into a rant, but it's so easy
right, uh, because remember I think we prefaced earlier that
You know you try to tune into what's being said whether it's mainstream or alternative
If you find yourself yelling at the speakers or the device you're listening to
This is the show for you. That's all i've got to say but
What's interesting though?
Is oh is is it really a show but but here here's the point
um, the point is
When you listen to what people sing because you kind of like try to meditate which means to revisit
Maybe go over it again. Let's say in your mind. I'm trying to find where are they where are they getting this from?
It just sounds good. Well, it resonates with me
Wow
So what if the lie is resonant and the truth is dissonant?
What if people really hate the truth?
about any matter
Isn't that an interesting concept? It's kind of scary
And and if it if that seems to be the norm
You ain't gonna change it. So I guess your only option is to set yourself apart from it
What I mean by set yourself apart, let's say you had to work in the sewer because they paid really really well
Would you jump in naked skinny dip and drink the water?
Or would you put on full body hazmat suit with breathing tanks?
you see
And a lot of people want to change things that ain't gonna change
so
How about thinking about setting yourself apart?
You know, how about
People say oh the opposite of love is hate
I found out by observation
Takes sometimes a bit of passion to love and it's almost an equal amount of passion to hate
Could it be that the opposite of it of love might not be hate at all?
That it's possibly apathy
Or just leaving it alone
Yeah, it's interesting. I want to throw in something because this might be non-secular but
In the biblical text and I hate bringing that up because it's been hijacked by certain religions
It says if your brother sins against you forgive him, right?
You've heard that people say that and by the way, I haven't well we can get into a little bit of discussion of these things
But you know, the word forgiveness is not in the biblical text
What they're translating as forgive
Is the greek word a feces which means to get away from it or leave it alone
Anyway, you're not supposed to be a masochist or is it a sadist?
so
Setting oneself you're also not going to find the word holy in there. Sorry. That's the word set apart
or unearthly or unworldly
So anyway at one time
These words, you know
They're as I was speaking to the the etymology in the history of words spoken and recorded in in literature
And how they were first used
It's not that the word holy isn't in there. It's that the word holy has
uh taken on
a a new a new thought pattern in in colloquial speech
When you say the word holy it doesn't simply mean something that is set apart. It means
uh, you know
Whatever those when you hear
someone speak the word holy not you greek, but
When you know when most people hear that word it's going to immediately bring to mind
a great many things
And that may not that may not just be coincidence. Yes, but
what the term actually means in specifically in you know, the
These these old texts is simply that it's it's something that's set apart
Right and like if you're something another term, uh
With uh in the same vein would be uh, you know unclean whereas that one actually is
uh
relatively
etymologically
Uh accurate even in even in modern english
Unclean, but that's simply what it
What it means, you know what it says it's it's unclean that that isn't clean. It should you know, so
But go ahead
Hmm
No, it's interesting because there's an interesting concept of what resonates with people, you know, uh, you go to a courtroom
They tell you to put your hand on the bible and swear
How about you just say wait a second? I've got it here on a thumb drive or a dvd. Can I swear on that?
Oh, no. No, no, you can't it's it's not the same thing
Wasn't the biblical text a form of communication if you don't know what's trying to be communicated now?
It's just a rabbit's foot
Or a talisman or a good good luck charm or some form of iconography. Yeah, that's uh, that instance in particular
Is not something that i've ever actually
had to do
but um, I would I would find it difficult to not
Uh ask the administrator of whatever proceedings those were
Uh, i'll say judge. I would not ask I I would find it difficult to not ask the judge
Just like this so what you're asking me to do
Is to place my hand on on this book that you have idolized that specifically says
To not make and to not swear
Exactly. It says to not swear first and foremost. It says to let your yes be yes and your no be no
um and to not
idolize
Uh physical objects, so you're asking me to place my hand
On this on this icon
And to swear on on this icon that if you look at the information that is actually preserved in this text
It specifically says to not do both of those things
Yeah, because it's it's basically you're you're
Have we ever discussed what justice is perhaps you're walking into a justice court? And yes, every nation every group of people
Uh has a patron deity you've heard of patron saints
But no one's talking about and justice for all oh boy, no, thank you
Why because maybe we've done a little bit of homework on that by the way, the internet is very sparse
Maybe because it's subject to human input
But if anyone does have a chance to research the ancient goddess religions that are being revived
One of their high days is coming up
Yeah, one of their set apart dates. I should say are you saying this in jest as in the first day of what they call april?
um
No, actually, uh tomorrow I believe at least here in the states, uh is what they call easter
Oh the festival of ashtar. Yes, and you know, I read something interestingly enough. Uh,
Sorry to to digress but I think it's let's go
Go down that road
um
That the name easter doesn't actually come from uh ishtar, but actually comes from
oyster
um, which is uh
proto english word actually but in the same text that was describing how
Easter does not actually come from ishtar and that rabbits and eggs weren't
associated with ishtar although she was
Babylonian goddess of fertility sex and uh, was it war?
and
But then later in this same article and it's not something that I I delved into greatly but it's a concept that i'm well
versed in I suppose
and
Uh later in the same thing that says that it doesn't actually come from uh, ishtar
Which was the this babylonian goddess that comes from oyster, which was uh, this like english or or druidic
Uh goddess of of fertility and things like that i'm going so you're totally missing missing the connection there right between the
So we'll pick this up
We'll pick up the a little more on the ishtar oyster, uh
Easter mess when we come back. You're listening to american freedom radio
And welcome back to uncommon sense with the greek and seth michael
Seth we just uh had the break and we left off perhaps talking about the entire easter ashtar oyster mess
And uh, what's interesting is these things have become so arbitrary
That have you ever heard the expression? I don't know whether we should laugh or cry
Yes, I would suggest laughing. I would suggest laughing as well
there is not to say that I haven't done, you know, my own share of crying over various things, but uh the laughter
um at that point where you
It's like well, it's one or the other and i've had to explain to people when I was laughing
At an appropriate time is like well, I mean
It's either we have a breakdown or we just look at it for what it is and uh and laugh about it
So and from and it's got to be from the quality of it because from a quantity
Point of view all the other boys and girls are doing it. What's wrong with you?
If you look at the quality of what's being done, though, you've got to say like little boys and girls do it sucks
Now, why does it suck? Let's just preface. I got to say this and I can't say it enough times. Listen folks
Whenever you hear someone come up whether it's on radio whether it's on print or in your university halls
And they start discussing anything biblical if the first thing that doesn't come out of their mouth
is
The biblical text has yet to be translated. Well what it was based on which is preserved in ancient greek and ancient hebrew
Has not been translated to this date
Well, wait a minute greek that's a pretty harsh statement because I got something that says the king james version
It's one of the best-selling books in the world
Yeah, and i've got the new new international version. I even got one of these blah blah blah blah the other bibles
But they're all versions
What are you talking about
And what's interesting is you've got people coming out and being interviewed and I get lots of youtube hits by the way
They're real must be really good
Oh that never existed and the interviewer is saying oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No one's ever saying well, wait a second
It's never been translated. How would you know? Did you do any research on the languages of preservation?
I mean you hear all kinds of stories
ranging from reincarnation
To none of these characters ever existed
or the son of god is the sun in the sky
or
It's really about chicken semen dripping out of your nostril
whatever, whatever whatever and you just got to do the double-faced palm and say
I can't believe i'm hearing this and the major and this resonates with the public. Why?
Because when you bring up any ancient writ of any culture, it has literally been hijacked by its corresponding religion
because
Guess what?
There's not a religion on the planet bar none that does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to
Yeah, yeah, it's it's tradition I would almost
because of my fondness of of words
I'm hesitant to use the word religion when someone asks me a question about things
of
you know
having to do with ancient texts
or
what is commonly referred to as
spirituality and the varying religions
Like, you know what what religion
Etc. I'm like, well, I'm I you know, I I wash my hair
Every day, I brush my teeth every day. Those are you know things that I do
With a lot of regularity those could be considered a religion
but what is often referred to or
What is always referred to?
statistically
is
In religion is simply the traditions that are commonly followed by a group of people generally relatively large groups
But that's not necessarily the case
On a regular basis something you do regular basis. I go to church on sunday. I go to temple on saturday all in the pope's work schedule
and uh, yeah, yeah real interesting, uh
You know, you know, here's the you know, the spirituality I think we've defined
Many times and we might actually want to do an entire hour on this
Is what the spirit and the soul is and let's just say it real fast
The soul is your breath
And if you're breathing whether you're a dog a cat an insect a bird or a man
That is the soul
Yeah, let me let me address that very thing for for just a moment and because that is a subject of
Uh of interest to me certainly and again it comes back to the the studying of the the old writings and where
We get these terms because the language that we used to discuss a lot of those things
Are very is is very arbitrary
And again when I say arbitrary, I mean basically someone is saying that this is the way that it is that's arbitrary
if someone says okay today
is
friday or today is
Yeah, and pick a day today is cow day, okay, that's arbitrary that's our blue day
Yeah, or blue day or red day. I would I would be fond of that. I like the color red. Um,
but before I digress and they're able to inflict that on the rest of the civilization and they agree to it now, it's
Still are through authority be that authority. Uh
Traditional or or religious or governmental and honestly, uh religious
Hierarchy is simply a government and so if you can look at history
That way and realize that these religious organizations are just simply another form of government using a different dialogue different jargon
You'll have
a more accurate way of things
Way of perceiving it and I suppose that's an opinion but before I go too far off off it and soul
Um when we say that soul when the specifically the greek, um says that soul is is breath and air
and spirit is
Is basic is you basically not the carnal you not not your hands not your feet
but that force that
what what
Brings in and lets go of thoughts
The the self the site and it's intangible where the soul
Yeah is that's that's spirit and
Now it's it's confusing
Because when you go into the etymology of soul and spirit both of those words are going to take you back
to
wind
Essentially, um, and i'm i'm paraphrasing it here for this. I have a feeling just interrupt for a moment seth
I just interrupt just to step on you just for a second because I think it's important. I'm not a conspiracy theorist
But if you really want to look for a conspiracy, this is it folks
You have the you have the definition
So obfuscated and obscured that there's something important about being able to discern that because
The soul is what the spirit is. You've pretty much got the three components of headquarters, which is you
Now, let me just put it this way if you're deceived about headquarters. Is it possible that you're going to be?
Emanating that deception and everything you do. But anyway, seth, please continue a lot of the deception that takes place
uh is not
Intended as deception. It's bad information
that has been
Traditionalized that has been repeated but on specifically spirit and soul
Um etymologically you're going to run into uh some speed bumps to use a metaphor
that both of those words when traced etymologically
Speak to wind air
um breath essentially
um esprit is you know french which comes from
Uh, the latin spire, you know, which is to is wind breath
but in
Just for the sake of our western listeners and I don't mean, you know, like the old west. I mean those who are you know
have grown
Uh and and learned in in the western
Perspective of things
What that is based upon is their use
in in the oldest text that we have available to us that use those terms where we have a version that has
We have a version. We don't have a translation
But in in the version that we have where the word soul is used and the word spirit
Those are two completely separate words
Um, and we've
Remember to go into them real quick
Yes, okay. Uh, the english speakers typically are based on the greek and this is an interesting prep
Would call it prefix before a word versus a suffix. Yeah
Um, if you look at the any ancient text and this goes across hebrew and arabic as well
But we'll just use the greek as a metaphor and as an example more than a metaphor. It's a direct example
When you see the word pneuma or whenever you see the p n e a u prefix
Um, that means soul that means your breath that's where in english words we get the prefix for pneumatic or pneumonia
It's very much has to do with the movement of air
for example, one of the first things that you look for when uh, someone is presumed dead or dying or
Mortally wounded is you look to see if they're breathing and then they look for a pulse
So when someone is not breathing, they don't have a soul. It's very simple folks
Now, let's just leave that alone for a moment and go to spirit
Now if you look at any of the greek texts the word prefix psy or psyche or psyche means spirit, which means mind
That's why when you hear the psy prefix for psychic psychotic
psychiatrist
Or psychopath or whatever it has to do with the mind
Yes, and it's intangible. Yeah. Now what's interesting about that is yeah
They could put in cephalograms or whatever fancy technological devices and see pulses on the organ known as the brain
But very few people recognize this is a medical fact there are brain cells in the heart as well
So it's beyond the brain one example to explain
The psyche would be let's say you have
a hundred
A given number of dvds that are unlabeled, but they're all recorded on
And you dump them in the middle of the floor. They all look like shiny metallic plastic discs
But not until you put them in a computer or dvd player to start playing it
Do you see what is actually recorded on it? Now if you send that dvd to a material scientist
He'll give you a long report on how it's made of this. It looks like that
But he won't be able to see what's recorded on it
You need a specific player. So the spirit
The mind is played or animated through the carne the body
The corpus and the soul and the soul is part of the body
So, you know, what's the funniest thing to say? Well, they don't have a soul
You know, how many times have you heard that as a criticism about someone like are they dead cpr?
Yeah, if they're not dead, of course, they have a soul. What are you talking about?
now this is the part where
When you hear such ignorance and stupidity
It kind of puts like a tightness in the solar plexus region of the body, right?
And that's where I suggest
You either laugh or cry about it because people ain't going to change when i'm using that term loosely, you know
Like they ain't going to change, you know
I mean like let's not be too serious even about the language here because they don't want to look at anything now
Who's they? Well, whoever's listening is going to have to decide who they is whether it's them or the people around them
and
This is so simple and let's just say this
What do you think the chances are?
As you go higher to the entitled classes the quote-unquote super educated academics and university
What are the chances of them even being able to discern these two definitions?
Would you say like one out of a million?
one out of a thousand
I have i've not found
any yeah, yeah, i've not found any and
Um, that's not for not looking. Um, I don't go to campuses and things like that
I have kind of actually sort of an avarice to
Most temples actually
but
um, I do
I have but I have sought them out. Yeah
have
and I tend to uh frequent establishments where
uh people who
are super educated
Congregants and hangouts and i've gotten into a number of conversations on on specifically spirit and soul
And it's very difficult because
As I said, even etymologically in english, it's difficult. You have to take it back and go. Okay, we're using
the text that
These concepts are based upon
Uh as as spoken where they were first arbitrated. Let's say
Because that's what etymology is a word was first spoken and recorded and how it was used its meaning then that's why i'm so interested
Yeah and decided as to be used as a reference like a tape measure or a scale of weights or something correct
And I you know, this is a time where uh, the comprehension of sound and what we refer to as syllables
um was
Okay, we're back. I think let's see if we get seth back in again
Okay, uh, and we're we're on again and we're going to have seth join us in a moment
And as we were saying before the spirit and the soul are just two interesting concepts are very little simple words that
Can allow one to really see what's going on around them when regarding these spiritual matters
Let's say and if one could even call them that anymore
And uh, seth, are you with us?
I am
Okay, so so let's uh, yeah, we're back as we were saying the soul and the spirit
Uh, these are two very simple things that have yet not been overcome by in definition
and um
by the way, we didn't throw in the uh for the quote-unquote arabic and hebrew audience that would be
the terms, uh, uh nefesh and rook
Uh, yes. Yeah ruach or rook. Uh ruach in hebrew rook in arabic
Uh meaning the spirit and the nefesh or the nef being the soul
Uh, which you might see in some versions and they were living beings or living souls
So if this is really really simple, you know, the funniest thing i've noticed seth
How many times have you heard someone proclaim? I'm a very spiritual person. I'm very much into spirituality
You heard that before?
Yeah
I've heard that a few times. Yes. Yes. Yes, and who hasn't go ahead and ask some of these folks and let's be polite here
uh
Can you define soul and spirit?
And you will hear a million reasons why it's not what you're explaining even though they could go look it up for themselves
I've i've heard generally
What I hear when I ask that question
Immediately what follows is well to me
It means
This i'm going. Okay. All right. So if we just get a pick what things mean
Then us talking there is absolutely no purpose to because nothing can come of it because I can say I like the color red
And you can say
Well, I talked to this guy named seth
He
He to me he really really likes colors
he likes colors this guy really likes colors whereas
that's
kind of similar
To what I said, right, but I like the color red and there's there are reasons behind that it's not just the aesthetic
Although that is part of it. What about
Yeah, just as an example. What about from a constructive point of view? Isn't it interesting?
That people go and buy shoes and they you know, let's say, you know, take a size nine
Well, what just you know, just try a size 11 or try six for now, you know, it doesn't really matter
That's what I think you should have. No, no, no, you know, but he
It's got to be a size nine or you know, I have a 34 waist, you know
Why not just throw on a pair of 36s or 28s, you know, what's you know, isn't it?
I find the hypocrisy to be interesting
A lot of these people that don't want to look at what these things mean or mean what they say or say what they mean
They do like doors that close don't they they do like windows that close and they do like when they go to buy
Let's say tires for their bicycle or car that it makes sure that it's the right size for their shoe or shirt
But when it comes to things like discussing what the soul and the spirit is
It all goes out the window
figuratively
Isn't that phenomenal?
But they love
accuracy and precision
When it comes to shoe size waist size
car tire size bike tire size or windows and doors working
interesting
What's going on, man? You know here this is
Yeah, and if you find what we're saying uncommon
Thank you
Yeah, that's why that's
If there is a reason that's that's why we're here doing this right now. Well, let us proceed on this because
Um the concept I think we brought up in time
uh
You know, what's interesting though
Uh in time here
This is a what they call a date of observance for them on the pope's work schedule because if you look at the date
Today it's a different day than last year that they're calling that date
And if that sounded confusing good, that means you're common and normal
But but here's the point
The point is where are they getting this from now? It's interesting. I've gotten several emails from certain marketing companies
and they're saying
They're giving me the history of what they call easter and they're very careful
legalistically to start out that easter is a church or christian church tradition
And they go on for paragraphs explaining what it is resurrections and crucifixions and all this stuff
But you know never once do they mention any historical or biblical reference
Very carefully. They don't they're quite accurate to do so
Is that interesting but most people presume that it is biblical and historical
right
What's interesting is should we get into what is in the actual biblical record that anyone could look at if they so dare?
Yeah, I don't are there any uh what they call
um
For just just for the sake of this question, uh, regardless of the you know, the the papal calendar
Are there any?
holidays
that uh
specifically um
Those that call themselves christians, uh recognize that are
Actually based upon scripture none and what's interesting
If you go into divinity schools and all that you just laugh. Um
They do tell you that most of the curriculum is based upon the teachings of the apostle paul
And what's interesting if you read any of his writings, he says you must do the week of unleavened bread
How are you going to do that on the pope's calendar? Most christians don't even know what that means
So the hypocrisy is just amazing but what's interesting seth
This goes in against what people hear even on the alternative media
There are quite a few characters for a long time that are trying to discuss biblical matters and I assure you
It's all false. Sorry, and i'm not looking for a challenge or debate because it would be
really sad
but here's the point
the point is
That if one looks at the biblical text even in the version and just watches the movie
about anything
You will see the anomalies that could be easily sorted out with basic logic and rationale what's going on
you know, um
What's interesting here? I keep saying that the biblical record matches precisely with the historical record, but it doesn't match any religious tradition
You know, should we go down that road for a moment?
certainly
If you look in the biblical record, let's be cursory because you know, this is a this is a very wide subject
There's a figure called the christ and even if you've never read it and watched the movie
There's a character called pontius pilate that he's finally brought to based on the roman occupation superseding the judean authority
He washes his hands of the matter and says I see no guilt in this man
And then they continue with the whole story just falls apart after that becomes fiction
In other words, there's no historical or biblical record of the rest of the movie. But if you go to the biblical text
And find where pontius pilate actually does the hand washing scene and continue to read even in the poor versions
Pontius pilate proceeds to say I find no guilt in this man and I am returning him back to you meaning the judean authorities
to use your law
in another book it says
Of the same what they call the new testament. I am returning him back to you have a law
I know you have a law use your law. I am making this exception
Now, wait a second
The judeans didn't use roman law
The judeans used mosaic law
So at the time they were subject to roman rule
That's right
Which is why they brought him to pilot in the first place
Exactly, it would be no different than if the chinese took over the united states and did things their way
But the americans wanted to do their fourth of july. They
They have to let the chinese authorities give them permission to do the fourth of july
So what you would see is the chinese military lining the streets and you'd see a parade of americans blowing off their fireworks
Right very simple
But what's interesting?
Is this exception was made?
So but if you look at the mosaic law if you're accused of a high crime
You're to be nailed to a tree and stoned and I just gave off the whole thing. I didn't want to there's a stoning involved
So so I don't know where this crucifixion stuff came about and I don't know
And now wait a second you could say well the word crucifix is there if anyone wants to look up the term crucifix
It's a botanical term
It has to do with botany
but nonetheless
It's just not good because people are so disgusted about what religions are doing that you can't bring up what they're based on because it
Sounds like a disgusting subject and I don't blame them
But let's just jump away from the biblical text for a moment
Let's go to the historical secular records poncho's pilot did exist
There are records of his writings and what's interesting
Is what you will find mostly of poncho's pilot's writings is when he became the prefect governor of judea
He was writing to claudius tiberius caesar
profusely
Why because he was severely understaffed and undermanned being an occupying force
At one point he suggested that his men go out in disguise
Looking like the rest of the judaeans so the people don't figure out they're so small in number
And he was constantly pleading with claudius tiberius caesar for backups
And in those writings he mentioned he heard about about about a one man named yasha who spoke against authority
And he personally checked it out and said he this man didn't speak against the romans. He spoke against the judaean religious authorities
and one day
He was brought to to them under arrest
But he couldn't do anything about it because the mob took him away to be
stoned
This is in the secular record which is in 100
Agreement with the biblical text because if you get down to the new that's why the quote-unquote authorities tell you
Don't look at the old testament. No. No, no, don't look at that. No. No, it's got no, just look at the new testament
well
It's one huge cohesive document and sorry folks
That the historical record
Is in 100 agreement with the biblical record or any ancient text what you've been told about it
Is not in agreement with anything
Whether secular or non-secular
So folks, you're gonna have to do a little bit of homework and if this sounds uncommon, we're doing our job
But you know, I didn't want to get too much into the detail and if there's anybody in chat that wants to put in
a question regarding that or anywhere else
Uh, we could expand on this further
but
This this is not only for the biblical or christian tradition or the jewish tradition, which is also allegedly biblical
But this goes for the hindu the buddhist
And everything across the board
No, no one is understanding or even looking even lifting a finger now
What's interesting is they can say they are but when you look at what they're doing
They take it completely out of context
Which can be done any and if you if you're fixing on reading into what it says
well
You've got a problem there also
So, you know and this goes across the board now
This goes also with your sciences with your medical field and your legal societies with your academics
You know, so we didn't really quite get too deep seth and I don't think we really need to but we could in the future
by request I believe
and
Let's not be arrogant, but let's just say it this way a lot of the things that we're going to start saying
at the uncommon sense place here
Haven't been said in a very very long time
maybe millennia
And a lot of people are going to hear it and get very upset because it makes them unnerving. There's a man named william reich
Look him up
And he talked about something called emotional armoring
When people hear certain things that make them uncomfortable
They don't like it for it to get under that armor that they put up
and
This is not a place and this is not going to be the place for that kind of reaction
In other words, if you feel like we're getting under your skin and making you uncomfortable
that is not necessarily the intent the intent is to be uncommon because
What I see as being common hasn't done
anyone questioning
I think knowledge itself is is uncommon. Um
I hear a lot of well, I know that
It's not anything
I know that
And a lot of the knowledge that we claim for ourselves
Is just something that has been told to us
Through tradition
through
Books things like that. Well, I read in this book that and it says this and this and this
You can find observations on the world around us and on writings anywhere
But it takes it takes some discern some some discern some discernment
to identify
Observation from conjecture observation from opinion observation from theory
observation from supposition
you can take
uh
Recently, I read through a book called the golden bow by uh, frazier
I can never remember his first name, but his last name is frazier and it's actually been
Popularly, uh debunked on on many levels, but what has been debunked is not the the author's
observations
But his supposition and conjecture
On to what his observations mean and and the observations
that are presented in that book are a
very interesting to anyone who is interested in
Uh, the religions or spiritual practices of the world
um as observed by
A guy who lived I believe the book was published in the late 1800s
Um
I don't know all that much about the author but as I said, I read the book
I I think I read through it twice
So would you say there was an ad hominem critique versus addressing what was being said? It was how it was said perhaps
I haven't
read into a lot in depth into a lot of the critiques just the cursory glance at what I said, um, or
what was
Said of the critiques is that the book is referred to in a few places is something that has been widely debunked
But as I said, it's not the observations that are being debunked but the conclusions that this gentleman comes to
And there are some inaccuracies
even in
the information presented but the
There is so much there
that
Would suggest that a lot of the traditions and rituals specifically
Of varying groups that could be referred to
As pagan if you have a comprehension of the word that is something other than
What is colloquial?
Pagan is just
uneducated essentially
um, you know the tribes around the world and the similarities in in ritual and
The ideas and thoughts expressed through their ritual
is very
interesting
Dealing with the fact that you know, uh modern academic history
does not
allow for the
communication between
these
uh, these tribes these peoples these societies all over the globe
and
there is
Undeniably
Similarities there are undeniable similarities between a lot of a lot of these practices and they go back to a time that
uh seems to be
Before we had a lot of accurate records being made
Yeah, but the thing is I believe that the concept of accuracy
Is typically found in things that are memorialized
Uh, and when they're not accurate they almost
Eek it out
You know, they almost like if you read let's say a court case it's all presumptive
There's nothing being stated
But people read it as if it's being stated
as such
Right, uh, there are many ways to really discern a communication
right
Uh, and perhaps in the future we'll get into that for for certain individuals
But you know seth one thing I wanted to mention like you mentioned the pagan tribes and such and there's maybe more
Definition that be be given to what's behind those traditions
in the form of what was really going on in terms they're based on something real and maybe have become debased but
I brought up the concept that
Mankind is not an animal
from the social sense
That we're the only creatures that are susceptible to external input
You know and the example would be if you had a six-week puppy dog
Let's say raised by a family of gorillas to adulthood and you adopted that dog as an adult
You really couldn't tell that it was raised by a family of gorillas. It would pretty much act
It's not going to act like gorillas, right?
It's going to act like a dog and you didn't know but if you had a six-week-old baby raised by gorillas
And adopted this individual as an adult guess what they're going to act like almost identical
To a gorilla
So this is why you'll find
The passing down of information the
The almost the necessity of what's called schooling and training for humans where you do find some of that in the animal kingdom
But you never see schools other than a school of fish
Okay, you know, but you're not going to find
You know, in other words the animals sort of they come pre-downloaded with an operating system
You know, it's already pre-loaded
In their
Body, let's say within their spirit
but with mankind
It's the operating system has to be garnered as the individual develops
and it's really unique and that's why I have an aversion to when people make comparisons to
the man or woman or humankind
Being an animal form we share similar organs and similar features skin
Hair some people might have fur but you know the organs and things like that
But we're not animals in the least when it comes to the spirit aspect or the mind
And I think this is one of the important things that discerns
Why we search for information why we search for reasons to do things and then all of a sudden it seems like when you look
Around us everyone's given up
On inquiring on anything anymore and they just go along to get along which by default. I want to go back to
Gustav leban about something he wrote called the crowd and the crowd mentality and
The purpose of talking about uncommon sense is perhaps bringing up some of these concepts
Along the lines of what why how these groups are formed and how when these groups are formed
they lose the basis of the concept
Of whatever was the original purpose of the group being formed on
And you know sometimes I tell people if you want to destroy a good idea form an organization around it
and it seems to be the
The norm, let's say well what's common?
and perhaps
If there is a big pile of bulldung
It only takes a little shovel to move it aside for a moment. At least we can do it two hours a week
And perhaps get into it
I'm perhaps various subjects
Uh, and it also depends on what feedback we get if there's anything that wants to be that anyone would like to hear discussed
But essentially there's a very long list of things pick anything any topic any subject
It's really simple to see what it's based on
And and what it's being promoted as and if you look at what any subject that man gets involved in
Is supposed to be based on you'll find that it's pretty much debased
I mean
Going back to the example
They produce a new model car every year. I guess they haven't figured out how to build it right yet
So
What's going on and
What's going on is basically?
It's what people want to go on, you know, I want to
be apologetic
Or not necessarily be apologetic for a lot of the things you hear from the conspiratorial
quote-unquote activism
In alternative media about there is a global elite
That is bringing demise and doom on mankind
now
Uh, I just want to say one thing
Could it be that this global elite if there is such a thing are simply capitalizing on the greed and gluttony
And stubbornness and rebelliousness of the average
person on this planet
If you actually pull back far enough, you might see that's what they're doing
They're just capitalizing
It's the average
common
human acceptance
Of what they find they want to accept as being common
That is the source of the problem
If there is a problem
Because if you decide to set yourself apart from it, there's no problem
So the interesting thing here
is
How does one put into words what is really going on?
And who is to listen?
You know and it's not a philosophical question
Because there really is just a sequence of events and then this thing called hysteresis kicks in which is basically a fancy
Term of a dog chasing its tail and I think that's where humanity is right now
And we can expand on that with greater accuracy like maybe the concept of we're in the credits part of the movie
And things like that, you know
So
I think it can get really interesting here and as we proceed with further episodes, it's called them episodic in a sense
but
It's very rational
And in essence not to go back to be apologetic for the global elite
But could it be that they're simply accommodating the masses?
You know when you see a travel on a barren highway
The middle of a desert one of these big interstates and you see this big
Service station in the middle of the desert
Do you think those people are like really bad at business to open this big huge truck stop in the middle of the desert?
That's a real terrible business decision. Hey, man
I need like 10 million to open this truck stop in the middle of the desert. Are you crazy?
That's a terrible business decision
Oh, but you see there's this four-lane highway with a half a million cars that drive by every day and trucks and things
Oh, that's a great business decision
So the reason you open this establishment in the middle of nowhere is to accommodate the passersby aren't you
What happens if that highway closes?
That business goes away doesn't it
That it does
So maybe these global elite are opening
are investing
into accommodating
the passersby in this big desert
maybe a desert of knowledge or a desert of
concept of reality
Maybe the desert in this case is what people have preferred in their minds
Yeah, well, we're
right now
Just there's commentary on that. You know, we're living in a time you talked about obsolescence and planned obsolescence earlier
We're not living in a time
Where uh a light bulb
company
opens up
to make light bulbs, you know, they open up to make
Money or what they think is money at the very least
Yeah, it's great and glad there's yeah
Absolutely. Yeah. Um
We are you know, the our carnal, you know, this body is is certainly
animal
but these
You know what animates it how how we think?
Uh, i'd say the question that sets us apart from the rest of nature
Is why
You know what what other creature asks
Why not not the how you know, that's a lot of where the varying conflicts between
uh
What what are commonly referred to as religious organizations?
uh versus
Say, uh, you know scientific what they were what they call scientific or scientific. Yeah
Scienticulous you mean right exactly, but it's one group, you know describing how
and the other group describing why
and
In some points, you know, even with the the lack of information that is available
Um on either side of that they they can they can get things relatively correct
But when one tries to go into the other
uh, you you realize how very debased everything is
Um, oh, yeah when when those
Who would be considered religious are trying to describe the how?
Or when those who would refer to themselves as scientists?
Start referring to
Uh the why um, you're going to find very quickly how um
How very we've become incredibly departmentalized in our thinking and who thinks about what and who does what about what things like that
uh, just generally speaking and
so
when both are working on
uh information that
functions for a
uh system of beliefs be that a scientific faith or a
You know a religious faith
Either is going to be working on incomplete information
and
That's just because we're you know, it's not being sought. It's not well
It's it's being capitalized
But by the way this ignorance or it's not really see ignorance can be is not the problem
A lot of people seem to say that's the problem. I don't see that as being a problem. You can fix that very
Quickly it's the stubbornness and rebelliousness against looking at what these things should be based on
you know, um, and by the way, the the majority of
Communication whether it's mainstream or alternative is still taking advantage
of the disinformation and misinformation, you know, the the truck stop in the middle of the highway kind of concept and
You know what I mean by disinformation those are the ones putting out knowing that it's false and the
Misinformation are the ones that are believing it, right?
So you have a world of the distant the disinformants are very few but the misinformed are the many
um, and but there is a rebellious and stubbornness not to look at the
Let's say the source or the or any reference material on both sides
You know and uh, and again, uh, it's very uncommon. Uh to discuss what things should be based on
According to the way we communicate about them, right?
Uh, you know how we just mentioned earlier, uh,
Go ahead and try to have a discussion with not just common folk but people that are supposedly
Educated in the matter and defining the soul and the spirit and watch what happens
you're gonna you're gonna either laugh or cry about it and
Or any subject, you know, and but i've seen there's a tremendous amount of gluttony
where people
There's something called ethics and morality
Right, and it's very easy to say well we you know, it's all gone downhill, but can you give specifics on it?
You know, you hear a lot of people discussing about there's an evil force controlling mankind
But can you give specifics on it?
You know, there are bad things happening in the world
Can you give specifics on it? The answer to all this is no
And if you try to give specifics on it that anyone can readily access
You kind of either try to either find yourself being
Resisted or the communication is resisted not necessarily yourself because hopefully you don't want to find yourself being resisted
because typically when you sense that
They're fixing on doing some kind of harm to you physically. So you might want to get away from them physically also
But these are the things that we're going to be discussing here and showing how simple they are
And how anyone can access it and here's the thing
When you bring up the term study
It's become a bad word, but you know if you have a uh, let's say 900 some odd page book if you read one page a day
Or you'd be done in three years, right? Or if you had three pages a day, you'd be done in a year
And I mean that's not really difficult to study, especially if you look at
documents
that
Where the introduction and the conclusion are basically the same
You might want to start at the end i've seen NIH documents on viruses, which is national national institute of health
And they're about 900 page pdfs. So I read the introduction where they're fixing on doing a study on what a virus is
Then I go to the conclusion page
987 and the conclusion says well, we still don't know what a virus is
Why the hell would you bother reading everything in the middle?
Right
So you can really go through
stuff pretty quickly and pretty easily
but this is just from
private communications and what i've heard of people in the
Alternative media and mainstream media as well because I used to work in television for a short time
Is that you've got to really dumb it down for the people people just want to be entertained and i'm like what?
And
When I speak to people regarding what they hear that's information-based like oh, yeah, I I think it's crap, but it's entertaining anyway
I'm, like what?
So there's there's really no exchange
Are you kidding?
This is why I said earlier, you know, hopefully we're going to be exploring the highest and best use of the medium
So
Yeah
Absolutely
Um, I do want to mention and you know, we're broadcasting on american freedom radio and you're listening to
The greek and seth michael on uncommon sense and you can find
us on on the internet or at least
a website
The uncommon radio is like a card. It's where you're going to get access to perhaps the archives and it's just you know
People ask you, you know, if you're walking around in society years ago and say well, you know, I do carpentry, you know
So you have a card?
Uh, yeah, here's a card. It's just you know, these days people that's what they ask you. You have a website
Yeah, it's uncommon radio.com
But you will find this sonic experience at americanfreedomradio.com and by the way folks
Uh, we're not selling anything and I don't really intend to sell anything and I do intend and do intend though
To dedicate a bunch of time
Uh, and I believe seth does as well
uh
He's right here. He'll tell you perhaps he does
But american freedom radio is um might consider it a minor internet radio
Station that has it's got big aspirations and they're really good at what they do
And they could use some help. However, you want to pipe it over to them
Remember, it's it's not the cost of the radio. It's the piping it to you that costs right?
so
They're they're all exceptions, uh all exceptions all any kind of contribution donation anything you want to send their way, you know, um
That'll help them along. It's well deserved
uh
And consider that an endorsement
Um, they could really they could really use
uh
the vote for lack of a better term if people are familiar with what's going on and
I guess the united states of america, uh, you kind of vote with your money if there is such a thing. So
Uh, yeah, if you if you want to send something over because you know, it's just like the water, you know
People complain about the water bill. It's not the water man. It's the piping it to you
Right. Yeah
Structure, it's the infrastructure. They really use it
Yeah, so you can find us on american freedom radio if you'd like to get in contact with me directly
You can email me at dear red shoes dot or at gmail.com your red shoes at gmail.com. Thanks
I believe we've reached the end. Yes, we have and thank you for listening and look forward to another episode
Absolutely. Thank you. Shalom everybody. Be well. Bye everyone