This is the first installment of this sonic endeavor with myself, Seth Michael, and The Greek.
We are going to stick with the moniker Uncommon Radio,
being that we are hosted currently at uncommonradio.com. If you're listening to this,
you're probably already aware of that. We will integrate with every format that we can to make
it as easy as possible for the listeners to get to the program. So iTunes and things of that nature
will be forthcoming. This, like I said, is just kind of a test. We'll call this episode zero.
And we're back. We're popping up like toast. So we're going to continue perhaps discovering
levels of discernment and subject matters and things that could be conveyed sonically that
just simply are not anywhere else. And maybe that's why we are doing it.
And welcome, everyone. And let's see how it goes. What's on your mind, Seth?
Oh, what is one is always on my mind. Scripture, I suppose, is what's on my mind.
It's left to me. That's where we'll go. Yeah, refer to as the scriptures. By the way,
I finished watching a series called Wolf Hall. It was a novel written by a woman novelist around
what they call 2009 on the Pope's work schedule. It was about the court of King Henry VIII,
and the main character is Thomas Cromwell. Not so historically accurate, based on some critics
on it, but a very enjoyable show. Do I recommend it? Perhaps. It's called Wolf Hall.
Unfortunately, it's a streaming type deal. You're going to have to purchase
somehow. It was on a PBS masterpiece theater. The reason why I brought this up, because around
that time, there was no English translation. This is in the 1500s. Tyndall and some others
were doing a reformist movement. What's interesting about that show or that presentation
is there was the Roman Catholic precedent set of what's called Christendom throughout the land,
which England was a part of and King Henry tried to break away from.
They repeatedly referred to the scriptures and how interesting the scriptures were versus what
the Roman Catholic Church, which represented and really founded Christendom, was purveying
throughout England. I just wanted to bring that up because there's a resonance in the mind still
from watching that short series, which I don't really partake in a lot of media. This was
something that I came across. I found interesting because it was a well-acted, well-done presentation
around Thomas Cromwell. The scriptures were a main feature of this presentation.
This is just something that's fresh in the mind, and I'm bringing it up because
people have to remember that, as we've said before many times, or I have said, the Greek has said,
let's say, even today in your modern time, you do not have an accurate translation of what is
known as the scriptures. Sorry, folks, that is the truth. All of the versions that you have
are not translations. There are very loose reference versions, inaccurate, that convey
the general story of what is in the scriptures, and that's it. Period. So you have no real
understanding, no real information conveyance of what is in the scriptures. Now, a lot of it comes
across in the versions, but unfortunately, when you combine that with the social aspect of how people
read into works of information or things that they revisit later on in life, that they were initially
exposed to that subject matter as a child through various social institutions.
What I mean by that is, if you right now pick up what they call a Bible, and you read something
familiar, you get to, let's say, Exodus, or the Flood, or Adam and Eve, or the Apostles,
most people tend to read in and overlay what they saw on television by Disney, Cecil B. DeMille,
what they were told in church, or the circus, or their parents, and unfortunately, none of it is
accurate. Sorry. And the reason why I'm saying it that way is because it's still a massive endeavor
to delve into that thing we call the scriptures. And what I mean by massive endeavor is it has to
be retold or restated. So with that said, yeah. Go ahead. With preface, with background, with
it has to be established that we're working with versions and not with a translation.
That's easy to do for yourself. If you'd like to find an interlinear, there are a number of
them available on the internet for free reference. You can punch the one that always comes to mind
first is what's called Genesis, Bereshit. The first verse of Genesis, as it is the version
that is available to English speakers and those who read English like myself,
the first verse in the King James Version is 10 words. In the Hebrew, in the language that has
been memorialized in, it's seven words. It could be argued that it's eight words because there's a
in there, which is in English, we translate that as and, and that's relatively accurate.
But at the same time, there are two words in the first verse of Genesis that actually the same
word. So it's one word that appears twice in the first verse of that book that is not translated.
And not only is it not translated, that word occurs in the scriptures
between six and 7,000 times. It's been omitted.
So just to sum that up one more time, because there are 10 words in the first verse of Genesis
1.1 in English in the version, but there are seven in the language of preservation,
but only six are being translated. Right? Generally, correct. And that would be the
Aleph Tav. And it would be the first seven words would be the fourth one that the fourth word that
is not being translated. So what's interesting about languages and names and things, they are
sounds that we attach to things, right? What is a name? A name is a sound that you answer to.
Right? So what's interesting about, you know, even we describe these presentations as being
sonic presentations, meaning it's of the sound nature of our perception, not visual yet, because
it's, you know, it's audio strictly. So just for the audience, just to have an effect on the mind,
just to, and it's good to start at the beginning, which we will find out later on that Genesis is
not the beginning, I guess, but that's for another discussion. In Genesis, basically 1.1,
it says, in the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth. But in Hebrew,
it would be something like, Bereshith bara Elohim et ha-shem yim v'het ha-aretz. Right?
Now, what's interesting is Bereshith, beginning, bara, we would say created or presented Elohim,
the gods, et, which is the Aleph-Tav, the first and the last, or would be the letters of the
Hebrew alphabet, or any alphabet, which would be the A and the Z, or the Alpha and the Omega.
And there's someone who identifies themselves as being the first and last, and the Alpha and the
Omega. Right? And then, the heavens, and, which can be namely the waters, and et ha-aretz, which
is the earth. So there you go. And you don't get that in the King James or any version.
So guess what, folks? You open what's called a Bible, you're on the first verse, the first,
of the first book, of the first chapter, of the first verse, of the first book, and you're already
spit out on the other end with an omission. How do you think you're going to fare on verse two,
or verse three of the first book? An omission and obvious mistranslation in the first verse.
Right. Now, a lot of, by the way, the side note, or footnote here, some scholars say,
the olive top is just a punctuation for them to show you something is important, or it's a
conjunction of some kind. I've seen it presented as, or I've seen it translated as the word the,
or the, which is also inaccurate. Right. Because it's defined.
That's right, ha. Yeah, and ha would be for plural or singular.
So, so we're going into this kind of like head fast, and I mean, head first, quickly,
only because there's a something here that needs to be set in the mind. You know, everything that
we do or hear has an effect on the mind, and that's how we tend to rationalize things. And
when I, when I mentioned earlier reading into subject matter that is brought up, that is
biblical, as be, and you know, we're actually overlaying and reading into things, because when
we perceive information, this is just a commentary on how the human mind works. There's a, there's a
maturity level that people reach, known as adulthood, and they feel that they can operate
freely in the world and do what they wish. And when they approach things, they are constantly
comparing what they're doing throughout their day with previous experiences. And that's how
people read, and that's how people interact. Right? So, you know, if you, let's say, are walking
on the street and you see a dog, you, you actually see the dog, but you're not really
seeing the dog. You, you see enough of the dog to know it's a dog, and you,
immediately the mind compares it to all the other dogs you've seen, and it's close enough,
and that's just a dog. But if someone were to ask you what that dog really looked like,
you would give it, oh, it's a dog, you know, but you're really not looking at it. You're just,
I mean, you just kind of glanced at it, it's enough, and you've compared it to everything
else that you've seen about a dog, it's good enough. That's what I mean about reading into it.
So when people are also having conversations, I'll notice, or reading something, if you ask
them to describe what they just read, well, if the subject matter is familiar,
they're not really paying attention because they're comparing it to previous things that
have been downloaded. That's where, in, I guess, in media school years ago, they used to talk about,
you know, man bites dog, right, and people were like, oh, okay, yeah, because it sounds like
dog bites man. That's pretty common, but man bites dog is very uncommon, right? That's the,
the story that you're always looking for, something that people see as familiar but
is very strange at the same time if you're paying attention. So we're, we're jumping into
scripture and basically we're only a few minutes into this sonic presentation and we laid out
pretty much a gem, I would say, about how you're not even getting anything true in the first verse
of the first chapter of the first book, so what do you think you're going to get in the rest of it?
So, very much similarly, the same attitude carries through.
So, the, I found it easier to discuss things that are written in the text with those who have very
little to no experience with study. Preferably, yes, preferably atheists or secular people.
That might be interested in the subject matter. I've jumped into conversations at coffee shops,
actually, where I heard, you know, something of interest to myself being discussed.
I'm like, but that's, that's not what it said. And the ones I've, I've, many times, actually,
and it's, it's much easier to talk to people that don't have
misinformed, preconceived notions to battle with when, when speaking about it.
Let's just jump into another concept, because we do bring up time very often. It's almost the last
week of the sixth month, and it's, you want to sound off the date, roughly, what it is on the
Pope's work schedule? It's August something? The 10th? Yeah, something like that.
I think. What they call 2016, I think. Right, the 25th of the sixth month.
Yeah, roughly, last week of the sixth month, going into the seventh month. So why is time
important? Because you have to realize that when we start discussing, let's say, Scripture,
one of the things we'll bring up is that the word forever is not in there, right? The word being
translated as forever is the word olam and the word eon, which means the age.
Yeah, unto the ages.
Uh-huh. And an age is typically a thousand or two thousand years, pairs of thousands.
Right? So there is no forever. And the reason I bring that up is because
all information is only pertinent when it's registered as pertinent in the time that it's
registered as pertinent. What does that mean? Well, if you're reading about, you know,
horse-drawn carriages, you will find information that is difficult to understand if you're living
in an age of what they call the automobile or the car, right? Because you've spent your entire life,
uh, most likely being driven around, as they say colloquially, in a rubber-tired,
reciprocating engine, gas-guzzling, gas-eating machine. You're not familiar with the basic common
things of what a horse-drawn carriage is, you know. Yeah, you might know that it's, yeah,
it's made of wood, and it's got a metal strap around the wooden wheel so it doesn't break,
which is called a tire. And there's an animal in the front drawing it, and that's simple enough.
But if you were to study, let's say, the Casanova wagons and things like that, and pick up some
reference material on it, the majority of the information conveyed will be unfamiliar to you,
even though they are simple terms and simple concepts. And this is very much what Scripture
is like, because people don't know how to place the information within the time period that they're
living in. So that's why time is very important. So what is important about time in Scripture is
knowing where you are in that entire story. And that cannot be garnered until you've basically
downloaded the entire thing, or been familiar with the entire thing, and then pieced it all
together rationally, just like the, I guess, the horse-drawn carriage. Because you can still
access a horse-drawn carriage somewhere. So there's something about it that requires,
let's say, an understanding of time, would you say, Seth? And how to keep time and things like that.
Absolutely. Especially if you're talking about something that is referencing times,
when to do things, or when things will happen, and you're trying to make proper observations
about such things. It's impossible with the Pope's work schedule, as they call it.
But even with the Pope's work schedule and mechanical clocks, time has to be measured
accurately, to some degree. Let's use the mechanical clock. And I just want to throw something in.
Right now there is a particular religion and culture on the planet that is allegedly adhering
to this type of information. And many people are under the misunderstanding that the day ends at
sundown, because a certain group says so. A religious group, let's say. And if you study
scripture with an open perception, where you see it objectively, you will see that the day starts
at noon. Because, very simply, you cannot make a measurement at sundown. Sundown is actually the
last hour. The noon time, using, let's say, what you might call a sundial, or just a stick in the
ground, can be measured very precisely. Also, there is a concept that the new moon is the dark
moon in scripture, and that is another mistake, because you cannot make a measurement with a dark
moon. It just sits around in the West, and it's dark. Where the full moon rises like the sun,
and it has its own noon time. In other words, when the full moon is at the apex of the sky,
at the zenith, it will cast a very sharp shadow, which you can compare it
to the solar shadow taken that day. And that's how you determine what's called the equinox.
It has nothing to do with equal day and equal night. It has to do with a measurement at night.
That's why it's equinox. Equi meaning measure, nox meaning night. If it was equal parts day and
night, it would be equimdeum nox. So, these are things I just want to, we're kind of like
randomly throwing in concepts here. And just to throw in a few other things here, this is kind of
like running into someone and pushing them around, you know, and I don't mind doing that sometimes,
but because kind of like a little bit, the subject matter is not really something we're
going to delve into other than the overall mindset. Like we said earlier, there is no
forever in the scripture. It's the ages, which are chunks of limited times. You will not find
the word. The other one that's important to consider is you will not find the word church.
The reason I'm saying that is because from a secular perspective, secular historians consider
this to be the Christian era. And when the first thing you bring up in the mind, or most people do
when you bring up Christendom is the church, you will not find anything that resembles that
in scripture at all. Zero. What they call church today is a revival of the ancient circus or the
architecture resembles the ancient sex temples. None of it is biblical at all. Zero. Period.
At all. You will not find hell as Dante's Inferno, where bad people go when they die.
And there's devils with pitchforks and things like that. There is no such thing in scripture.
Period. You will not find anyone being animated in a heavenly realm after they die,
where you die and you find yourself with a light and a cloud and plucking a harp and doing all that.
That is a lie. You will not find any of that. Actually, you won't find any of those in any
ancient texts. Those are inventions of a particular character or group of characters
inspired by a magician in the first century. So this is the truth of these matters when you
discuss the time, because you're in a time right now, people, where when this topic is brought up,
you think of heaven and hell as plucking a harp in the pearly gates or being in a fiery,
infernal place with demons or forever or church. And all of these things are completely
irrelevant and not in scripture at all. Period.
Give me a quick example. The word congregation or ecclesia, as it is in scripture, just means
a group of people. And that is being translated as church and what's called the New Testament.
And if you actually do some research, there's an unruly mob protesting or ready to do some harm.
And they're referred to as an ecclesia of people. I think it's in the Book of Acts. I think when
Shaul was there, he roused up a crowd and he was arrested for rousing up the crowd.
And that crowd is referred to as an ecclesia. So it just means a crowd or a group or people
grouped together. So when you hear us say things like there's no such thing as a church in
scripture or heaven or hell or forever, we're going to try to throw in a very fast reference
on how and why we're saying it as well, which I think is important.
Absolutely. Absolutely. We're doing this on our own, independently from any other
media outlet or anything like that. Currently, it's going to be available just here.
And I am fond of that idea. After having experience with sonic projects in other venues,
it's a lot more comfortable to sit in our own venue and speak.
Yeah, definitely. There are no time limitations. We can broadcast very short episodes
or very long ones. And we can speak freely without
the implied audience that is common to other venues.
Yeah, media was, I think it was Edward R. Murrow, someone that when the advent of television,
meaning it was popular and available to most people, he said it should be taken seriously
because it's almost a cross between a national park and a library or university. And a lot of
the media that people partake in, known as internet radio, can be viewed very similarly. And we've
tried that, and we're very grateful that we were given the opportunity. But if you don't have to
be associated with it, why not not be associated with it is the point. And in essence, being able
to do this, being very grateful that the website can host it at the moment, and we'll see other
ways to get information out. I think the four or five listeners that we kind of like semi-jokingly
talk about will be able to access it. So, with that said, in terms of media, folks,
I've heard that there's some frustration regarding media. I hear that constantly, but people still
use it. And I think we've mentioned in one of the sonic presentations that this is all a beta
test, what you've been watching throughout the human course of events with television, radio,
and the internet. Right now, it's just a beta test. That's why it's all junk. It's just like I
think we did an audio test here, get on the mic, testing, testing, one, two, three. That's all you've
been experiencing all your life. There's events that are going to be occurring in the future
where there's going to be an imparting of information. There's going to be the witnessing
of events in real time with audio and video throughout the world. This is what this entire
evolution, let's say, or an opening or unraveling from radio to television to internet
is. So, if you're frustrated about all the junk out there, yes, and it's all junk, because if it
wasn't, we would probably be saying, go listen to here or go over there. We wouldn't be doing this,
you know, at least in private. So, what the attempt here is to give maybe a little bit of
credence to maybe a cross between a national park and a university. And by the way, folks,
I want to throw this in as another commentary, because, you know, I kind of rambled, but I
tried to tie things together. You university folks, your academics, whatever, look up the
word academic in an etymological dictionary. To paraphrase, it means theoretical and practical
never leading to a conclusion. And if there is any benefit in the current system of academia,
and you live in a benevolent society, and you have such free media available,
why can't you turn on the television or the internet and have these wonderful universities
that want to help mankind do all of their teaching online? Because first of all, this is the truth,
folks. It's not worth learning from them. They have nothing to teach you. When I say nothing,
there's a, yeah, there's something there, because even a counterfeit note has to look like the real
thing, you know. Sorry. And you've been pranked. You've been pranked by your parents to go to these
schools. And then, where if you study intellectual minds of the 19th century, they never received
their graduate degrees by 15 or 16 years old. They only went through several years of schooling.
That's all you need. The kindergarten through 12th grade in university is a prank.
It destroys your formative years. It steals all of your formative years.
Now, this might sound like heresy. And by the way, the word heresy means what one prefers or one
likes. And this goes beyond that. This is trying to be objective. So when you hear us discussing
certain subject matter, this is the kind of stuff that makes academics crawl out of their skin.
Or go into convulsions and fall on the ground and vomit.
Right? Because it is possible to take very large pieces or chunks of subject matter and reduce it
down to a few sentences where the man or the woman listening, or even the child, can digest what's
been said and understand it. And that is one of the things we like to do. And it's based on
discernment and clear, concise communication. Which is a big contrast to academia. Which I think
is just what anyone can think, actually. If you were to objectify it, it's a prank on humanity
at this point. And it actually has always been these public institutions. And I'm not speaking
against them that they shouldn't exist or anything like that. Just like ice cream shops shouldn't
exist or shoe stores or whatever. But if you're trying to associate knowledge and learning with
these institutions that are in place, you are really, you don't get it. Sorry. And you never,
probably never will. So I wanted to bring that up because conveying and imparting information
can be done very quickly, concisely, and effectively. And that might be one of the
things that we might start, you know, endeavoring on these sonic experiences with.
I think that we do. I think that a lot of what is spoken about requires, you know, explanation.
And the more that we get into it, and the more that things are explained, we'll be able to speak about
them without the explanation and be able to refer back to where we have explained it, where it has
been explained. But I think that explanation is important, especially to anyone who, you know,
makes it a habit to listen, to seek out such conversation as we have.
And I require it myself for my own, you know, knowledge.
You know, instruction is something to be sought. And that's certainly a large part of why I do
this and why I have enjoyed the conversations that you and I have had over the years, public and
private. And with this endeavor, I think that we have the ability to do it in a more comfortable
setting. There have been, you know, we've had some objectively or relatively good broadcasts
in the past, and I don't mean to speak derogatorily of any of the venues that, you know, we've spoken
because, well, they allowed us to speak, and that in and of itself is relatively rare.
But there's no pressure with this, and that's wonderful.
Yeah, in other words, you can have a beautiful venue and they serve food that is synthetic or,
you know, bad ingredients in it, right, let's say, but the venue is fine. We'd like to have a good
venue, let's say, with good ingredients, right? You know, when we serve cheese, it's made with
milk, not cheese made of whatever, right? Or if it's salt, it's real salt, not, you know, something
from the aluminum industry. So, yeah, but here's the thing also, the partial rant and commentary
regarding internet radio or other venues or academia or any of these things that people are
going to, where the hosts, the teachers, the professors, those professing, you know, those
behind a microphone or a lecture hall or writing a book, they are just part of the human collective
that have decided to do such a thing. And they come from the same, let's say, maladies and flawed
aspects of the society that we're sort of being critical about. Now, if you told me that a wormhole
opened up and a bunch of people came from another dimension, let's say, which is only one dimension
or another universe or planet to be your internet radio hosts or your professors or whatever, yeah,
you might want to give a listen because they haven't been subjected and pranked by the insanity
going on on this planet by the human race for thousands of years. You see, they haven't been
subject to that. So it might be worth listening to. But all of these professors and whatever,
all these people pontificating, they have not realized that the majority of what they're saying
is a product of prankdom. None of, I mean, I shouldn't say none of it, but very little of it
is accurate. Very little of it is based on anything. It's just the typical social chatter
that you hear, whether it's academia, all the way through, I mean, any form of media.
So this is the point, you know, can information be imparted in an objective,
clear, concise matter regarding any subject to a surface-dwelling Earth inhabitant? And I believe
the answer is yes. And that might be the crux of this whole thing. Absolutely. Absolutely.
I would say that it can be, but how, whether the seeds fall on fertile ground
is, I don't know. I guess there's plenty of fertilizer out there. Yeah, there is. Flowers
need a lot of bullshit to grow, but I think sonic experiences can be free of it to a certain extent,
because you're not really growing flowers. But the thing is,
the point of conveying information is also that it has to fit the time period,
so it's more relevant. Because I think we've mentioned how the nature of existence is very
simple, folks. It's basically where spirit's animated through material. You know, the spirit,
the soul, the body. The spirit is the mind, the soul is the breath, and the body is the physical
matter. And the three working together to animate the show, known as everything that we consider a
reality, is the reality of it. And that's all it is. It's very simple. It's not easy, but it's simple
to explain what's going on. And to give information that is pertinent to a mind animated through
material is not being done effectively or efficiently on this planet at the moment. It's
astounding to observe. So that, again, would probably be the way we would like to discuss
things objectively, as if you're just visiting a place, clearly and concisely. And just to go back
to what we started with, the interest in scripture, just to give a thought, the reason
we brought up the concept of maybe discussing scripture more, and please, you have to bear
in mind that this has nothing to do with any religious affiliation at all. And even you folks
out there that think you're non-denominational, that's just like going to a supermarket and instead
of buying a particular brand, it's the generic white box. That's not any better. It's still
macaroni and cheese with whatever in it. We're not discussing any religious affiliation or anything
in that aspect, which I think I brought up. There's no forever, no church, no heaven and hell
as people discuss it in certain religious circles and certain timekeeping things. It's just maybe a
little bit of a preface. Absolutely. I would recommend that for anyone that is interested in
studying such things or looking at things objectively, use the, you know, the internet
only has what the internet has, but there are tools available there, and you can find free
interlinear software, things like that, that make it, I wouldn't say make it any easier, but make it
more fruitful studying such things. I'd like to recommend coelesthes, ecclesiastes, as it's
called in the English versions, to anyone who is considering such things. It's not going to
make you friends. It will be a point of contention if it's something that you are
looking at objectively between you and anyone that you speak about it with.
Or anything in scripture. Yeah, absolutely. But there are tools available.
How about this? How about, not a promise, but a consideration that if people adhere to what we're
presenting and piece it all together, they'll have a pretty good idea of the rhythm of
what is going on. What I mean by that is, yes, koaleph is important, proverbs are important,
the book of Jeremiah is important, because those things are universal. Those are pretty much for
everyone. Most of the other things in scripture are directed to certain groups, right? Just like
you would go to someone's mailbox and they're being addressed specifically. But, you know,
I just gave a handful of things there. Now, that's a lot of information right there in a very short
sentence. Consider that, anyone listening. Now, the rhythm of it is, let's give an example,
like the band Fleetwood Mac. The first time you hear a Fleetwood Mac song, you're like, oh,
okay, I see what they sound like, how they play music. And then you hear another song from them,
let's say on an album, and okay, all right, I can see it's the same band, but it's a different song.
And if you're familiar with, let's say, 10 Fleetwood Mac songs, if you were to go about in
life and another song comes on, you'll say, oh, that sounds like Fleetwood Mac, even though you've
never heard it before. And on the same note, if someone plays a song for you and tells you that
this is Fleetwood Mac, and it's not, you'll be like, this doesn't sound like Fleetwood Mac at all.
Yeah, exactly. So what we will do, besides reading the books of wisdom and things like that,
and maybe the book of Jeremiah, which is addressed to everyone, like Seth likes bringing up Ecclesiastes,
and rightly so, let's say we'll discuss certain very specific topics, like we mentioned, let's
say, the flood, a very short thing about very specific interlinear kind of etymological aspect
of a certain part of, let's say, the flood in Genesis, or like we just started out by doing the
first verse of the first book of the first chapter, we just gave an illustration of what's going on
there, we could pick and choose various aspects of scripture and go into it in great depth very
quickly, in short, and concise and objectify it all over. And you will notice that it's obviously
there, it's all tied together, it's the same band, it's playing, it's the same, it's the same band,
but different songs. And let's say we do a dozen examples of like, example, something in the flood,
something in, let's say, the Garden of Eden, something about when the Israelites left Egypt,
or something from what they call the New Testament, and we'll explain it, and people will figure out,
hey, there seem to be, these things have something in common, even though they seem that, you know,
they're all set, you know, separate instances and separate events, these guys are showing us what
all these things have in common, and there's an understanding here, how it's all tied together,
and the mistakes they're pointing out seem to have a frequency and a rhythm in an app.
There's a mindset to what makes the versions that you're given so bad, if we reveal that mindset,
and then we reveal the mindset that when you do research what is really being said in the
language of preservation, you'll have a good contrast. And just giving maybe a half a dozen
examples, like we just started out with the first verse of Genesis, the listener then will be able
to have almost a pretty good understanding of what is going on on their own, like listening
to Fleetwood Mac, for example. So this is just an example. So just like we gave the example right
out of the gate, we will perhaps go into many other explanations like that, and this is not
a lot of people resist this because it goes contrary to what they believe, but if belief
is based on nothing, well there you go. If you say you believe in something and someone questions it
in terms of why do you believe that, and it's based on nothing, well then you just need to
kind of like walk away, because guess what, nothing is based on nothing.
So yeah, if you're listening, it's like listening to music in a different tuning,
that is unfamiliar, if it doesn't, if it sounds, it's going to sound discordant to many.
Now why scripture? The big question here is very simple, folks, and we'll lay it out really quickly
and really simple. If someone has a lawful mind, meaning that when you have a communication
and you have a lawful mind, you see if that communication sets a precedent, if it's an
important communication, or is it trivial, or is it, you know, how much attention does that,
what you just heard or read, require? Like for example, if someone says, excuse me, I have to
go to the bathroom, well that's a communication, but you know, it's like okay, fine, it's common,
no big deal, but thanks for letting me know. But if someone, if you read a communication that says,
I created the heavens and the earth, and I am the supreme being, oh, that's so trivial,
I don't really believe in that, I don't care. Well, you see, that's the typical mindset. But
if someone has a lawful mind, and they hear that, they're like, wait a second,
that is a really, really tall claim, right? And it sounds extremely important. And I mean,
and has it been rebutted? Is it true? Right? Or whatever, right? So that's why we go to scripture,
because you will find things that are claimed in there that are really tall claims. I mean,
we're talking big claims. And the majority of the surface dwelling earth inhabitants
are apathetic to it, because they don't have a lawful mind. So that's why, that is why I would
like to say from the Greeks perspective, is why I have an interest in it. You know, if someone says,
hey, I got to go to the bathroom, or else, you know, I've got to go, you know, rearrange the
sock drawer, that is a communication, just like I created the heavens and the earth, for example,
is a communication, but they have different veracities. You know, one needs to be considered
to see if it's true. And if it is true, well, that is really important information.
And it's been hijacked, just like all information, right now, has been somehow
conveyed through some corrupted kind of presentation, or individuals that are loose
and apathetic and don't really care. And I say not all, but you know, typically. And here,
the reason why I'm saying that to be ranty or critical, is because I like the truth. I like
information. I like learning. This is a personal thing, right? And I like to see and hear that
other people are doing, you know, just like if someone likes, let's say, basketball, they like
to associate with other people who have a fondness for it, right? Or playing instruments, or cooking,
or whatever. So I like learning. I like, you know, learning things, and especially if they're big
things that are important. And I have certain people that I communicate with. And if I had
found a source that was able to convey important information clearly, concisely, and objectively,
wouldn't be doing these sonic presentations at all. I would just sit back and people that I
communicated with, I would, you know, send them information, say, look at this, look at that,
look at this guy here, or whatever, right? And you would not know about the Greek at all.
But the reason why I come out and speak, is because no one is saying anything. You know,
I mean, when I say no one is saying anything, it's just, yeah, it sounds kind of arrogant or
whatever. But on the other hand, it's like, what the hell is going on? Are you people lost your
minds? Are you crazy? Oh, they're saying, they're saying plenty. But generally, what they're saying
is just a complaint about the symptoms. Yeah. Is anyone paying attention? Yeah. So, you know,
sitting back, there's a, there's a, if I was not speaking, I would feel that there's a level of
negligence incorporated in my existence. So I have to come out and say, I mean, if you want,
if you folks want to know what I'm talking about, just go to the internet radio and turn on
anything. Right? Or go to YouTube. Start watching stuff. It's like, huh? What the hell is wrong with
you people? So anyway, you may not, you can't really say they're wrong. Right? But you can't
say they're right. I would say that my interest and the reason that I, as I said, right when,
right when we started this, that if it's up to me, that we'll, we'll discuss scripture.
I, I guess that I grew up in an environment where it was spoken of quite a bit. And so I was
familiar with it from a relatively young age and put together pretty early on that what is written
and what is said in these congregations is very rarely congruent. Not, not even to touch upon
what is actually done, but just, just what is said, what is taught is not, it's not there.
And there, you'll get various explanations from any of these groups as to the why, the
apology. You'll get an apology. They'll speak in defense of it. But so I've always, it's, I guess
I've just kind of been drawn to it for that reason. I'm going, well, there's, there's good
information here. It's obvious there are directions, lots, lots and lots of directions.
It's almost like a handbook for living on the surface of this planet. And, but it's, it's
ignored and distorted. And so I see this, this object, if you look at, you know, the scriptures
as a whole, as, as an object, as a singular book, although it's many.
49.
Yeah. 49 books, right. That are being discussed, but not being directly addressed.
The only time that I could tolerate being in these places is when we were sitting in a circle and
just reading passages and discussing them, because it's very hard to skirt things
when you have the ability, but I can't, I can't, I, it's been many, many years since I've
subjected myself to, to that particular form of punishment. But
I've, I've, there's value in it. It's, it's valuable. It's something that is
rare. You know, there are many, many textbooks and I'm sure we'll get into, you know, who edits
textbooks these days, but there's lots of information available. But when you start
going and looking for what this information is based upon, it's just, it's not present.
Theory, lots, lots and lots of theory going from scripture to what people refer to as
science these days. Science is just a word that means knowledge. It kind of is a pet peeve,
I suppose, when I hear people talking about science, because that's, that's simply what
it is, you know, knowledge. Being aware of it, being aware of something else.
It's been turned into an, you know, a faith instead of being natural philosophers. Now we have
the priests in the white coat that call themselves scientists or that other people
refer to as scientists, or they were, it's just, it's absurd. The, the way that information is
communicated, good or bad currently is, is just absurd. And there is so much that is left out.
And when, instead of things being discussed, people start insulting people that do not agree
with their beliefs, be them quote unquote scientific, or even if the beliefs are founded
on nothing. If you peel away the onion, there's nothing there. And it just, the whole process
just brings tears, right? Right. One of those people that's just looked around them and like,
this, the way that we exist, we, I'm using very, very lightly, I guess, but referring to,
you know, service dwellers and what I've had the occasion and the opportunity to observe,
there's three O words in a row, is that it's, it's just, it's, it's absurd. And yet, the absurdity
is only referred to in art, it seems, art seems to be where the absurdity at least is reflected
in a more accurate manner. But yeah, punk rock and hip hop. Yeah, no, I'm just joking. Yeah.
I'm surprised, man. There's lots of both now. Once upon a time, you could pigeonhole it. But
these days, music is one of those things. I'm a musician, for those that are unaware. So it's
something that is, it's certainly a passion. It's something that I've done since I was very young.
And it's all I've ever really wanted to do, as far as work goes. But it's, it can be used,
you know, it's a medium like any other, it can be used properly or improperly, you can impart
good information, or bad information.
Sonically, yeah, using an instrument, and the voice can be an instrument as well, if you listen
to opera. I want to go back to the concept of scripture of perhaps calling it a manual. I
Now, whenever you have a benevolent creator of anything, they fit whatever they've created to
the end user with a manual, you ever notice, buying something, even a very rudimentary
appliance, like a toaster or hairdryer, you open the package and in what falls out a manual.
And you ever notice on these manuals, especially electrical devices,
that the first couple of pages are filled with what not to do.
Danger could cause shock, potential injury and death, do not submerge in water,
do not write you ever noticed that? Yeah. Yeah, the first few pages are the dotes.
Right? Isn't that interesting how it? Yeah, think about that for a moment, folks.
And it seems like right now humanity is, they've got a product, let's say a blow dryer,
and they've got the manual. They're aware of it, but they don't want to look at it.
So what they do is they take the blow dryer, plug it in and dunk it in water.
Right? It's discordant to current society. It's, it doesn't, oh, I don't like it. I don't like
that. It's like, this is how it's done. I'm not going to do it like this. It's like, well, okay.
So it's interesting, what we'll get into is what most of humanity is incorporated in,
incorporating their behavior in and their actions and deeds and works are the don'ts
in the, in what's called the scripture. Like, for example, I've stated before, there's not
one religion on the planet that knows or does anything that's in the text that they
allegedly subscribe to. That's a tall statement. But if, if you are, have a faith in one of the
main religions, you might find that to be offensive. That's too bad, because you're
not pursuing the truth of the matter. And if essentially, if you, on a cursory level,
start looking at, let's say, whatever religion you are in the book that is supposedly
based on, you'll say that what I just said is not true and you don't see it,
because you're reading into it. If you actually sit down and study it, you'll find that you might
want to light your hair on fire and run down the street screaming how you've wasted your entire
life following these ridiculous institutions. But anyway, the other thing about, about,
is that you'll find that what they are actually partaking in, no matter what religion it is,
is the don'ts in what the book that they allegedly subscribe to are. So when I say nothing,
that they don't do anything, that, that, that's a general statement. But to get more specific,
most religions are doing things that are in the texts that they allegedly subscribe to,
and the things that they're doing are the things that are considered abominable or forbidden.
I would say most, most. I would say there are, and albeit a lot of them are just a disguise for
something else, but there are, you know, charitable organizations out there. There are people out
there feeding people that don't, or don't have the ability to feed themselves, clothing themselves,
you know. There's still good being done, but what is, what is discussed and what is taught, it's,
honestly, what is discussed and what is taught, it's kind of amazing that there are still good
things being done. Well, the good things that are being done are out of a guilt. Just like,
for example, I bring up the example, whether it's good or not, just something that is in your face.
After 9-11, you notice how most government officials started wearing these little American
flag lapel pins to show how patriotic they were when they were actually in on what was going on
prior to it? It's to kind of like cover their guilt. And it's not really, I shouldn't say it
that way, because the government, I've never, all governments and all throughout time, current,
past, present, any country in the world is the government you deserve, period. There's nothing
wrong with it, even though they might just be doing wrong in certain cases. They are there to
fit what the society is about. That's all it is. So, yeah, it's like a mirror. You don't put
a pink elephant in the mirror and expect to see a green giraffe. You put a pink elephant in the
mirror, you're going to see a pink elephant in the mirror. If you don't like the people that are
ruling you, you need to just look at your neighbors and your family and whatever, and you will find
that they are identical in nature. So, yeah, that's why if you look at the things about wisdom
is don't try to change any of this because you're not. Just set yourself apart from it. It's like if
you had a well-paying job working in the sewer or with high tension power lines, do you go in there
with a tank top and flip flops and touch everything? Or you go in with protection? Yeah, exactly.
So, yeah, you don't want to touch, yeah, because you will be zapped or you will be dirty and stinky
and unhealthy. So, that's the other good advice is avoid people that talk about making humanity
better and the world a better place. Those people are clueless. They have no clue. They are just,
yeah, it's just not good. It sounds good, makes you feel good,
but, and here's just another note, folks. This is not about pessimism or things being dark or
evil or whatever because you are at the precipice right now of, from an age, from the ages point of
view, you know, the 30 seconds or 10 seconds to midnight where things are going to end.
The next stage of humanity is going to be so wonderful and so incredible compared to
all of the things that have been recorded about humanity, good or bad, that even the worst things
that you've ever imagined done by humans will be nothing, will be considered trivial when you
compare it to the benefits and the wonderment and the existence that you're going to have in the
future as humanity. So, the most atrocious, horrendous things that have been done by people
will be just like peanut shells falling on the floor compared to the wonderful things that you
will be open to. You will fully understand all the misery, the evil, the mayhem, the lying,
the deceit, the corruption and you will see that it has its place and why it had to be done the
way it was done and in the future, but not now. And we will discuss what's coming in the future
because there's only a couple of years left where you can actually discuss it and then
those who know what's coming will not be speaking because it's going to be kind of dangerous to do
so. So, the reason why is because the closer you get to a point where things are going to go south,
let's say, meaning not well, the window dressing and what you're going to be shown in society and
in your personal lives is going to be the opposite. Things are going to appear to be getting better
and better and better, judicially, economically, academically, let's say, religiously,
government-wise, financially, economically, all these things are going to be getting better
and better and better the closer you get to what I call the kill shots. So, it's going to be very
difficult to explain to people what's coming next when they're fully engrossed in a real society
with real things going on that are getting better. Yeah, they're going to get harsh and we will
explain how and why with detail. One example would be of what the future is going to be like
in the next decade is if you run into someone who lives in a big mansion and has a very expensive
exotic car and fancy jewelry and you say, wow, look how wealthy this guy is and then you find out that
it's all borrowed and rented and the person is just one day away from being homeless.
Right? People don't want to hear that. They just want to see, wow, look at that expensive house that
he has, an expensive car and all that jewelry. There's no way this guy is completely destitute
and broke and none of it is really his and that is how humanity, this is what humanity is going
into in the next decade. You're going to be exposed to the pinnacle of human society but you are going
to be subject to pretty much a condition that's going to last three and a half years that is going
to render the entire surface of the planet only with a small remnant of humans left. Right? And
the reason why is because most people are unrehabilitatable. You cannot have seven
billion people with the mindset that they have right now to go to the next level. You just have,
and the remnant that's going to be left, it's not because they're better. Well, only the good
people. No, it will be a representative sample. So the reason I'm throwing this in there is
because this is part of the subject matter that I found is very interesting and can be conveyed.
It's an interesting basis, that's for sure.
Yeah, and it's, you can rationally sort out the information, even though it seems irrational when
you incorporate the mind and the body because the body likes comfort. And when things are getting
better and feel better in society, both personal and social, and when I mean social, I mean
geopolitical and personal and all around, when things are seemingly getting better and better,
people don't want to hear that the whole thing's going to crash next week or in a year or three
years, or this is how it's going to go down. They don't want to hear that because the body is
comfortable and the mind is comfortable. It's housed in this container that is experiencing
joy. You're a party pooper, right? So right now, before these things are incorporated into society
and this upward swinging tide comes through, it's kind of interesting to those that have eyes
and ears to be aware of what to be aware of. And we will discuss that in detail as well.
I'd say that we've already gone into quite a bit of detail.
Yeah, so what do you think? What's the time on this? Should we wrap it up or what do you think?
I think we've been going for like half an hour, something like that, a little bit longer perhaps.
Oh, it seems like hours. Okay, anything else?
That much worth of information, certainly. If you would like to get into contact with us,
the email is uncommonsenseradio1 at gmail.com. I know that's a mouthful, but you can go to the
website uncommonradio.com. www.uncommonradio.com because if you put in uncommon radio as a general
search, we're not near the top of the query result query on that. So www.uncommonradio.com
brings you very close to it. And there's a form there you can email directly from the site.
The sonic broadcasts that will be forthcoming will be easily available there as well.
Okay. We also have a blog done by someone that really thinks the reporting that we've
done and the Greek has done is critical and important for others. And it's a blog,
Just Greek Speak, I believe. And there's also a Skype setup, which anyone that's interested
in joining the Skype. And there's also a chat in the blog. And I don't have that in front of me,
but you will find a link to the blog on the Uncommon Radio site. And it's listed as the
unofficial blog. And it's not done by myself or Seth, but it's done by someone who has invested
quite a bit of time into it and has found that what is being said as being important enough that
a blog would have been a good project for them to engage in and invest in that amount of time
into it. And I'm very appreciative of them doing that. They have their own way of expressing what
has been expressed, which I found to be, I haven't really spent much time on it. I just put it up for
everyone else. And there's also a Skype setup as well and a chat there. So I just want to throw
that out. Things to look for. We might be more engaging in the future. Yeah, absolutely. And we
will respond to emails when opportunity is there. You can get into contact with me directly at
dearredshoesatgmail.com. D-E-A-R-R-E-D-S-H-O-E-S at gmail.com. And that's a relatively quick way
to get in contact with me. And yeah, come back. We will be doing this. We're not going to do it
scheduled, really. We're going to do it as we have the time and the topics to discuss.
Let's say weekly or four times a month or maybe not. You know, roughly the weekly thing seems to
be okay, right? Maybe in frequency. Certainly. And we're going to do that. If you'd like to
help support the broadcast in any way, you can email us and we'll let you know how to do that
as well. Everything is appreciated. I'm glad that there are some people out there that are
going to be able to hear these conversations. And I do encourage you to get into contact with us.
We will explain what we can. Yeah. Perfect. Okay. Well, thanks again, Seth and everyone who's
listening and hearing as well. Absolutely. See you again soon. Be well and we'll speak to you again
in the near future.
Bye.