Hello and welcome to Uncommon Sense here on AmericanFreedomRadio.com as well as Ustream.
My name is Seth Michael and I'm joined as always by the Greek.
Welcome Greek.
How are you doing today?
Doing great.
Greetings everyone.
We're here another, it's been about a week and we're here and maybe we're going to talk
about more things people are pretty much never going to understand.
But it doesn't mean you can't talk about them anyway.
It's just the funniest thing.
The reason I say that is, you know, talk about money system or health or anything at all.
It's like you get this look like, wow, you know, but it just kind of clears through and
stays blank.
I don't know, man.
I don't know what's going on.
I mean, I kind of do know what's going on, but people don't really want to hear why,
you know, but they just want to maybe hear about things that they don't know about.
So I don't know.
Yeah.
What do you think?
I'd say that if all reality is just making a broad generalization here, all reality can
be viewed as being a symphony or an orchestra or a group of people making music instead of,
you know, varying experiences that what we talk about is tuned a bit differently than
what everyone else is used to.
So it sounds quite discordant to the reality that everyone is used to.
So even the things that we discuss that are obvious to those who have been, you know,
had the feeling that things are wrong, we're being lied to, et cetera, et cetera.
Even those things that are discussed here are discussed in a way that is quite opposed
to the way that they are discussed generally, because we're not the people that say, well,
you know, if it makes you feel good, it must be right and isn't that pleasant and, you
own truth and all of that good stuff.
I say that euphemistically.
And so what is heard here is it's discordant.
It doesn't vibe.
It doesn't resonate because it's so very different from what you're going to hear the rest of
the choir singing, that if you enjoy what they're saying, if you're enjoying that tune,
it's going to be difficult to take information out of what's being shared here.
So maybe turn down the background noise.
Yeah, if possible.
You know, what's interesting just on that thought came through when you were saying discordant,
the majority of the things we discuss are essentially the matters or the things that
most people subscribe to mentally, meaning in their groups, you know, whether it's religious,
scientific, social, economic, what we're doing is discussing the foundation of those things
that they can access with just a few minutes of research or hours or just a little bit
of inquiry, you know, and it's their own stuff.
It's real interesting.
Right. And they don't want to pretty much go back and see what things are based on.
It's interesting.
It's like a runaway situation, a self-consuming situation.
It seems like once the lie and the deception was started, it kind of like locked itself in.
And everyone, when I say everyone statistically, meaning most of the people you've ever met,
most people, you know, and most people you're going to meet will typically not have interest
on looking at the foundation or what things are based on and essentially are leading patterns
of thought and a life that is baseless, but yet adequate enough to maintain what's called
food, clothing and shelter or some semblance of.
So it's interesting to see that.
And I believe part of it might be taking things for granted.
You know, if I wake up in the morning and I'm breathing and I can walk or talk or do things
that I was told I'm supposed to do, that's good enough.
And the rest of it has been somehow hijacked and re-led or re rebooted in a way that is based
on nothing. It's the most interesting thing.
Well, it's the nothing is not really nothing.
It's based on a perception of the thing.
You know, like we've talked about all the world's religions, none of them are doing anything
that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to, quote unquote, the scientific community
does not pass its own scientific method.
Forget about economics, there is no money.
How you know, it's a credit based economy right away.
By the way, folks, prophetically, the majority of the people on this planet, if not most of
the people, will never understand the money system.
Isn't that interesting? Until a very certain specific time, which is when you're pretty much
out of time. So that is a moot point to discuss.
You know, I was always thinking about doing a couple hours with you, Seth, on how the money
system works. And I've kind of abandoned that because, again, prophetically, people will
never understand that.
Actually, what they will do in the future is they will just stop using it.
It doesn't state that they will ever really comprehend how it works either.
So I think discussing economics is a moot point.
And just to throw a little dig or a jab to the imbeciles and morons, by the way, if you
haven't noticed in listening to the show, especially the past few episodes, that is the
term that we refer to as the typical surface dwelling earth inhabitant.
And it's a polite one, by the way, had a message about someone maybe taking slight offense
to it. And I'm like, well, if you read any of the ancient texts, the gods think a lot worse
of you on that. So when you hear the Greek referring to your typical surface dwelling earth
inhabitant as an imbecile or a moron, take it in a good light.
That is about the best description that can all be a fitting
and maybe not as polite as one might perceive it to be, but it is actually quite
fitting. But wanted to go back to the discussion perhaps on economics is
that it's just boggles the mind on how there is not one, not a one,
this is a definite that I've discovered so far on the Internet or anywhere,
economic commentator that is even slightly accurate or discusses
the credit based economy in its true nature.
Not a one. Not one.
And there are several of them that are quite popular.
They have thousands of subscribers and they're quite popular and they're idiots,
every single one of them. And they don't even come close to discussing
anything. I was going to ask that.
I was going to ask if any of them even come close.
Nope, not at all. It's just amazing.
And some of these guys have celebrity status, just like in the conspiracy community.
I mean, you have people that are supposedly studying the occult and discuss the occult
and they get on and they talk about for 20 minutes.
No one knows who the pyramids were built.
We don't even have cranes today that could lift them.
Oh, boy. Since when?
Really heavy. This is just absurdity,
but there's an interesting word that came by this week
and it's called, I'll just sonically say it's coprophagia.
Starts with a C and it's a PH.
C-O-P-R-O-P-H-A-G-I-A.
And it's a it's a behavior.
So do you want to look it up?
Just a general search, coprophagia, and this is what's going on.
So anyway, just for you guys out there that are also into wordsmithing.
Coprophagia, it's an English word.
Yeah, it's basically Greek, but it's been used very often in terminology.
You want to read the definition?
This is yeah, this is just out of what they call the dictionary.
That's fine.
It's the eating of feces or dung.
Yes.
Coprophagia.
From copros, which is feces.
Phagia, which is to consume.
Yeah, it's a Greek prefix in a Greek suffix.
Yeah. Yep.
This is what's going on.
Right. If nothing is based, if what's being discussed is not founded.
Then what are they eating?
There you go. So.
Interesting. Anyway, we like words.
And so you mean it's not all about going back to the gold standard or the silver standard?
Or what are they auditing the Fed?
You could audit the Fed.
Yeah. Yeah. Why does the Fed need to be audited?
That's not their purpose.
There's nothing there to audit.
So they are basically think about it, folks.
As I said, I wasn't going to discuss.
Yeah, we're not going to dedicate a show to it, let's say.
But you've heard of stockbrokers colloquially like they get a cut from the transaction,
whether you buy or sell or whether you get an increase or profit or loss is irrelevant.
They get a cut from the transaction.
So that's all. There's nothing there to audit, folks.
If you want to know what the Fed's doing, just look at the money supply that's reported.
That's it. Takes about three minutes to audit the Fed.
So ridiculous.
And yeah, they're all endorsing this stuff.
You know, hey, how about this?
You know, this part of the world, by the way, it's getting warm.
And that means these little pathogens that allegedly cause the common cold are increasing
and they're quite active.
I don't see people really complaining about the common cold in the beginning of summer.
It's not interesting.
I just thought I'd throw that in there, folks, because apparently the Medical Society of
the United States is never going to understand anything either.
This is real simple stuff.
So if you'll notice that things tend to prefer refrigeration when it gets warmer to retard
the growth of bacteria.
But yet you're told that when it gets cold and the bacteria are dormant, they are the
cause for your illness.
OK, guys, just let that sink in for a minute.
I think that's comprehensible.
To some degree. So then what is if that is not the cause?
Obviously, it's not the cause.
It's temperature, right?
Yeah. Yeah. We use refrigeration, as you said, cold temperatures to inhibit the spread of
these bacteria or when viruses, pathogens, we'll call them pathogens.
But, you know, by the way, viruses and black holes and a couple other things don't exist.
You know, they're only a method.
Well, they're all they're figments of one's, would you say, presentation because they're
presented to you.
You'll never see a black hole and you'll never see a virus, folks.
You'll see an animation of one or a drawing of one.
But you'll see it's basically they're inaccurate ways of explaining a phenomenon.
Yeah, it's really it's cellcopro is what it is.
This is what it's yeah, it's broken up.
Things are created in the liver.
So anyway, these things are really, really astounding when you think about them, how
simple they are to approach.
It's the emperor has no clothes, you know.
Now, that was that uncommon.
I think so. But either way, there's a level of appreciation.
But, you know, we just touched upon medical a little bit.
Well, not medical health.
What is it? You know, well, one one suggestion is that the human body.
For lack of a better term, is very tightly integrated into its environment.
You know, sensory, of course, you know, when it's cold out, you're going to want to
you're going to feel cold and you're going to want to warm up.
And when it's hot out, you want to you're going to feel hot and you want to cool down.
So you are integrated very tightly into the environment.
So could it be that you're at the intake of what you consume, what you eat?
Foggy, right, has a systemic effect based on its seasonality and its latitude.
In other words, foods that are grown in a tropical location are going to influence those
that consume it chemically, at least as if they are adjusting the body to be in the
tropics. So if you're eating tropical food when it's cold out, your body will adjust to
living in the tropics and you will not fare well.
And the opposite is true.
If you live in the tropics and eat, let's say, for example, food that's grown near the
Arctic, typically the most commonality on that I've seen is people living in summer
months eating cold water fish.
Right. And they wonder why they can't cool down.
It's the most unusual thing.
And you tell them and they're like, oh, wow, that's really a good idea.
And then what do they do?
They go right back to it.
So, yeah, it's interesting.
I don't think the information, I think you and I have always discussed it's the
information or the ignorance of something is not what is driving this mess.
Let's say it's the stubbornness and rebelliousness and the, I guess, taking things
for granted concept is another thing.
And the gluttony. That's why, for example, back to the system, people will never I
think they're being cosmically blocked from understanding it because what's called
currency is derived from the signature.
So you really don't. All you have to do is go sign you sign the name that's attached to
the account that was created when you were born and you get whatever you want.
But they can't be made available to your common surface dwelling earth inhabitant
because they won't do anything.
So, yeah, that's I think enough said about that.
But yeah.
And the media, the sources of information that you're getting and the talking heads are
suggesting. Well, the entire group, both the ones giving the information and receiving it
are in the coprophagia dimension, I should say, because the stuff is just so
poor. So anyway, that's the word of the week, folks.
And speaking of the week, lawfully, it appears to be the third week of the fourth
month. What the hell is he talking about?
Yeah, lawfully, something people don't know.
Fourth day. Yeah.
Twenty third reckoning.
Twenty fourth. Yep.
By noon. Much.
I'd reckon the 24th of the fourth month.
Yep.
Lawfully. Now, you know, typically what most people reckon time with allegedly is a
work schedule, which is not a lawful timepiece.
And no one really cares, obviously, because, you know, most people are looking to be
socially accepted or find things to be, let's say, sociable.
So I guess there's a tipping point.
If you if you get the majority of the people that perhaps perform or think a certain
way and then they find comfort in it, then it's self-consuming.
I think it's, you know, they're looking for free energy.
There it is. Social memes, traditions and customs.
There's your free energy, folks.
Keeps on going. Yeah, it's important.
I think it's important to point out that your environment, the environment has become a
word that is used in a lot of like dogmatic speech currently with the, you know, the
state and being what it is and where we are.
But I think it's important to point out that your environment is not simply, you know,
like the state that you live in or the climate in which you find yourself.
But the environment is everything that is surrounding you.
And when you say that we are a very subject to our environment, it's not solely on a
health, but it's also on a the way that we act and the way that we think our abilities,
the ways, you know, our capabilities to think and act are limited by our environment as
well. Be it, you know, not just the extremes of, you know, extreme temperature, but the
from the clothing that is your immediate environment to, you know, the couch that you sit
on to, you know, the porch that you stand, it's it's all inclusive and being as subject
to input as the human form is, it's it's important to consider all of those things
because all of these things will affect you in one way or another.
And being aware of that makes it a lot easier to be conscious of those effects and
gives you a little bit more of perspective that is valid for seeing what is correct and
what is incorrect and not only what, but, you know, why comprehension, understanding.
So I just want a little aside there, but I wanted to point that out.
No, that's that's good, because it's how tightly you are integrated to that, you know,
here, a state of being environment environment now in 1600, the aggregate of the
conditions in which a person or thing lives first recorded 1827.
So it's a fairly new word here.
Specialized ecology since first recorded 1956.
It's fairly new, stating that it doesn't give much of an origin.
But the word economy is the same way, meaning people think that has to do with
currency and money, but actually economy actually means a set of laws or guidelines
or covenants that one lives by.
Like, you know, when I discuss, for example, certain things, I'll say in the biblical
economy, so and so and so.
And they're like, what are you talking about?
That has nothing to do with money.
Like, well, the word economy, ekos means house and nomos means law.
So it's a it's a control, it's a structure that is being controlled by a set of rules
or laws is the term economy.
So, you know, so when one states, let's say, the American economy, it also would
incorporate pastimes and customs and traditions and the way things are done, it's
not, you know, but perhaps the way they do things is why they believe they are in such
poor shape, which they're not.
So that's a real interesting thing.
In Vyron, in Vyron, yeah, the broken down in its original, the end, the end at the
beginning is, you know, in in English and Vyron, which is a circle or a circuit.
So encircled essentially what is around you.
Right, right. And how and how tight, you know, tightly integrated you are to it, which
is, you know, there's a series of boundary layers, like, for example, clothing is a
boundary layer, a dwelling place is a boundary layer, you know, you know.
Right. So, yeah, absolutely.
And seeing yourself as, you know, in an environment or being aware of how how it can
affect you, you know, is one way of separating yourself from it instead of just being a
part of that environment or a piece of that environment.
You can realize that you were it's something that you were in, as opposed to
something that you are a part of, like the fauna of the area or something or flora,
plants or animals.
Either way, there is a it's the guidance of the mind.
You know, there there's certain discussions I've had this week and people saying, well,
they're distracted by this and distracted by that.
And I said, wait a second, this is you're the third or fourth person that said that the
cause of these ills and things that people are going through are because they're being
distracted. Now, let's I think I briefly mentioned this last week, but a distraction is
simply a detour or a slight change that course corrections are made.
And I made a note to this fellow that, you know, if an airplane or a ship is on a on a
course and there's a distraction, a storm or a roadblock, you consider it a detour or a
course correction or a change and then you go back on course.
So the distraction cannot be the cause.
The cause is that people have no rules or covenants to live by.
They have no purpose that they are looking to attain.
So if the distraction is all there is enough to throw them off, you know, then, yeah,
that again confirms what we've been saying is that these things are unfounded because
people what they go upon are unfounded.
Yes, the distraction is can be critical and fatal in many instances, meaning fatal,
meaning where the the cause is it dies.
Right. Or whatever they're thinking about.
So or catastrophic.
But when one has a set course, for example, again, just like an airplane or a ship on the
ocean, if there's a storm, yeah, they might have to do a detour, go around the storm,
which is going to add time and distance, but they still end up arriving to their
destination. So this this metaphor or this is more direct than a metaphor is very much so
that when we say the religious societies, the scientific societies, medical size, legal
societies, because they're not based on anything while they say they are, but they're
not doing anything or not familiar with it is is kind of there's no stability, meaning
that the people are not aware that these religion sciences and so on and so forth are
based on something they're aware that they're supposed to be, but because they're not
aware of what's in what they're supposed to be based in, they fall for all the other
machinations, you know, like black holes and viruses and, you know, look at what's going
on in all the religions.
I mean, I'm you know, here's a thing that was a personal private thing.
I'll say I'm in complete shock still today that there are schools of divinity or
biblical colleges that are still open teaching what they teach.
And I'm still shocked that there are law schools today still teaching what they're
teaching. I'm in complete shock that there are medical colleges still teaching what
they're teaching. You know, forget about the people being unaware and naive, the gall
and the just just the the how would you say when someone just doesn't give a crap in
your face, blatantly wrong, still procuring this stuff.
You know, it's unbelievable.
I'm in complete shock that these schools, these professional schools, you know, that
people go to get a quote unquote degree still exist.
It's shocking. And what makes it shocking is you look at the curriculums and what they're
teaching. It's nonsense.
It's it's just it's yeah, it's just you got to really just grab yourself and say,
well, wow, you know, you can't really turn around and say the people are too naive,
let's say. So these people that supposedly know, how can they be responsible?
You know, why aren't they being held responsible for what they're doing?
So is it throughout history?
Has it been uncommon for the majority to rely upon the the presumed comprehension of
a few of the much because currently, like what, you know, I'm limited by my own
experience here inside of the States, but what is taught and how it is taught from
what little I've gleaned from history certainly appears to have changed significantly in the
last 60 to 70 years and in the last 50 and in the last 20, et cetera.
So like I'm familiar with the concept of like the, you know, the trivium and it seems
like they've just kind of picked one.
And currently what is being taught is the rhetoric for whatever, quote unquote, field
one is going into, at least on the higher education level.
You know, if you're planning on doing something other than simply pushing buttons or
building something, they teach you how to speak, but not how to do.
Like you brought up, you know, law, the legal society more specifically than actual law,
because that's not being discussed.
But as well as, you know, the the practical side as well, as opposed to just the.
Well, that would be the vocational vocational training you're referring to, like
technical training, like versus purely academic.
No, actually, I was referring more to the the rhetoric side of the academic part of
everything, because, I mean, there are still things being made.
You know, there's still machines being built to do things could certainly be improved
upon. But it's not like we're living in relative chaos.
Yeah, I wouldn't say it's chaos.
I think there's a brashness and an arrogance in the academic world or the places that
procure degrees in fields, the major fields being, let's say, the ones regarding faith,
the ones regarding science, which is the same, the ones regarding medicine, the ones
regarding law, legal, which is not law, let's say at this point.
In other words, even though there is no law, there is order, you see, and that's done by
motivating the society through penalty.
There's a big difference.
I'll say it again. You're living in a society pretty much across the board on the
planet that does what they do and maintains order by authoritative figure because the
motivation is within the penalty.
In other words, how many times have you heard with your, you know, this guy got away
with it. That means he wasn't subject to the penalty.
Well, how about having instruction and inspiration into the society that they should
do the right thing? See, very few people are in the legal society ever discuss what the
right thing is. They always discuss the penalty side, the motivation through that.
And this seems to be pretty much carried on by the population as well.
I mean, this is the way things go.
But back to the what is a complete shock is the arrogance of how trivial and incorrect
and inaccurate these higher forms of education are within their system, within their
curriculum, within the knowledge base that the so-called professors have, the texts.
And no one is paying any attention to it at all.
I mean, there are the ones that will criticize it to a degree.
Right. But they can't give specifics generally.
And I think that's why we get together to give maybe little slices.
You know, sometimes we go shallow and wide, sometimes we can go narrow and deep on a
subject. But I assure the listeners that never do we discuss anything in a very highly
specialized form.
Typically, we discuss things in a way that you can notice immediately just within your
immediate surroundings, within a few feet from you or just using a good rational
objectivity. You know, and that's pretty much uncommon.
Speaking of uncommon.
Yeah. If you if you like to contact us, we do have a site and it's just basically a site.
That's all it is. Not much on there other than just contact information.
And you can do that at www.uncommonradio.com.
And we'll link you to archives and where to listen at AFR as well and an email.
So, yeah, just wanted to throw that in.
And also American Freedom Radio is wholly and solely reliant upon the listenership for
support. So if you're listening, you know what to do.
Homepage will direct you on how to contribute.
So I just wanted to put that in as well, because we've received quite a courtesy by
showing up once a week here from AFR and doing it on what's called Internet Radio.
So, yeah, but nonetheless, many of the things that are discussed here might sound kind of
brash again. I'll say it is people will never understand.
Typically, as a society, it will never be understood as a group.
So most of the things that are spoken of here are not conducive socially for making
friends. You will not make friends if you listen to what's being said here and tend to
repeat the subject matter or the way it's being approached.
You will not be welcomed.
So that's very unusual to say, but it's unfortunately or fortunately, it's true.
We also like to think things are based on should be based on quality, not quantity.
Quantity is important, of course.
It's a rational measurement, but it seems that they're rationalizing quality has left
most. They don't really know how to rationalize quality, you know, and that's another
thing that's always being discussed here.
What is the quality of the thing?
Well, it's like having having one pen that functions or having, you know, 15 pens that do
not function or function well.
Yeah. You know, for the guys, I always say, you know, you're blessed if your feet fit in
Spanish or Italian shoes, if you if you if you can fit in Italian or Spanish made shoes,
buy them. They last very, very long time.
Yeah, they're 200 bucks or so.
But yeah, by quality stuff, I bought a pair of cycling shoes about 20 years ago for 400
bucks. And guess what?
Still have them and they're rocking, you know, and where if they weren't the best that I
wanted to afford at the time, I would have gone through five pairs at about a third of
that price, which would have made made it more expensive, believe it or not.
So, yeah, there's something about quality, you know, there's a question or a little bit
of a question from the chat on Ustream that you mentioned just a moment ago, you know,
things that are easily referenced and that are right in front of us.
And so this kind of goes along with that.
But it's the question goes like this.
What of ignorance of the stars?
Understanding the times and seasons communicated by the sky is uncommon and many
comments, a couple of things about what we've been talking about.
The Bible school dummy load has to keep rolling until the heavens roll back as a scroll.
And he says, you know, the universities and Bible schools are trade schools effectively.
And that's how they are pagan, Hellenistic paganism.
If you want to be specific, let's let's get into a little bit of that, what they're the
trade school, what they're teaching is for people to partake in ritualistic, Hellenistic
paganism with Assyrian, Assyrian and Babylonian symbology.
I'll say it again, it's a mouth load.
What the all of them, whether they're biblical or any other religion, is essentially
Hellenistic paganism with Babylonian and Assyrian symbology.
Now, a lot of these higher ups in these religions in private have other rituals that
work on the Philistine and Canaanite and Babylonian rites and rituals.
So, yep, that's pretty much as accurate as you can get and specific as you can get.
But regarding the stars, the stars pretty much reckon the ages, which are broken down
into one thousand and two thousand year chunks.
I just want to address one other thing.
I just went into the Ustream here until the heavens roll back as a scroll.
Well, what's interesting about that, and we kind of like to give a little things about
that. You ever see a time lapse photography of the North Star where it looks like the
star is in the center and then you have these white lines of streaks.
That go around because of the time lapse.
All the other stars are kind of rotating around it.
When you look at the end of a scroll, it has this rolled.
Look to it, right, a spiral almost, you know what that means, by the way, and what it if
you look, if you look at the heavens rolling as a scroll in context, it refer it's
referring to the pole shift, by the way, of the planet, which will happen in the future.
So something to think about keeping things in context, which which I wanted to throw
in. We usually like to do dispel a little cliche every time we've missed the past
couple of times. So it's going to take this opportunity to do itself regarding a
biblical cliche.
How about it? A biblical cliche?
Yeah, but you'll use versus inaccurately as cliches.
They don't know what they mean or they're out of context.
Like, for example, no one knows the day or the hour.
Isn't that supposedly it's the return of someone out of the biblical text.
That's what they apply it to.
It has nothing to do with that.
If any, if you read the verse that comes before it, the Christ is asked, when will the
sun and the earth wither away or go away?
And he says, no one knows the day or the hour.
But if you're asleep, you're going to miss the time of my return.
Isn't that interesting?
So anyway, just thought I'd throw that in there.
So whenever you hear someone says no one knows the day or the hour, it has nothing
to do with what you think it does.
It has to do with the wearing away or the destruction or the entropic effect on the
sun and the earth and the stars.
So I thought I'd throw that in there.
There's not much understanding.
And, you know, just like if you look at what's called this, you know, you've got this
guy long and long hair nailed to a Roman cross wearing a diaper.
Right. That's Assyrian symbology.
That never happened. You could read the King James Bible a million times.
If you are reading into it, you will never see it.
If you're reading out of it, you will see everything that's being put in front of you
is a lie. So so I throw that in there.
Yeah, it's baseless rhetoric or the basis that is being used is inaccurate to the text
that was. But even in that has been preserved.
But, you know, even in the in the crappy King James versions and any English version is
pretty crappy, by the way, because singular things are turned into plural and plural
turn into singular and words are changed and it's just not even it's just make you want
to crawl out of your skin if you look at it.
But and you figure out what's what's been done.
But but here's the point.
It's just going back to that guy nailed to a cross.
If you read the text.
It's very clear that Pontius Pilate, he was the last jurisdiction he was brought to
cleared him any wrongdoing and returned him back to the Judean authorities to use their
law. Very clear.
Judean authorities are not familiar with Roman laws and Roman execution.
There was no crucifixion, folks.
Doesn't matter how many times it says it.
Very clear about that.
Word crucifix, by the way, is a botanical term has to do with the flower of a tree.
So anyway, I figured I'd just throw that in there because it's just shock.
It's just shocking and how relevantly irrelevant what people believe in is.
So. Absolutely.
So any comments on what is referred to as the Zodiac or the concept of astrology?
There's a question in chat asking if it's accurate or it is, but but they don't use the
Zodiac. They use more like the Maserat.
It is very accurate to a degree, but you have to look at the entire thing.
In other words, the movements of the planets and the stars, just like anything like if you
ever heard of the obsession with the occult, with the penis and the vagina.
Yes, I said it.
And, you know, like all of your church architecture and temple architecture is based on
the ancient sex temples.
Why did they focus on it?
Because the the the flower where the seed is is the most important part of the crop.
Well, obviously, the yield of the crop is important.
But if you don't have a flower in a seed, there's no crop next year.
So what was recognized is the genitalia as being the most important organ because there's
a limited lifespan to the living thing.
And it's important that the seed continues.
So they went a little overboard.
Well, the movement of the stars and the effects of the planets on the Earth, they went a
little overboard with that.
And they think that's it and that's it alone.
And it's not. There's more to it.
Now, there's also a comment in there.
There's too bad the Bible is a flat Earth book, numerous references to the Earth being
flat. I guess now there is no reference to the Earth being flat in the biblical text
whatsoever. Zero, it is very clear that the Earth is round.
So it's now what obviously this person is reading King James or Fenton or NIV or all
that stuff there.
They have not gone into the intralinear aspect yet.
So there's what there's a lot to do.
This is it's not time yet to discuss that.
But here's the point.
Have you ever heard of the four corners of the Earth?
Yeah, that's exactly what was yes.
Yeah, that's just like just without giving the explanation how it's derived and how it's
defined. Well, actually, I will.
There's one place there where part of the economy states that you are not to shave the
four corners of your head or the four corners of your face.
Right. It's what's called Leviticus.
Right. So that means your head is flat.
Right. It's talking about someone else.
Obviously. Yes.
The way you derive four corners on something that is round is by two intersecting lines,
right, like taking a pie and cutting it across and then rotating and cutting it across
again where those two lines intersect.
Now they become four lines and they're in the center of the circle.
So whenever you hear of the four corners, just like the four corners region of what's
called America is where four states intersect.
And you could with two legs actually standing, you have two people standing in four
states at the same time.
Right. So the four corners typically symbol is is very specific about the center of
something that is round.
So anyway, let's let's go on.
We kind of landed on that question.
I think there's much to discuss on these things.
Yeah, it's an interesting thing as well, because, you know, the easiest reference
material available is dramatically flawed.
Dramatically is not the right word, but catastrophically flawed in many aspects,
especially if you're trying to study minutia or not minutia, but details.
The details have been obscured.
So, you know, interlinear is an easy tool to find if you have access to the Internet.
And if you're listening to us, chances are you have access to the Internet in one
form or another. Right.
Be careful. It only has what the Internet has.
But yeah.
And the thing is, even in the interlinear, they're going to show you a lot of
differences. But still, there's still pretty tricky little scoundrels.
Yeah. You'll see that certain things are not being translated and you see that they
lean towards a certain bias again on certain things.
But here's a here's a thing.
And I tell people this is pretty it sounds dogmatic, but it's actually very true.
And it's so true. And it's so simple.
It should be said whenever you hear anyone discussing anything biblical, they have to
preface that even today to this current day today, meaning all right up until this
current day, there is no translation of the biblical text from its original languages of
preservation, period.
That is a fact. And that is the truth.
It has yet to be translated.
What the hell do you got?
Well, ain't no translation, that's for sure.
Or interpreted versions.
Yeah, it's a very poor version.
Extremely poor.
Actually, if it was any poorer than that, you'd find a cell phone and Julie and Julius
Caesar and Mickey Mouse or something like that.
I mean, it is so poor that it's it's absolutely scraping the bottom in quality.
But why?
Why, why, why?
I'm sorry, I don't mean to.
We've discussed cosmic censorship.
Humanity was put under major, the last major axial period was around twenty five
hundred years ago. And at that time, there was a big obfuscation of general knowledge of
the spiritual world and the true history of mankind.
I know, again, this might sound a little crazy, but if anyone wants to look at what's
called the axial period of 500 B.C.
or twenty five hundred years ago, you're going to find a little bit of what emerged and
what was taken away.
And at this point, what we're saying, all of this stuff is still accessible.
Right. It's just that it takes a little bit of effort.
But you've got to remember that there is still very heavy cosmic censorship.
Recently, someone said to me, oh, I read a certain book of the Bible and I didn't get
anything out of it. I'm like, wow, you know, you could spend a year on just a chapter
of that. I figured it doesn't matter.
You know, here's someone who is censored.
You know, you could read it, but are you reading it with comprehension?
You know, so there is a time and a place where things are properly discussed.
And now is not the time to discuss certain things, believe it or not, you know, even
for the very few. But there is a time coming in the next couple of years where things
that are more lawful.
Can be presented in a more rational way.
You see. Yeah, there's a.
Well, here's an example.
One way to measure timing is when you go out into public and you see what's going on.
Right. All right.
Give an example. All right.
Look at all black and white films.
When you had, let's say, men going out into public, they all wore hats.
You ever notice that? You ever notice in the old black and white prior before the 1950s
or so, you're looking at the old films, everyone wore a hat.
And believe it or not, most of the shops or retail areas had hat shops.
And then all of a sudden, haberdasheries, haberdasheries.
Yeah. And and all of a sudden, within a decade or less, they all went away.
So it wasn't hat time anymore.
I mean, if you guys are familiar with Charles Fort, 14 times he talked about anomalous and
paranormal things at the turn of the century.
And he was in a discussion once and said, well, you know, look at something really simple
as a steam engine. You know, there's inklings of its invention 2000 years ago and things
like that. But how come it's so prolific today?
And he says, well, it wasn't steam engine time.
Then it's steam engine time now.
Right. The reason we have the steam engine is because it's steam engine time.
The reason why you have the airplane, it's airplane time.
The reason why you have no biblical translation is because it's not time yet.
So it's very interesting.
It's it's the same with all religions, by the way.
I have yet to meet anyone in any particular faith that knows anything really about what
and, you know, what they're professing.
And this is not just the average, you know, socialite, you know, the person who subscribes
to the group. I'm talking about the people that lead these groups as well.
And the same with the scientists and the same with the legal society and the same with the
medical society.
You know, the ones that tend to be more foundationally based or like Seth was saying
earlier on, we're more like the engineers, people that make stuff.
I think you said it several times that people that build stuff and make stuff, they
can't skirt around the issue of being practical or, you know, truthful to some degree.
Like if you're an engineer designing a bridge and decide to make it out of paper mache,
well, you know, there's going to be a lot of other people on the way that are going to
stop it from happening in paper mache.
Right. But when you have scientific endeavors put out by the scientific community or the
religious groups or the medical groups, it seems like no one kind of gets in the way
and says, hey, did you ever stop and think there's no such thing of what they're telling
you? I find that to be a phenomenon, almost paranormal in its existence.
That's why we bring up the concept of cosmic censorship.
There's more in control here.
There's also some people that do discuss, you know, they'll typically say, oh, there's an
evil force controlling the world.
I don't know what it is, but there's something bad.
Well, how about starting discussing these things?
Yes, there's going to be a time for it.
But not this time.
You know, we can actually what can be brought up is that what's called as how many times
have you heard, you know, man, we're going to ascend to the next dimension and all this
really I don't even want to reference all the dumb shit that's out there.
But basically, your existence is very sure and very clear and very simple.
You have all things that are perceptible and all things that are unperceptible, meaning
things that you see, touch, feel, can ponder.
And then you have the things that you can't see, touch, feel or imponderable doesn't mean
they don't exist.
And just like any information about anything, if you decide that it's bunk, don't look at
it. You can criticize it and you can call it stuff, whatever.
But if the information is looked at, let's say, can it be validated?
Is it memorialized to some degree of importance?
In other words, it's preserved.
And that was from a long time ago regarding certain matters.
Let's say the matters here would be the things that are imponderable, unseen or
imperceptible. If we start looking at these things, we get a chock full of information,
albeit not written in the way that you're willing to accept it.
Because, for example, when you look at timekeeping, you will not see the Pope's work
schedule or the Gregorian calendar on there or anything.
Right. And there's no such thing as, well, these people keep time this way and these
people keep time that way.
It does. That has nothing to do with keeping time that has to do with the work schedule
or some kind of cultural functioning calendar.
But lawful time is reckoned by the sun and the moon and the stars.
Right. So there's many, many things that need to be overcome to understand what's
been memorialized through from ancient days till now.
So. And that time is coming, it's not now, it will be more prevalent in the future.
But you're being set up for it.
I think Seth, you and I were discussing this years ago on how humanity will be set up
to have more of a spiritual mindset or a mind mindset.
Right. Same thing about considering the realm of the gods.
Most of the information that will be discussed, of course, will be inaccurate.
And I'm saying, of course, facetiously and also being accurately accurate.
You know, they will not have any accuracy, very little or precision or being true to
what's been memorialized.
But their minds will be leaning towards that direction increasingly as time goes on.
Also to other things as time goes on.
But certain things will not be understood until in this society at all.
And one of the things that we mentioned is the money system will not be understood.
It will change when people will just decide not to use it anymore.
And this is a time that's coming in the future, not now.
So I guess these things can be considered uncommon, but always referring back to
things that people can commonly access.
Any other comments we have, Seth?
Well, the guy in chat still commenting on the Flat Earth book.
Oh, it's fine.
And I'd ask them to be specific because we can address something specific, but that's
just not the case.
Yeah, there's an interesting thing regarding the Flat Earth thing.
You know, people brought it up, by the way, and I've also asked what I think of it.
And I'm like, that's really funny.
I'm like, how old are you?
I'm like, what do you mean, how old I am?
And they give me their age.
And I'm like, you just so you've been on this planet all these years.
And all of a sudden, this idea of it being flat came to you.
I doubt it.
You're just falling for Gustave Le Bon's the crowd mentality.
You're part of the crowd.
It's an interesting phenomenon.
Recently, within the last year or so, I've seen a lot of, I haven't actually watched,
but I've seen a lot of things commenting on Flat Earth.
It's a dummy load.
Yeah, it's a dummy load.
It's a hamster wheel.
People have a lot of energy.
All the way to the point where a soccer mom's minivan turns over and she could lift the van.
Where did you find that energy?
So let's find some more energy for the next hour.
All right.
We'll be right back.
You're listening to Uncommon Sense here on American Freedom Radio at AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Welcome back to Uncommon Radio, Uncommon Sense here on AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Which is Uncommon Radio.
Yes. At least for these two hours.
Yeah, you can find us at UncommonRadio.com, which is like a calling card, I suppose, contact
information and whatnot, possibility of archives and things like that as well.
So, yeah, welcome back.
Yeah, we're back.
We just finished off saying we're not going to discuss the Flat Earth, but it is one of
those things like, do you remember, if you know anyone old enough, going through photo
albums and they were, let's say, already adolescent or adult in the 70s and they had
polyester bell bottoms with big lapels and all that.
Remember those days?
Or you might not remember them, but you've remembered the fashion.
And they thought they were so cool going out and buying a Kiana nylon shirt.
And now it's like, oh, no, that's so that's so hideous.
Put that away, you know.
So there's very often when I in public hear people discussing things that are in vogue.
I say, well, do you remember polyester bell bottoms?
You're like, what does that have to do with it?
I say, well, you'll figure it out.
Anyway, it's one of those things, the thing that all of these questions that do come up
regarding things that are in vogue or fashionable to discuss or whatever, the answer
perhaps might be, where's the mastery in that?
Any subject, any concept?
Is there a mastery?
Like regarding the earth and the sun and all that, there is no mastery in being told, for
example, that the earth goes around the sun.
That doesn't help anyone in anything.
What helps a surface dwelling earth inhabitant is a very good comprehension all the way to
the mastering of these movements as they refer to you, meaning existing on this planet,
meaning mastering that the sun rises in the east and the sun sets in the west.
So that gives the appearance that the earth is in the middle of it.
And why is that important?
Because there's something called orientation with buildings and houses.
You know, someone likes to sleep in late.
You don't want to orientate the windows of that house towards the east.
Or if you're planting crops, you want to plant them in a certain way that they get even
light so certain parts of the crop don't get just the warm afternoon sun.
You know, you see, so, yeah, so you're looking for mastery within the subject matter,
but not the way the subject is being discussed.
And this is regarding anything.
It also comes up with the religious aspects, for example, with regarding what's called
Christianity. Some people say, oh, no, I used to be Catholic, but now I'm Mormon or now
I'm Quaker or now I'm Protestant or Luther was better.
I'm like, oh, boy, they all miss the point.
They all miss the point.
None of that stuff is based on anything.
Again, you see, it's not so the problem is there is no problem.
The problem is that the subject is not being dealt with from a mastership perspective.
In other words, let's first exhaust what's been memorialized on the subject and stop
just looking at what has emerged in the last five minutes or five months about the
subject. Right.
And this is something that humanity in wholesale lacks.
I think, again, bringing it up, I'm not promoting the book, but it's Gustav Le Bon in
the crowd talks about it.
There is a certain crowd mentality.
And in order to have the crowd form, what's common about them is that the crowd forms
under a subject idea or subject matter, let's say.
And in order for those participating in the crowd to accept it and come together under
it, the idea has to be so simplified that it no longer represents its original form.
That's why Le Bon refers to them as imbeciles.
Typically, you will find these crowds still forming there, especially in the alternative
media. Well, I should say in the mainstream as well, very much in all sorts of causes
or subjects.
And if you actually look at the heart of the matter, you will see there's not much
there other than the way things are being discussed.
But what is being discussed is no longer being discussed.
It's the way it's being discussed.
So it's very interesting.
Again, so all right, so let's be uncommon.
All right. So we're here on the second hour.
And by the way, I just want to interject something that I've gotten a lot of positive
feedback regarding the cooking tips, you know, rice and starches and various other
things past couple of weeks.
So I just want to thank the four people and actually another four or five maybe that
have gotten back regarding having good success regarding making perfect rice or nearly
perfect rice I've heard and various other things.
So you're welcome.
And yeah, let me add my own voice to that as well.
Thank you. I've the wife and I've made rice several times actually in the last week
it's yeah, it's the outcome was it's perfect.
It's good stuff. Yeah.
Used it for a few different dishes as well.
It's just it's very, you know, tasted it after just cooking it.
So it's just plain, you know, long grain rice, no no flavoring or anything to it.
And it's the flavor of the rice itself is really good.
So right. And it would be the rinsing and the cooking with a tight lid and letting it
rest and fluffing and you had a good sheen and a good flavor on the rice.
Good. Absolutely.
So, yeah, there's much more to do on things like that.
And I have one personally that I think we could go through this program or this
broadcast relatively quickly that might be a benefit.
It's I make we talked about it in passing a little bit, but I thought maybe we could
walk through it like we walked through the rice for the benefit of anyone listening.
And that's just a simple, quick flatbread.
Hmm. Yeah. Well, why don't you go through it?
You know, I would, but I don't measure anything.
I've done it so much that I just kind of work with the materials that I have at hand.
And if it's not the right consistency, I'll add a little bit of water or a little bit
more flour or something like that.
So I don't have I mean, I can I can walk through the process of how I did it.
You know, the evening before or yesterday, actually.
Yeah, go ahead. No measuring is fine as long.
See, the reason we bring up the measurement for the rice is because it's extremely
simple. Well, for example, just, you know, whatever volume you measure out of dry rice
would be equal volume of your liquid.
And it's simple because you typically would use something to, you know, scoop the rice
or measure the rice.
Typically, you know, I've actually done it for so long.
Believe it or not, I don't even I just pour the rice out and do it visually.
And just when the liquid covers about a four fingers depth over the rice, I've pretty
much got equal volume.
And that's how pretty much I reckon we're going to discuss things with the flatbreader
if there's no measurement, right?
Yeah, it's a it's a visual, intuitive thing.
But essentially, do you want you want to give it a shot or you want me to jump into it
real quick? It's up to you.
I can give it a shot and then go for it.
Like I said, it's relatively quick.
Essentially, you're going to start out with your flour, whatever flour it is, you can
find unbleached stuff relatively easily.
I'd recommend that because who wants bleach in their flour?
But so take your flour and I like to do it with an egg.
I've done it without, but egg adds a little bit of good flavor to it.
So and butter or is what I used last night, like I said, I'm just kind of going to walk
through how I did it last night because it came out really well.
And you mix a little bit of salt, mix in with the flour, you know, to your own taste, I
guess. I don't like predominantly salty bread, so I just add a little bit of salt.
And by the way, Seth, I like throwing in very, very coarse rock salt.
So it's so if you occasionally you'll get a bite of it.
But anyway, go ahead. Yeah, it's just really flavorful.
So go ahead. Yeah.
And the I use just salt that doesn't have anything added to it.
No additives. It's relatively inexpensive, which is always a concern of mine, I
suppose. But so I mix the salt in with the flour and then mix the butter in, you know,
not melted, just mix it in by hand.
I'm doing this all by hand on a clean countertop.
Mix that up a little bit.
It makes it easier for the butter to mix in.
And then you could break up the butter by squishing it between the fingers, let's say
while you're doing it. Yeah.
Yeah. And if you do that in the flour, it makes it break up really well.
And then add add your egg, just crack your egg on the counter and drop it in there.
Not the shell, obviously.
And then I mixed all that up with my fingers right there on the countertop and had a cup
just I did measure the water, but I didn't use all of it.
I just had a cup of warm water sitting on the counter.
Slowly add the water.
Uh huh. Yeah, exactly.
And add the water slowly, kind of keeping a circle or a ring of flour around where you're
working. So you can add a little bit more in and it kind of will help it keep from
spilling out if you accidentally add too much.
And then you just start working.
I work the egg in to the flour and made it almost like a dough like that before I
started adding the water and then, you know, add a little bit of water.
You can add a little bit of sugar if you like.
But I didn't, you know, I didn't add any yesterday was just flour, water, butter and an
egg, a little bit of salt.
And then instead of baking it, I just turned a skillet on low heat.
I have an electric stove that we use and, you know, a thick bottom skillet and brought
that up to temperature low heat.
Didn't put anything in the skillet at all.
No, no butter or anything to keep it from sticking.
It's just stainless steel.
And rolled the I have an empty Merlot bottle.
Well, it's not empty. It's full of water, actually, that I use as a rolling pin.
And I, you know, mix the the dough up between my fingers, add a little bit of water as it
was necessary or a little bit of flour till it comes out like a dough.
You're familiar with what dough feels like.
That's kind of what you're going after.
Then you however much you're making, you twist a little bit off, you know, make a ball
with it in your hands, set it on some loosely spread out flour on the countertop and then
roll it out flat with a rolling pin or an empty bottle of repurposed bottle of wine, I
suppose. And then take it off the counter, stick it on the skillet.
Medium to low heat is better, actually.
If you're using electric skillet, low is still pretty hot.
And then you throw it on the skillet and cover it, put a lid over it and let it cook for
maybe a minute, a little bit less or a little bit more, depending upon the stove,
probably, and the skillet till it starts to you see the you see it bubble just slightly.
Then I was just reached in there and flipping it.
My hands were covered in flour, but you can flip it, you know, with tongs or a spatula if
you like, and then let it do that on the other side.
It'll brown just slightly and, you know, it's ready when you see that basically you're
just heating it up until the water is slightly cooked out of the dough and it changes
color a little bit and goes a little bit.
If you're using, you know, white flour, it'll turn white instead of kind of an off
white yellowish color as it's not golden brown where it bubbles up.
And essentially it's like making a pancake, but less time and it's more durable.
Or a tortilla.
Yeah, or tortilla.
Yeah. Another way to do it is the whole thing that, Seth, I'm glad you mentioned doing
it on the stove top uses very little energy, right?
You what when I'm in an area where I have limited cooking abilities, let's say
visiting someone's house, I would do I would start off with the skillet on the
stove top, flip it and then or not flip it so that the side on the pan is flat and
where the bubbles are, then I immediately turn on the oven on broil and just put it
in the broiler section with the door open for about 30 seconds or so.
That's another way to do it.
But yeah, that's pretty much how it's done.
And the I believe the suggestion for a rolling pin is just that anything that rolls.
Yeah. Will will act really well.
I think we discussed this a while back, even if you don't roll it out with a wine bottle.
That's right. You could you could.
Yeah. And the thing is, the thinner the better.
You don't want to make it so thin where you know it's too thin.
If it becomes translucent, you see the counter or the space below it.
But it's the thinner, the better to some extent.
You might want it slightly thicker for a different thing.
And again, what this does is there's nothing like fresh bread, right?
Nothing like fresh baked bread.
Now, in this case, you're not going through the complexity of using a leavening agent or something
like a yeast and using a lot of energy like firing up an oven.
But you are going to get the effect of a fresh flatbread, unleavened flat cake bread.
Let's say we will leave the cake out.
Most Western places, cake is a pastry, but a flatbread, which is a wonderful starch,
which would substitute a starch in any meal.
Right. And actually, in your case, you mentioned that you use it sometimes
as a tortilla. You can wrap things in it as well, right?
Yeah. Yeah. And I would second you certainly on the for that particular method.
If you're actually going to do that, the thinner the better, because if you especially cooking
it on the stovetop like I did, where you're bringing it up to temperature very quickly,
you want to have it thin so that it cooks consistently all the way through.
And if you roll it out, fold it over twice and then roll it out again, it will it will
puff up a little bit more kind of if that's what you're looking for.
And then we used it.
I made hummus as well.
And that was that was dinner last night.
And it was it was splendid.
It's wonderful. Excellent.
Yeah. And the thing is, we're stressing here is the quality aspect for as long as anyone
can remember through historically flour products were intended to be,
I guess, assembled and used immediately.
Right. Like daily bread.
Right. Like again, I'm in shock.
You know, I go to the to the shops and I see there's bread on the shelf that's supposed to be
there for a week or so, you know, and I'm like, wow, you know, typically anything that was
baked that was held over to the next day was heavily discounted.
And, you know, the today's fresh batch was procured typically.
Right. So what this is, the reason I think not necessarily stressing the flatbread, but
what what we're trying to say here indirectly is that when you're looking for a flour
type bread product, right, it should be as fresh as possible.
And it doesn't get any fresher than making it yourself on the spot.
And there's something about the experience.
I mean, it's the smell, the taste, the whole thing.
It's just a wonderful attribute.
And it's a starch, basically.
So if you're having a meal and you're thinking of making rice or potato or starch to go
with that meal, consider a flatbread and you will if you want to enjoy a flour based
product. And it could be even a more of a whole flour.
You can experiment with it or do 50-50, you know, a refined flour and a whole flour.
And it's a very, I would say, Seth, you know, if if I'm preparing a meal and I would
like a bread to go with it, if I make a flatbread, that goes over way better than going
to the store, let's say, and buying a flatbread.
Right. It's always a much better quality to do it yourself.
And it's much more pleasurable to your senses.
Yeah, yeah, it takes a little bit more time and there's a little bit of mess and clean
clean up involved, but it's you can do a whole bunch of it at once.
It'll keep a day or two relatively well.
I would not keep it any longer than that.
It doesn't have anything in it to preserve it.
You could freeze it, you know, you could freeze it for a couple of months if you wanted
to. You can refrigerate it for a few days.
I would leave it more than like, you know, three, three or four.
But it's it's good.
It's versatile. You can use it with anything and you can flavor it to taste.
You can throw herbs and spices in the dough if you want.
Or, you know, like I said, sugary, throw cinnamon and sugar in it.
Sesame seeds. Yeah, anything at all.
And well, with it within reason, I guess.
But yeah, it's quick.
It's easy. It's it's inexpensive.
And if you have someone helping you, it's it's a lot easier on the cleanup, too.
So yeah, but yeah, good stuff.
Food prep. Yeah, yeah.
An hour, an hour per meal, like a like a like a large meal, which would be, I guess, in some
places late afternoon, you know, your main meal.
It's not unusual to spend an hour to prepare or at least a minimum of a half an hour to
prepare. This is not anything required, but typically half an hour to an hour.
To allocate for the main meal of the day is totally fine.
And it's amazing how humanity, well, not all of humanity, but generally the Western
culture has gravitated away from that food prep time.
Yeah, absolutely.
Quick, convenient, right?
Convenience.
To what end? Yeah.
To what end is that convenience?
Well, I'd say it was about 45 minutes from when we started with on the bread to when
we were, you know, eating.
The hummus doesn't take much time at all.
That's just adding some ingredients to a blender and then blending it till it's desired
consistency, essentially.
But a bean paste, basically Middle Eastern style.
Yeah, bean, Middle Eastern bean dip, essentially.
Bean dip.
Yeah, it's interesting.
Most cultures do have some kind of a bean paste, bean dip, like, for example, in Asia,
there's a dookie bean or red bean, small red variety is sweetened and it's made in a cake.
It's a filler where that type of filling would be more of a fruit filling or cream
filling in Western countries.
In Asian countries, a sweet filling for a pastry would be a bean, believe it or not.
So a bean paste, red bean cake.
If you ever go to a Chinatown type place or Asian market and you see anything packaged
and says red bean cake, it's a sweet filling.
Yeah, this is another interesting way to look at various things.
Again, consider these things, by the way, when you're trying to pursue some kind of
cross-latitude way of eating or eating seasonally.
The thing is to have variety, folks.
When you have variety, there's health in that.
So, you know, there's something to be said about variety.
And, you know, again, you will get variety when you eat seasonally, you will get variety
when you pretty much cook things or prepare food for yourself because you will just gravitate
towards making things different every time.
So these are things to consider.
And not to be misconstrued here, this food stuff, by the way, this is another form of
what I call bioterrorism that's been put on society.
Many people have been discussing, oh, yeah, food and health, you know, it goes together.
Well, yes, it does go together.
It's very important, obviously.
And we're not flipping around here and saying that it's not important.
But usually when Seth and I are, I guess I could speak for you on this to a certain degree,
Seth, let me know if I shouldn't.
When we're discussing food preparation is just to enjoy a quality meal.
It's the quality of the meal and health stuff aside for a moment because most of the
comments that I do get a lot is regarding health and food.
And it's just too much of an emphasis on that.
And yes, it should be emphasized.
But when we have food discussions, it is how to obtain the highest quality and the highest
level of enjoyment from what you're doing.
Are you with me on that?
Yeah, absolutely.
It's that.
And like I said, it's really inexpensive.
Yeah, it's those things with the, you know, it's yeah, you know, even though money doesn't
exist currently in the system that we're in, things are still expensive.
And if you're going to exist in the society and, you know, just to interact with it, you
need you need credits.
And bread and rice are two things that are inexpensive, easily available, you know, everywhere.
It's just I've listened to a lot of programs talking about these very exotic and difficult
to acquire or expensive or very exclusive, like helpful products and things like that.
And in order to consume things that are not consumed, but in order to eat, you know, good
food intake, it doesn't have to be expensive or difficult to to do.
It's just the very simple things have kind of been left out of a lot of stuff.
So it's uncommon.
And so, yeah, everyone has access or nearly everyone, you know, statistically everyone
has access to rice and flour.
So now, you know, at least a couple of methods to prepare very basic things inexpensively,
easily, relatively quickly and to an end because you can use the rice, you know, in just about
anything, just like you can use the flatbread, which is about anything.
You know, you make a sweet dish, you make a dessert, you can make a hearty meal.
I've done a very similar recipe to that in a waffle iron and added, you know, a good
quantity of oats and just cooked essentially the flatbread with oats in there to make a
little bit heartier oil instead of butter, although I do use the butter to keep it from
sticking.
But, you know, so there's just it's easy, it's useful, it's good and it's uncommon.
So there you have it.
Yeah, okay.
Someone just commented, yeah, we're becoming a food show.
That's I like that.
In essence, that's something that we enjoy, Seth and I do, and we're not going to put it
on the listenership anymore.
There's just, well, it might come up, but it might come up again.
But either way, yeah, the thing is, though, also the quality over quantity.
This is regarding all things, for example.
You know, we were discussing earlier, just to jump off the topic for a moment, I tend
to sound kind of ranty when I discuss the various societies.
But essentially, when you objectify, when I say various societies, medical, scientific,
religious, so on and so forth, these little specialist groups, because they've debased
themselves, they go into the realm real simplified over maybe oversimplified for some, but it's
quite objective.
They've gone into the realm of being pranksters.
And when you mention things being expensive, what ran through the mind is, yes, you know,
it's a credit based economy.
So what's interesting right now, there is a balance.
I wouldn't say perfect balance, but there is a balance that maintains order with the
surface inhabitants of this planet, that the balance is such you have a population on the
planet right now that is pretty greedy and pretty gluttonous.
And they are being ruled and overruled, let's say, or controlled by other entitled societies
that are pranking, that are pranksters.
You might want to consider the legal society.
OK, they are pretty much what most people will interact with when it comes to what they
think is law.
And they are the ones that actually procure the penalties that motivate the people to
stay in order.
But if you actually look at what the legal society is supposed to be based on in their
own writings, what they have memorialized and how they're supposed to function, they're
not doing any of it, very little, if not any of it.
So that would put them clearly, the legal society, all of them, legal society would
be law enforcement, attorneys, judges, all the way up, legislature, all that.
They would be in the category of a prankster, right?
Now, this is which is interesting, because the reason I bring them up is because of them
being the legal society is because they're the ones that procure the penalty, which is
what motivates the order, because people are not motivated to do the right thing.
They behave generally in a certain way or ways, because if they didn't, they would be
penalized, right?
So you have a society that's motivated by penalty.
And this is, again, tied in pretty much directly with the legal society, which is not
based on what they're supposed to be based on.
And this is in their own writings, right?
So that means that the legal society, then, they're just pranking, right?
And this is, again, going across the medical community.
You know, I mean, it's very simple to see that if you look at what's called the human
body, the state of affairs today regarding health and medicine is a very good testament
to the robustness of the human body.
If you look at the level of quality that the quote, unquote, scientific and medical society
is inflicting, you know, their medicine, let's say, and techniques that are being inflicted
upon the society as quote, unquote, health care, right, is a testament to how robust
the human body is.
You know, there was an interesting study.
And by the way, they're pranksters also.
You know, so you can actually research the medical society and how they work.
But there was an interesting study, by the way, regarding socialized medicine.
The doctors are typically unionized.
And when they go on strike, a lady did a study quite a few years ago, and she noticed
that when in countries where doctors had gone on strike, the morgues were empty.
People stopped dying.
I found that to be quite interesting or frightening statistic.
And by the way, speaking of people dying, there's a lot of that being used in the media
for sympathy calls.
Yes, it's very sad when people die.
But right now, the number, of course, is very conservative.
But there's over 1,000 people per day directly killed by the medical establishment through
sheer negligence.
Another 1,000 by accident and another 1,000 from the pharmaceutical.
So you have roughly 3,000 people per day in the U.S., what's called America, being
outwardly, we use the M word, maybe not, killed by the medical society.
That's almost a million a year.
And no one is, well, I shouldn't say no one, but where's the outrage?
None at all.
That's 1 million people a year, folks.
And that's very conservative.
The actual official number is three quarter of a million.
And we know what official numbers are meant for.
So right now, just to kind of recap on this thought, because
basically, if we were to leave Earth right now and go and explain what's going on here
somewhere else, we have to leave ourselves out of it and be objective.
And essentially, all you have to do is say it's basically a society of greedy and gluttonous
people ruled by small subgroups of pranksters.
Now, why do I say people are greedy and gluttony?
Not all of them, but the majority are.
If they did understand how the money system worked and the legal system did what they
were supposed to do, you wouldn't really be considering things as being expensive because
you would go to the store and buy your flour and butter and egg and you would sign the
name that was given to you.
That is an authorized signature behind the credit line.
And you would take your stuff and walk out.
That's it.
And this would be the same with all of your utilities.
If you need a car, if you need clothes, you need a house.
All you got to do, sign the name.
Typically, when I'm out in public and I see people set up stands to raise charities for
different causes, and I stop and I say, OK, what are you doing?
This is, oh, we're raising money for this and such and such group of people.
And I'm like, are their hands broken?
Why are you out here asking for notes?
Are their hands broken?
What does that have to do with anything?
So can't they sign?
All they have to do is sign the name on a piece of paper.
That's why, folks, that if you know any investment banksters, if they're driving down the road
in their limousine, let's say in a limousine, and someone writes a name on a bubble gum
wrapper and throws it on the ground, he promptly tells the chauffeur to stop, pulls over, picks
up the bubble gum wrapper with the signature on it, and can use that as money.
You can't, but they can.
Why?
Because they're pranksters.
And this is a fact, and this is the truth about being on this planet right now.
So this has to do with the religious societies as well.
All of them, not some of them.
Everyone in every religious society that is part of that society that administers any
religion, whether it's a temple, a synagogue, or a church, is engaging in pranksterism.
Yes, they are.
Sorry about that.
You may not like that.
Now, those that are being pranked, by the way, are very, very confused.
And the best that they can do is attain a level of rationale that states, well, I'm
doing it because everyone else is doing it, or we're doing it because this is how the
system works, or, or, or.
But never can address what's going on directly.
And one of the things, since we brought up the religious society last, it's funny how
an alternative in mainstream media, or even in public, you will hear people professing
a very strong religious faith, but they're extremely concerned about the politicians.
Like the politicians are going to make things better or worse.
But yet they believe, oh, so they've abandoned their God for a politician.
Very interesting.
I just listen to these things, and I find it to be, again, shocking and appalling.
But nonetheless, if you have a common type of reference and think commonly, you will
find what's being said here shocking and appalling, if you understand it.
That's the other thing I wanted to state.
During the week, I get some people trying to communicate and saying, hey, here's a link.
This guy's saying exactly what you're saying.
And I, well, you know, I try to be courteous and I go and look at the link or whatever
it is, and it has nothing to do with what I'm saying.
So that pretty much tells me still a great majority of the people out there are not listening
to what's being said.
But nonetheless, we know we have got at least four or five listeners that do listen.
So that's, that's something that might be worth doing an internet radio show or not.
I don't know.
I may not be very efficient, but would you think we have more than four or five listeners,
Seth, at this point?
Perhaps not.
But nonetheless, this is the situation about being objective.
And perhaps you're muted.
Were you there?
I was muted.
Yeah, I believe that we have probably at least a handful.
And that's and I don't need any reason to have the conversation.
But having, you know, four or five people that would like to listen in to the conversation
is motivation enough to broadcast it.
So, yeah.
Yeah, I think that's quite enough out of seven billion.
That's pretty good number.
Only four or five.
That would put it in the point zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, one more zero, I think
zero percent in terms of the quality, which is very good.
I think it's a pretty good, pretty good odds for if there were four or five people that
get it out of seven billion, that is actually quite a success, I believe.
It's better than none.
So that's the optimism.
But nonetheless, folks, there's a lot of stuff going on that you will encounter, whether
it's one form of media or another.
And be sure to discern what you're listening to.
Be sure to discern even what you're perceiving or thinking.
And you will find that typically you have the two sides.
You have, there's some authority or some subject matter that is supposed to be based
on something, right?
And the authority would be either the host or the, depending on what society the subject
matter might be attached to, you usually might get a professional or an expert in that society.
Learn to discern what's being said and try to gravitate or even rush to see what is based
on and if what they're telling you is actually based on what they're saying it is or if it
even exists in the real world, right?
That's why I pretty much say there is no economic commentator publicly right now that is saying
anything worth a can of beans or actually shouldn't put down a can of beans.
They're actually, I should say, how about all economic commentators at this point are
coprofagos?
Anyway, so at this point, because this is a very common thing to hear people concerned
about the economy.
There's another thing that's going on right now in the States regarding some kind of a
presidential election, which I'd never get into and don't want to get into because.
Melodrama.
Well, in order to be a president of what, right?
And that what no longer exists.
So the whole point is moot, but nonetheless, it's melodrama.
This is a level of imbecilism or moronism or whatever you want to call it that is way
below worth discussion at this point.
The leaders of the people, by the way, are always discussed, but the patron deity that's
behind the country is never discussed, which is very interesting.
And this is just the way things are done on Earth.
It doesn't matter if you believe in it or not.
If you do a little bit of research, you will find there is always a patron or matron deity
behind a country.
And there's a lot more going on to that, folks.
And that's where you get your law from, by the way.
It's from your god.
And if you look at the Western world, they've revived the goddess religion.
Someone recently wanted to discuss justice and they're being very specific about it.
And I said, well, first of all, before you start trying to comprehend what that means
or what it is, the easiest way to comprehend it is to actually state that what you are
talking about, justice, is nothing more, nothing less than one of the revived goddess religions.
It's a revival of a goddess religion.
So the question here would be then, why go into justice very deeply when you are not
familiar with what goddess religions are based on or how they functioned in the past?
So one of the things that I advise this individual is, instead of getting hung up on what justice
is and how it is indeed a goddess religion, is start researching the ancient goddess religions
and how they operated.
And you will find out it was not positive for those that partook in it.
So these are, again, when you hear a certain subject, whether it's the shape of the earth
or various societies or various matters, go and see what it's based on.
And first of all, see, can it be rationalized within your practical experience?
You know, that's why we like to poke fun and be sarcastic about what is caused, what is
typically blamed on being the cause of the common cold or diseases in wintertime
are these little critters.
And we know that these little critters go dormant when it's cold.
So how can they actually be the cause?
So it doesn't make these very simple way of looking at it, not oversimplifying,
but simple and rational and objective.
And this is how one might consider, not necessarily deal with the pranksters,
because you typically want to avoid the pranksters.
Right. You know, all of these professionals, if you can, that's not advice,
because most people feel kind of like you just pulled the rug from under their feet.
But if you keep in the back of the head or the mind that all of these professionals,
all of them, bar none, are acting in a pranking capacity, whether they're religious society,
legal society, scientific, medical, political society, on and on and on,
they are acting on a prankster level.
And it's very easy to see that they're pranking by just doing a little bit of cursory inquiry
into what they're supposed to be doing from their own reference works.
You will see that they have abandoned
and are operating through some kind of custom that's accepted.
So, yeah.
Absolutely. I'd like to remind everyone that you can find us on the internet at
Uncommonradio.com.
You can find a contact email, anything of that nature there.
You are listening to us here on American Freedom Radio at Americanfreedomradio.com.
Currently, they're listener supported as well, could use your support.
So, if you'd like to help them keep broadcasting,
nothing else for the sake of this program, you can do that at Americanfreedomradio.com.
And if you would like to get into contact with a Greek or myself for any reason,
clarity on a topic or anything like that, you're welcome to email us
and at the email you'll find it on Uncommonradio.com.
Now, one thing, by the way, we're still getting comments on doing a show on water.
Now, what we've, I wouldn't say every time, but very often bring up the concept of water.
And these are the two most important things, keep it in the dark and keep it cool.
And yes, we will do a show on water, just have an organized one as it should be.
But we tend to bring up several things repeatedly on the uncommon sense.
And maybe if we keep repeating that people should keep water cool and out of the light,
if they actually start doing it and experiencing the increase in quality,
then when a water show is done, there'll be even more to connect to
because they've already had some practice.
You see, that's one way of thinking of it.
But the water show will be coming, Seth, soon hopefully.
And also we're threatening a recap of all of the things that were discussed or most of the things
and filling in some of the blanks on the previous sonic experience that was done on this
radio station, let's say.
So again, for those that have been requesting the water show, remember, keep it cool.
39 degrees Fahrenheit or 4 degrees Celsius is optimum and keep it in the dark.
And again, facetiously and sarcastically to say that's why when you go to the shop to buy water,
they always have it in a clear bottle in room temperature, which is contrary to what it should be.
So what you will discover by keeping water in the dark
and keeping it cool is that its quality will raise on its own.
And then we will discuss, well, we've also discussed,
the shape of the container is important as well.
Ovoid, meaning not square, even something that resembles what you'd find in nature.
If you notice that all stagnant fluids or fluids that are not flowing in and out
in all of nature take on this ovoid shape, meaning ovoid like egg type of shape,
not extremely archetypal to the egg, let's say.
Sometimes it's more elongated.
Sometimes it's more squat and flat and less egg-shaped, but nonetheless, typically egg-shaped,
meaning spherical somewhat, not elliptical somewhat, but egg-shaped,
meaning one end is slightly more curved than the other.
Now, someone asked me why, why not an ellipse?
Now, what's interesting is that when you have an egg shape,
there is an internal reflection that creates an instability that promotes movement
without putting energy into the system.
And someone asked me to give an example of that.
And I went through the three typical shapes.
One would be the sphere.
The other one would be the elliptoid, which would have more points,
like a football, let's say, an American football, and then the egg shape.
Now, when you have a sphere, the distance to the center is equal all around.
And if there's any motion, it comes to rest very quickly, and you get stagnation.
When you have something elliptoid, where the two ends are slightly at a point,
but are equal in geometric form, when there's any movement, yes,
there's an unequal distance from the pointed ends to the center.
So it will promote a little more movement.
But because the ends of the elliptoid shape are symmetrical,
it will find stagnation again, and it will come to an end and a stop.
But when you have an egg-shaped or ovoid shape,
where one end is slightly pointier than the other,
where there is a slight bit of movement,
when it moves to the slightly pointier end,
it will contract more than when it moves to the slightly less pointy end, let's say.
And the center of these two dissimilar curved ends are not equal.
And because of that, when the fluid will move from one end to the other,
not only are they dissimilar in shape,
but they're dissimilar in distance from the center,
it promotes a consistent movement of the fluid.
So there you go.
There's a long-winded explanation why the ovoid shape.
There's a question here also, the material that it's made of.
A material is interesting.
Now, depending on what you're looking to do.
Typically, avoid metal.
If you're going to have metal, it should be a noble metal,
silver, pewter, or semi-noble.
Copper, perhaps, could be avoided because of oxidation.
Glass is good.
Wood is good.
Terracotta is good.
Porcelain is good.
Polyethylene might be okay in plastic, polypropylene,
but not polycarbonate and not chlorinated plastics like PVC.
Those are to be avoided.
I tend to avoid plastics if possible.
So stone, glass, noble metals are fine.
Glass would probably be the easiest.
Now, the material does have an effect on the water on charging and discharging.
Here's an example.
You could take your mind and apply it to this example regarding water.
If you have crops, for example, and there is a heat wave coming,
and you know it might damage the crops,
the best way to inhibit some of that heat wave to the crop would be to spray
water on the crop through a copper nozzle, perhaps copper and silver combination.
That will tend to lend the water to have more of a cooling effect.
Now, let's say you have a crop and there's going to be a freeze.
You might want to spray the crop with water to prevent them from freezing
with an iron nozzle.
When you run water through something that has an iron nozzle,
it will tend to give the water a quality of a warming effect, right?
Let's just think about that for a moment.
And I've actually suggested this to people and it has worked both times.
And if we're going to raise the quality of water and keep it stored cool and in the dark,
I would suggest avoiding any type of ferrites-based material, including stainless steel,
albeit it being chemically neutral or chemically viable to not oxidize, let's say,
or they say stainless steel, you know, is a very good material for these reasons.
It still is a ferrite-based material.
And what's interesting about that,
there's a big fad that started maybe two decades ago
by people carrying little water bottles around.
And then there was a big fad about having your own little personal water container.
There were many of them that were made of stainless steel that people carry around.
And I've gotten many reports that they went to plastics because they noticed
that there was a bacteria or mold developing in the stainless steel that didn't on the plastics.
And I told them why.
And they were kind of befuddled by it because it has nothing to do with it degrading or decomposing.
It's the very presence of the iron that promotes that type of growth.
So nonetheless, things to be considered.
And these are very subtle.
I would say, hmm, okay.
Subtle meaning subtle, the effect and the outcome is not subtle,
but the application might be subtle.
You see, there's a lot of discussion on water,
and it sounds very technical and very far out there about structuring water
and all these other things.
But I can assure the listenership that water is one of the least understood materials
that man has ever interacted with, albeit one of the most significant.
So I think we included a few more things this time.
I think every time just including a little bit more about water
so people that are interested can proceed.
And by the way, there's nothing wrong with having interest.
I do get some feedback, by the way, about a lot of the quackery that's out there.
Yes, I'm calling them quacks.
There's a lot of people discussing water.
They've got...
I'm not going to give specifics or names or what's irrelevant,
because, again, if water is going to be discussed,
I've heard and been sent links to YouTubes and other things
about hours and hours of people discussing this type of fantastic water.
And not once, not once, do most of them ever state it should be kept cool and in the dark.
Right away, there's an agenda in there that I find extremely distasteful.
So because they're missing the most basics.
So if you've missed the most basics, the rest of it is just quackery.
And sorry, folks.
We tend to be polite and kind, but sometimes using the term like quackery
or moron or imbecile is too accurate to not use.
So at this point, learn to keep the water cool.
Learn to keep it in the dark.
If you can seek out a ovoid-shaped container, you will notice a rise in the quality of the water.
And like Seth had once mentioned, perhaps discussing the health benefits,
which are going to be very interesting as well.
So we'll figure out somehow how to do a two-hour strictly water conversation
in the near future, perhaps, Seth.
Yeah, absolutely.
The health, it's makeup, what it's made of, what can be done with it.
Water's very useful, not only to, I mean, it's key to the existence of surface dwelling,
earth and evidence like ourselves, but it's also very useful in other things as well.
So, and just not, there's not the comprehension.
No, and the problem with it, and it is a serious problem, by the way,
is that the infrastructure that's been enabled and put throughout the planet
in most cosmopolitan industrial areas, places that have running water, let's say,
they're using, they're moving water in the opposite way that it should be moved,
through straight pipes and putting chemicals in it to prevent the rise of pathogens.
It's the opposite direction because, just because you're putting antibacterial chemicals in water,
it doesn't mean that you're giving rise to a classification of bacteria
that you're not familiar with and other things.
So, and also moving them, moving water in straight ditches, straight pipes,
straight canals, straight tubes is basically a straight jacket for the water.
And if you have someone that is fairly sane,
and you put them in a straight jacket for long enough, they become fairly insane.
So, maybe we should call it the insane water that people are partaking in,
meaning not healthy itself.
Yes, very accurate.
Yeah. So, the movement of water is very different also from the storage of water
and handling of water, which tends to be more static.
You know, most people that engage in water,
dealing with water for, let's say, consumption and other things,
it's in some static form, unless you're washing dishes or taking a shower or whatever.
But when you're seeking out quality water,
typically it would be in some form of bottle or container.
And that's what we're addressing at this point.
It gets a little more complex to address the moving water
because that involves modifying infrastructure and things like that,
albeit to a home or plumbing or other things.
And also, I have much experience with devices that can be made or acquired,
but I don't promote them as such.
I'm not, quote unquote, in the business of doing that publicly.
So, that is another discussion, maybe sometime in the future.
Maybe someone might want to do that because we are working with, let's say, we,
whoever the we is, with ways of dealing with water that are quite unique and quite effective
and have not made it available on these public sonic expressions or shows and things like that.
Just giving people the ability or knowledge to do what they can do
with what they have, I think, is more effective at this point.
So, with that said, being effective, folks,
if you would like to contact us, it's at www.uncommonradio.com.
And you're listening to us on Americanfreedomradio.com.
And again, if you folks find it within your avail
and would like to afford to donate to AFR, please do so.
And then again, here we go, another two hours of Uncommon Sense.
We will see you folks in about a week.
Thanks, Seth.
Yeah, thank you.
It's a pleasure.
And yeah, we'll be back in about seven days.
Be well, everyone.