Start record.
Start broadcast.
Welcome to Uncommon Sense with the Greek and Seth Michael.
How are you doing, Greek?
Hey, doing great.
Welcome, everyone.
And here we are again.
Let's do some more Uncommon Sense.
Absolutely.
So jumping, just kind of jumping right into it,
the Greek shared a communiqué with me,
an email that he'd received from a listener that was,
I didn't have the chance to,
it was actually about a 26-page document,
and I've not had a chance to get through all of it,
but what I was able to peruse earlier today
while I was drinking some coffee was very interesting
and brought up a lot of subjects that we have discussed
in varying depths over the last two or three years.
And so I thought that perhaps we could use that,
if not as specific bullet points,
but as kind of a springboard into what we'd like to talk about today.
And the letter opened with the first few points
were having to do with gods, essentially, with the gods
and the history behind how they are perceived today
and how they are interacted with, I guess, would be a way of stating it.
But if I can pull that,
I don't have the document right here in front of me.
I'm going to pull that up so I can address it specifically.
Seth, just a quick note.
I'm at the UStream site, and it seems pretty blank.
In other words, I can't get it to play,
and I got a couple of messages.
Are we broadcasting?
So maybe it's something to consider.
Okay.
It says I've got the broadcast going.
It says we have six viewers.
I just asked in chat to clarify, make sure that it's going out.
So if you can hear us, there will be probably 20 to 30-second delay,
I imagine, for UStream.
Maybe not quite that pronounced, but we are going to find out.
Is the audio live?
Yep, we're good.
Just did a check.
We're good.
All right.
Wonderful.
So, yeah, this is Uncommon Sense with the Greek and Seth.
You can find the webpage, which is essentially just a business card.
Not really a business card, but a calling card.
And that's at uncommonradio.com.
And, yeah.
Also, Seth, I shared the document with you because it was partially,
if not indirectly, addressed to you as well, or directly, I guess, somewhat.
And I think it's interesting as a bullet point just to go back to the document
that you mentioned.
But there's many things to be discussed every time we get together.
I think this might be the third or fourth time, perhaps,
sans the technical difficulties we do consider this might be maybe number four,
perhaps.
I just want to throw in that what we're trying to do is a sonic project,
and what makes it uncommon is itself being uncommon.
All right.
What does that mean?
Well, right now when people are going to any, let's say,
topically labeled forum, institution, or even man or woman for a particular genre
of information, they're getting the opposite or none of it.
If you go to electrical school, you learn nothing about electricity.
You go to divinity school, you learn nothing about the Bible.
You go to medical school, you learn nothing about the body.
You go to science school, you learn nothing about science.
So what's going on, right?
That's, I guess, what I always like to preface as the views here
and also the strangeness about it not being recorded, perhaps,
and bring your own recorder.
But this one might be.
But I just want to interject this is uncommon,
and it's uncommon in itself as well because we don't really want to tell anyone
anything.
We just want to share certain discoveries in a sonic way that maybe might
stimulate some thought or stimulate some perception.
Absolutely.
I've actually said many times over the last few years that if I have any goal
or agenda in this, other than the fact that I just enjoy the conversation,
if we can get anyone out there listening to think in a way that is just a little
bit different or a lot bit different than what is common,
then that is something I would, I don't know if take pride in is the right word,
but something that would further my enjoyment of the conversation,
at the very least.
Yeah, it's just a way of being set apart.
You brought up some of the points that you might want to bring forward on the
document, but before maybe I want to share something.
I had a chat.
I've been going around certain people inviting me to have discussion with,
and this one person was befuddled in the scriptural text of,
I'm going to paraphrase here,
it's not what goes into someone's mouth that defiles them,
but what comes out that defiles them.
You've heard of that cliché sort of phrase.
And I've brought it up in cliché form because just about any time I've ever heard
anything biblical being mentioned, it's not accurate.
Sorry, folks.
And I didn't say everything, but just about everything might as well.
What's interesting about that verse, when you look at it,
it doesn't say that at all.
The word that's being used to defile is the prefix koiné or kinoiné.
Whenever you see that k-o-i-n prefix or part of a word, it means common.
And that's where you have like koiné, Greek, was the lingua franca of the age
and things that are, let's say, common is the k-o-i,
either prefix or mid-root part of the word.
And even in Strongstein's Concordance, he says, well, it means common.
It means to defile.
But what's interesting, being a concordance, it's not a defining.
Concordance just means what everyone agrees on it meaning.
And this agreement actually came from, it's in Matthew, by the way, 1511, I believe.
And this agreement and perception has come from the following verse,
which was after this was said, the Pharisees were very insulted or offended.
So it makes more sense, even in context, because someone being a high-level priesthood
or an entitled class, if they're told that they're common, indirectly or directly,
feel offended where the common man wouldn't.
So it's quite interesting when we look at even something as simple as the clichés
that are thrown out into society.
And what's interesting about this dialogue that I had with this person in chat
was they were pondering, how can that be?
How can something defile you that way?
And I'm saying you missed the point.
It doesn't say defiled.
So now your whole struggle with it is an illusion.
Isn't that interesting?
So a parable to that or a comparison would be, you know how they say electricity is like
electrons going down a wire?
You know, and everyone kind of agrees on that concordantly.
But I'm telling you, I've done so many experiments with a live wire,
where I've cut the wire with a dustpan in hand and a microscope,
and I still haven't found any electrons flowing.
And just such a simple method to test their crap, right?
Unfortunately, with certain things that have many layers,
where you have different conveyance of translation and language,
and even within the same tongue you have shop talk, right?
A technical language that most people are not privy of.
There's a conveyance that creates distortion and changes the meaning so much
that now the people are off track.
So I just want to bring up, these are the things we like to discuss.
Would you think that might be another way to describe what we're trying to do?
Certainly.
Yeah, absolutely.
And by the way, I hear a background, maybe a speaker or something on your end,
but since we're kind of like brought up one of the first bullet points
was the discussion of the gods,
will we bring up any kind of a topic regarding the gods?
The first thing that maybe should be evoked in one's mind is that
we're talking about formative beings,
things that come before, right?
Because even in the cliche form of the gods make things or made everything, right?
So we're looking at things that are being made.
That's what they do.
And what's interesting, just as a common thought,
you ever notice when things are being made they're dirty?
Like if you're machining a whole bunch of metal,
even when the product, even though when you've succeeded,
according to specification,
you've got to clean all the cutting fluid and chips off of it?
Right, absolutely.
Or if you're doing pottery, the pot is finished.
I'm not talking about it being completely fired up and all that,
but when it's finished there's like clay being slung everywhere and it's kind of messy.
Or when you're growing stuff in the garden and you pull it out,
it's kind of full of dirt.
When you paint a room, it gets cut.
You see my point?
Oh, yes.
Isn't it interesting?
Isn't it interesting how when, quote-unquote,
active creation or bringing forth is taking place or has taken place,
there is a certain element that has to be cleaned up?
What's called, let's say, the afterbirth when a woman bears a child?
First thing they do is start cleaning the baby.
Isn't it interesting?
You know, baking a cake.
I mean, it's interesting how formative activities in the material world
create a situation that needs to be cleaned up.
Think about that.
I think this is kind of the first time we've brought this up.
Boy, we're full of surprises sometimes, but think about that for a moment, folks.
Could it be that this epoch of man, quote-unquote, being created,
socially as well, is going to render some form of cleaning in the near future?
So just think about it.
You know, it's just when we think about these formative actions in the material sense.
Absolutely.
You see how much discussion?
Yeah, go ahead.
I managed to pull it all up.
I'm ready to roll with that.
There was one thing immediately that came to mind when I was reading this.
I'm just going to read the first paragraph here.
Also, we want to keep it anonymous as well.
Yeah, absolutely.
You can just do it loosely.
Okay, that's fine.
Okay, this is basically the question of the gods and the many myriad interdimensional beings
that share our world, if not our dimension,
as someone who has had the occasional paranormal experience, et cetera.
And what immediately came to mind is the concept and the terms dimension and interdimensional,
while being useful perhaps for thinking about things, is really not an accurate way of describing it
because dimension is just space.
There's only one dimension.
Exactly.
You have the seen and the unseen, the tangible and the intangible.
So it's a way of describing what is present but unseen, or what is present but it's intangible.
The very purpose of such a condition existing has brought forth the necessity of communication
and memorialization.
It's no different than having your great-great-great-great-great-great-great grandfather's diary.
The reason why I said great-great-great-great-great-great is because he's almost physically immaterial at this point.
Because if it's just your great-grandfather, some people might just want to dig him up anyway.
But I mean like someone that you had found, you had interest in, that lived so long
that they don't exist in the material sense at all.
The only thing that's left is a good memorialized communication.
Even in the pagan sense, or when I say pagan meaning let's say a lower level sense,
they're always trying to do what? Communicate.
Some form of communication.
Or even in the non-pagan way, when you get to the more informed way of how the world works,
there's still a communication. It's called prayer.
Or manifesting certain actions that show yourself.
Absolutely.
So it's all about communication.
And that's how it works with electricity as well.
And other things that are not tangible until they become tangible.
Electricity for the most part is unseen other than its results, if it's being done correctly.
Yeah.
You don't see the electrons doing what they say they do.
And as a matter of fact, what do you think people are going to do when they discover there's no such thing as an electron?
Not even close.
It's going to be interesting.
I always like to...
If you want to learn about this field, by the way, this is not a diversion.
This is to make a point about electricity in your conventional institutions.
It doesn't matter if they're Ivy League or 8th grade.
Well, let's say in universities.
There's two places where you learn about electricity.
One is the physics department.
The other is the electrical engineering department.
They usually cross the street of each other.
If you go to the electrical engineering department, they focus on the positive part of the pole, as in electricity being a positive negative phenomenon.
And the ground, the negative is sent to ground as common ground.
So you could put a plus one on the electrical engineering building.
If you go across the street to the physics building, they focus on the negative polar phenomenon of electricity.
And the positive is just marked as positive or source.
So you could put a negative one on the physics building.
So when you go to university, any university, what you're going to learn about electricity is what you get when you put minus one and plus one together.
Seth, what do we get?
Minus one and plus one together, that's nothing.
You got it.
And that's what exactly what you're going to get at university when you go to study electricity.
Plug it into the wall.
Yeah, plug it into the wall.
Don't ask questions.
I had once an academic.
I was trying to explain that an electrical generator doesn't generate electricity any more than a water pump generates water.
You know what he actually said?
This is a guy with tenure now.
This is a guy that your children, people who are out there are spending tens of thousands, right?
You're being mocked.
But anyway, he said there's no such thing as energy.
It's electrons moving down the wire.
You know, it's like it's such a cosmic joke.
I think when the gods want to play a joke on humanity, they get the most elevated people in any field and they place a total idiot or complete moron in that field, regardless of what field.
The least among you.
Yes, exactly.
And just to prove how blind.
And how undiscerning the people are.
They go along with it.
And there was an interesting story about the emperor has no clothes.
And it was a child that pointed it out, isn't it?
Absolutely.
They're OK.
So dimensions.
Would the encountering of apparitions and the like mean that we've encountered one of these gods?
Not necessarily.
What's interesting about the gods is you really don't know unless you're well informed and communicating.
There's something written about testing them.
Are you of such or you of the other or you of this or you of that?
Absolutely.
Well, and there's a part the rest of the hierarchy as well.
Even those entities that are nonphysical, at least in the sense that we think of in the commonplace physical that are, you know, in any sort of hierarchical organization that we have reference to on Earth.
It's not just, you know, one tier.
There are several tiers.
So there's the lower, the lower beings, the imps, spirits that would be called demons.
Colloquially, I don't I don't like using that word because the connotation that we have with it in English is just inaccurate.
Comes from the Latin, you know, Damon, which is just a word for spirit.
It is one that we have through through tradition.
We have demonized the word, as it were.
So, you know, by the way, I was on a discussion recently.
It was actually a public one that was on air and there were maybe half a dozen people there.
And they all admitted with their own volition that knowledge and information has nothing to do with anything.
It's your intent.
Could you believe?
I just wanted to bring this in here because this discussion gets very touchy because how many people say, I don't believe that I am quite happy with what I believe.
And there's one thing to be able to drag out something tangible and material.
Post discussion to confirm or provide as evidence.
But you're not going to necessarily pull a God out of your hat to show someone, you know what I mean?
Right.
So they've taken the high ground regarding really any topic that information and knowledge has nothing to do with anything.
It's strictly what your intent or belief is.
This is how people are rolling in public, folks.
Oh, there are people making thousands and tens and thousands and hundreds of thousands of dollars getting up in front of large groups and telling people that very thing.
The other comment was when I brought up some things that anyone could access, you know, the soul, the spirit, reincarnation, things like that.
They didn't want to acknowledge what was being said.
They just wanted to acknowledge that.
How can all these people be fooled?
The reason why we say it is this way, because all these other people are saying it.
Right.
And and again, like in terms of the alternative media, it's the same thing.
Have you ever noticed TV ads?
Millions have been sold and everyone's like, oh, good.
They sold millions of them.
You know, must be good because everybody's buying into it.
It's kind of like another analogy.
I went to this or natural store.
I wanted to get some spray on insect repellent for some people complaining about bugs.
And of course, it's the way they eat that bug.
Anyway.
So I asked the lady, you know, where the insect repellent is.
And can she please guide me through?
Because I didn't want to sit there and read everything.
And she goes, this is the one that everybody buys.
And I said, oh, I don't want that one then.
And she goes, what do you mean?
I said, have you met everybody yet?
And have you met the general people?
Do you are you paying attention who your customers are?
I don't want what they want.
I want something more set apart.
You see, I want something just because everyone is getting it.
You see the point here?
I immediately reject it.
Based on statistical information.
Not because what everyone wants may not be good.
Because everyone wants to breathe air.
I'm not going to say I'll breathe water instead.
Right.
But categorically, it's pretty safe to reject it if the public has accepted it.
And even the private in many cases.
It's pretty safe, but you have to discern it again.
You see.
What brings them, these apparitions referred to, to our realm?
A magical call, a personal visit of their own accord with an agenda.
And I would, again, that's the whole question.
But I would say the idea of bringing them to our realm.
Is sort of a miscommunication or a misnomer.
There's several problems with that.
We're simply because what evidence does anyone have that it's our realm?
But that's the language that man will develop.
This is not a criticism on who wrote it at all.
This is typical.
I mean.
Yeah, absolutely.
And if the author is listening, please don't take it as that.
This is just the way that we address language.
Well, that's why I would suggest maybe just being not adhering to the literal message.
But just the general gist of it.
Because there's so much.
Even with a wheel that's like loose and wobbly and semi-flat.
You'll still get to where you're going.
Is the point.
Okay, so let me rephrase this question then.
What would cause these non-physical entities to interact with us on a personal level?
Nothing and everything.
It's not up to us.
And a lot of these interesting aspects are well worth thinking about.
But a lot of the, let's say, what might seem more mechanical or technical aspects with interacting with the gods.
Sorry, folks.
I hate to say it.
But you lack the maturity to do so.
We're talking about beings that have relatively, you know, using the colloquial term IQ of 2 million plus.
Even their most simplest communication.
They don't do anything in futility, by the way.
Anything that even man sees as being befuddled by is their baby talk.
We are given enough information about the gods.
And this is a general brush statement which is fairly accurate.
We are given information about the gods and evidence of them for simple reasons such as you don't have to wonder.
Right?
And also you've been told certain things.
So you're without excuse.
And also given we're made privy of the gods and their ways so we can actually have an advantage over those who don't.
When I say we, it's whoever we is.
And that goes both for doing harm and for doing good.
Typically the human element, this might be a little off the question, that wants to manifest a lot of the things that the gods are instructing or capable of giving are doing it from malevolent purposes.
Just about across the board.
The benevolent side of it, if you look at the benevolent side of these communications, it basically tells you to set yourself apart and do nothing.
Sorry.
You know, in other words, within the group at large.
Right.
The benevolent side seems to be ever present.
Not something that has to be coaxed.
Worked.
Yeah.
Like doesn't have to.
It's.
Like you do.
Yeah.
The actual.
All the religions of the world.
All of them.
Shall we say it again?
Every denomination of every religion is 150 percent malevolent.
Why did I say 150 percent?
Because 100 percent for the exacting fact and truth about them and 50 percent thrown in for what they're going to do tomorrow or the next day, which we don't know yet.
But that's pretty easy to see with a little bit of discernment.
And when I say easy, meaning all you got to do is look at what something is based on.
Period.
Doesn't matter if it's a religion, if it's money, if it's a story that's supposed to be about something that is accessibly physically accessible, about a communication.
If it's baseless, unfounded or fiat, well, they're fixing on doing something that ain't very good.
And the only way.
Yeah.
The only way you could succeed with fixing on doing something bad.
Let's keep it simple.
As always, by presenting it as something as being good.
Absolutely.
With fail safes, with fail safes built in, like plausible deniability, all this other stuff.
Very simple.
You know.
Yeah.
Question.
I'm not going to read it anymore, but the question comes up on the word deities and referring to these entities as the specifically the gods and that deities just comes from Dios or.
Or dual.
Yeah.
And that's just one of the words that English translates into the word God or God's deities.
You know, plural would be gods.
The phrase adios in Spanish to come to mind.
Yeah.
Well, what's interesting about this is we've said publicly years ago, Seth, when I say years more than two or three, perhaps that the society at large, every culture and all people will have this urge to gain.
Interest in this realm, the realm of the gods and spiritual things, let's say, of the mind.
But you can see an increased discussion as a product of the interest.
It'll be, you know, the everyday discussion all the way to Hollywood, to literary art, whatever government.
But one thing we discussed years ago is opposing or within this interest, let's say, is the lack of still the lack of clarity and accuracy.
But that's not the important part.
The important part is that there is a focus on that topic or this topic.
We brought this up years ago, and we could see now how more people are catching on to whether it's the large institutions or just the man on the street or woman on the street.
There's an interest in this subject, but all in all, it'll be very still inaccurate and misplaced.
And that's pretty easy to discuss why when you actually look about what's written about this time and what's called prophecies and things like that.
So, yeah, I just want to bring that up as well.
So this is sort of concordant with the times what we're discussing right now.
Absolutely.
And in these deities and gods have been referred to in many different ways throughout history and where they are referred to, a lot of it is considered myth.
And in the Western world, we are taught that it is simply allegory and ways that what we see is primitive man describing a natural process or natural processes that would be otherwise indescribable to these primitive minds,
which is not an accurate way of being facetious.
But, well, yeah.
And the irony of it is they're calling electrons after Electra anyway, which is mythological.
So it's in line.
So anyway, absolutely.
I've through my studies, I've come to look at most mythology as simply just a history that's been relatively obscured through language.
One example that you shared with me probably more than a couple of years ago was the instances in myths where you will hear of people being turned to pigs and the connotation there is actually cannibalism.
I mean, where you see read in a myth or a story or history of like a group of people being turned into pigs, it very most likely means that they were slaughtered and consumed.
And what's what's interesting about that is that let's say you brought up the myths.
And we look at what's being handed to us, served on a plate about the myths.
And we start researching, let's say, the literary origins, how these stories have been preserved.
Because if it's just oral, I mean, you can only go back to whoever's alive.
But if it's literary and written, you start looking at how many hands it's changed and the studies that have been done through the years.
And you find that there's some research being done where some of these demagogues and especially through what's called the Age of Heroes before the dynastic reigns of Egypt, for example, you will find that these were kings or personalities that were deified as well.
And it's still being done today.
That's why you have something called idolization of musicians and film stars.
I mean, you know, they even have what a merit show or, you know, Elvis has left the building or something.
You know how this is idolization.
This has been going on for a very long time.
I mean, could you imagine if there was another four or five hundred or a thousand years?
Isn't it possible that the very existence of a man called Elvis Presley walking the earth can be twisted and turned into a demagogue and some mythological figure who rained lightning down from a microphone or something?
Yeah.
If you believe that there are electrons running down wires, you'll believe any anyway.
Would you say that?
OK.
Yeah.
And if you feel the apotheosis of George Washington is a painting inside of one of the Capitol domes that comes to mind.
Oh, yeah.
What's next after that?
A hologram of him?
You know, what's that?
And then after the hologram, what are they going to do?
Put some glue and meat and metal together.
You know, this is how humans roll.
Speaking of hologram, that is another concept that is brought up in the in the email.
The question of whether we exist in a holographic simulation, the holographic, you know, coming from the words hologram or holograph.
Holo being the whole link is in holistic.
Yeah.
And, you know, gram or graph being image the whole picture.
So in one way, yes.
And simulation.
Well, you know, what we are experiencing, I would say, is is real colloquially.
But at the same time, whether or not it's a colloquial holographic simulation would be completely and totally based upon your perspective and where you were seeing it from.
Because, you know, to my experience in my, you know, my mind or spirit and the observations that I've I've made, it's very real.
But at the same time, looking if I had, you know, I was looking at it from a higher perspective, be that of number of years or literal, you know, just height that that could be considered differently.
You know, the question, you know, the Matrix films always come to mind when people talk about that, because that's the main premise is a simulation within a simulation almost.
And so looking at the word hologram or holograph like we did, we look at the word Matrix and that word is just womb.
That's that's what that means.
You know, formative, a formative place.
Right.
So the Hollywood of the mind and how such motion pictures and, you know, all media affects the way that we think and bleeds over into the way that we color in things that we don't comprehend completely is is very interesting.
And it's can be difficult to kind of separate thought from the images that have been pumped into our minds.
But it's I think that that's an important thing to do, especially with studying these things, because the things that we're talking about, you know, any of the scriptures and stuff like that, what is presented through any form of media, even in discussion about it's inaccurate.
So, of course, the the images and the stories that are reproduced from these poor versions are lacking in in any sense of veracity.
Yeah, there's there's an objectivity also that you could lay out all the pieces and to say that it's a hologram is lacking.
But if from certain respects where, you know, there's an empirical and ephemeral, you know, the part that can't change and the part that can change.
And we're told that anything can change by the formative forces.
So from that aspect, maybe.
And from another aspect, what's interesting about a hologram is that if you were to tear a hologram up into smaller pieces, the entire images in each small piece can still part of it is preserved.
Right. If you hold it on just the right angle, you still see the whole picture in every fragment.
So there's a fractal nature to it. But I believe that using that term can be applicable.
But it's it's heavily discounting what can be perceived.
And just to throw this out very often, I've said, well, I'm not going to discuss certain things.
I'll just throw those things out just to satisfy some curiosity.
And you just spin off and people could look at it at themselves.
There is a subject of the intangible, not only about the gods, but also like we keep bringing up the nature of electricity.
Well, what's interesting about electricity, for example, what we call electricity or this manifestation.
Rudolf Steiner wrote something about counter space during the early development of electrical engineering.
And which was also this thing called counter space is a space that's counter to space.
So in other words, when you're in counter space, space seems to appear solid.
But material seems to be space when you're in a material world.
The material is solid and the space is just, well, space.
The interaction between these two spaces and they're both quite physical, by the way.
And it's really difficult to imagine the properties of counter space because you have to be able to turn your mind inside out like a sock.
But either way, because we're very materialistic.
The concept of counter space has to be understood before you can actually work with electricity and engineer things.
Before you find out that you made something so big it tends to you can't shut it off or it explodes. Right.
And Charles Proteus Steinmetz is one of the most intelligent engineers that ever lived.
Or I should use that word intelligent, most diligent and fruitful.
It was now hidden in history, by the way.
Einstein wouldn't be worth tying his shoelaces.
Pretty much came up with the concept of the square root of minus one, which is another concept.
I mean, not with the concept of square root of minus one, but to apply it to discerning how we manage counter space manifestations into space, i.e. electricity.
So I just want to throw that in there because the concept of a hologram is very easily received.
But what really is going on, as evidenced by electrical fields and magnetic fields and other things like that, is far more different, not complex.
Because if you can't use eighth grade math to rationalize anything, it's not worth rationalizing, really.
So there are many aspects to this physical world that evidence a non-physical world that predominates in many instances.
So I do like the analogy of the hologram.
But it's an oversimplification, like Gustave Le Bon wrote in his crowd, that now has gotten it away from the meaning so it could be easily accepted.
So I don't know if we cleared anything up or not for anyone, but there's a discussion.
I think that one of these programs in the near or distant future, we may open to call-ins through Skype because that's the easiest way to do it.
But I've done that a lot and that's not what I'm trying to do with our conversations here.
But I know that there are people out there that would like to join us, perhaps, for a little while in discussion.
And that came to mind, so I thought that I would speak it.
Oh, clearly. I do like the input of any kind as well.
Absolutely. Ed, the website UncommonRadio.com does have an email address listed there that you can send us any sort of communication that you would like.
UncommonSenseRadio1 at Gmail.
That's right. UncommonSenseRadio1 at Gmail.com.
Numeric one.
Another thing that is brought up that is certainly in line with the discussion is the concept of external input as dealing with thought, actually.
With the brain as a receiver and a transmitter, not just a closed system, as it were.
And we are, you know, humans are kind of built like trees upside down with our roots, you know, the myriad of nerves, as they call them, and whatnot that make up the brain.
Root ball.
Yeah.
So we're kind of like upside down trees.
Our limbs, you know, our legs and our arms.
And still this concept of, you know, where do thoughts come from?
Some of the obvious things that I think are often missed because they're not really addressed is the super form of those, like communication, listening to people speak, you know, words, television, images.
These things cause us to think in ways that we would not perhaps think if we were not subjected to them.
But beyond that, I think what is being referenced in the question and bringing it up is the more, certainly our physical but intangible inputs that are received.
So where do thoughts come from?
Well, in order to process the thoughts and the input, also you need an operating system.
I like to give that plain example, and that mankind is very different, and we're not animals in that respect.
And I always give the analogy of a dog, a very young puppy being raised by a family of gorillas, then adopted as an adult dog, would act just like a regular dog.
You would not be able to discern that it was raised by apes, where if a very, very young child was raised to adulthood by apes, guess what?
It would be very easy to discern that they were.
Anyway, I've been in public lately, and I've seen what, but anyway, that's another discussion.
So the concept of the operating system and the thought being the program or the file, let's say, being run.
But again, going back to the upside-down plant, this is an ethereal, primal, formative energy approach.
And maybe discussing the nature of plants might be something that can be used allegorically or metaphorically,
simply because it's a very interesting analogy to say that maybe the human body, ethereally or formatively, archetypally, is an upside-down plant,
the brain being the root ball, the limbs are, well, the limbs, and where the seed is and the flower are the sexual organs.
So what's interesting about that is what do you know about plants?
And just to give a discussion I had with a university dendrochronology department, dendro meaning tree, chronology meaning time,
it's actually the number two or number one lab in the world, and they wanted to discuss trees.
And I said, well, you guys are really into trees, and it doesn't seem like you do a lot of describing but no explanation.
And I said, well, you know, I'm not going to ask you.
In my mind I'm thinking I'm going to ask these dummies what a tree is.
These are like high-level university people.
So what I figured instead of like berating them like I do on radio in person, what I did was I said, well, listen,
if you could explain to me how one blade of grass grows, I'd be glad to spend the time that you're asking me with you to look at what you want to present.
And they all went, mom, they all just looked at me, you know, like, can't do that.
Yes, absolutely.
They can't even explain how one blade of grass grows.
They could describe the how but the why, like why does one blade of grass grow?
Now, you can't fault them for their ignorance, but you can, you should, because they're bleeding.
They're parasitical on society at this point, but yes, they are parasitical.
And if you want to know what I mean by that, look up the word parasite and predatory on the people, which I find disgusting.
I'm not saying that they shouldn't exist.
Places of higher learning should exist by all means.
We just actually said that we require that as a species.
But the current condition is, to say the least.
Now, those are the good words.
I'll tell you what I really think of them.
But in a sense, the aspect of approaching them with even an archetype or parallel or anything that might be comparative is completely rejected and refused.
Of course, you know, they're running a religion.
I think we've discussed this before, something that they want people to do.
When I say religion, I mean it loosely.
If you approach any of these people that supposedly hold knowledge in society today and you refuse to bow at their altar, you are quickly shown the door.
Or, if you're wise enough, if you realize there's an altar that they want you to bow to, why hang around and wait for them to hit you in the knees with a baseball bat so you do bow down?
Just go for the door while you can still walk.
So, in essence, a lot of the things that we like to say are not because this is how they are so.
But it's like, why isn't anyone looking at these simple things, at least for the young ones, the young people that we know are so impressionable?
So the concept of looking at the mind, looking at the body, and the plant as being an archetype is quite interesting in itself.
Which, by the way, Seth, we could dedicate the next four hours on just that discussion.
We may not want to do that.
But the concept of being eluded and being distracted by change, in other words, when we discuss things, we take a slice of things that change, right?
Like a photograph, right?
Or when you go to learn about something, you know, a machine, or you're looking about how a car works, you look at a piston.
That's not the piston in action.
It's a slice of it, right?
And it does change as it wears out, and it did have material had to go through change to form a piston.
But I mean that we have gone away from actually being objective about these slices in time, how things do change.
And we figure because they do change, and how they change, we grade them on their significance, right?
So if we look at elements of change and take a slice of reality, like in a still photograph of something moving,
if you were to study the dendric nature, or the branches of a tree, or the root system of a tree as it spreads through soil,
typically not a root ball now, but the actual spreading out, or the capillaries of your eye, or a lightning bolt,
which is I guess described as a Lichtenfield or Lichtenberg pattern, or high voltage sparks, photograph of a high voltage emission,
you'll notice they all share the same geometric forms.
You see? So there's an underlying archetype.
Now, if you want to say that it's just random, that's fine.
But how can something be judged so random, and ha, ha, ha, oh, isn't it funny how it's similar, and not be observed with scrutiny?
You see my point? This is what the academics have failed.
And they will not, by the way.
In your society, currently, you will never get the truth or anything tangible, a tangible explanation out of the academia in this society.
The next society will, quite clearly, because if you didn't, there would be no reason to end this society and start another one, or a continuance of it.
So the interesting part here is just a real simple way to sum it up.
If you look at a high discharge of a high voltage emission through gas, or even across a piece of solid, you know, what we call a lightning strike,
or high voltage discharge, look at how similar it is to the capillaries in your eye, or the roots or branches of a tree.
You see? And that's a good place to start.
And we're talking about not the change, because, well, Greek, how can you say a tree that takes 300 years to grow is the same as a lightning bolt,
which flashes in a tenth of a second, or a second or so.
I'm not saying that.
What I prefaced earlier is that because we've been deluded by the nature of things changing, we don't see the similarity,
but we have the ability to take a slice and freeze frame of all these things and show how they're all the same.
So this is partly the study of how formative things work.
And believe it or not, this is a discussion for the gods.
This is, if you're discussing this with people who are completely descended, have descended into materialism,
they will quickly shift into how things change and show that as the irrelevant point, where, you know, how, again,
how can a 300-year-old tree have anything similar with a tenth of a second lightning strike,
where if you're to eliminate the delusion of change or what you have emphasis you've put on the rate of change
and looked at a freeze frame of it, you would see they're almost identical in archetype form.
In other words, there's a pattern, and this pattern is behind everything.
And not only is this pattern behind everything, it's behind things you don't see and perceive,
and it's being used over and over and over at different rates of change.
It works really, really well.
Yes. And this is the foundation of all discernment, by the way.
In other words, if someone's screaming hateful stuff at you for three seconds or 30 hours, what's the difference?
Stop thinking of how long something is being done for, whether it's good or bad or irrelevant.
It's that it's being done.
And a practical application that I have, I don't know, adopted with that, you know,
just with the considering of where thought comes from,
is that if you are aware of the similarities between, you know, transmission and reception of information
and the interaction of the mind with the physical world, you know, if you're, just as an example,
if you're watching something on a television and you don't like it or don't want to watch it for whatever reason,
you change the channel.
And when you start to have the realization that thoughts are coming in
and they're not, you know, they're not always beneficial.
Some of them are very detrimental to the health of one's mind or one's body.
And you realize that you can metaphorically change the channel.
It's not always quite that easy or simple, but just having the awareness that it's not all coming from within,
that a lot of this is external input and external input that is not tangible.
You still have, you know, the brain is a pretty neat organ for the mind and for the spirits to interact with the physical world.
And in that with, you know, the more that you're aware of how such things work,
the mechanics, specifically those that are, you know, not widely discussed,
it gives one the ability to think better, I guess, or at least differently.
And, you know, almost the ability to change the channel.
The whole process seems to be taken for granted as people do many things.
Some of it is just absolutely taking for granted and being insensitive, like the concept of walking.
Or once you've got it, you never forget.
You know, once you learn to think, you don't forget.
It's kind of like riding a bicycle, right?
There's the aspect of the manipulation of the thought, meaning, you know, using your hand or figuratively of your own thoughts,
understanding that they're streaming in and going out is difficult because it's just simply taken for granted.
Ask a six-month-old why they can't get up and run around the block.
Well, it's because they're still crawling on the rug and they're very happy with learning how to stand and walk.
Or someone who can't ride a bicycle, you see.
But once you learn those things, you don't think about them anymore.
That's the aspect that's being taken for granted and the discernment falls apart because of that, let's call it emotional or spiritual laziness.
And on the other hand, the thoughts are simply like Seth was relating on the television.
Right away, my mind went to the psychotronic aspect, but I don't think you were discussing the psychotronics of it.
You know, subliminal messages and pulse frequencies and things.
You're just discussing the simple suggestion of a thought or concept.
And like the television changing the channel is very much the thought process, again, bringing it forward to the senses,
would be as if you walked into a cafe and you're asked, what would you like to eat?
And you're presented with a menu and you see, you know, chicken sandwich, tuna sandwich, veggie sandwich, salad, soup.
That's exactly what all of our thoughts are like, but it happens so quickly.
And because we take it for the process for granted, we've pretty much fallen into this emotional laziness and in this befuddlement and bewilderment state.
Absolutely.
And yeah, there's a concept also.
The speed of thought, people are instant.
We think very quickly.
And I would say that it's almost better to think slowly and to consider one's thoughts.
Exactly.
Think before you speak.
Absolutely.
So the thought aspect, that will be understood more as we get into other things.
And by the way, there's a lot of, do we want to preface, there's a field called psychiatry or psychology around this, right?
And the PSY means the spirit.
Yeah, study of the spirit.
Yeah, the study of the spirit is what they are.
And by the way, folks, anyone who wants to see one of these guys should have their head examined.
So anyway, and the only purpose these psychos are there, psychiatrists, psychologists, are there to keep you in check.
Because typically when these topics are brought up, it's a threat in modern society.
And even back then, if you actually look at it objectively, the field of psychiatry or psychology is generally brought up in common when someone is being threatened by it.
So it's actually weaponized spiritualism.
Anyway, I just thought I'd throw that in there.
Maybe it sounds creative.
I don't know.
It's like most anything that we come into.
It's a system of government.
It's a system of a religious organization with tenets and scripture that they follow.
It's just a lot of it's very recent.
And what's interesting, what's been brought forward in these fields and the people that have been accredited with it, like Freud and Jung and others,
if you go and actually study what these people that were accredited with these fields were actually studying or trying to bring forth,
is not what the field that is using these men's names is doing anyway.
Freud started off, for example, with the study of electrical impulses in the body.
You notice that when different emotions gave different electrical fields on the skin.
So, I mean, it's just bizarre what's being put forward that what these men were about.
I mean, obviously, they descended into something to be socially acceptable.
If you look at alternative media, you know, forget about it.
Thank you.
I've seen that. I'm good.
Yeah. It's just bizarre. Yeah.
So, again, folks, I mean, where do we...
Seth, you know, I don't know what we stepped into with this Uncommon Sense Radio because it's so bizarre, so sublime to discuss reality from an objective point of view.
It almost feels like you're... you cannot communicate it effectively.
Yeah, well, certainly with difficulty and with complete accuracy, I'd say at this point in time, it's next to impossible.
But with more accuracy than what is common, absolutely.
And I, you know, I think that's what we've stepped into.
Yeah.
Meaning I think that one of the things that mankind or current society across the board has succeeded in is their ability to not communicate
and still get some things done.
If you think about that for a minute.
Yeah, I had no interest in further broadcasting radio or conversations at all until we spoke about doing this together.
So, you know, it's on one level, it's certainly self-serving for me because I find the conversations very edifying, very building and uncommon.
You know, these are conversations that are very uncommon.
It's an aptly titled broadcast.
Something that I did want to jump into just a little bit is health, health.
You know, we spoke last time about a little bit, you know, scratching the surface, as it were, is health.
And I had one one specific thing I wanted to talk to you about.
And I was going to bring it up privately, but it's nothing that needs to remain private.
I was just curious, you know, with the seasons changing as they are where I am, you know, on the rock, at least the weather changing can put stress on the body as well as, you know, the foods that we eat and the things that are not food that we eat.
But cheese, some cheeses.
Yeah, I found out.
So on a specific level, I'm curious what what your input would be on like a swollen or irritated lymph node.
Not not for myself, but for a friend, because I like to help people.
Well, essentially, there's something people could research, especially if you're hearing about us on the computer.
Lymphology.
And you'll notice is very little about that.
And there's more lymph fluid in the body than blood.
So it is very important.
The lymph fluid somehow has a very interesting way in its presence in all living things.
And typically anything that's swollen is a state of expansion, heat, explosiveness.
It's not it's not functioning correctly.
Right. That would be the simplest thing.
So if anyone wants to go and research lymphology, unfortunately, there's only there's very little about it.
And it's most of it was sort of parented.
The study was parented by a fellow in the 50s or 60s under the name of Wood, perhaps, or something.
You know, something called the golden whatever bow or not the golden about golden mean or something about lymph system and golden.
And he's the only one that I found online that's published anything or anything prevalent out there.
But essentially, the lymph fluid doesn't is very passive compared to the blood.
Swelling through general tissue is when the lymph fluid gets in between interstitial spaces.
And part of the simple things of understanding lymphology is it likes compression.
That's why if anyone gets a cut or a bruise, your initial reaction is to grab it and squeeze it.
Well, what's not really taught is that when there is a cut or an injury to the body, it should be squeezed as much as you can for as long as you can.
And then releasing it to let things flow.
But if you have a swollen lymph node in an area where you can't do that, typically they're in between joints or under soft parts of the body.
That would indicate something is the body is producing that it shouldn't be producing or is being stimulated to produce.
It's behind the jaw.
Yeah, that's it.
That's a typical one for something very local near the head.
So it could be a tooth.
It could be a sinus.
It could be an eye.
It could be.
Yeah.
I've actually seen an experience myself and through others that just the very nature of working.
Let's say someone out in the field and gets a splinter in their hand.
The lymph node around the elbow or armpit will swell if it's not treated properly.
So usually in terms of diagnosis, the best diagnosis is self-diagnosis if one is looking for self-treatment.
But anything lymph like that, typically the most susceptible in the jaw or in that part is the teeth, right?
And there's the teeth or a whole other study.
But all of these things need to be looked at from a lymphatic point of view and what the lymph system is about.
And, for example, I think the pusture.
Don't hold me.
I'm paraphrasing here.
It's been over 25 years since I've looked at it.
But you've heard of how blood testing is done in the medical fields very prevalently?
Yes.
Well, one of the older institutes in Europe that were quite successful in many of the initial studies and discoveries made, let's say, in the 20th century, which are very few, they do lymph testing, lymph fluid.
And it's far more accurate and shows more of a – if they know what they're looking at, which is – it's kind of frowned upon discussing the lymph system in the standard medical field.
And because it is, I think it should be looked at.
But typically something like that is stagnation, right?
Any kind of swelling or anything.
And if it swells to the point where you notice it and it's discomforting, I would go look up lymphology on that.
But more of a rudimentary aspect, not like the new agey stuff that's going to send you off into a tangent.
But typically, you know, you could judge by the area of where it's at, what's the most sensitive.
You know, near the mouth is usually the teeth.
Could be a reaction.
Or it could be dietary, many things.
The interesting aspect, again, is these fields have been specialized.
Why?
I mean, we all have teeth.
We all have hair.
We all have lymph systems and blood and livers.
Why aren't we being taught, right, 12,000 hours in school?
And you ask anyone who spends 12,000 hours, which in kindergarten and high school, what you learned, and they're like, I don't know, but I'm glad I'm out of there.
12,000 hours, folks, come on.
If you're not completely disgusted by what's going on, you're not paying attention.
So, yeah, this would be maybe a parallel study.
And there's more that can be said on it.
But I don't know how to say it.
How's that about the lymph system?
Right on.
Yeah.
Well, I appreciate it.
Now, what about health and nutrition in the broader sense?
Kind of diverting away from the e-mail.
But that's, like I said, springboard.
Yeah, well, what's wonderful about that is the obvious.
You notice how we're standing on the earth and we rely on agriculture.
And you notice how as temperature changes, so does the agriculture and the food stuffs, right?
Right.
Even if it's fit and proper food or not fit and proper food, the food stuffs change.
Like in colder places, things grow differently.
You have different types of fruits and veg and animals as well.
And wildlife and, you know, if you're into eating meat and fish.
Where if you go to a warmer climate, you have different types of fruits and veg and fish and other things that mankind has decided to consume.
The most obvious thing here is that there is an effect on the body chemistry and energy on what you eat.
And it's not only based on the chemical side that is discussed to us, meaning humans, inhabitants right now.
But there's an energetic side and a formative side.
Certainly not just the ingredients that something is made of, being that something an orange or an apple or a cow.
But how those ingredients are structured in whatever organism this is.
Now what they're doing, the academics and the scientists, in terms of measuring the quality or quantity of things.
Is that their measurements are actually changing the thing.
And what I mean by that, I'll give a stark metaphor.
If you're a carpenter and you're on, let's say, on a site, construction site.
And someone asks you how much does that, you know, one inch thick by 12 inch wide by three foot long oak board weigh.
How much does it weigh?
So what he does is he takes it and he mills it down to complete sawdust to put it on a scale.
It's no longer a board, it's a pile of sawdust.
See my point?
So when they tell you there's vitamin C in oranges, the way they determine that is so radical.
That no one really knows if there's vitamin C in oranges.
Just like you wouldn't know what that pile of sawdust was before it was a pile of sawdust.
You see?
Anytime you're dealing with a living thing in their system, not with their system, meaning the academics.
Academia in general, which means to be impractical, theoretical, never coming to a conclusion, look it up.
Is that they've, not only can they just give you a description and not an explanation.
But what happens is that they've lost the ability to observe it when it's alive.
And whenever they separate something that is in a living state into a fragment, it is no longer in a living state.
Now it goes through chemical decomposition.
That's why there's a lot of criticism on the conventional medical field, which is just based on battlefield practice, by the way.
With all their testing and their lack of success in, quote unquote, curing disease, is because the study is based on the study of cadavers.
Right?
Samples of tissue.
If you take a liver sample and view it under a microscope, that is not a living, it's no longer alive.
It's now dead.
And you're viewing the chemical decomposition of it.
So this is so radical.
And no one's noticing.
No one's really, and I say no one.
I mean, it's not, that's the reason why they should be viewed in contrast to reality, is what I mean, academia.
Right?
There's such a contrast.
But the people have just, everyone wants to pursue things that they like.
If they want to know about the body, they go to a medical person.
They don't want to, but it only takes a few minutes to acknowledge that the medical people only acknowledge dead things.
You see?
So this is, you know, again, the rift.
This is a spiritual problem.
So to go back with eating seasonally, this is a long way around the block, let's say up the driveway here.
Let's go back to eating seasonally.
Could it be that the seasonality or temperament of the food affects the body chemistry?
So another simpler way would be to explain it is if you live in a cold climate and you eat food that was grown or pervaded from a warm climate,
it will change your body to adapting to a warm climate.
But you're in a cold climate.
So you're going to get sick and vice versa.
The reason I'm stating this is because anyone I've ever encountered that had a problem of being cold in the winter,
I've always asked them or went over to where they lived or saw what they ate, and they typically ate some form of tropical foodstuffs.
And I made a suggestion.
I said, hey, look, did you ever consider that the food will actually change your body chemistry?
We use the term chemistry because people kind of like to go with that to the opposite climate that you're trying to adapt to.
And they're like, never thought of it, but I'll try it.
And 10 out of 10 people that do that have success and varying successes.
But they all come back and say, yes, I've noticed a big change.
And this is not being discussed.
It's the simplest thing.
I'm one of them.
The problem with this is that you could be knee deep in snow in a cold season part of the world.
And you go to one of these what they call markets, and they're selling you things that are from the tropics.
And people look at it from a dead chemical sense.
Oh, it's freezing outside.
But I heard potassium is good for you.
And I heard that bananas have potassium.
I'll just eat them.
I do drink coffee with a little bit of chocolate just about all year long.
Yeah, but if you were in 15 degree Fahrenheit, you know, or minus 10 Celsius, and it was 39 degrees indoors,
that was the warmest you can get, or 4 degrees Celsius, you'd give up the coffee.
You'd have to go strictly with like roasting roots from local things and making something brown and hot.
Yeah, that would be the suggestion there.
But you do have the convenience perhaps to be within the medium temperature so you could get away with certain things like that.
And this is why people in the Western cultures get the cold, the flu, and things like that during the quote unquote holiday season.
They have their holidays in the middle of winter, which I'm, you know, guilty of it growing up in this society.
But then I discovered there are no holidays in the winter really that are fit and proper.
And I discovered that the reason why they're getting sick, it's a cosmic joke, is because during their holidays,
not only are they overeating, but they're elaborating on just about anything that tastes good,
which goes down the path of, you know, sugars and chocolates and, yeah, all the concoctions and things that, you know, are out of context.
So seasonally.
Oranges is one thing in particular that I've noticed just in my own physiology,
that when I used to I say when I used to several years ago, let's say three, four years back,
any time I thought that I was starting to feel under the weather or starting to get sick, you know, irritated throat, coughing abnormally,
things like that, I would immediately go and get, you know, a big jug of orange juice.
And every time I don't know why it took me so long to piece it together or just I didn't I didn't piece it together.
You know, I was told it's external.
And I I would drink that orange juice and I would just get so much worse.
It would cause, you know, a significant noticeable increase in, you know, mucus and phlegm and things like that.
It would make my throat worse and the cough worse.
And I, you know, I've changed dramatically the foods that I eat and year round, you know, not just when it's cold or just when it's warm.
But, you know, I haven't been ill with anything other than I've I've had.
I've been sick to my stomach once.
I've had an ear infection bad enough to actually seek out medication for it once.
But other than that, you know, my health has benefited significantly from just being more aware of not only what I'm eating, but why I'm eating what I'm eating.
So this goes beyond the it is and it goes beyond the what is right in terms of discernment, because there is a very heavy commercial aspect to this.
Because on one side of the world, when it's summer, the other side, it's winter.
So that the people that are been promoting commercial farming where it's summertime are now transporting their food to where it's winter for convenience purposes.
So you can have these particular things that grow in during season now out of season.
So there's a very strong commercial element behind it as well.
And how many times have you heard, you know, people do things for money?
Well, there are industries that are set up for money and there is no money.
That's the other cosmic thing.
One day we'll discuss that there is no money and what that really means.
Yeah, well, that will be a that will be an entire couple of hours for a couple of hours.
Yeah. Just to preface it. Exactly.
Because there's another thing.
Speaking of a couple of hours, just to preface, there's another thing is I was reading.
I was reading. I was reading aloud and, you know, commenting on it as loud as I was reading it.
And I'm going, you know, a lot of these things that are brought up in this, not only would they take several hours to explain with any sort of accuracy or precision, but also, you know, more, more hours than that, just in prefacing what's being spoken about.
So, yeah.
Yeah, because it's humanity, as we stated earlier, as their greatest success to this point is they've succeeded in almost eliminating all viable forms of communication, but are still able to function somewhat, making things, going places.
What's interesting when I out in the world or digitally or physically, I hear and see people trying to communicate.
And it is one of the most one of the funniest things that I mean, you just got to really hold back.
It's like they're saying nothing.
Yet they're doing things.
I mean, that's kind of harsh, but just want to give that as a perspective.
No, it's it's accurate.
Yeah.
Or they don't know what they're saying, but they still get things done.
You know, and I mean, you know, more than just like filler up 20 bucks regular.
I'll take a dozen eggs, but anything outside basic food, clothing, you know, basic was a food, clothing, shelter.
It seems to be so obscure and almost irrelevant that it's just fascinating to see that their crowning achievement is controlled chaos or controlled confusion and controlled ignorance.
I like to add.
I like to add the to the food, clothing and shelter list that reminds me of a lot of the discussions I've had with people that would refer to themselves as preppers and things like that.
And they they tend to miss the fourth thing that is necessary to not only to comfort, but to just to existing as, you know, surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
And that's in a word, I would call it fellowship.
You could call it companionship, just other people.
You know, it's not just food, clothing and shelter that is necessary to any sort of accurate idea of survival.
But it is also, you know, other people, because if it's just, you know, just one, we are, you know, from the very beginning of what is recorded, that is that's not how how we operate.
It's not how it's not how we exist.
And then there's attached to that might be the ethic and moral aspect of people just to tie back into the conversation about money, which we won't have when you bring up even to the most staunch conservative.
What what the money system really is or how they're endorsing it by their actions and their words and their pen.
Ultimately, if you press them just like a religious person about they're not doing anything in the text.
You know what they say is they I don't really care, ultimately, as long as I can go to the store and get something for it.
So there's no. So even the most active, pragmatistic type conservative, we got to do the right thing.
Person pressed to see objectively what it is going on, what's going on and how there's two sides, let's say, to it.
They really don't care. So there's a moral and ethical problem with humanity across the board right now.
And, folks, if you're going to use the Napoleonic Code, which is, you know, you're guilty till proven innocent in society, you're going to be safe.
So when you meet people, if you judge them as being moral and unethical before they even open their mouth and then you have to make sure they have to prove to you that they are, you're going to be very, very safe.
Yeah. Yeah. So this is this is a general view.
If you just dropped out on this planet, I bet that before anyone comes here, I bet they probably preface them and say, listen, whatever.
This is what this society is like. They're really stupid and they're really simple and they're really wrong.
And they're quite easily provoked to violence. It only takes 15 minutes to explain humanity.
And I'm sure that they finish off by telling whoever's visiting here and whatever you do, don't talk to any of them because anything you say will confuse them.
So anyway. Absolutely. Yeah.
Now, this is a very, you know, but just just to throw something in for things.
This is not for anyone to believe or even think about, but just jot this down as a note to self, folks.
You're not going to go through any kind of survival type situation like that, by the way.
You're not going to have other than maybe some local catastrophes like are always happening.
Earthquakes, floods, you know, localized things like that. But but not on a national level anywhere.
At this point, unless it's temporary, like, for example, you know, there's some political manifestation that cuts things off for a while, then, you know, might be considered.
But generally in the in most parts of the world, you're not going to be forced into that situation because what's coming on the scene is the opposite.
Is that mankind will go through these this period for the next, let's say, better part of a quarter of a decade and such, maybe half a decade.
And then everything's going to start turning around where you're pretty much going to have a perfect society on the planet for a short time.
So, yeah, perfect society, not like from the top down and bottom up.
Yeah. No war. Yeah. Access to things.
Time of peace and prosperity for all surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
And the deception of that. Well, what's wrong with that? Greek, where's it?
Just, you know, what do you mean by deception of that? Deception is that it's going to be promoted as this is how it's going to be for the next thousand years.
That is the great deception. You know, when I say that, it's like, why am I saying this in public?
That's worth like a million bucks. Just that one statement. Just that clue.
The great deception really is that you will be told you all of you, meaning that all of humanity at large will fall for it.
So, yeah. So when you read in the ancient text, the great deception, it's that you will fall for this perfection because you have to be given this.
So later on, no one's without an excuse. I say, well, we didn't have a chance to have world peace.
We didn't have a chance to end world hunger. You know, that's the last thing the gods want to hear from.
So you'll be granted that for a very short time, a third of a third of a decade or so.
And then while the glitches start coming.
The there'll be some very unusual request to put it back on track and it's just going to get worse and downhill from there.
And you're going to suffer a couple of cosmic kill shots. And yeah, that's the end of the story pretty much.
So, yeah. Anyway, not not very exciting or super exciting if you want to research it.
Yeah. Every would. Every would. Jitrali speaking specifically in alternative venues.
You'll hear a lot of people speaking about cataclysm and about the end of everything.
And realistically, it was last September. That was supposed to be last September, by the way.
Oh, I could I could list at least probably 10, 15 solid dates that have come and gone that I've heard just in the last two years.
But, you know, realistically, even though it is an ending of sorts, it's going to appear to be quite the opposite of that.
It's going to appear to be the beginning of something very, very good.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. That's the whole thing. Well, yeah, it's the it's the credits.
Yeah, it's the part it's the part of the film that's thrown in at the credits.
It's an outtake, let's say, you know, it's thrown in there and you're like, oh, wow, that wasn't in the movie.
They talked about that, but we didn't quite see that.
Yeah. You know, I mean, look, if you believe there are electrons going down wires, you'll believe anything.
So, I mean, come on, folks. So, yeah.
But it's not. Yeah. And this whole thing about no one knows the future.
You've heard of that. It's like, geez, Louise, you know, it's like, well, you know, I'm baking a cake, you know, we'll eat cake in an hour after it cools down.
Well, how do you know the future?
Well, it's simple. You see, you make the rest, you know, you make the batter, you put it in a pan and an oven for an hour and or 40 minutes or so.
And then you cool it, you serve it. That's why I'm not psychic.
Yeah. The sun's going to appear to go down here in a few hours.
Yeah. Well, how do you know? Right.
Well, it's happened before and you've been told even if even if you get a recipe to make something you've never made before, how do you know?
There's a certain element of trust and a certain element of skill.
The skill here is can you see clearly? But anyway, the thing is not think not see not thinking deeply, but thinking clearly.
You know, an insane person can think deeply, but it takes a good amount of sanity to think clearly.
Sanity being health, health of mind, body, soul.
And what's and what's coming after all this stuff, which is great, is is a level of existence for all living things that is so beyond what exists now that it almost escapes description.
You can hint at it. That's the wonderful part about it.
So nonetheless, yeah.
Before we get too far away from the, you know, food idea, there is, you know, something I guess you could call it an addendum to that.
What about foods that are preserved, such as pickles, you know, or anything that is changes pickled?
It changes, right? If you were to have a well, let's say the typical in the Western world, let's say American or the States, when you say pickle, you, you know, something you slice on a burger or sandwiches and such.
And that is actually a preserved cucumber variety.
Well, if you were to compare that to a non preserved cucumber, it's almost a completely different thing.
Well, guess what? When you preserve something like that, it is completely different in its property.
So there are many things that could be considered the canning and pickling.
Even eating those things out of season is proper through experimentation, believe it or not.
You can do it yourself. So there's something like banana chips. Have you heard of those dried banana chips?
Well, should you eat those if you're in a cold climate? Well, you know, here's the thing. It's so extreme and so specific.
No, but if you do, it's not going to have the same effect as if you ate a live banana, let's say.
So considering the preserving of things, changing them, it's almost the mildest form of alchemy when you think about it.
Absolutely.
Anything else in that department could be discussed?
Or go ahead, give us any experiences that you might have with preserved foods out of season.
None negative. And it's something that I, you know, as I have attempted to do, eat seasonally.
And as I said, you know, there are things like coffee and stuff like that, that would be breaking away from that.
But generally speaking, that's something that I do, you know, year round.
And I've found it to be over the last, you know, two, three years to be of great benefit, not only just to not being sick, but just to the well-being of my physical body.
Even, you know, I've gone through, as we all do over the last few years, some very stressful things.
I would say non-physical, but that's inaccurate, you know, emotions are a physical phenomenon.
That's formative.
Yeah, that could have very well made this meat puppet ill, had it not been for the fact that even through all of that, I was still eating.
Perhaps not as much, but the quality of intake was still very considered in anything.
So I would, I'd recommend it to anyone who, especially if you have a tendency to, toward, you know, illness of the body, seasonally or, you know, sporadically even.
Think about what you're eating and maybe, maybe change it.
It was grown where you got it and where you got it from.
It doesn't mean, it doesn't mean just eat what, you know, within a few miles or locally.
That's for economic purposes as well, what's called self-sustainment and all that economically, locally.
But you can go cross latitude across the world.
So if you're, you know, somewhere in the States, let's say your type of diet or what you eat can have extreme variety.
You know, let's say mid part of the States, you go across, you know, the world and you'd see, you know, parts of France, parts of Northern Italy, parts of China, parts of Russia.
And then you could flip the globe or go on the lower half and that similar latitude of seasons.
You can enjoy those types of food as well, you see, but in different times of the year, it's usually spring or spring or fall is a great equalizer.
Where both sides of the world, you know, the people down under, let's say Australia, New Zealand, South America, and the people on the northern part, that transition.
It's possible to have similar temperatures on similar days where other parts of the year, summer and winter, it's polar opposite, right?
You have winter in one place, summer in the other.
So spring and fall is interesting.
It's an equalizer for the entire planet in that respect.
But the actual seasons manifesting like that and the actual foodstuffs are different because they contrast.
When it's winter, one place they tend to ship to the other.
So you might want to look across the world just for variety, you know.
We gave the contrast of if you live in a cold, it's a cold time of year for you.
If you eat food that comes from the tropics, there's a good chance it's going to adjust your body chemistry, let's say, to being in the tropics and you will get ill because you will not be able to adapt to the cold.
And vice versa is true.
If you live in the tropics and you eat, let's say, salmon or things that are grown in very cold places, you will not be able to adjust to the heat.
And actually that I have seen, let's say, in places in summertime in the desert southwest.
I've found someone who liked eating salmon in summertime and went to their house, they had the air conditioner down so low you felt like you're walking into a cooler box, walk in refrigerator and they were still warm.
So.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I, you know, my personal experience just with avoiding tropical fruits during the cold months here has had a, I've noticed, you know, it's something that I've been aware of.
And as they say in the back of my mind constantly, because it's something that I did consciously.
And I've, you know, it's been, it's been good.
So I recommend it to anyone out there who thinks about such things.
And I'd recommend that you maybe think about such things if you're not in the habit of doing so.
Health of the body is, I mean, that's, you know, that's how we interact with this physical plane that we find ourselves in.
So having it as healthy as possible will make everything else just that much more tolerable and pleasant.
Because it's a crazy violent place out there, man.
You said you've been out in public recently.
I know it's pretty scary.
Yeah, I'm not agoraphobic or anything.
I just find that the level of quality of individuals from every aspect now it's like as if everyone's lost their mind to some degree.
But anyway, the, you know, Seth, how we discussed earlier the external input with thoughts.
It's interesting how the external input with food is parallel to that, isn't it?
So.
It is.
Yeah.
So what else, what other external input can we discuss other than thought and food?
Well, on this on this time coming around, I think we preface by reading some things that were sent to us.
Actually, a thing is quite a document.
And just going from the gods to pretty much the external input and the food.
What do you think?
We just give it a rest.
It's been about an hour and a half an hour.
Better part of almost almost two hours here.
What do you think?
Should we just.
Yes, it's fine with me.
I'm getting relatively hungry as well.
Yeah.
So usually we we have the convention of the two hours from previously coming together on a radio network to do two hours with breaks and such.
But I think I think we've.
Put out a pretty good presentation for this episode, let's say.
Yeah.
And we've touched on some some topics and gone a little bit more in depth than maybe we have in the past.
And, you know, being that this is only the second or third broadcast that we're doing, we a lot of it can be new to people that are that are new to the concepts that we're sharing anyway.
So I think that we have done a relatively good job, as they say, such things.
And I also want to go right ahead.
I just want to present one thing in closing, just to answer this.
We've been getting some feedback as in terms of text messages on Skype and emails and such about discussing certain specific topics in greater depth.
And that will come.
And some of these topics include alternative technologies, Tesla, Victor Schauberger and such various things about ancient texts.
One might say the biblical text.
Now, the first part that could be done pretty substantially, basically just discussing the matter of fact aspect.
I think there's no real right or wrong time for that.
But discussing something like the holy rites of a particular culture or even something that might be called the biblical text at this time publicly is met with great indifference.
Only because it's not quite time yet to discuss it.
You see, would you be in agreement with that, Seth?
Or it doesn't mean we should bar the topic and not bring up things.
But I think it really coming out with what is really trying to be conveyed there is you think it's time yet?
No, but it does seem the time, as they say, gets closer every day.
So, yeah, there's a lot of stuff going on.
I just leave with a metaphor.
Someone, an individual once contacted me a couple of years back about doing a video presentation on Da Vinci's Last Supper and how it explains the stars and the Bible and all this.
And let them go on for hours and hours, a very long presentation.
And I said, wait a second.
By the way, there is no Last Supper in the Bible.
It's the Passover.
What you just did, all that effort, all that time is wasted if you try to connect it to the biblical text.
But it's not wasted if you want to make it like maybe an art review.
Right.
So you see, there's two aspects to it.
So when we discuss the biblical text right away, they go to church yet any church, Christianity, Islam, Judaism.
Like that's social stuff.
That has nothing to do with the biblical text at all.
See, see that.
I just wanted to put that in as well.
That's why it's not time yet.
So with that said, any let you close it off, Seth.
Thank you, everyone attending and listening and recording and B.Y.O.R.
I don't know if Seth's going to successfully achieve a recording on this, but yeah, we have recorded the entire thing.
We'll see if it all goes through once I hit the stop button.
But don't don't hang up.
Hang on after we are going to go ahead and in the broadcast.
So thank you all for being here and participating.
If you would like to contact us.
The easiest way to do that is going to be to go to uncommon radio dot com, where the email address is listed.
That email address is uncommon since radio one.
The number one at Gmail dot com.
And I'll drop that into the chat here as well.
Actually, I'm going to do that right now.
At Gmail dot com and go, so that's in the chat and we will be back, barring unforeseen circumstances,
broadcasting again on what they call Saturday, right around one one p.m.
Pacific wartime, four p.m.
Eastern wartime.
And, yeah, thank you all for being here and, you know, making this worthwhile.
We we I enjoy doing it.
I can't speak for both of us, but I enjoy the conversation.
So I'm grateful for that as well.
And until next time, be well and think.