Hi everybody, it's April 28th, it's Thursday evening and it's a beautiful day in California
except for all the chemtrails, but anyway, tonight our special guests are Ed Waller and
Lewis Hughes, and perhaps you know of them, they won their case.
Why don't you go ahead and tell us a little bit about it, Ed, and Lewis, for those of us
that aren't familiar with what's gone on in the past couple of years, three years, whatever.
Fill us in.
Well, it started on August 24th, 2004, with a raid by the FBI on me, Lewis, and three
or four other people all in the same day.
They cleaned out basically all our computers, all our ability to do much of anything, and
I went and met with the FBI agent and said, you know, what the hell is your problem?
If you think I did something wrong, then I'll be happy to demonstrate it in court.
Well, time went by.
Well, wait a minute, in the meantime, I was in jail because I refused to let the Yehoos
in, they never would show me a delegation of authority to come onto the state, and
so we had a little standoff for 31 hours.
When they started bringing up things that shoot through my house and three other neighbors'
houses at the same time, I decided it was time to do other things, and subsequently,
I spent the next little over ten months in jail.
Yeah, and I talked to Lewis on the phone for about five hours during this standoff.
That was kind of fun.
Wow.
Oh, and I was communicating with people all over the place via the Internet, and after
the feds cut my phone line and my cell phone, they didn't realize I had a DSL Internet connection,
so I was still able to communicate with the rest of the world during the next day, so
it was interesting.
Wow.
I do not recommend anybody try it.
No, that's not the way to go, but anyway, we danced around with the FBI agent for about,
I don't know, almost four years.
Yeah.
I went to court, tried to get my property back.
That didn't happen.
The FBI agent was still running around town saying they were going to indict us, and so
we finally went to D.C., the Article III court, after we completed an admin process and sued.
We did a preemptive lawsuit to have the law declared, and we sued the FBI agent and the
Treasury agent that he had brought into the mix, and they didn't answer the lawsuit.
On June 12, 2008, the clerk docketed our default win in the U.S. District Court in Washington,
D.C.
It settled all matters, and four days later, on June 16, we were arrested, me, my wife,
and Lewis went on the lam.
I disappeared on them.
Excuse me.
And so I spent the next 17 months, four days, and eight hours a guest of the feds in the
county jail until we went to trial in November of 2010.
County jails.
We got to see a number of them in our sojourn.
Yeah.
And, you know, you're basically starved to death.
You've got, you know, food that won't support life.
And so we've got all kinds of ongoing health problems that we're still trying to rectify
with respect to that.
Yeah.
I went down to 128 pounds, and I'm six foot three.
Wow.
So that'll tell you how bad the food was and how bad the treatment was and everything else,
but just to kind of fill in a little bit there.
When we saw that the indictment had been handed down, there were some things I wanted
to try before I was taken into custody.
So I disappeared for four months.
And so they were not happy with me.
Let's put it that way.
They're still not happy with me.
But before we ever made it to trial, I had been cross-country back again and back.
At that point, I'd been from Seattle to North Carolina, back to Seattle, back to North Carolina,
and had seen more jails than I care to count.
Ed was strictly in a couple of places, so he didn't get to travel as much as I did.
He didn't get to fly on FedAir, Conair, whatever you want to call it.
They actually call it JPAT, Justice Prisoner Air Transport System.
For those who want to know the technical name of Conair, that's it, JPAT.
Correct.
All right.
So you guys did, you were going, you know, they were doing diesel therapy on you and
taking you here and there, different jails, and really, they didn't like you very much,
and that's what they were showing you, how much they liked you.
Oh, yeah.
Every time we went into court, the marshals just hoo-hawed and laughed at us.
You know, we were just a bunch of lunatics, and my wife and I made the top three domestic
terrorists for the FBI in 2008.
Wow.
So we were on the FBI Department of Justice website as their top three domestic terrorist arrests.
Now, that's almost a trophy nowadays, if you get to be on their list, you know?
It's like, wow, you must really be a true patriot to get on their list.
Pretty much, you know, we are domestic terrorists.
So anyway, we went to trial with no attorneys.
We basically played our own counsel.
Yeah, well, we did have standby counsel, if you want to call it that.
The guy who was assigned to me had never defended a criminal case in his life and had only been
in the federal court one previous time.
Now, how's that for experience?
And the guy that they assigned to Ed wasn't much better.
I mean, it was pathetic.
No, I fired him, and he hates me.
And then I ran into another guy in jail who had paid him $100,000, and the attorney was
just lousy.
And as we saw in the Bernard Von Nothouse case, if you take on a public defender, even if
you have the best case in the world, you know, you're going down.
So I would strongly recommend anybody in that position, you know, do not use an attorney.
You're going to go down with the attorney.
Even if you screw it up yourself, at least you've got a chance.
Right.
Yeah.
So after about two weeks of jury selection and trial and about 13 hours of deliberation,
the jury came back with innocent on all charges for all three of us, my wife, Lewis, and myself.
Yeah, it was interesting.
We found out later that when the jury went out to deliberate about 1.30 on Thursday,
they took, well, immediately they selected a foreman, and Ed and I both had figured out
who that was going to be before they ever went to the jury room.
They took a first vote, and it was an even split, six and six.
And from then until a few minutes before 4.30 on Friday, it slowly worked its way down until
there was one holdout.
And just before 4.30, he says, nope, they're not guilty.
And we came back in.
Yeah.
Well, you know, right up there with the birth of my children, my wedding day, that was probably
the most amazing day of my life.
Yep.
That's so great.
Since then, we have done a number of things.
We filed Form 95 with the feds.
For those not familiar with the Form 95, it's the Administrative Claim Act, which is
the first step in suing the government.
Because the government had a number of problems when they arrested us.
First of all, we had a standing default in the D.C. court.
Everyone knows that the same issues cannot be in the same court at the same time.
So the U.S. D.C. that handed down the indictment did not have jurisdiction over the case because
all the issues before the court were already in D.C. and had been for basically two and
a half months.
The North Carolina court, not the D.C. court.
North Carolina handed down the indictment, but the matter was already settled in the
D.C. court.
Yep.
So at the time of the arrest, there couldn't have been an arrest because the case couldn't
have been in the Western Carolina court.
So that's a problem.
Number two, let's see where I was going to go with number two.
Since everything was settled and we had pretty much taken care of everything and had gotten
everything agreed to up front through our administrative process, etc., they just couldn't
do what they did.
Then on top of that, they denied Lewis and I bail so that we didn't defend ourselves.
Oh, and they sent me over to F.C.I.
Butner for psychological evaluation because I wouldn't sign their stupid paperwork and
I wouldn't cooperate in court.
So therefore, that means you're insane.
Of course.
So I spent four months in what is actually a very nice facility.
If Ed and I could have been housed there, we wouldn't be in as bad a shape as we are
right now.
I didn't talk to my wife for basically 16 months, 16 and a half months.
Oh, my God.
Why?
Well, she was ordered not to have any contact with me.
So I wasn't allowed to start talking to her until we started the trial because we were
co-counsel at that point, so they couldn't keep us from talking.
We had to defend ourselves from jail with basically pencil and paper.
We had no computers.
The law library was a joke.
If you could even get to it, it was very highly controlled and outdated.
So we defended with both hands tied behind our back.
Sure.
I've seen that before.
That's the way they do it.
Oh, yeah.
But you prevailed.
That's the wonderful thing about it.
Well, we had the creator on our side, and there were other things in play that we do
not know and do not understand to this day.
During jury selection and during the first two days of trial, which was a Thursday and
a Friday of the first week, Judge Voorhees was a total asshole toward us.
I mean, he was absolutely mean.
And we came in Monday morning, and we basically could do no wrong in his eyes.
We don't know what happened.
We have no clue.
We've never been able to get any word out of anybody on what may have happened.
We have some theories, but since we can't prove any of them, we're not even going to
bother mentioning them.
But pretty much every motion we made was granted.
Every motion the prosecution made was denied.
Our jury instructions were just extremely favorable.
And anybody will tell you that in the federal system, your instructions are either live
or die by them.
Right.
So somebody was pulling for us, evidently.
I'll say.
That's the only thing we can say for sure.
So what has that led you to up to this point?
I didn't hear that.
Say that again, Angela?
What has all of this led you to up to this point?
Well, at this point, what we are doing, of course, we're not being very quiet about this.
We have now written, and the draft is available on our website or is available on RBN and
numerous other places, a United States Supreme Court case, original jurisdiction.
In other words, we're filing directly in the Supreme Court.
We're not appealing.
We're not playing any of those games.
It's essentially declaratory judgment action, even though that is a statutory thing.
We're not going in statutorily, but we're asking for the Supreme Court to declare, declare
rights, declare the status of our republic.
Is this government going to protect private rights instead of allow people to be forced
to convert everything to public rights?
And it's our last ditch effort to see if we're going to be able to regain the form of
government that our founding fathers promised us in the form of a republic.
And if not, then the whole idea through the public awareness campaign is to show the
American people that we have been left with no choice but to abolish or amend per the
preamble to the Declaration of Independence.
So we're actually trying to get 50.
We're trying to get plaintiffs from each of the 50 states as so because we're not only
suing the United States, but we're suing the 50 de jure states as well as the 50, what
everybody calls corporate states.
We use the term body politic and body corporate because that's actually the proper terminology.
But there'll be all those parties named and we're going for things like having Supreme
Court order the states no longer can accept federal money, that property is once again,
you know, untaxable, untakeable, untouchable, that...
In other words, you have a loyal title to your land.
Right.
And all of your property because property, your rights are property.
Your political will is property.
The income tax is gone.
You know, basically re-hold up, re-hold Bruce Schaber and the six cases that followed the
16th Amendment where the Supreme Court said, you know, 16th Amendment gave Congress no
new taxing powers.
Basically, if you've got to be...
Lawful money has to be reissued, public money basically, pursuant to the article in Section
10, etc.
So if you can think of a beef you've got with our current status, I think we've pretty well
addressed it in the body of the suit.
I think we have to.
Go ahead.
Who's she talking to?
Both of you guys.
Well, it sounded like you were going to continue saying something, but you stopped.
Well, I didn't have any questions to that point.
Well, we can ask.
Basically, we are dedicated, you know, pretty much full time to the prosecution of this
lawsuit.
We've got some pretty amazing researchers involved.
We are getting a lot of interest in it from some quarters who, you know, we have a Saturday
night program on RBN, Republic Broadcasting Network.
So a lot of people have been listening to us for quite a while there now.
And we had some doubters.
You know, people said, you know, this is worthless.
It's a waste of time.
And so what we've tried to do is set this up so that it's win-win.
If Supreme Court hears our case and sides with us, holds, you know, for the relief we're
seeking, we win.
If Supreme Court says we're not touching this with a 10-foot pole because it's too
disruptive, you know, we've sold out, you can't have your country back, then we win.
Because by asking, we believe by asking the right questions, framed the right way in
law without all the crazy theories that people have about, you know, commerce and
accepted for value and all this stuff that gets people in trouble.
And we know that because that's what we're prosecuted for.
Then at least when the Supreme Court says, no, we're not going to touch this, then we
know when we can hold our heads up high and say, OK, then we know what time it is.
OK.
And the American people are going to have a choice to make.
We are going fiscally bankrupt.
They're playing games about whether or not they can cut 30, 38 billion dollars from a
3.4 trillion dollar budget.
And so, you know, if the people don't step in, Lewis and I talked about the fact that,
you know, elections never make people free.
Nothing's changed since the last election cycle, even though everybody had great hope.
And so it's up to the people.
We are the progenitors.
We, you know, of the people, by the people, for the people.
Well, we need to do our job.
We need to step up and say enough.
This is what we want you to do.
And if you don't do it, we're kicking off the chains.
Yeah.
And so people can go to your Web site and join in or how?
Yeah, we actually just made.
Yeah, we just made some changes where you can now actually register to become a plaintiff
right on the Web site.
USAV.me.
It's not a .com or .org or .info.
It's a .me.
So it's USAV.me and that's USA versus me or USAV.me.
Got a couple of good plays, dumb words going there.
And you can read the lawsuit.
The text is downloadable as a PDF.
You can watch an hour long presentation I put together on, you know, the issues, why
we're going to Supreme Court, what we plan to accomplish with it.
We're asking for, like, say, plaintiffs to step up and play the role.
You're not going to have to actually litigate anything.
The lead plaintiffs will do all the heavy lifting for you.
But in order to sue the 50 states, we have to have standing, legal standing in those
50 states by having a plaintiff in those states.
So by all means, please visit our Web site.
Take a look at it.
I'm asking, you know, anybody, if you think we are totally all wet, fine.
You know, I respect your opinion and I hope you're doing something to change the status
quo and instead of just bitching about it because, you know, as Americans, we're really
good about bitching about things.
But Louis and I have paid, you know, kind of the almost, just sort of the ultimate
sacrifice for this country of ours.
Yeah, we basically lost everything we had.
Yeah, I lost, you know, a year and a half of my life.
I've lost all my possessions.
You know, my children are definitely, they have issues from this.
They're scarred.
I've lost three years of my life because I did two stints in federal prison relative
to this case before we ever went to trial.
And I've lost everything that I had in terms of property and everything else.
And, you know, it's a it's a severe price to pay.
But if somebody doesn't step up and save this country, where are we going to be?
You know, what are you going to do when when gasoline is fifty dollars a gallon
and we're like Zimbabwe where a piece of toilet paper is worth more than a million
dollar bill?
Yeah, pretty bad.
It's getting there.
We've got to learn to barter.
We don't have the money now.
You know, they are they think they have no bounds with what they can do to you at
airports and monitor you.
And we know none of this is actually the way it's supposed to be.
But if you study history, every democracy devolves into violence.
And in a democracy, the control function has to be ever escalating.
And right now, you know, the people are the polls are saying, look, 60, 70 percent of
people don't want their taxes raised.
But go ahead and tax it, raise it on the rich.
And people don't want Social Security, Medicare touched.
Well, of course, at this point, 50 plus percent of the country doesn't pay income
tax and is on the government dole.
So, folks, you know, lead, follow or please get the hell out of the way.
You want to take some questions?
Sure, whatever.
Sure, sure.
All right.
Anyone that wants to ask a question, press star eight.
That'll put you up in the queue.
I just wanted to you guys coauthored the book USA vs.
U.S., right?
Well, I did with two other gentlemen, U.S.
of A.V.
U.S. loss of legal memory of the American state.
And that that was with T.J.
Henderson and Kegley.
Kegley's disappeared.
I don't know where he is.
But basically, the book is still right on.
I mean, it talks about that the root of the problem is legal relations with the
United States.
And that's what we have to fix.
We have to be able to sever those ties with the United States or we can't move
forward. We can never go back.
It's interesting.
There are people in position of public responsibility who are starting to figure
this out.
Yesterday morning, I had a conversation with the sheriff of Grant County, Oregon,
Sheriff Palmer.
First off, I was surprised that I got right through to him.
Sheriff Palmer is engaged in an internal battle with some of his department over
not operating with the U.S.
Forest Service.
And his belief is the U.S.
Forest Service has absolutely no police authority within the state.
And their police activities should be terminated.
And his undersheriff and several other deputies are bucking him on that.
They want the federal funds.
They want all the toys that come with federal participation.
And he's saying, no, that is not how this country is.
Was founded and how it's supposed to operate.
And so I called him to tell him about the website and he seemed to be rather
interested.
And so I left him my phone number and asked him to get back with me if he had
any questions.
And he was very cordial, seemed very interested.
So we shall see.
Wow.
You know, our message for a long time has been we need you need to start calling
your representatives.
We need to let them know that we now know.
And so if you watch the presentation at USAV.me, of course, your listeners
are far more astute and versed on the subject.
But so many people don't understand that Social Security can only be
administered within the several within the D.C.
zone. It cannot be administered within the several states.
The law is written, says the administrator can only administer Social Security
within D.C.
and the territories.
You know, if you look at the Brandeis rules, rule six of Brandeis rules says
the Supreme Court shall not pass upon the constitutionality of a statute at the
instance of one who has availed himself of its benefits.
So by simply accepting Social Security, you know, you you ashwander yourself is
what we call it from the Ashwander case so that you can't even go challenge it.
Now, the funny thing is, Supreme Court has said that unalienable rights are
unalienable.
You cannot sell, bargain, transfer or in any way through any commercial process
get rid of those rights.
Nor can your state.
Nor can the state get rid of its sovereign powers.
Right.
So what is it going to be?
Beg your pardon?
So you can't have it both ways.
What is it going to be?
Well, that's why we're going to Supreme Court to settle this once and for all
and have them say, see, that's the really interesting thing about this case.
We're not asking the Supreme Court to overturn a bunch of precedent.
We're not asking them to do anything but reinforce and restate what they've
already said time and time again for years and years.
Mm hmm.
It's going to be real because we have all the case law.
We have all the statutes.
We all know that Title 26 only taxes federal employees.
We know that 5 U.S.C. 552 AA 13 says that simply being eligible for for any
deferred retirement benefits of the United States government makes you
federal personnel.
We all know this.
It's in the law, black and white.
There's no secrets here.
So what are they going to do?
Say, well, whatever we said before, it doesn't matter anymore.
You know, we're not going to touch that.
Either way, like you said, though, we win.
Right.
Either way.
That's the way we're playing.
We're doing this like a chess match, figuring out where they're going to stay
ahead.
If you read the lawsuit, it's very clear that, you know, we don't want them to
seal this.
We want it to be out in the open, that if they don't meet their burden, I mean,
the first first and highest paramount duty of any court is to protect the
people from the excesses of the government.
We're putting in there the fact that all U.S.
district courts today are no longer and haven't been constitutional courts.
We can't go to any other court, even though the states and everybody are
suing in these lower courts, even though Article one, Article three, Section
two of the Constitution says anytime a state is a named party, the court of
original jurisdiction is United States Supreme Court.
You know, how could these lawyers, all bar card carrying lawyers, not know which
court to sue in?
Hmm.
Isn't that interesting?
Maybe they're not really suing states.
So, yeah, no one has done anything like this, put this to the feds, you know, to
the Supreme Court in this way.
And we know, I mean, we also want the Supreme Court to say that they do need to
overturn themselves because they overturned themselves before with respect to
federal judges paying income tax.
Mm hmm.
You know, you've got a built in conflict of interest when you go into a United
States district court on a tax matter and the judge pays income tax.
Yep.
That's a criminal conflict of interest and they never bother to recuse
themselves.
Mm hmm.
So there's a lot in that suit.
If people want to read it, I don't know if you had any questions, anybody
raise their hand for questions.
Yeah, we do have a couple of questions.
James Madison.
Let me see.
There you go.
Hi.
Did you have a question?
Yeah.
Can you hear me OK?
Yes, we can.
Good to hear you again, Angela.
How are you doing?
Thank you.
I'm fine.
My question is, I'm curious just to know if you gentlemen are aware of what Dr.
Livingston is doing.
I've seen your video.
I went to your website and was fairly impressed.
It doesn't seem to be as in-depth or as inclusive as what Dr.
Dale Livingston is going on.
And we filed a shooting in Colorado against the federal government because
they're not supplying us with a Republican form of government as we are
guaranteed in the Constitution.
OK.
Who are the plaintiffs?
Who did he sue?
Well, we're taking it to the tribunal court.
He's actually suing the federal government, all agencies and judges and
all of them.
So it's a little difficult of a case.
OK.
But what court is it filed in?
It's in the 10th Tribunal Court.
What the heck is that?
Well, that's a malarkey that came out of a guy down in Arizona that several
people up here tried to help him.
I really wanted him to answer the question.
OK.
I know what it is.
You know, it's a waste of time and resources if you want my honest opinion
because what are you going to do if you get a ruling out of that court?
Who's going to recognize it?
Well, as I understand it, it's eventually going to England and Wales courts
because it's above anything that was created here in the States and the
colonies even.
So, you know, it's a very in-depth...
Yeah, and Dr. Livingston wants to prove that the Constitution was a fraud
from the get-go, that we have to tear it up and start over.
And I won't disagree with his...
Throw the country in chaos.
Right, with his conclusions.
But guess what?
It's never going to happen.
Courts are not allowed to create chaos.
And that's about as close to chaos as I think you can get.
The second problem is, as you just said, it would have to go to the court of
Wales and England and make that no say within the United States.
Nope.
So...
We can't solve our problems here.
As the creators of this nation, how is somebody somewhere else going to
step in and solve the problem?
We haven't even done the right thing, and I'm sorry, suing to have the
Constitution declared null and void ab initio.
It's nuts.
It's nuts, yeah, exactly.
Oh, boy.
Okay, let me make a comment here on that.
For your information, it is recorded in the Congressional Record, 1835,
that the Constitution was never lawfully ratified.
There was a book published in 1804.
If you'll hold on a moment, I will get you the title for it,
because I've given away dozens of copies of it.
I've just got to remember where in the world I put that.
It's in the Congressional Record that the Constitution was never lawfully ratified.
So, what's the point?
Okay?
I mean, it's in the open record.
There's nothing to argue.
But do we have anything better to operate under for the last 200 years?
If so, I guess I missed it.
And you believe that it's operational now?
No, it's not.
That's the problem.
That is the problem.
That's what I'm saying.
Now, I'm saying that we want to go back to something that's failed.
No, it did not fail.
People failed it.
No.
Okay, we failed it, right.
People failed it.
It wasn't perfect when it came into origin.
It wasn't ever brought forward properly.
It's always been a nation of men rather than a nation of law.
And it's failed, but we don't need to look into getting it going right, though, huh?
Well, first of all, the first 90 years of this country went pretty well.
It wasn't until the Civil War.
It took a civil war to totally destroy what was left of the people's memory of the Constitution.
Now, that happened in the War of 1812, but that's okay.
Well, that one was a pretty bad little time as well.
Yeah, that war was to do away with the 13th Amendment.
Article 13 of the Constitution would be the correct way to say it.
The War of 1812 was to destroy the Freeman documents, as you know, which was the original writing.
My forefather, James Madison Bowe, was the Republican Declaration of the United American Colonies.
Which has been usurped into something, a contract we call now the Constitution.
Which was brought forward by William Hickey in 1846 and adopted by select members of the Confederate Congress in 1847 to be this nation's Constitution.
It's under glass in the National Archives today, displayed as something that our forefathers brought forward.
And nobody bothers to add the numbers up to determine it, since James Madison was the last person to survive.
Who was one of the 39 supposed signers on that document, and he died in 1836.
Nobody questions how can a document that was created 10 years after everyone who supposedly signed it was dead be anything but a forgery.
Okay.
Well, I mean, at that point, you get to call a Constitutional Convention, or the people get to come together to change their form of government.
And we believe that will probably be the ultimate end-all of this.
That's definitely going to have to be.
I don't really see any other way that we can really go forward and fix anything that we have right now.
Wouldn't you rather get large numbers of the American people on your side before you take that very drastic step?
Oh, sure. They're coming along.
You know, I believe that James Madison really had it together in his day.
And I'm hoping this one today, an ancestor will be able to do the same.
And I like to quote my forefather a lot.
And this one out of Federalist Number 14 is my favorite.
He says, Is it not the glory of the people of America that whilst they have paid a decent regard to the opinions of former times and other nations,
they have not suffered a blind veneration for antiquity, for customs, or for names,
to overrule the suggestion of their own good sense, the knowledge of their own situation, and the lessons of their own experience?
Why do we believe in this nation today that these men who wrote this document and tried to bring this nation forward were something like gods,
and that there's no people in this country today that has the knowledge and wisdom and ability to go forward from where we are
and create a form of government for this nation that can be successful using the information we've got off the last failed one that we can improve on and go forward?
I just don't understand it. Can you explain it?
Why are you making the assumption that everyone believes that they're deities and that nobody has the intelligence to go forward?
I don't know if anybody's actually said that.
Well, why is everybody stuck on the Constitution then?
Because if you try to do anything else directly, you're going to be waging war with people who have a lot of guns, a lot of jails, and a lot of other things that I don't think you're going to be successful going down that road.
That isn't currently going on?
Exactly. So why don't we use their own system against them, the one that they claim is in force and that we have the right to protections under, before we pull out the ultimate control alternate delete on the country?
Well, I must tell you I am very much approved of what you're trying to do, and I hope you're successful.
I have joined your site today, and we'll be keeping an eye on it, keeping track of it.
Hopefully I can help in some way, but like I said, I just think we need to go forward and take what we've learned.
The country needs something new. That's just what I believe.
The problem is, once you start tearing up what we have, there's not enough people in this country today that would get behind the fact and even know what the role of a government is.
Walk into a supermarket and ask the people standing in line, what's the function of government?
And if they don't say to protect rights, which they won't, then do you really want those people getting involved in trying to craft a new government?
I would answer to you, not no, but hell no. That would scare the hell out of me.
So at least if we try to show them that the Constitution is where we need to at least start out, and the Supreme Court says, screw you, we're not giving you that back, then we can have the conversation about where we go from there.
That's our view on it, and we may be wrong.
I appreciate that you feel that they're not going to tell you that, and if you feel that it's not a wasted effort to do that, I will support you in any way I can like I do anyone else.
I think as long as somebody's doing something that's better than what we've been doing, which is nothing.
So I support anyone and any effort they have, and I congratulate you on your idea. I think it's pretty sound.
So with that, I thank you for giving me your time, and I yield the floor.
I love a healthy debate, and you notice we did it civilly. Everyone kept their tongue, and that's really what we need more of.
That's the way we do it here.
Yeah, James, if you're interested, the book that I'm referring to about the Constitution is called Secret Proceedings and Debates of the Constitutional Convention of 1787.
It was written by R. Yates, and it was published in 1804.
You can get a reprint of it from Omni Christian Book Club for $7.95.
I highly recommend it to you. I think you'll find it a very interesting reading.
Yeah, I don't remember exactly where I got it myself, but I downloaded it online somewhere.
I don't remember where, but you're right. It is a good reading.
Anyway, thank you for that.
You're welcome.
Thank you, James.
I'll be back in a minute.
Anybody else?
Yeah, we do. Hold on one second. I'm trying to unmute him.
Bassadar. There you go. Bassadar, B-A-S-S-A-D-A-R. Did you have a question?
Yeah, I wanted to ask the brothers if they were familiar with the Libra Code.
Very familiar with the Libra Code. Written by Abraham Lincoln's general, and it's still operational today.
Right. I think that it would be best if the brothers went about the situation in more of a forgiving manner.
Please explain. I'm not following quite yet.
Well, our Lord taught that we should be forgiving towards one another.
Okay.
And the key to rebuilding the problems that we face, especially the debts and the claims,
it's going back and forth, is forgiveness.
And the thing we're doing is really claiming property that doesn't belong to us as ours.
And we're making claims against an institution that has been set up for our protection.
So, the situation your brothers are in is a tough situation.
But I see that the best way to come out of the situation and have the federal government in your favor
is to render to them what's theirs.
And what would that be? Just so I'll follow. What should I render to them that's theirs?
Well, we could start with money.
Aren't they getting enough of that?
Well, they have to borrow it. It has to be borrowed into the economy or taxed from Peter to pay Paul.
But why is that the case now?
Because they're bankrupt. They have no money.
So when you cash your check, you get notes which are promises to pay money.
Right. We don't have a lawful monetary system. That's correct.
But we also have a system where we have gone into a socialist state.
And as we know, the government has taught people for ages that every democracy fails and turns violent
because you end up stealing from one group of people and giving to another.
Governments are instituted among to protect rights. That's it. That's the only legitimate function of a government.
If it starts taking money from one group of people and giving it to another,
you didn't have that power to give to the government when you loaned them your sovereignty to create a government.
You're not allowed to go out and steal from somebody. So how can a government do it?
And I don't know about you, but the government is only doing what it's authorized to do.
Is it? Is it authorized to steal from one group of people and give to another?
Is it authorized to take away your rights?
What is it stealing?
It's stealing my hard work, my children's future. It's stealing my rights.
It's stealing my property?
The concept of ownership is an illusion.
So your work doesn't belong to you. Your work belongs to who it's rendered to.
When did my work not become my own? When was it taken from me?
Because you did not create the talent for your work. The talent for your work was given to you as a blessing.
By whom?
The talent which you do your work with is a gift.
From whom? Who gave it to me?
Your creator.
Okay, and so if I don't preserve his blessings as my own, aren't I forsaking his gifts?
His blessings are not yours. His blessings belong to your brothers and sisters and your people.
Yeah, this sounds like a whole bunch of new age socialist mumbo-jumbo to be honest.
You know what, we're done with it because it's boring me.
We're going to move on. I'm sorry.
Bassadar, you find another talk show.
This is not your place to air your grievances. I'm sorry.
Okay, West Michigan, go ahead. Did you have a question?
I did. I had a couple of comments.
One comment I'll make real quick, I think you'll appreciate it.
Maybe you won't appreciate it. The battery on my cell phone died,
so fortunately I did not have the pleasure of listening to everything that the last gentleman said.
And having heard the last few words of it, I'm really, really pleased I didn't
because things like that raise my blood pressure.
On to the lawsuit that you mentioned.
You said earlier that, and one thing really, I'll say, threw me for a loop about it.
You said if you win the lawsuit, then they'll prove something.
But you said if they don't take the lawsuit, I think you said that's also a win?
Did I misread that? Or was I not paying close enough attention?
No, you heard that correctly.
First of all, keep in mind, we're not going up on appeal.
This is not a writ of certiorari.
This is not an original action.
So they can't say we're not going to hear it.
They cannot deny a cert or a writ.
So in essence, the case will be filed in the Supreme Court.
The defendants will be served.
They can answer, they can do the 12B6s, although there's really not quite a 12B6 type motion under Supreme Court rules.
The federal rules of civil procedure are just guidelines.
They aren't necessarily hard and fast on the court.
So at that point, the Supreme Court can either grant the states or the feds motion to dismiss, which would mean they don't hear the case,
or the court on its own motion, of course, could dismiss the case.
Either one of those is a win for us, because as part of the public awareness and education campaign we're trying to mount, we're getting good support on,
the American people are going to see that all we're asking for in the case are rights back, rights to be upheld and protected by the states and the federal government,
the law to be upheld the way the Supreme Court has already ruled that it works.
And so at the end of the day, if the Supreme Court says we're not touching this case, we're not going to rule out, we're going to dismiss it, we're going to try to make it go away,
that is tantamount to holding a mirror up to them and them basically having to say it's over.
There is no law, there is no remedy, we are no longer a republic that protects rights, we are a fascist state.
So by getting that opened and aired once and for all in front of the psyche of the American people, then it comes down to where do we go from there?
We have a choice to make.
The Declaration of Independence says we have the right and the duty to abolish or amend our form of government when it becomes destructive of our rights.
So at least that will be settled once and for all in that the Supreme Court, which of course all the Supreme Court justices pay income tax,
all of them have a built in conflict of interest simply trying to hear this case and we point that out to them.
We're not naive about what we're going up against.
But the question we have to ask is if not now then when and if not us then who?
You might also let the people know that this is the first time since 1835 that a case has been brought to the Supreme Court in original jurisdiction.
Here's the thing with that though, when you go ahead and, I didn't know it was only the second time,
I thought there were more cases that have been brought there in original jurisdiction.
First of all, I've done some research on judicial disqualification and essentially if all the judges would be disqualified for the same reason,
in this case the income tax issue, then none of them are disqualified based on that issue.
We're not trying to disqualify them.
We are not trying to disqualify them.
We're basically saying look, we know who you are.
We know the disabilities that you're operating under.
Now what do you want to do about it?
Do you want to uphold the law?
Do you want to give the people a remedy which is what you owe them, which is what we're supposed to get?
If you don't, that's fine.
Just let us know.
Yeah, just let us know because then we know what we have to do.
And then we can start a whole new discussion about either constitutional conventions or a simple meeting of the people to get together to say,
control, alternate, delete.
We're going to reboot this puppy.
But keep in mind, there are some people who are on our side, Congress creators, there are judges.
These people have a pulse.
These people can see this government is headed for absolute bankruptcy and that if we don't do something, it's over in every way you can possibly imagine.
So I'm not writing them off completely yet.
You said the sample copy of this lawsuit is at USAV as in Victor.me?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Right across the top on the options are the lawsuit.
And if you scroll down through, you'll find another link to it.
Okay.
I just look at this, I've got way too much of a familiarity with the courts.
And I know that if they don't want to hear something, I know how they're capable of punting an issue.
And the first thing that comes to mind is a character out of California that sued because the word God was in the Pledge of Allegiance,
and he didn't think his daughter had to recite that because he was an atheist.
His mother, his ex-wife wasn't, but he was.
He didn't want his daughter having to recite the word God in class.
So it gets all the way up to the Supreme Court.
They looked at it, and they said, wait a minute.
You don't have standing to bring this because you're not the girl's custodian, guardian, what have you.
So since you didn't have standing to bring this, we're not going to hear it.
And I thought to myself, why did you even take it?
Why did it get to the point where you even said you were going to take it
and then come up with a jurisdiction issue when you could have threw it out on the jurisdiction issue a lot earlier?
There's a big difference.
If they didn't grant the cert where they weren't going to hear it at all, then the lower court's ruling would stand.
By doing what they did, they overturned the entire case, the entire ruling, everything went away.
It's a huge difference.
Well, that's true.
Okay, and so like I say, if you want to talk about someone who knows these courts, in our criminal trial,
we put the evidence in front of the judge that he was not an Article III judge, that it wasn't an Article III court.
He perjured himself from the bench and said, I am an Article III judge, and this is an Article III court.
But he never would answer the question, have you taken the Article III oath of office prescribed in Ronstadt 73?
I asked him three times, and he never would answer me.
We caught him on a lot of stuff.
So you're preaching to the choir when you talk about not trusting these courts.
But the point is that until we the people go to the final authority on the rule of law in this country,
and right now under the Constitution and all the other games you want to play, it is the Supreme Court.
They are the ones charged with the responsibility for protecting the people.
They're the final say.
Okay, if you read the lawsuit, and I implore you to do so, we are coming in in law.
We're not playing  people are  you didn't say these particular words, and you didn't
look, we're not playing any games here.
We're coming in in law. We're stating our jurisdiction as plainly as it can possibly be stated.
We're not playing any games with commerce and de jure versus de facto.
We're using the Supreme Court words, which are body politic and body corporate.
And by the way, folks, there is nothing wrong with the corporate.
There is always a body corporate and a body politic.
The people are the body politic.
The government functions through the body corporate.
That's how it builds roads.
That's how it signs contracts with vendors.
That's how it negotiates with foreign powers is through the corporate form.
That's not a problem.
Get over it, okay?
But when the body corporate claims jurisdiction over the body politic, now you have a problem.
Okay, so what we're trying to do is educate people on what the real problem is,
the way governments are really set up, and so we're going real law into this case,
no shenanigans, no games being played, and it's straight up.
Supreme Court, shit or get off the pot.
Pardon my French, but that's the way it is because we're done.
This is it.
Either you do the right thing here or it's over.
Yep.
Also, for your information, we have stated in the complaint that all legal terms are as defined
in Black's Fourth Dictionary and anything which is not defined in Black's Fourth
in the definition in Webster's original 18, what is it, 29, 28?
Actually, the legal dictionary reference is Beauvier's, 1854 or whatever it is.
Oh, did we change that?
Yep, that's back to Beauvier's original.
Okay.
That is what the Supreme Court said is the controlling definition of words.
Anyway, we have told the court what we're using as the definition of the words in this filing
so there can be no confusion, no argument, no playing of games, period.
I'm looking at it now.
You've got it spelled out pretty good.
That's all we ask is people give it a fair shake, take the time to read it.
It reads pretty easily.
And, you know, if you like what you see, become a plaintiff.
Okay.
Join in.
Let the world know that you want to take a stand for the right reasons.
And, you know, we've talked about this.
We aren't a bunch of  all we want is equal protection.
We want equality under the law because that's what we've all been promised.
Under any form of law you can mention, either the Constitution, the Articles of Confederation, whatever,
John Locke and international law, I mean, it all follows.
And so this is it.
We want the whole country to get on board.
Even after we file, we're going to have, as the press, you know, as the word of this spreads,
you're going to be able to sign up as a plaintiff later, probably every 30 to 45 days.
We're going to do a motion to add plaintiffs.
We hope to get 10,000, 100,000, 500,000 plaintiffs on this thing.
Wow.
Whatever we can get, we're going in with it.
Now, you don't have any attorneys involved in this, right?
Not a single bar card to be found, high or low.
Okay.
Well, well, well, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We do not have bar cards directly involved.
What we do have is we have some resources who are bar cards who have looked at this and gone, wow.
Yeah, but there's no bar cards involved in the litigation at all.
Exactly.
But we are utilizing all the resources that we can get our hands on to make sure this thing is right the moment it's filed.
Well, exactly.
Once it's filed, now you're saying for you want at least one person from each of the 50 states to go ahead and be involved in this.
Does that, let's say, in other words, you're not going to, if you only get 45, you're not going to file it.
You're going to wait until you get the other fives.
You've got one from each state, and then everybody's represented in it.
Right.
Every state will have standing.
See, some of the relief we're seeking, the federal government can't give us.
Okay, the states are denying their Milne duties to the people.
And so we want relief against the state, and therefore we have to sue the states.
Yeah.
Now, if you don't know what a Milne duty is, there was a Supreme Court case from 1837 called New York v. Milne.
If you would like to read that case, it's on my website, freedomrequireswork.org.
Just go on the public access side.
On the next page, go to court cases.
And then there is a link to the Supreme Court posting of the case.
But there is also a teaching synopsis from one of the law universities on how Milne duties are taught to law students.
The teaching syllabus is actually shorter than reading the case, so you might want to read it first before you read the case.
But if you didn't get that, it's www.freedomrequireswork.org.
It's a .org, I'm not commercial.
There's a number of other things up there that may be of interest to you.
There's a copy of Black's Fourth Law Dictionary.
There's a little booklet that's only 12 pages, which lists all of the major Supreme Court cases,
which state that you can be a state citizen without being a United States citizen.
You are an American national, but you are not a U.S. citizen.
There are a number of things up there, legal-wise, that hopefully people will find helpful in broadening their understanding.
I'm scanning this. You've done a very thorough, good job on this lawsuit.
We've got a whole lot of people involved, and some of them are quite high-powered.
I can't reveal certain things, but let's just say there's one bar card who has been in an extremely high place in our government
who has taken a look at it and went, yep, that looks pretty good.
Just a suggestion, I don't know if you've thought about this.
I would make sure, obviously, you get one person from each state,
but I would not keep loading this thing up with people, because otherwise you're going to get more confusion than you want.
You've got to get people you can work together with and not have a bunch of confusion.
Actually, that's not a problem, because basically everyone who becomes a plaintiff will be signing a power of attorney,
or put in other words, we will be the lead plaintiff in this, myself and basically one other gentleman.
We also are having people sign what we're calling the rules of engagement, which is you do not speak publicly about it.
You don't go to the press, because they're going to be looking for weak links.
We know that every potential plaintiff is a potential weak link for them to exploit.
You're also going to have to fill out a questionnaire about what felonies you have on your record,
what you currently have going on with the government.
We're vetting very carefully, because we know they're going to have to attack this other than legally.
They're going to have to attack this any way they can to make us look like a bunch of raving lunatics.
By the way, that is the way the government now speaks of us in reference to our criminal case.
I had a friend call me just this week. He went and picked up the last of his stuff from the FBI.
He said, well, I guess I should have pled not guilty, because he pled guilty.
Then he went to trial, and he said, oh, you would have been found guilty.
Those other guys, they were just buffoons. The jury felt sorry for them, and all that kind of stuff.
We know they're a bag of tricks. You all have seen them. If you've been in court, you know what kind of games they play.
We're trying to do this in a way that ensures the highest level of either win rate or at least control over this thing,
so it can be about the issues and not about whatever they try to make it about.
Was that it for you, Matt? I had to mute you out, because there was background noise. Do you have anything else?
No, I've all said that. I think you've done a really, really good job on this, and I wish you success.
Certainly, you've touched on really good substantive issues in here that most people can sink their teeth into.
Most people understand what they are, and I think that's definitely a direction we need to go,
because somebody has to jar these people psychologically into doing the right thing.
I think things have just gotten to a point in this country to where it's beyond what anybody ever thought they would be.
Maybe not everybody. A lot of people knew this was coming, but now it's like, okay, let's try to turn this thing back before it's too late.
This is certainly a step in the right direction. Thank you for answering my questions.
Thank you, Matt.
Thank you for coming on. Always a good participant. Let's move on, though. We have several more.
Anna88Bell, go ahead. Did you have a question for our gentleman?
No, my questions have been answered. Thank you much. Appreciate it.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, I like those deep ones.
Yeah. All right. Arizona, did you have a question? Go ahead, Arizona. Maybe you have to unmute your phone.
I unmuted you on this end, but did you have a question?
Angela, it's Jon Stewart. How are you?
Hi. Hi, Jon. How are you?
Hello, Ed and Lewis. How are you guys?
Oh, we're doing pretty good. Thank you.
Yeah, I've read your documents. I'm quite impressed with them.
I have a caveat that  I've been doing this for a long time, too, and ran into my share of problems.
The issue seems to be not only the corruptness of the individuals that are in the government, but we have a major issue with our people in as much as
I no longer believe that that many people really want this to be a republic.
I deal with a lot of different groups. As a matter of fact, I have to go speak to literally a seminar full of nothing but attorneys this weekend.
So the system seems to have created a scenario where the more corrupt it is, the more the people that are in charge can make money.
But then the other side of that, the slaves, the people walking around that like the crap that's going on, get to be taken care of better with doing less effort.
And the numbers are  it's just phenomenal. I mean
Well, you said you read the lawsuit, right?
Yes.
Okay. Then you know that the lawsuit itself is not about taking anything away from anybody, although we know that Social Security is illegal, etc., etc.
The issue is can they force those of us who don't want to participate into the slavery and peonage and force us to do that?
And that's really the crux of it is if somebody wants to get in bed with the government extra constitutionally
I'm not going to call it unconstitutional, but it's outside the provisions of the Constitution.
If you want to go play with those benefits and you think that the government can provide you those benefits better than a private retirement program or whatever, that's fine.
By all means, have a ball. I think their track record shows they've been absolutely lousy at managing that particular thing.
But the point is if I don't want to participate, can you force me to?
And oh, by the way, Mr. State, North Carolina, California, wherever you might be, I'm going to hold you to your duty to protect me from all invaders, foreign and domestic, and that includes the United States government.
Okay?
Part of what the states are supposed to do is protect us from the overreaches by the federal government, not try and profit by it.
Well, and I noticed that in your suit it's very repetitive about the FSA contract.
And I've been  I'm totally with you on that. I agree 100%.
What I see that the average person kind of just going through their life with the blinders on is they are repetitively asked what their Social Security number is.
And you see it on forms, applications, licenses, your Social Security number.
That in and of itself is fraud because it's not physically possible in or outside of law, whether we're talking about the body politic or the body corporate, for an individual to have a number.
The number is owned by the agency. It's just like you don't have a bank account.
Well, actually, let me correct you. It is absolutely possible, but you better be a federal employee if you have that number.
Oh, but the number is still possessed by  it's just an acknowledgment of the contract. You are not in possession of that number.
Social Security is not a contract. Don't use that word, please.
Okay. Well, without delving into the intricacies, I don't know how else you would explain it to the average person.
It's a franchise agreement.
Okay. Absolutely it is.
That's what it is. It's a franchise agreement.
And that's what gets everybody.
And you're not allowed to participate in that franchise unless you are a federal employee.
And by doing so, you're actually committing a crime if you're not a federal employee and you go around saying you do have one number.
Absolutely.
Well, therein lies the problem.
Why is that a problem?
Because people don't get that.
It's no different than filling out the so-called tax forms, which are really nothing more than a return.
A federal employee is supposed to return part of what he's paid to whoever it is that truly pays him.
Now, the issue is that people look at that, and they believe it is their number.
Most people, at least my age and older, never really did volunteer, and the younger people.
I mean most people are getting their social security numbers while they're too young to be franchised into anything anyways.
Agreed.
But I mean all they have to do is flip over the card and look and see that it says property of the SSA.
But as maybe destructive as being naive about whose number it is, the real issue is what does it do to you?
What happens because you use that franchise agreement?
And of course the answer is you become subject to all kinds of federal taxes, all kinds of federal jurisdictions.
I mean Supreme Court up through 2006, which is the last time I've looked, has said Congress cannot legislate for the internal affairs of the people of the states.
Why is everybody all upset about Obamacare?
I mean they told you it was only for federal employees because who was going to be the enforcement arm on Obamacare?
The IRS.
And the point being that people constantly reiterate that franchise better than contract, but they reiterate the fact that they want to be involved in it somehow.
Fine. Let them.
Right.
And the government can only use money that they do not bring in from taxes to pay that office.
By the way, that's going to kill it right there.
Because if only those people who are going to someday collect it are the ones paying in, and they can't use tax money to distribute that money, the system's doomed.
Oh, yeah. I think that's where if you were to wake the average person up to the fact that most of this stems from that sort of, whether it be a tacit or purposeful agreement, if they had a way to walk out of it, they would.
You know, there was some guy earlier that was claiming this was all voluntary. You volunteer yourself into prison. You volunteer yourself into jail. You volunteer into that.
That's not true. Those of us that have been in my situation is not unlike what you guys experienced.
In some ways, yours was worse. In some ways, mine was much worse.
I didn't volunteer for any of it. They got me at the point of, you know, 12 guys with machine guns.
That's what we had. I had M-16s pointed at me.
I was a little more fortunate.
But let's talk about who the audience for this lawsuit is, okay? And I'm sorry, what was your name?
Jon Stewart.
Jon. Okay, Jon. Let's talk about the audience for this suit, because really what you're talking about is we have a product.
The product is called a Supreme Court lawsuit.
Now, who is our consumer, right? Who is our user? Who is our target audience?
And we, to be honest, it's not patriots.
Most patriots are so invested in the stuff that they have learned, and you would not believe the emails I get from patriots.
Yeah, me too.
Our audience is not patriots. We can't teach them anything. They know everything. Just ask them. They'll tell you.
Our audience is not the 50 to 55 percent of the country who currently is on the government dole.
Because guess what? They've already figured out they can vote themselves largest from the public trough,
and they're going to keep voting themselves as much largest as they can possibly get.
So they're not going to be interested in this lawsuit. They're not interested in freedom.
Okay?
Our audience is that 30 percent or so of the country who became politically aware in the last election cycle.
Maybe they went to a Tea Party rally.
Maybe they read something outside the mainstream media,
or they're just flat out concerned and scared about the path the country is on.
I can't tell you right now, because I'm sworn to secrecy,
some of the groups that we have been given permission to do email alerts to their lists.
One of them has 16 million members.
Wow.
Another one has 5.5 million members.
Okay?
We're talking to the NFIB, National Federation of Independent Businesses.
They are going to take a lawsuit.
Their legal people are going to analyze it and tell their membership what they think about it.
They were one of the ones who sued over Obamacare in the Florida federal courts.
Okay?
So there's a lot of potential support for this.
What we basically found, and Lewis heard this even more so than I did,
but people said, look, I need to read the suit.
So last week we released it out into the wild.
The response has been amazing.
It is very well written.
You bring up one thing in the suit and in the discussion that I think is very powerful.
In talking about the patriots, they are so lost, and it's probably the biggest confusing factor,
and that is what a body politic is and what a body corporate is.
And hearing you speak when you said that the body corporate is really not a bad thing,
it has to be used, and the whole patriot phenomenon,
it's almost insidious the way that one concept has pervaded into the patriot network
to the point where people don't understand it.
They don't understand the separation, what the two differences are.
And I think this is going to help clear that up, but nothing more than
see, the patriot community scares me more than the government at this point.
You've got these guys like Kenneth Turner.
Yeah, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Yes, yes, we're on the same page. We agree.
These guys scare the shit out of me.
I mean, all of a sudden they're going to do something stupid, and I've already seen them.
His  Turner's mistress is trying to get me killed right now and has been for a while.
And these people are just  they're going to do something stupid and violent
and give the so-called body corporate the position where they're going to be able to move in and do stupid shit too.
And people are going to side with the body corporate against its own body politic and the people.
I think they're much more dangerous than the government.
Well, I'll tell you what, it's neck and neck.
I mean, I have a hard time deciding which side of the coin to come down on.
But we have lost a number of plaintiffs because I expressed my opinion about Tim Turner.
And these people thought that we're lunatics.
We've been attacked by L.B. Bork.
So I lost a plaintiff because he listened to L.B. Bork and his 14th Amendment crap.
But I don't care.
We are going to be attacked.
We are going to be excoriated on every level that they can think of,
whether it be the government or the patriot segment of society.
All I can say is if you can think of a better way to put this,
if you're doing what you think is going to be best for our country, then do it.
But don't tell me that I can't do what I believe and try and get it organized to bring people in
when we're running out of time, folks.
Time is short for this country.
If we don't do something fast, the police state is going to be irreversible.
We are going to be in the next World War because that's what they're setting up with these African countries
and militant countries they're attacking.
We are 1930s Germany right now.
I didn't know better.
I thought I was listening to me.
Well, good.
Then we're on the same page.
I don't want to tie up any more time because I'm sure there's probably a line of people who want to talk to you guys.
Just real quick.
First of all, for those of the people that are listening, you guys have 100% of my endorsement.
Send an email to ed at usav.me and make yourself a lawsuit.
Send me your street address and a phone number and I'll put you on the list.
You can always back out up until you sign the agreement.
But show your support by signing up to the plaintiff.
Well, and I don't really have much money because I myself live off donations.
We're not asking for money.
No, I know it is required.
Well, but we're not asking for money from you.
If those who sign up can make a $100 donation to help offset copying.
Remember, we've got to serve every state in the union, two parties.
We've got to serve the Attorney General and the Governor of each state.
And so they are expensive.
But you do not have to contribute to be a plaintiff.
We want your mind and your body first and foremost.
We want your participation.
So don't let that be a reason not to join and be a part of this.
You've definitely got that.
I can tell you that in some cases you may not have to serve documents.
In some of them you can actually serve CDs which can save a tremendous amount of money.
I mean, that's going to be pursuant to the state rules of acceptance.
Go read the Supreme Court rules initially.
The lawsuit in paper form will be served on them with a summons.
You know, standard legal procedure basically.
But the point is that, yes, there's going to be a lot of work to be done.
We're going to be bombarded with answers to the lawsuit from 50 states.
And, of course, the United States, which is no small undertaking.
But we're in this.
And this is what has to be done.
And if someone has a better idea, we're willing to listen.
But in the meantime, get on board.
Well, I am, and I'll let the people that know of me know how I feel about it.
One final question, and then I'll let everybody else have their turn.
The Treaty of Paris, do you guys have anything to do with that?
What's your opinion on that?
I'd like to get your take on the whole Treaty of Paris between the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution and how that falls into the fold.
Can I take that one?
Yeah, yeah, I'll take that one.
Have you ever seen the original documents?
I've seen supposed pictures, but, you know, I trust pictures as much as I trust one of my actual eyes, you know.
Okay, the reason I ask the question, how did the King of England sign the Treaty of Peace?
You know, I'm sorry, I don't know.
Don't quote his signature.
Okay, I will tell you, he signed it.
Prince George, Prince of the Holy Roman Empire, King of England.
If that doesn't tell you everything you need to know, I don't know what will.
Oh, I know where you're going on. Okay, I didn't know you got into that. Oh, I agree completely. I know and understand and believe.
Okay, well, fill me in. What? What?
Okay.
For those of us that don't get it.
Do you really want to know this?
Yeah.
Well, I'm going to lay a couple of other things out there that you don't know, because unless you had had personal contact with a small group of people in British Columbia, you couldn't possibly know this.
But let me, let me, you just, I'll give you a thumbnail sketch and then I'll go into the other.
Okay, the signature indicates that the King of England was subservient to the Vatican.
As were 10 European nations at the time, all of the kings of France and Spain and Italy and Greece, they all signed their legal documents, King of blah, blah, blah.
But above that, they put Prince of the Holy Roman Empire.
Now, I'm going to drop a bombshell on you.
There is a band of Native Americans in British Columbia who have a treaty, which was signed in 1655, which gives them sovereign authority all over all of North America from the Chihuahuan Desert of Mexico to the North Pole.
In commemorating that treaty, Queen Victoria presented the chief of the tribe with a royal staff, which is, it looks to be about 18 carat gold.
She also presented him with a gold medallion, which is about four inches in diameter, which has her likeness on it.
But that treaty is also signed by the Pope, and the Pope issued a gold medallion, also about four inches in diameter.
So, all of that predates everything else.
Part of that treaty says that any point in time the Europeans become a problem, these Native Americans have the right to throw them out of the country.
That treaty was reaffirmed in 1835, and was reaffirmed by both England and the Vatican in 2003.
How's that for a bombshell?
Is that that Turtle Island group?
No, ma'am.
No, ma'am. This is a group you have probably never heard of.
The National Confederated Tribe spokesman is a gentleman, I will pronounce his name as best I can, because I can't quite master the native tongue.
It's Max Juan.
There have been things happen all over Canada and the United States that have taken a different path because he stepped in and invoked the treaty.
It's quite interesting. I had the privilege of meeting the man five years ago.
What kind of an effect does it have on the United States?
Well, the effect is that we are operating at their pleasure.
And if we ever become a big enough problem, they have the right to throw us out.
Because their treaty predates anything and everything we've done.
It's a chartered treaty, and it's perpetual.
But I just thought I'd share that little tidbit with you as kind of an off-course diversion.
Okay. Alrighty. So that doesn't have anything to do with what John was talking about, though.
Well, in a way it does, because everything ultimately boils down to treaties.
And we have ignored treaties that have been in place since before this country came into being.
Are you familiar with a gentleman by the name of Sherwood Rodriguez?
It's a Portuguese spelling, I think.
Yes, I am.
Okay. You know that he went to the Supreme Court in 1982,
and the Supreme Court declared that Skagit County and Whatcom County of Washington State
are not in federal jurisdiction for those who avail themselves of the original charter of the Hudson Bay Company.
Okay. I haven't seen it. Have you seen that case?
Yes, I have.
Okay. Where can I see it?
Well, unless you can find a printed copy somewhere, you're not going to.
I read Sherwood's copy.
If you do a search on it in the Supreme Court, it doesn't even come up.
They buried it a long time ago.
Gosh, why doesn't he scan it in so we all can take a gander at it?
Well, you've got to realize that Sherwood is 80-something years old now.
Yeah, but he's had it an awfully long time, hasn't he?
Oh, yeah.
I've been hearing about it for at least six years, seven years.
Yeah. Well, I had the pleasure of meeting him about 2002, 2003, somewhere back in there.
And I got to read the case then.
Geez. I wish you would have scanned it in.
Well, back then I didn't have a scanner. Sorry.
Oh, well.
All this modern technology that we take for granted today existed 10 years ago.
You know, I'm still running...
Yeah, I do.
Oh, never mind. I'm running ancient technology here.
It's okay. I was using it.
But anyway, was there anything else, John?
Did you have anything else to ask or conclude?
No, just really the whole take on the Treaty of Paris thing.
I mean, we got a little off track on it, but I understand greatly what you're talking about.
I'm sorry about that, but I just thought I would...
You seem such a knowledgeable individual. I thought you would appreciate that little bit of information.
Oh, yeah, I greatly do.
See, I've been doing this a real long time, and I've got to meet quite a few interesting people.
And the issue I have in dealing with the general people is they really don't get how everything is tied together.
And yes, it's all tied through treaties.
I mean, you get these nutbags like Turner and his groups talking about the corporation and talking about the Constitution,
and they've never even heard of the Treaty of Paris and how it affects everything.
Yeah, well, he needs to go to Independence Hall in Philadelphia and take a look at it.
Well, I think he needs to go there.
I think it's still there. I'm not sure. That's where it was when I saw it.
For the gentlemen, so they know, John has a call every Sunday on talk show,
and John covers the foreclosure fraud and the mortgage fraud, and so he's quite knowledgeable.
John, would you get a hold of me? I've got some information you might find useful in that area.
Sure, sure. How do I do that?
You can just send me an email, John, and I'll forward it to him.
Yeah, I've got some stuff that was just filed in the Washington State Supreme Court relative to foreclosure fraud that I think you might find useful.
Boy, I appreciate that. I mean, I disperse a lot of information.
We actually win quite a few cases, and like you guys, we're not in it for the money.
We're just trying to save people. I mean, I literally have it broken.
Exactly, exactly.
The point where I hate money is it makes people do stupid shit every day.
That's disgusting.
Yeah, in fact, get an email to me, and I'll give you my private contact info,
and I think we can have a couple of interesting conversations.
Oh, I appreciate that greatly.
Louis, if you want, I can just, well, well, go ahead. I'm sorry.
Yeah, Angela, just when you get a minute, send me over his email, or send him my email, or both at the same time.
Yeah, either one or all of them.
I can send him your number, John. How's that?
Yeah, that's great, too.
Okay.
And we'll touch base, and I really appreciate it.
I'm taking up a lot of your time, and I know a lot of people are just hammering to talk to you guys, so I appreciate it.
I'm on your guys' side.
I probably agree with everything you guys believe and teach, and I've got time.
Well, there's something wrong with you, then.
You better go take a couple aspirin and call us tomorrow.
Oh, there's all kinds of things wrong with me, and I've got people who'll tell you what they are.
All right, John.
Hey, appreciate talking to you.
Thanks for coming on, John.
Anybody else have a question?
Press star 8.
Angela, can you ask the name of the Indians again?
Oh, what's the name of the tribe?
You didn't mention the name, actually.
No, I didn't.
I will have to spell it for you, because I can only give you an approximate English spelling,
because they have a couple of sounds in their language which don't translate to English.
Okay.
Sound it out for us.
It's W-I-L-P-S.
Whoops.
And the middle name is Dachshund.
It's as close as you can do in English.
It's D-A-A-X with an underline, A-N, hyphen, Sachs, S-A-X, N.
Welch, Dachshund, Sachsund.
Uh-huh.
There's a hyphen between Welch and Dachshund and a hyphen between Dachshund and Sachsund.
And like I say, I can't quite form the Native American words exactly, but that's close.
Let's see here.
Kodiak123 is asking, are they on Vancouver Island?
No, they're on the mainland.
Okay.
Anyone else?
Their reservation covers most of the southwestern quarter of British Columbia.
A lot of what people think are crown land is actually their reservation.
Well, I wasn't a party to all that, so.
But anyway.
Well, I'm not sure how I became party to it, but it happened, so, you know.
It's been very interesting having a relation with them.
Well, I hope it's been a good one.
Well, I don't know yet, but I find it very interesting.
We have a question from southeast Arizona.
Go ahead.
Well, good evening, Angela.
It's the Greek, and good evening to your guests.
Hi.
How are you tonight?
I'm doing quite well, and I'm quite inspired by the courage of these men,
and I sympathize with their hardship.
Oh, thank you.
Yes, I frequent these calls, and very seldom am I motivated to call,
and when I see acts of courage coming from men these days,
I feel like I just have to say something about it, and that's why I said it.
I wanted to add a few things based on my study,
because when you've got something that you think might help someone,
you should share it with them, whether they accept it or use it is up to them.
Thus, it's not advice.
What inspired me to call was how you folks earlier mentioned the involvement of what's called
the Holy or Sacred Roman Empire.
I've been researching this now for quite a few years, as well as been researching words
and how words are a technology, and how people are word controlled,
and also how that ties in with the power base there.
One thing I wanted to share with you are two things, actually.
One is a few words and meanings of words, and also the current state of the involvement
of the Vatican, of course.
Many people with a little bit of research can see it goes back almost into time immemorial,
back to the Caesars.
Basically, to sum it up, the governments of the world have the temporal power,
and the Vatican maintains the spiritual power.
In other words, the governments of the world look to the Vatican for their spiritual approval
or blessing.
Unfortunately, unawares to most people, but aware to some, it has nothing to do
with anything biblical, other than there is a real spiritual world that masters
and governs and controls this physical temporal world.
Now, what's been going on at the Vatican over the past two centuries,
and I want to tie that in with the Native Americans, is they've become increasingly
fascinated and, for lack of a better word, overzealous and greedy with dealing
with the spiritual world through the summoning of entities and evocation.
I found documents in private libraries where, as the armies came across this country
and met the Native people here, there was always a Jesuit following that was very interested
in their knowledge and power of evocation and of medicine men and what spirits dwelt here,
which was not normal for the regular people that came here, the white men,
let's say, to conquer understood.
And once they met these old men or medicine men, let's say, that retained this ancient wisdom
or knowledge of this, they quickly retained or got as much of it as possible
and then got rid of them, and they sat in that position.
Now, of course, the common Western man today is very unfamiliar
with the spiritual reality of things, and I am not a spiritualist or anything like that,
but this is secular history that I'm speaking from.
This is not my opinion. These are things that I've discovered.
Now, fast forward, the current intelligence agencies of the world,
as you, with very little research you can see, are based out of the same system,
out of the Vatican, if you look at the international intelligence agencies,
and we don't need to name them.
And also, I have gotten some of this information from some people of the Din,
Dinali, which are called Navajo.
If you actually investigate on what's going on in Arizona with them and the Jesuits today,
anybody can research it. These might be considered medieval in thought,
because, again, like I said, the modern man is not in touch with the spiritual reality.
They think this is hocus-pocus, but they still play a very important role in that end.
So I just wanted to share that with you, that you will come across indirectly with those powers,
in one way or another, whether you're trying to do the right thing or the wrong thing.
Secondly, through my research, I would like to just invite you to consider the meaning
of two words that I've discovered, and it's very difficult to speak the truth about this to people
because of the indoctrination over many centuries.
The two words, one of them is justice, and the other word is democracy.
And I'd like to just share with you the etymological roots of those words.
For example, if you say chandelier, well, you know, that's a French word, it means ornament.
That's the etymology of it.
So justice, if you look at it, forensically, let's say, not even that deep,
but if you look at the etymological and do some forensic study,
you will see that justice is an ancient right.
It is a religious order. It has nothing to do with law.
It is a portion of secular, temporal, and spiritual power that merged
to create what's called the court system.
And it's represented frequently throughout the world.
Wikipedia has an excellent page on it because it displays the statues of justice or justicia
in about 30 different countries.
The statue of a woman, she's not blind, but she's blindfolded,
and she's carrying a sword and scales.
And you can trace its roots back to Babylon,
and it has to do with feudalism and other things like that.
So when you look at the preamble and the Constitution,
the forefathers did state that they came here to establish justice.
Now, what people don't realize is that 90% of the people that left Europe
came here to escape justice because it was destroying them.
So that's just one thing I'd like for you to consider, and I will not continue.
The second word I'd like for you to consider etymologically is the word democracy.
And the etymological root of that word means, well, it's a Greek word.
The suffix is krasis, or krasi, which is a governing body.
And the first prefix part of that word, demo,
the accurate translation of that is if you look up the planet Mars,
and it has two moons.
What are the two moons of Mars? Phobos and Deimos.
Phobos means fear, and Deimos means terror.
So democracy literally means terror state or terror rule.
And if you've been watching the news in the past 10 years,
you can see that it's coming to its fruition.
Now, what you believe or what you think is not relevant to what I'm saying,
I'm just telling you what I've discovered in the root use of words.
And also if you look at the establishment of a democratic form of government
here under public policy under FDR, if you look at the actual chronology of it,
it was also the establishment and worldwide support of the Nazi state in Germany.
Nazi state, I'm not talking about the German people, I'm talking about the Nazis.
That all happened at the same time, and I think it was 1933.
If you go do some research at Time Magazine, guess who was man of the year?
Adolf Hitler.
He had worldwide support.
The only thing is he discovered that he doesn't have to be subjected to the bankers
when he can print all of his own money based on the labor and resources of Germany.
And then the banker said, uh-oh, he kind of backfired on us.
But, you know, they had put certain things in place that allowed it to come down.
But the German people lost the war, the Nazis didn't.
Yes, and if you actually look at the financier who followed the money,
Martin Bormann, which started out with a young Adolf Hitler had,
well, his mistress was his niece.
And it just so happened that she was suicided,
and it happened to be done with Hitler's gun.
So Hitler at the time knew a detective named Goebbels,
and he says, can you take care of this for me?
And he said he knew one of the people in the police named Martin Bormann.
Yeah, we'll take care of it for you.
And Hitler remembered these men as he rose in power.
Now, Martin Bormann is a type of character that makes,
well, he's kind of like Dick Cheney without all the warmth and charm.
Okay, and these people have escaped.
You know, I don't want to get into it, but this is what's going on today.
And one example of this might be if you look at the recent bailouts
and the lack of oversight and the lack of response to where the money went,
you're looking at a group of people, meaning the banking interceders,
the bankers that are interceding on the political scene.
If you look at the bluntness and rejection of any answer whatsoever,
you're looking at a bunch of people that are in desperate shape.
They are desperate, as if someone is holding a gun to their head.
Now, if you can piece things together with a little bit of the history I've given you,
you can almost see that this international Nazi contingency is still in place.
And Bormann was quoted as writing that whether we lose the war or not is irrelevant.
We are here to create an elastic, political, extraterritorial state.
So he knew the language of the New World Order.
So I'm going to leave you with that, and please investigate justice
because you will be coming across that term, and it can be used against you.
And if you seek justice, please examine what you're seeking,
because it's an old mystical rite that can be traced to Babylon and beyond,
and it's been adopted here.
And I'll leave you off with this.
Avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
And with that said, thank you for having me, Angela, and blessings to both of these men.
Well, thank you.
Always interesting when he comes on, he has such great information.
Keeps us captivated.
Thanks. Let's see here.
Zizek has a question for you guys.
If I can unmute him.
I'm clicking it, but oh, there we go.
I'm here.
There you go.
There I am.
He's got a question.
Hi.
I don't know if this is so much of a question, but I'm sorry.
I can't buy so much of that stuff.
And the reason why is because what we have is a tower of Babel here,
and there is no government.
I mean, every time we use a euphemism or some kind of a fictitious name
to describe some kind of mindset that is behind things,
we don't draw credence to an actual mind behind things.
What we're dealing with here in this world right now is a cascading array of leftover language
that people don't even understand.
And it's not so much that the history of the language goes back to Greek or Latin
and all that because people don't even understand Greek and Latin,
and maybe even I don't believe even the courts do.
And I'll tell you the reason why is because if they did,
they wouldn't be in the positions they are.
This is a world of greed in every capacity.
That whole line where he says, oh, the governments look to the Vatican for spiritual guidance,
there is no government like a brain, like an individual, like some kind of entity
that's actually saying, oh, what's the Vatican?
The Vatican is the name of a city.
And it's like one entity can't talk, a fictition can't talk to another fiction
unless it's all fiction.
If it's all fiction, then what are we talking about here?
It's absurd to even say such things.
It's like when they say, well, the statesman in Manhattan is not going to do this or that
or is not going to do this or is going to do this.
There is no chaste Manhattan.
There are people behind this thing and all the corruption that's going on on this planet.
And it's virtually turned into a cannibal planet in all these monetary and financial circles,
and they're just out there to eat everything they can.
And I'll tell you what, here's a really interesting fact that I figured out,
is I got really into this law thing, and I found I got a rush out of actually figuring it out
and actually figuring out how this thing works and actually solving some problems legally.
And I said, you know what, it's really weird.
This is an addiction.
And I kind of contend these people in these legal systems and this government
are all addicted to this thing, and it's not the addiction to anything.
I mean, who would want to work behind these benches and listen to these whining people
who are irresponsible to themselves, who would live in no honor day after day after day
so they could get a retirement and sit on their fat asses and eat freaking bonbons
or say, I'm going to go to Hawaii and sit there.
I've had friends go on worldwide trips, and the only Americans you see on these worldwide trips out there
are these fat, loathing pigs that travel the world outside of the ultra-rich,
maybe like Donald Trump or something like that, who has his own limousine and stuff like that.
But the general Americans and even judges, they might have a retirement,
but they're not getting dynamically rich.
Take a breath. Take a breath.
You're going a million miles an hour here.
What are you trying? What point are you trying?
I think I understand what you're trying to do.
The point is really this.
It's like, to say these entities have a mind behind this is absolutely absurd
because there are no minds.
There's individuals, just like George Bush saying, oh, we're the compassionate nation.
Who's he talking about? He doesn't know anything about compassion.
He doesn't know the first thing about compassion or even what the word means.
It's like, nation is compassion.
I walk here in this living world with living people, and they're virtually dead.
They're zombies.
And I don't see any compassion in it because they would say, hey, you know what?
Support the veterans.
Meanwhile, they're talking about the veterans from one war,
but meanwhile there's veterans from three wars back sitting on the street saying,
help me out.
And they overlook them, and they've got these nice big yellow ribbons on their bumpers and stuff.
We've got an unconscious society, and I don't really see any hope of really waking it up.
The only thing that's going to happen is each and every individual has to wake up themselves
and take a little clue.
Most people do have a little spirit.
That's a living man.
It's not an entity.
You go into these courts, if you assert that living man,
you're going to go into court one way or the other.
You're in court every single day.
When you go into these places, you're being the living man,
and you listen to the way these people are talking.
You can address the issue exactly like that,
and you can win because I don't care what their laws are that they want to propose
to push on people.
You can try to grind people into, like, these little melons.
I went to a water board meeting last night.
There were only 440 people there trying to hold back an entity.
I said, who are they addressing?
The people on the board are all virtually kind of like volunteers who get a little stipend,
and they're trying to, like, raise the water rates up in the local area,
$4 per person per month, as if it's not a big thing.
You've got 61,000 people putting $4 a piece in per month.
Okay, all right.
Where are we going with this, sweetie?
Well, where we're going with it essentially is this.
It's like people have got to stop talking about these entity names
as if they have a consciousness.
That's really what comes down.
You're talking about the banks of this, the oil companies of this.
Well, then how do we refer to them?
There's Bernanke.
He runs the Federal Reserve.
Don't talk about the Federal Reserve.
Turn to Bernie, man.
The Bernie man.
The Bernanke.
Or talk about the Vatican.
Why are we talking about the Pope?
The Pope, he's an old man who can barely friggin' walk.
It's a collection of a bunch of people.
If they really wanted to help humanity,
they cut loose with some of that Vatican gold.
They're not interested in helping humanity.
They're interested in herding the sheep.
They're not interested in educating the population.
I'll have to have you on a call all to yourself so that you can go into this.
I'm sorry, but this language about giving these entities
some kind of power over our lives,
there is no.
There's no brain to our government, even.
Everybody's looking at a snake that has no head.
You know what I mean?
Anyway, my two cents in there.
I'll catch up with you next time.
Thank you very much, Angela.
Thank you.
That was interesting.
Does anyone else have a question for our gentleman guest?
Press star eight.
I have to check here.
Okay, New York City.
Hold on one second.
I'm trying.
There we go.
Go ahead, New York City.
Did you have a question?
Hey, New York City.
Can you hear me?
Yes, go ahead, Harold.
Hi.
How are you doing?
Fine, thank you.
Okay, interesting conversation.
Going back to the caller before the machine gun had unloaded,
I had agreed with most of what he had brought out,
but there was a point that he brought out with regards to Adolf Hitler.
Hitler, based on my research, and I've done perhaps close to 30 years of research,
dealing in the matters of the Vatican, and he was a made man.
He had a talent that they tapped into.
He didn't write Mann Kampf.
He was brought along, coached along.
He was brought along by Jesuits, as he mentioned that their powers is.
And with regards to when he mentioned Vatican or these corporate entities,
I think most of us know it's the people behind them that makes it move.
I hope most people do because, you know,
a corporation can't do nothing without its representative agents.
So that's a given.
That's a given.
But, yes, I agree with the last caller, you know,
we ought to recognize who's doing what.
Yes, that's true.
Even in my legal writing, you know,
I don't say the corporate appellee states or this.
No, no, it's counsel talking or whatever record they're referring to.
No, I agree in that regard.
But in the overall context of things, I think most of us on this call
and the majority of people that visit your forum have an understanding that
when we speak of corporate, we're talking about the people behind it
that using the corporate shield to do their devilment.
But words do play a key role because the spiritual entities,
as someone alluded to earlier,
that is their way of manipulating the human family.
Because they don't have physical power over us,
they do it through the mind.
And how do they communicate it?
Through words.
So, yes, words do play a key role in how this whole system goes.
And there is a lineage and a root.
And whether people want to believe it or not,
that which is unseen actually controls that which is seen.
And with regards to our guests tonight,
that is something that they have to be prepared for also
because it's not what we see in the letter,
the men that are sitting on the bench, the paperwork that's being exchanged,
but what is the source behind it.
And also with regards with those that bring in the element of the spiritual dynamic
of where we're at in this day and time,
we have to take into account where we are in that history.
And there are some things that we're not going to change.
I mean, so far the majority of the prophecies have been fulfilled.
On the dying.
So why are we going to think that we can change that which has already been forecast?
So, yes, there's some things within our circumference that we can, you know,
have some control over because we have little control over anything
and sometimes not even ourselves.
So as one person said it, save yourself from this untoward generation
because what we're dealing with is bigger than ourselves.
And until the Redeemer comes again, we're not going to change a whole lot.
We can change some, yes, but not a whole lot.
And we have to. We have to look at reality.
We have to look at reality.
The brief that was written up, the appeal document, wonderful.
And I wish it all the best.
But I do realize some dynamics that is beyond us.
And if it's not meant to be, we can't put a square into a circle.
And right now the people that are in charge at this moment, you know,
their time is limited.
I just hope and pray that there is some room for this petition
and perhaps some things can be changed.
But overall, based on the way history has played out thus far,
and I'm a student of history, the dynamics of history repeating itself,
I heard somebody bring it up several times before,
how we're living in 1930s Germany right now.
I've been saying that for years.
You know, people used to laugh at me.
Now people call on me and say, oh, you were right.
I've been talking about this 10, 15 years ago.
But now that things are being accelerated
and the people that are behind it, they're not even hiding anymore.
They put the stuff right in front of your face now.
They even tell you what they're going to do.
And people still don't see it.
Okay, so what are you suggesting?
Well, we're all talking about the problems.
We all know the problem.
We all know the system.
What's your solution?
Like I said before, dealing with things in your circumference
and getting yourself connected to your creator,
there's not a whole lot we're going to do to change the system.
We can change, perhaps.
Okay, then I'm sorry.
You have nothing to contribute.
And I hate to be rude, but acceptance is not the human condition.
It never has been.
It's not what my creator taught me.
What did your creator teach you, and who is your creator?
That I am a god.
I have the power of god.
I can change my world.
I have to change my world.
My gift of freedom is a gift from my creator that if I forsake it,
I am forsaking the gifts of my god.
I can't do that.
Okay, I have to respect that.
We're not talking about the same creator.
Okay, then there we go.
And we have to agree to disagree.
There you go.
And I thank you very much for your time.
Thank you.
Okay.
If anyone has a question, press star 8.
However, we have gone.
What?
I wish I had been thinking a little quicker
because I would have told them that if too many people had accepted that
viewpoint, then slavery would still be on this continent.
It would still be in the world.
Yep.
Not just this continent.
It is still in places of this world who accepted the status quo.
Yep.
But I didn't think quick enough.
Sorry about that.
Okay.
All right, West Michigan.
Go ahead, Matt.
Did you hang up?
What?
I'm sorry.
Hold on a second.
Matt, hold on.
Harold is still.
Go ahead, Harold.
No, I'm still here.
And I heard what he said.
But contrary to what many people believe, we're still enslaved.
And I'll leave it at that.
Yes, we are because we allow our minds to be controlled by the status quo,
and we're not willing to fight for our gifts.
But anyway, please watch what happens, and we'll all learn from it no matter
what.
Okay.
Go ahead, West Michigan.
Actually, I think that Harold and your guest tonight are both on the same page
because there are some things in prophecy that it said this was going to
happen, that's going to happen, something else is going to happen.
But guess what?
It takes us to make it happen.
So you're both right.
If there's things that are going to be, we are in Germany 1933.
That makes sense.
But there were a whole bunch of people back then that knew something was
wrong and tried to do something about it, and obviously it failed.
Now, if there's a whole bunch of us, and hopefully history is a good teacher
here, if there's a whole bunch of us, more of us, that know more things to do
that will be successful or potentially successful and go out and do it, we
might well be able to preclude some of these problems.
Now, you alluded a little bit earlier to Sherwood Rodriguez, who has a Supreme
Court decision back in 1982.
Well, hey, if he was able to do that and take a couple of municipalities out
of federal control, more power to him.
But he had to be the one to actually go ahead and do it.
Somebody has to be there to go ahead and cast the first ballot, throw the first
stone, or fire the first gun.
Somebody has to be there to do it.
But that's how practicing is fulfilled.
Everybody just decided, okay, I'm not going to do anything.
I'm not going to do anything to change the system.
All I'm going to do is when I get up in the morning, I'm going to worry about
food, clothing, and shelter, and nothing else.
If it means go along to get along, I'll do it.
If it means I have to go do something illegal, I'll do it.
But food, clothing, and shelter, period.
I'm not going to get involved politically.
I'm not going to try to change anything.
I'm just going to let the thing roll off the edge, but I'll protect myself.
I guarantee you, if a lot of people that I know that are in the so-called
Patriot Movement or around these calls or what have you, if they took all,
myself included, right now, if I had taken all the time, effort, and energy that
I had over the last 20 years and decided, Matt, all you're going to worry about
is your bank balance, I would be a millionaire today, no doubt.
But I've got myself involved in a whole bunch of political activities,
and because of that, I'm not.
I'm not complaining about it.
It's just the fact it's the way things are.
So you're both on the right page.
You're both in the same book.
You're just both not on the same page tonight.
But I just wanted to point that out because I've listened to Harold over the
last few months, back over the last few years,
and he's on the same page the rest of us are.
So I just wanted to point that out.
Well, we're all on the same page.
We just got a little bit different point of view, that's all.
And I want to let it be known, because most of you all know this already,
I don't take a pacifist stand and just take it.
No, I've been fighting on behalf of others for the last 25 years,
often with no pay.
So, no, don't get that twisted and take that out of context.
I'm just talking about the overall scheme of things regarding prophecy.
That cannot be changed.
No, but if we don't try, then we are not worthy of our gifts.
I mean, if we don't try, then are we human?
Are we any better than the sheep and the cattle being herded?
I mean, my problem is that, and Louis, you know, we've both been through this.
We've been through the ringer.
We've seen how corrupt the system is.
We've seen very good people, and I worked with Bernard Von Nodhaus.
He, you know, what happened to him was a travesty.
Is he a perfect character?
No, he's got his flaws.
Okay, but because he wasn't able to defend himself,
he potentially is going to prison for a long, long time.
Well, probably a death sentence because he's already 68 years old.
Okay?
You know, why aren't the people rising up in support of him?
Why do we allow our fellow brothers in this freedom movement
to be taken down one by one?
Why do we accept it?
Why do we sit by idly?
I agree with you 100%,
and I'm one of those people that has been in the mix since 87,
doing just that, helping out those that can't help themselves.
Well, when I ran my own company, which I did for a number of years,
we had a motto in the company.
That was, if you do it once, you do it well.
If you do it twice, you automate it.
And what I see is that so many people are fighting the same fight,
going into their local courts and getting their butts handed to them,
getting their, you know, kicked where they don't want to be kicked,
that we can't win the overall war individually in the local courts.
They just divide and conquer us and they wear us out.
True.
The only thing I knew to do, and Lewis and I talked about this a lot,
is to take the final push to the place where it belongs,
which is the Supreme Court.
I don't think anybody disagrees with that.
Whether or not they're going to give us what we want,
well, that's not within our control.
What is within our control is to put the best effort forward
to make the right arguments and expose the system for what it is,
and if then we lose, that is a win.
That's instructional.
Because we've done what we're supposed to do,
and we've given it all we can,
and I can accept the results no matter what they are,
because then I know that anyone else following behind us is not going to succeed,
that there is no chance, there is no remedy,
which the patriots like to talk about.
So let's go do this one thing,
and then if you want to go down the road of getting rid of the Constitution
a la Dr. Livingston, fine, we can have that discussion.
Everything is on the table at that point,
but I don't buy that you have to pull over this.
You need more exposure.
We're going to get it, but you can't do that until the suit is written.
We talked to people beforehand, and they said,
great, let us know when you get it done so we can see something.
Well, we just published it last week, and it is going around like crazy.
Now people have something they can sink their teeth into.
Now we can have a discussion about what it really is instead of somebody's pipe dream.
So we can all jump on board and make it go viral, because that's what we do.
When something is righteous, we do it.
You guessed it. That's what it's going to take. That's what we want.
I know. Me too. Me too.
I mean, there's a lot of tasks out there,
but what we have to do is direct it in such a way that it can accomplish what we want.
Not that we're looking for a field general or anything like that,
but if we don't hang together,
we're all going to hang separately in some famous last words.
That's true.
All right, so direct everyone again to your website,
where I highly recommend you read the lawsuit.
It's posted there, right?
Yes, it's posted there at usav.me.
Okay. I also have a link to it on the poster there,
and I'll have it also on the guest speaker's pages.
I have links to all your stuff, your radio broadcast,
your websites, and the limited...
I have four documents.
Thank you, by the way, Lewis, but I already had that one.
Okay.
I have like four documents from the case,
but if there's anything else you'd like to send over,
I'll get it up there so people can look at it from the Waller case,
from the other, you know, the original,
the thing you were found not guilty of.
I don't really have anything to say from that.
What we do with that case later on
will be separate and apart from our Supreme Court case.
Okay.
First thing is I want to make this country a place where my son can grow up
and enjoy what my grandfather enjoyed.
Yeah, what our forefathers died for.
Our ancestors, you know.
And it wasn't $254 a month in Social Security.
No.
All right, is there anything else?
Well, wait, wait, wait.
Let's see if there's any more questions.
Anybody else?
Press star eight if you have any questions.
No? Okay, good.
We can close it down.
It's been two hours and 11 minutes of interesting conversation.
I really appreciate you guys coming on,
and I hope you come on again and update us on how it goes,
and maybe we can watch the country come back to the way it's supposed to be.
Well, it's either going to be dead or it's going to be torn apart.
I hope not.
Well, nobody's going to be able to sit on the sidelines with us.
You know, the people who think that they are entitled to other people's property
and, oh, by the way, folks, if you haven't seen Atlas Shrugged,
go see the movie, support it, read the book,
because it's the movie that the powers that be don't want you to experience
because it talks about the moochers in society.
So go take a look at that and understand that that's where we're coming from.
Either you're going to be totally for us if you are able to care for yourself,
or the people are going to be totally against us if you're a moocher on society.
And so that's the whole idea with this is we have to decide what kind of country we are.
The one that was successful was the one that allowed people to care for themselves.
There was far less poverty in this country before Social Security.
There was a whole lot more freedom before the bankruptcy in 1933.
And so it's time.
The North Carolina Constitution says that a return to the foundations of law,
the Constitution, are necessary for the preservation of liberty.
We are going to have to go back to the founding documents.
Were they perfect? No.
Were there some issues? Probably.
But it's a darn good place to start.
And if I was living under the Constitution today, I'd be a happy camper.
Yeah, be a better place.
Much better place.
We've got one more question.
Do you want to stick around for one more?
Sure, go for it.
Okay, Ray Shaw II, go ahead.
I just wanted him to repeat what he said that movie was.
Atlas shrugged.
Like the big guy Atlas that had the world on his shoulders, he shrugged.
If you haven't read the book, it was Ayn Rand's opus.
It took her 12 years to write.
If you don't know who Ayn Rand was, I highly recommend you go read her biography.
What she went through as a Russian prisoner and everything before she ever came to this country, it's quite astounding.
And once you read the book, you'll find that phrases, it took her from 1940 to 1952 to write the book.
And it's about the collapse of society.
And you will find that phrases and words and quotes from the book are being uttered today in the public without their even being conscious of it
because what she wrote about 60 years ago is now coming to pass in this country.
So another 1984, huh?
Well, it's more detailed than 1984.
1984 was about concepts that could happen at the governmental level.
Ayn Rand is about the details, about the psyches of men, about what happens to good nations.
Good nations that go bad.
So I'm trying to get the word out.
My wife and my family, we just went and saw it.
Even my 10-year-old little girl got it.
It's the first part of three, so you're only going to see part one of the movie, the whole thing.
They're being very true to the book because you really couldn't have fixed.
Of course, it's a 1,400-page book, so obviously they had to shorten it down.
But if you haven't read the book, the Library of Congress admits that behind the Bible,
it is the book that most people say has influenced them most in their life, behind the Bible.
It's number two in the Library of Congress for the most influential writings of all time.
That ought to put it in perspective for you.
Okay, we have one more.
Was that it for you, Rayshaw?
Yes.
Okay, thank you so much.
Okay, go ahead, Oyak.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Okay.
I thought it would be interesting to toss this into the mix.
You sound like you're underwater.
Wait a minute.
Change phones.
I don't have anything but this microphone, Angela.
This is all I have.
All right.
Well, we'll try to listen real hard.
Go ahead.
Is it any better now?
No, you still sound underwater.
Just talk loud.
There's a book by the name of Vatican Assassin, Wounded in the House of My Friends by Eric John Feltz.
I don't know if any of you have ever read it, but it's quite interesting.
On page 225 of that book, there are a few paragraphs I'd like to read to you.
Like Cromwell, it was Washington who wept on his mother's neck after he heard her last words.
You will see me no more, but you, George, fulfill the highest destinies which heaven has assigned you.
Go, my son, and may heaven and your mother's blessing be with you always.
Having released all his slaves, it was Washington who brought each colony into statehood.
For in the Treaty of Paris in 1783, they were declared to be free, independent, and sovereign.
I assume he's referring to the slaves at that point.
I don't know for sure.
It was Washington.
What?
Are you still there?
Something went haywire in my computer.
I've got to stop some stuff here. Hang on a minute.
Well, I think we got the gist of what you're talking about.
Just call it good.
What?
He said just call it good.
Okay. Thank you.
Anyone else?
Okay. If no one else has any questions, we're going to close it down.
It's been a good 2 hours and 18 minutes.
And for those of you that came on late, it's recorded, so you can go back and listen.
It was a really good call.
Again, thank you, gentlemen.
I appreciate your time and all your energy and sacrifice that you're sticking your neck out for, you know,
something that's righteous and good and the good of the country and the future.
And I appreciate what you've done, and we love you.
And we're going to make your efforts worthwhile.
My pleasure.
And will you come on again and update us as things progress?
Be happy to.
Okay, great. Thank you so much.
It's what we do now.
That's wonderful.
And we're also going to listen to you on Saturdays on Republic Broadcasting and catch your show.
Thanks so much.
All right, everybody.
It's been a good one.
I love you.
I'll see you on Sunday with Jon Stewart and then on Monday with Dave.
And that's a wrap.
Thanks, Angela.
Everyone, be blessed.
Thanks, Harold.