Hi everyone, it's Thursday, October 21st, and tonight our special guest is the Greek.
Maybe you heard him last week when we were on and he spoke a little bit about some esoteric things and Bible prophecy.
Hi Greek, how are you tonight?
Well hello Angela, and hello everyone. Thanks for having me.
Oh yes, looking forward to this one. I'm excited actually that you're on.
So you're going to fill our heads with all kinds of new things, right, that we've never heard about.
I hope so, in a good way.
I'm going to get some critical thinking going and powers of discernment,
and when we take in information we can process it right.
Not to say that I have the right way of processing it, but we all are so capable,
and I look around and I see just people operating not in a way that they can.
And it's kind of like you have a Ferrari and you're going down the road at 50 miles an hour all the time,
and I say, well this thing does 80 miles an hour in second gear, did you know that?
And it's like, well no, well there it is, go for it.
So we have a lot of potential and there's so much information to take in,
but all that information is not really useful unless you can use it or process it right.
And I came on the call and I wanted to get in touch with Greg because we have a similar heritage
and kind of give out some information along the lines.
And he did bring up the scripture and what people call the Bible,
and by the way the Bible just means the book.
And years ago they used to call it the good book, right?
It's kind of a cultural thing. I like to call it, I go between the Bible and the scriptures.
And I figured, well, if people are on this call for four hours and he's making biblical references
and they haven't thrown eggs and tomatoes yet,
maybe I can go on there and speak on the Bible a little bit one day.
And here I am.
Well, have at it. Where would you like to begin? I know there's so much.
What intrigued me about what you said was you mentioned something about the months,
like October and November and December and what those words mean,
but they don't correspond to what we think they mean.
Why don't you go start with that a little bit.
Time. Yes, time is very important.
We need it for navigating. We need it for keeping appointments.
It's part of our sensory perception.
And again, part of the critical thinking aspect,
there's a saying in every lie there's a little bit of the truth.
For example, something that's counterfeit has to look very much like the original.
And all these things are in front of us. We just can't discern them and don't discern them.
Like, for example, sept is a prefix for seven. Oct is a prefix for eight.
Nova is a prefix for nine. And dec or decimal is a prefix for ten.
So sept in its name itself is actually calling out the seventh month.
October is the eighth month. November is the ninth month.
And December is the tenth month.
Yet, in the legal commercial system, they stick a number in there
and they make September 9 and so on and so forth up until December being 12.
And no one's standing up and saying, wait a second,
if December means 10, why is it the 12th month?
Right. I never even thought about it, you know?
It's right there in front of our faces, but don't even think about it.
Right. Now here's another little interesting anomaly.
If you look up the history of the U.S. presidents,
then you'll find that George Washington is the only president that was born in both 1732
and he was also born in 1733. Can you tell me how that's possible?
No. How does that work?
Right. In 1750, they went into the current reckoning of time that we're using today,
or I should say the people of this planet are using today,
and they went ahead and made some adjustments before that.
So they wanted to just change the records to reflect that change in 1750,
so they went back and started changing records and just bumped everything up a year.
So you really don't even know what year you're in, really.
Really.
And what day is it?
Here's the interesting part.
The days are functions of weeks, the weeks are functions of months,
and the months are functions of years.
You'll say, well, there are 12 months in a year,
there are four weeks in a month, and there are seven days in a week.
So you have these various functions.
So I started looking at the religious groups,
and they say, well, the command says on the seventh day you should rest.
Well, if the week is a function of a month,
let's start with the Christians first.
Well, they say they're observing the commandment,
and Sunday is the seventh day of rest.
But what if it's June 1st on a Saturday?
Well, isn't Sunday the second day of the week there?
Or third day of the week?
How are you resting on the seventh day of the week
when the first day of the month was just a day or two ago?
Do you see my point?
Yeah, but explain it to me, because I don't really understand it.
Okay, in Judaism they say we observe the Sabbath,
and Saturday is the Sabbath.
Okay, so let's say it's the first day of the month on a Wednesday.
Well, let's see, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, that's the third day.
So how can it be the seventh day when your month just started a few days ago?
See, the week is a function of the month.
The first day of the month is the first day of the month.
The day after that is the first day of your first week.
That's complicated very quickly, doesn't it?
Yeah, it does. I don't quite get it.
It's the first day of the month.
Well, here's another way.
Let's look at another function of time.
It's 2010, right?
Well, you turn on the TV or something, go to the history channel,
and they say, well, the dinosaurs lived 60 million years ago.
Well, why isn't it 60 million 2010, then?
What happened to all the other years?
It's kind of like the emperor has no clothes kind of thing.
Well, they just rounded it off, or what?
Nope, nope.
It's just when I was speaking to someone that does manage time,
they said, well, this is just something that we all agree on.
Oh, really?
Okay.
So because everyone agrees on everything, it makes it true.
I see.
How about if everyone agreed that the Earth was flat?
So when you turned on the television, you know, everything on TV said the Earth was flat.
The church, the school, your doctor, your priest, everyone says the Earth is flat.
Government says the Earth is flat.
So here you go, and you make this globe, you know, globe of the Earth,
and you start proving the Earth is round.
It's not flat.
You know, everyone's going to say, well, everybody knows the Earth is flat.
What are you talking about?
No, they just don't see.
You see, it's information that's in front of us.
It's very easy to prove the Earth is round and it's not flat,
but yet everyone can be convinced the other.
Here's another maybe way to look at it.
I'd like to go maybe through some mental stretching before we go right into the run.
And time can be complicated because we're taught time probably before we're taught how to tie our shoelaces.
And if you were to bring an ancient that really knew how to tell time into our modern system,
he'd have a difficulty with the calendar and the clock as well,
where we just look at these things and they're automatic to us
because we've been trained to reckon time with these artificial creations,
and they're just tools.
But there is a way of keeping time that transcends the artificial and man-made creation,
and it's far more accurate.
But, again, this is like getting into an athletic event without stretching,
and my concept of conveying information might be to best do a little mental flexing first
and kind of get people in the mindset that maybe is required to convey this kind of information.
And it's very similar to how you asked about the monks.
And these things are all in front of us.
It's right in front of us, and we just don't see them because we've been told not to look at them
in a way that's not direct, but because everyone else does it this way
or this is the way it's done, we accept it as well.
Like everybody knows the bank lends money, right?
Everybody knows this is that, and everybody knows this is that.
You can find out otherwise.
Well, you're going to have a little bit of a struggle with it in your own mind as well.
Yeah, the bank doesn't loan money.
Yeah, but even when you first found it out...
Everybody doesn't know that.
I know, but even when you first find it out, you're like,
well, wait a second, how come my parents and my neighbor and everyone else told me they did?
So you kind of have to relax and meditate on it and say,
okay, everything's going to be fine, all right, I'm finding out the truth.
This is a different path now I'm on.
Here's another way to think about things that are right in front of us.
Okay, you notice how when the weather gets colder and winter comes around,
people start getting what's called the common cold and the flu in the colder weather.
We have refrigeration in our houses to put food in there to prevent it from spoiling
because the cold temperature prevents bacteria and other critters from growing
and actually makes them dormant, right?
That's how you preserve food in the cold.
But yet when cold weather comes around, people are getting the cold and the flu
and these little critters are being blamed for the cause.
But yet at the same time, we're creating a cold condition to slow these critters down.
So why are people getting sick in cold weather
when the actual cold weather is eliminating the bacteria
or making them dormant or slowing them down?
Why do people get sick when the weather changes to a colder temperature, you see?
It doesn't make any sense.
You see, when something is warm and then the bacteria are living on it,
they're going to multiply at a very high rate compared to when it's cold.
So why aren't people getting the common cold or quote-unquote flu season during the summer
when these little critters, you know, it's a perfect condition for them to be active and growing?
So why is it in the cold?
Why does it seem like the description of these little critters that are causing all these diseases
is going to be flipping and doing the opposite?
Why? Or maybe it's not these little critters that are making people sick in the first place, maybe.
You see?
What is it? Why?
Well, it has nothing to do with these little bugs
because in the winter when it gets colder, all these little bugs that everybody is blaming,
the scientific community is blaming all these diseases and colds and flus on,
well, they're just decreasing in number and going to sleep in the cold.
So what's really causing it, you see?
Because if you go to a regular biology class,
they'll tell you the cold will stop these pathogens and bacteria from growing.
So there's probably people saying, get to the point.
The idea is your body takes in food.
And the food that you take in, based on where that food will grow or does grow,
adjusts your body chemistry to that climate.
So if you're living in a cold weather climate and you eat tropical food,
like an orange or a banana,
that banana or orange is going to adjust your body chemistry to the tropics.
And your body is going to want to thin out your blood for the tropics,
but you're living in a cold climate or cold season when you should have thick blood.
So it's going to try to eliminate all those chemicals that are blood thinners
and it's going to make you sick in the process.
And if you ever notice all of the quote-unquote holidays that come around in the winter,
all the sugary treats and all that stuff,
where do those foods come from? The tropics.
So you end up eating all these foreign foods,
things that are not grown within your temperate climate,
and your body chemistry is adjusted to those foods, and now you get sick.
It's a very simple rule of thumb.
And if you look at places that have not commercialized transporting of food
from one region of the world to another, they have no common cold, they have no flu.
And if you study how commerce has advanced,
where it's okay to eat a banana or an orange in the winter in New York,
you'll notice that the amount of people that got the flu or the cold have increased since then.
It's very simple.
So your food should be more with your habitat, more in line with where you live.
Right. And then you've got, well, I'm a school teacher,
and when the children get a cold, I catch it too.
Well, not really. What happens on the weekend,
you'll see the school teacher pushing a food cart through the grocery store,
and there are the parents with the other children, and they're all buying bananas and oranges,
because they read somewhere that vitamin C keeps colds away.
Very few things are actually contagious that way.
I'm not a doctor, but I'm just doing this from historical observation
by just observing what's been going on historically.
So you're saying we get sick because we eat the wrong kinds of food at the wrong time of the year.
Yeah. Now, here's a very, yes, precisely.
Yep. Very simple, but very difficult to do.
You go into a grocery store, you see all these wonderful fruits and vegetables,
tomatoes all year round. Yeah, okay, great.
Bananas all year round. Go ahead. Enjoy.
It doesn't work. Let's look at the antithesis.
If you lived in the tropics and you ate some whale blubber,
which is what's used by the inhabitants of the northern climates,
they eat that because it thickens their blood to deal with those northern climates.
If you ate that whale blubber in the tropics, you'll probably die in a few days.
Sure. Yeah.
Some disease or something, you know, that they label.
We're going around, and what we're doing is we're claiming things by our wants
and our ignorance that we shouldn't be claiming.
I'm not saying you shouldn't, but I'm saying if you do claim it,
you have to pay the consequence.
It's all action, reaction, you see.
Yeah.
Now, whether you know about it or not, you know, you've heard, like,
ignorance of the law is not an excuse.
You know, if a yellow light means stop in China, and you just don't know that,
and you run it, well, they get stopped.
Well, now you've got to argue. I didn't know. It doesn't matter.
You have to sort of understand the rules and the laws of the place
before you start operating there.
Yeah.
And we are on the planet Earth, and things are set up a certain way,
and we're just trying to change them.
You know, here's maybe another thing in science.
For example, when you heat and cool your house,
the hot air always rises to the ceiling, and the cold air always goes to the floor.
Right.
So all year round, you've got a hot head and cold feet.
But in nature, when it's hot in the valley or at sea level,
where do you go to cool off?
Go to the mountaintop, higher in elevation.
So in nature, cold rises and heat goes down.
It becomes dense, and it sinks.
So why is it that when we either cool our houses or light a fire,
the heat goes the other way?
There's two opposite forces working there.
One is explosive, one is implosive.
One is based on the life-giving cycle.
The other one is based on the death-giving cycle.
One is based on growth.
One is based on chemical decomposition.
And that's why we're not getting a lot of progress in society scientifically,
because for the, let's say, good past 5,000 years,
most bodies of knowledge that are preserved and taught
are based on the death cycle, not on the life cycle.
That's why, for example, the medical community studies the death cycle.
They take cells, and they take them in the laboratory.
They've separated them from the living being, and they start decomposing.
And they study the chemicals that these decomposing cells give off.
So now they find a way to counteract the decomposition,
and they give it to you in a pill or an injection.
That must be good for you.
But when you study a living being,
there's some very complex processes going there.
So it sounds like we need an instruction manual.
It's kind of like no one's read the instruction manual.
Well, we have, but we read it wrong, I guess.
Yeah, where is it?
You know, here's the thing.
You know, there's a premise.
You can say that there is a supreme being, that there is a creator,
or you can say there isn't.
And if you're rational, either way,
you would accept statistically or mathematically,
if you were, let's say, adamant that there wasn't a creator or a creation,
in a debate or an argument,
you would have to accept the mathematical probability,
even how small it would be, that there is.
And then you can start looking at, from the point,
where it is possible that there is a creator.
Is it a benevolent creator or a malevolent creator?
Well, it could be one or the other.
If we look, we pick and see the benevolent route,
that he's a good creator,
just like any good creator or creator of a thing.
When you create something, you put an instruction manual in with it.
So if you create dishwashers, you have a dishwasher factory.
When you pack and ship these things, and they get to the end user,
when you unpack that dishwasher, you'll see, lo and behold,
there's an instruction manual in there.
Same thing with a television or a car or anything you buy
that requires some form of operation or usage has an instruction manual.
So if we follow on the premise that there is a creator and he is benevolent,
did he give us an instruction manual?
And could it be possible that this instruction manual was dictated to men
over a period of maybe 2,000 years?
And could it be possible that when we look at this instruction manual,
it tells you that one of our days, meaning the creator's days,
is equal to 1,000 of your years?
So if you start accepting the possibilities that these things are true,
I'm not saying to believe in them, but look at them from a mathematical perspective
and start reading the instruction manual.
In this case, I'm referring to the scriptures or what people call the Bible.
And understand that this is a message from another dimension,
from extraterrestrial beings.
When I say extraterrestrial beings, I'm not speaking of little green men
in a flying saucer.
It just means they're not here present right now on the planet physically.
You'll start to see that it actually makes sense.
And from that point of view, you see the content of what's in there.
And you'll see it does not agree with anything that's been taught about it.
If, for example, the religious aspect of the world says,
you've got to do this, this is this.
For example, this is who the Christ is.
This is what angels are.
This is what they call God is or whatever.
Well, you go and read the manual or the Bible,
and you're like, well, none of that seems to apply here.
I don't know where they got that information from.
It's not in here.
And when you look at it, and people will say,
well, you're taking that literally.
Well, guess what?
It's a literal document.
It's not oral.
I have to take it literally, right?
Written.
Right.
Right?
So when someone says you're taking that literally,
you should stop and say, well, is it literal or is it oral?
If it's oral, it's hearsay.
If it's written, and it hasn't been rebutted,
and it isn't in the declaration form,
you have to take it literally.
You see?
So it's very interesting.
So I started taking this perspective on it.
And you kind of feel like you're going insane,
because the world says up, and the manual says go down.
You know, the world says black, and the manual says white.
You know, regarding a particular subject or something, you know?
And, you know, you can't listen to both.
But here's the thing.
They're both in agreement.
I found that what man teaches,
and I'm not talking about modern times.
I'm saying this goes back a very long time, recorded history.
I can't find anything that agrees with any of their information in Scripture.
But I do find all of the information in Scripture
agreeing with what man teaches.
What I mean by that is basically the Scripture very clearly tells you
that you're going to have a lot of messing around with information on the earth.
And I see that.
You're going to have a lot of deceptions posing as benefits on the earth.
I see that.
You're going to have these events happening very specifically
at these very specific people, places, and times.
And I see that happening.
And I look at the information that man has been putting out
regarding a creator or this manual, the Bible,
and it's all incorrect and erroneous.
That's some of it, all of it.
And I decided to speak out on this a few years ago,
and as I started learning more about time,
I was wondering why it wasn't accepted,
because the timing isn't right.
The actual time where the people on this planet
will start to learn and discover what's in Scripture,
it will be coming within the next 14 years.
Actually, 11 to 14 years.
So the reason I have a desire...
Well, what I mean by that,
oh, there's going to be a public disclosure.
In other words, within the next 11 to 14 years,
the majority of the planet's going to be pinned to their TV sets.
You know, like for a week.
In disbelief or in belief.
And it will be proven to them.
There's going to be an event.
And it'll be proven to everyone that without a doubt,
all the inhabitants on this planet will all be in agreement
that everything in Scripture is true.
You know, there won't be any more TV shows that Moses exists
or was the Ark of the Covenant real or this, that, and the other, right?
Okay.
It'll be things that'll be discovered and brought out.
And it will be...
Okay, let's check this one off the list of, you know, fairytale list, you know?
This is fact now.
This is real. This time is coming.
It's a little too soon to fully disclose what's going to happen.
But the point that I'd like to make, at least at this point,
is the reason why I'm speaking on these things
is because in the prophet Ezekiel, there's some passages there
and it talks about a watchman.
It says if you're a watchman on a city wall
and you see danger approaching the city,
you must let the inhabitants know.
Now, if you don't warn them or blow the horn,
if anyone is hurt,
their blood will be on your hands.
But if you blow the horn and you warn them and they do nothing
and they're hurt, the blood is on their hands.
And that's fair enough, right?
It's like the boy who cried love.
You don't want to do that either.
So in a way, it's not to clear my conscience,
but it's in a way to say, well, if you know these things,
you need to speak them.
And if people don't want to hear it, it's irrelevant.
It's been said.
So from that point of view, that I'm not here to warn anyone,
but to give information,
what you do with the information is up to you.
And none of this is based on belief
because all of this information is literal.
And I can start getting into a little bit of what I've learned
that really shocked and bothered me
from reading the Bible
that I found is not taught and not known
by the inhabitants of this planet.
And, you know, when you read the scriptures,
there's one of the main characters,
if not the main character, actually, is the Christ,
or they call him the Messiah.
They call him the Savior.
And when you look at what the persona, let's say,
I'm using legal and lawful terms here
because legal and lawful, it both applies in scripture.
There's been a great identity theft
in the image and the character and who this was
and when he came and what his purpose was
is not being portrayed by any religion
or any academic sense at all.
There are very few people on the planet
who actually even know what his purpose was,
who he was, when he was born, and how he died.
The images and the information that religion is putting out,
organized or unorganized,
because today there's so many groups.
You have the Christianity aspect, by the way,
this historic era for the past 2,000 years
is called the Christian era, right?
So you have the Christianity,
then you've got those that are the messianics
who kind of mix Judaism with Christianity,
and then you've got Judaism and you've got Islam,
and I've been looking at all of their information,
what they put out, what they preach and teach,
and none of it is accurate, not even in the slightest,
according to the literal message.
One way to start before I get to the identity of the Christ
is, you know, a few years ago,
do you remember they wanted to take the Ten Commandments
written on the stones out of the courtrooms?
Right.
They did, didn't they?
Yeah, they did.
Yeah, I think they, yeah.
And actually, when people were calling me,
I said, you know,
are you talking about the Ten Commandments
that were written on stone?
And they said, yeah, they're taking it out of the courtroom.
And I'm like, well, can you, like,
give me, like, maybe two or three of those commandments?
Maybe they're not accurate.
Maybe it's not the right ones from the scriptures.
No, they're the ones from the Bible.
Well, like, can you give me, like,
maybe two or three commandments,
so maybe identify them, maybe so, you know,
we're talking about the same thing here?
I said, yeah.
It says, do not steal, do not murder,
respect your parents, and I'm like,
yeah, those are the Ten Commandments,
but those weren't written on the stones.
These stones, they look like big tombstones.
I'm like, yeah.
Well, they could take those out of the courtroom.
Those weren't written on the stones.
That's all mixed up.
Yeah, that's fine.
They could take them out if it's not accurate.
They're like, what are you talking about?
I'm like, do you have a Bible?
They're like, yeah.
I said, go read Exodus 34.
Call me back.
Never get a call back.
Never.
I've done this over a dozen times.
I said, I promise you're going to call me back.
Go read Exodus 34.
That's where the Ten Commandments written on the stones are.
Can you call me back and we'll discuss it?
No one has ever called me back.
It's right there.
If you read Exodus 34, he told Moses,
cut out two stones like the first that you broke
and write on them exactly what you wrote on the first stones.
And the commandments are listed there.
And if you read them,
it's not what you've been told in Sunday school.
Kind of shocking.
Well, what is it?
Well, it gets a little lengthy to get into it.
If anyone has the Bible, you could read Exodus 34.
What everyone thinks are the Ten Commandments written on the stones
were the commands that they were given when they came out of Egypt.
And that's in, let's say, Exodus 21, where he says,
you shall have no other God before me.
Do not make any graven images to worship.
Do not murder.
Do not steal.
Keep the sap.
Those are the ones they teach in Sunday school, right?
Right.
Respect your parents.
Okay, those were not written on the stone.
Those were oral commands, like no shirt, no shoes, no service.
Like rules of behavior, because they had just come out of Egypt.
They didn't know how to act.
They were the first time in the presence of the Creator at Mount Sinai.
So they're acting like a bunch of Egyptians.
And if you actually look at those commands that were given in Exodus 20,
they were oral.
They were not literal.
They were not written to be part of the covenant, let's say.
It was what you would tell a disorderly mob, right?
Like, don't do these things while you're in this presence.
It's very basic ways to act.
And also, if you study the laws in ancient Egypt,
each one of those rules actually counteracted one of their laws.
In ancient Egypt, they had child informers.
So he said, well, you can't do that here.
Respect your parents.
If you had enough money, you can go and buy your neighbor's wife.
You don't do that here.
These were very basic rules of behavior.
What was written on the stones were things completely different.
Two of them, I think.
Actually, only one or two of the commandments that were written on the stones
are the same as the commandments that were given orally.
And they weren't written on these large stones that look like tombstones.
To give you an example, the first commandment was,
do not go into a covenant with the pagans.
If you go into a covenant with them, you will stray away from my laws
and your children will marry their children and you'll forget about me.
You won't worship me.
You're going to follow strange gods, let's say.
Another commandment would be, all men are to appear before me three times a year.
Another commandment would be, you are to ransom a donkey with a lamb
or break its neck.
Do not mix the blood of the Passover with leaven.
Another commandment would be, do not boil a kid in its mother's milk.
These are things that are not taught,
but they're actually the ones that were written on the stones.
Now, this doesn't make the Ten Commandments that are, let's say,
taught by the churches or whatever invalid.
It's just, these were the ones that were written on the stones.
Do you see how subtle the confusion is?
It's very subtle.
It's kind of like when you have a Federal Reserve note and you say it's a dollar.
It's not really a dollar because the word dollar means the weight of precious metals.
It's like pounds and ounces.
Eventually, you should be able to get something for it.
It should be a dollar, but it's not.
These commands that people think they know were not written on the stones.
It doesn't mean they're invalid.
It's just there's a problem with accuracy here and discernment.
Another example, well, again, back to the Ten Commandments.
When you say the word Ten Commandments, what's the image everyone thinks of?
Charlton Heston carrying these two stones, right?
Looked like tombstones, right?
When you say Noah's Ark, they got that from Cecil B. DeMille.
When you say, for example, Noah's Ark,
they think of this big boat and there's a rope off the back
and there's another little boat with two skunks in it.
They got that from Walt Disney when they were five years old.
These things are not accurate.
They're not in Scripture.
For example, in Exodus, when they did cross the Sea of Reeds,
in Cecil B. DeMille, he used Jell-O for special effects.
The waters are parted and all these people walking on the bottom across.
I don't know where he got that from.
It's not in Scripture. It didn't happen that way.
If you read Exodus 15, it's very clear that he says
there was an easterly wind blew all night, right?
And even today, if you go and look at the weather at the Sinai,
it's 20 degrees in the springtime, in the evening there.
That's enough to get really cold at night.
A wind blew all night and the depths of the waters became solid.
Hmm.
What do you call solid water?
Ice.
And there were 600,000 fighting men that left Egypt.
Not a one of them was crippled or incapable.
And in Cecil B. DeMille movie, he kind of, little wink-wink,
three or four times they show an old man being carried in a stretcher.
That's like saying, okay, you guys that know, read Scripture and know it,
don't say anything to those that don't know it,
because you'll ruin it for them.
So to show you that I know what I'm doing here,
I'm going to show you a man in a stretcher,
because if you read Scripture, you know no one was carried in a stretcher, right?
So he's telling you right there, this is all, you know,
these are all fictional events.
Anything that resembles anything living or dead is by coincidence only.
But it's very hard to pick up on that.
So if there's 600,000 fighting men that crossed over,
and if each one had one or two family members,
that's at least 1.8 million people.
If they had three or four family members,
you're getting into the three to four million people crossing.
And that's going to take roughly 10 football fields wide.
At four miles per hour, that's roughly going to take the whole night.
And then if you read in Exodus 15 further on,
he says, when Pharaoh tried to cross,
they fell to the bottom like a stone,
they fell to the bottom like lead.
Well, if they're already walking on the bottom,
how do they fall to the bottom like a rock or like lead?
It's not much of a fall, you're already standing there, aren't you?
Yeah.
See, so the ice bridge collapsed and they went down.
So where did Cecil B. DeMille get the idea for those special effects?
I guess it looks better in Hollywood
than, you know, some ice breaking and falling through, doesn't it?
That doesn't say in the Bible the parting of the Red Sea?
Yes, yes, you got it.
You know, when you put a bridge across a body of water,
it's called a parting of water.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, it says the water was piled up in Exodus 15.
Well, how do you pile up water?
Well, the only way would be to, yeah, frozen, freezing it.
Yeah, I love watching the academics.
You know, you can't pile up water,
you know, these biblical scholars of 50 years,
14 PhDs, you know.
You can't pile up water.
Here comes a four-year-old that says,
go get a bucket of ice to a four-year-old.
Come here and just dump it at his feet, pile it up.
What's that?
Oh, it's a pile of water.
Okay.
Well, you see, no one could ever really figure out Scripture.
No one really can understand it.
So why bother even making the message
if you knew no one can understand it?
Why is it 900 pages long?
We're lacking discernment.
Critical thinking as you started out with.
Right?
Right, yeah.
I mean, we just take what it says at face value
and leave it at that.
Plus, it's reinforced by what we've learned in school,
in church, and so forth.
But no one questions these things.
Just like the IRS.
You can grow up watching your parents
doing their 1040s every year on April 15th.
Right?
You never questioned it.
Just did it.
It's a thing to do, yeah.
And all of this, again,
everything is backwards.
Just to jump around a little bit,
you know, when you look at
the political system and all that,
and you become a little more awake
and alert to what's going on,
you know your voting doesn't really count.
You know, I mean,
you could vote all you want.
Voters don't elect.
Electors elect.
It's in the word itself, right?
You vote at a poll.
You know, like CNN and Fox News
do polls all the time.
Right?
But this poll you have to go register at.
You know, oh wow,
that feels so important now, you know?
But they tell you, electors elect.
Voters vote at a poll.
Electors elect.
It's not a voting.
It's an election.
They're telling you.
You need a dictionary, you know,
and just read your dictionary.
Well, I think everybody does it.
I think everybody does it
just to feel like they're doing,
they're taking part in the, you know,
whole thing, you know,
so they can say they, you know,
did their part.
You know, it's just like
paying your fair share.
It's all these soundbites,
stupid things.
Right.
When you read scripture,
it tells you that man will tell you
to do things that will make you feel important,
but if you do things the creator tells you,
you won't necessarily feel important,
but you will be empowered.
I think being humble
and not feeling important
in a particular system
is not a good trade for being empowered.
You see?
Right.
There's a difference.
If you could actually put the leader in,
you would be actually empowering,
but it's not empowering to vote.
You just feel important.
It's just a feeling.
There's nothing really there.
Right?
Just like a bank account.
Show me what's in the account.
They can either tell you a number
or show you a printout
or something on a screen
because there's nothing really there.
Right?
It's the same thing
with what's been taught
for 5,000 years.
It's not this country
and it's not recent history.
This has been going on
for a very long time,
but again,
if you read scripture,
he says,
I put the leaders in there.
He says,
I put them there.
I put the rulers there.
I am the ruler of rulers,
so everyone can vote
for one candidate
or everyone can try
to elect one candidate,
and if it's not the one
that he wants to put in,
he puts in another.
How many times have you seen
elections where they have
one guy win
and then they recall it
and they put someone else
who was just meant to be.
Right?
They say,
just meant to be.
Well, no.
Someone's actually in control
doing that.
Well, yeah.
They did, I think,
with every single election
there and then.
Well, I mean,
the creator actually
puts the leader in,
so if you actually read scripture,
you don't care about voting
because he tells you
it doesn't matter.
I put them in,
he says,
and he tells you
how he puts them in.
He says,
well,
the less agreeable
the society,
the leader I'm going to give you.
In other words,
I don't want to seem judgmental,
but the actual words are,
the more evil the society,
the more evil the leadership.
But he tells you
what you people down there
have been told is evil
is actually good in my eyes,
and what you've been told is good
is actually evil in my eyes.
So,
what's being taught is backwards.
And when I came on the call
on Saturday,
I said,
if you don't know
what cannibals,
birthdays,
and dolls have in common,
you won't comprehend
what's going on
on this planet right now.
I came on like a steamroller
saying,
you know what cannibals,
birthdays,
and dolls have in common?
It's kind of shocking.
I think Greg was like,
what?
Cannibals,
birthdays,
and dolls?
What does that have to do
with anything,
you know?
And,
yeah,
for whoever wasn't on,
I'll repeat it
maybe quickly here.
Please do.
Don't do it quickly.
Okay.
Take your time.
Take my time with it?
All right.
If you read scripture,
there's a lot of,
just to preface,
a lot of talk about
don't pass your children
through the fire.
Don't sacrifice your children.
You know,
don't put your children
in the fire.
Don't kill them.
Don't slaughter them.
Don't,
you know,
for prosperity.
That's why people did that.
There were ancient religions
that were pretty macabre,
really macabre.
And back in those days
in the Mesopotamian region
from Babylon
all the way to the coast
of modern-day Israel,
people were told
to worship
this little statue
or this entity
called Baal,
or Baal,
however you want
to pronounce it.
It's written B-A-A-L
in the English translation.
And simply,
Baal or Baal
translated to English
just means
the Lord.
It's kind of scary
when you think about it.
And this was a statue.
They were usually
gods of nature.
You know,
Baal of thunder,
Baal of the ocean.
And they had different,
you know,
shapes and sizes.
But for example,
you know the garden gnomes
that people put
in their garden,
those little garden gnomes.
Travelocity uses it
in their commercial,
you know.
That's a Canaanite statue
of Baal in the garden.
They thought if they put
that little statue
in their farms
they'd have prosperity,
right?
That's why they're called
garden gnomes.
So those things
have survived
5,000 plus years.
But, you know,
if you call it Baal or Baal
they'll say,
well that's a bad thing.
It says right here
in Scripture.
But if you call it
a garden gnome
it's good, right?
So the priests
back in those days
in the Chaldean Hebrew language
that preserved
these kinds of
entities or idols,
a priest of Baal
was called a kahan
or kohon
or kohanim
however you want
to pronounce it,
you know,
like tomato or tomato.
Basically a kahan.
So the kahans of Baal,
the priests of Baal,
or the priests of the Lord,
does that sound familiar?
Yeah.
Still exists today.
They would tell the people
if you want prosperity
you would bring us a child
and they would bring a child
usually under the age of six
and they would put him on an altar
and they would slaughter the child
and everyone in the ceremony
would take a small piece of flesh
and a little bit of the blood
and eat it.
That's why kahan Baal-ism,
if you take out the H
you get cannibalism, right?
It's the same word.
That's what it means.
Cannibalism or kahan Baal-ism,
in other words,
the priest of the Lord
was equated with the eating of human flesh.
Wow!
Now you know where that word comes from.
Pretty wild.
And when I found this out
I was like,
whoa,
this planet is not doing,
now I know why this planet
is not doing so well.
And the parents now,
after this ceremony,
this was an agricultural society
so people were not afraid
of having many children,
you know what I mean?
They wanted big families.
So if you took a child
and left
and you went to one of these ceremonies
and you didn't tell the other children
where you were going
and you came back without the child,
the first thing all the other children
are going to ask is,
hey,
where's our brother?
Where's our sister?
How come they didn't come back with you?
Right?
Well,
the altar boys of the kahan Baals
or the cannibals,
they would make an effigy of a child.
We call it a doll.
And they'd give it to the parents
and say,
when you go back home
and the children ask
where's the brother or sister,
you give them this little doll
to play with
and they'll forget about it.
So now you know the history of dolls.
That's why we have dolls.
Oh no,
it's spooky.
Here I thought growing up
as a little girl
with my tiny tears,
you know,
it was like to prepare you
for motherhood or something,
you know,
or get,
I mean,
why do they get little boy director sets
and tools,
you know,
little girls' dolls
and baking,
you know,
fake baking toys.
Well,
they did get little dolls,
G.I. Joes,
finally,
right?
Didn't they make little dolls
for boys also?
G.I. Joes,
they call them,
don't they?
Or Raggedy Ann
and Raggedy Andy,
right?
Are you still there?
Hello?
I'm back.
Okay,
I hope you can hear me.
Is that you,
Greek?
I'm here.
Okay,
sorry,
I lost my connection.
My cable went down completely.
oh,
gosh,
that was hair raising.
Anyway.
Okay.
That's fine.
That's a really long delay
and I guess we've all prevailed.
Yeah,
well,
we might have lost a lot of people,
though,
but we still have a lot on.
So,
good.
I'm glad we're still recording.
I don't know why,
did you go,
did you put yourself on mute?
Because you were muted when I came on.
No,
I didn't.
That was really weird.
Because I was hoping someone would type in
and say,
I was hoping someone could still hear me
as I was yelling in,
going,
I lost my connection.
Anyway,
okay,
I'm glad we're back.
Yeah,
me too.
And this is part of Proof Positive
that,
you know,
there's
entities,
the spiritual world,
they don't want this kind of stuff being spoken.
Right,
I know.
And it's been going on for thousands of years,
and the last thing,
you know,
is to be exposed,
right?
Yeah.
I'm glad we're back,
though.
Gosh.
Good,
we're back.
How frustrating.
Well,
where were we?
you were,
I'm sorry?
Balls,
I think?
Yeah,
you were talking about Ball
and the different ways he,
you know,
is portrayed,
like,
with the garden gnome
and so forth.
Right,
where the origin of dolls
that little children play with
came from.
Right.
So,
that's where it came from,
because people were killing their children
in sacrifice to the gods
so that they would have more prosperity
or whatever,
right?
Or whatever is right,
yeah,
they didn't get it,
right?
And the dolls were made
as an effigy of a child
to appease the other children
when they asked about their brothers and sisters
that didn't come back.
Right.
So now,
you know,
how many times have you seen a mom
or a family,
you know,
they go and get dolls for their children
and you ask them,
do you know what that represents?
No.
Do you want to know?
Why do you give them the dolls?
Because I was given one
and my parents,
parents,
and their parents were given one.
Right.
Yeah.
So,
this is going on
and this has been going on
for 5,000 plus years.
Yeah,
they do that every year
at Bohemian Grove
up north in California.
Here,
they,
they put a child in effigy,
they burn it to that big
Moloch owl.
That's another one,
that's another aspect of it.
Yeah,
it's not,
it's not quite,
I'm speaking more on the ball aspect.
Well,
you know,
but they do,
they have the little,
this little,
creepy,
crawly person,
guy,
that is the typical,
what you would consider,
ball,
because he's,
down in the corner,
you know,
watching it all going on,
like,
it's,
it's weird.
Yeah,
they,
they understand,
you see,
the,
see,
that's why these secret societies,
they,
they call each other's brothers
or the brotherhood,
you know,
like the Freemasons
and whatever,
there's countless groups
that call themselves
part of the brotherhood.
Yeah,
religion too.
and the reason why they call themselves,
see,
if someone is your brother
when you live under the,
under the same covenant,
you see,
you have the same oath
or allegiances,
you know,
that's why when I meet people,
they find it very strange,
I,
I ask them,
you know,
what covenant do you live under?
They look at me like,
excuse me?
I'm like,
yeah,
where do you get your law?
I'm not talking about traffic law,
I mean like,
what you eat,
what you wear,
how do you keep time,
what days you worship,
how do you,
how do you operate in commerce,
how do you treat your wife,
how do you enter into contracts,
what set of rules
do you live your life by?
They look at me like,
I don't know.
Oh,
okay,
so how can you be my brother?
You see,
I,
I try,
I try to live in the covenant
of the scripture,
you see,
it's all about law,
you get law from your deity
and that's how people are wired.
You cannot escape that.
So,
if you say,
for example,
when I don't have a deity,
I don't believe in God,
I don't believe in
the spiritual world,
you know,
there's no proof of it or whatever,
I'm scientific,
alright,
hold on,
before you keep going,
do you believe in the laws of the state?
Absolutely,
well the state is your God
and there you go.
That's true for a lot of people.
Yeah,
well you see,
well it's because
that's the way we are wired,
you cannot escape it.
If you rewire a cell phone,
guess what,
it's not going to work.
The reason why it works
is because of its wiring.
The same with a computer,
if I pull the motherboard
out of your computer
and start rewiring it,
do you expect me to
plug it back in
and it work
the same way it did before?
Uh-uh.
Yeah,
so we're all wired
that we get our law,
in other words,
our morality
from our deity
and that's why in Scripture
it says that
do not corrupt little children
and it gives you a metaphor,
those that corrupt the children,
it would be better
that you tie a millstone
around your neck,
which is a large stone,
and dump into the river.
The reason why
is because
when you have an infant
in your house
from when they're born
up until let's say
three, four, five,
six years old,
they have no concept
of the divine world
or of a creator
and they view the parents
as their God.
What you say goes,
they know of no other authority.
So,
now you wonder
why children have so many problems,
you know,
they're taught,
well, you've got these,
you know,
you've got to celebrate
the Tooth Fairy,
the Easter Bunny
and the Santa Claus
and when they're seven
or eight or nine
and the child asks
where's Santa Claus
and the parent turns around
and says,
what's wrong with you?
Don't you know
there's no such thing?
And the child's like,
oh, oh, oh,
you know, major trauma,
you know,
it's like,
my God just lied to me.
So how are you supposed
to have a normal life
when your own deity
lied to you?
You know,
you're being your parents
because you know of no other
at that point, right?
Right.
Well,
nobody ever
springs in
a child like that,
though.
Well,
I've seen,
I've heard of,
you know,
parents telling children
those things don't exist
but it's like,
mom, dad,
you know,
we celebrated that
for all these years.
What do you mean
they don't exist?
And then you grow out of it.
That's sort of the excuse,
I guess.
We just grow out of it
and then we all...
Actually,
you don't.
You ever wonder
why teenagers
are so rebellious?
Because this is a very
deep-rooted subconscious problem.
They know they've been
lied to by the
absolute,
ultimate authority
when they were
in their formative years,
right?
Formative years
were, you know,
as an infant,
so now how can you
go out and trust,
you know,
people outside
or in the spiritual realm
or anything?
And one way
to fix any familial
relationship
with a,
when you have
a rebellious teenager,
I've helped
quite a few people
with it,
you know,
they'd say,
well,
you know,
I've got these
rebellious teenagers,
you know,
or they'll wreak havoc
when I leave them alone.
I said,
how old are they?
You know,
like 12,
13,
14.
I said,
oh,
I know why,
because you lied to them
and you never apologized.
They're like,
what?
I said,
did you ever do
Christmas,
Easter,
or anything like that,
you know,
Easter Bunny
or Tooth Fairy
or anything fictional?
Did you raise them
that way
and then tell them
it didn't exist?
And when you told them
it didn't exist,
did you apologize
for lying?
Nope.
I don't recall
feeling that way
about my parents
or my mother.
I never got mad
at her for lying.
You just sort of
grew up
and realized
that's something
you told little kids
to,
you know,
make them
believe in fairy tales
and stupid stuff
like that.
But it wasn't like,
you know,
well,
in my family,
I didn't grow up
rebellious.
Well,
I mean,
I didn't,
you know,
do bad things.
But it is very common
in society.
Okay.
On a society level,
you do see rebellious,
and you do see problems
with parents
without what they call
adolescence.
And they wonder why.
These are very
deep-rooted problems.
And also,
you're being set up
to believe in a fiction
and then told
that it's not.
Maybe,
if you're lucky,
you'll grow out of it,
right?
That's why when people
get older,
they say,
well,
you just lost your whole retirement.
Get over it.
You know,
life isn't fair,
you know.
You're going to be lied to.
Right?
Yeah.
That's pretty much it.
Yeah,
you're going to be lied to.
Life isn't fair.
You're going to be lied to
in this and that.
Oh,
I mean,
you haven't gotten used to it.
you know,
you see what's going on?
Uh-huh.
In a society that follows,
has some sort of covenant
or some set of rules
that are based on
a benevolent
deity,
there's no lying.
There's no fiction.
You see?
So,
back to these cannibals,
kahanbals,
or the priests of the Lord.
You know,
they give the doll
to give to the children,
and obviously,
they don't get prosperity
from doing this kind of stuff.
Sometimes they did,
actually,
as a society,
and they did acknowledge
that it came from
this particular deity,
but what a macabre thing
to do.
You know?
But when they didn't
have prosperity,
they went back
with another child,
and the kahanbals,
or the priests of the Lord,
would say,
wait a second,
you know,
if we keep taking
all their children,
they're going to figure
this out somehow,
and they might purge us
from here,
and they might come
and tell us to leave.
We're not welcomed
here anymore.
So,
instead of taking
this other child,
they told the parents
to go back home
and put the child
in a high chair
with a pointy hat
like they wear,
and to bake a loaf
of sweet bread
and put candles in it,
and ask the child
to make a wish
of prosperity
and blow out the candles,
which represents
blowing out the light,
and then everyone
eats a piece
of sweet bread,
which represents
eating a piece
of the body,
and to show that
that wish of prosperity
works,
everyone attending
the ceremony
has to bring a present.
What does that sound
like to you?
Yeah,
really,
that's scary.
Yeah,
so people love
doing birthdays,
you know,
so why do you,
well,
you know what that
birthday cake represents?
No,
I don't care,
I don't want to know.
I really don't want to know.
I have a great time with it.
Oh, really?
Okay.
It's a pagan ritual.
Yeah,
you're actually
making enemies
in the spiritual world.
A pagan
sacrificial ritual.
Mm-hmm.
Well,
that's similar
to the communion,
which is a ritual.
Right,
that's a whole other
story there.
That's very similarly
based.
You know,
it's interesting,
during World War II,
when they bombed
the crap out of Europe,
they hit a lot of
cathedrals and churches
in Europe,
and there was a particular
architect,
I don't remember
who it was,
if anyone wants to
reference it,
you could just put a
description of the
architect who went to
restore the bombed
cathedrals in Germany
and all parts of Europe.
What he did was
he went and surveyed
the damage,
and most of the
big churches,
he found,
you know,
where they have the
altar,
you know,
where the priest did
his ritual?
Uh-huh.
There was another
altar underground,
very similar to it,
in a functioning
chamber.
What's a functioning
chamber?
In other words,
it had doors that
go in and out,
and people could
sit around and
watch what was
going on.
Okay,
so there's a whole
other room down there.
Yeah,
yeah,
just like the one
above,
yeah.
And he started
asking questions,
you know,
what's this for?
And they're like,
uh, uh, uh,
you know,
never got a straight
answer.
What was it for?
I don't know,
you can let your
imagination run,
I just thought I'd
bring it up.
That's interesting
because the church
here that,
I was going to
say that Mahoney,
the Catholic,
what is he,
cardinal here in
California,
Los Angeles,
built this cathedral,
and underneath,
the hole underneath
is a,
it's like a
cemetery,
it's where
people get
buried.
Did you know
that?
And so maybe
that's what it
was.
I'm not sure,
I just think
you can let your
imagination run
with it,
because things
are not as they
seem.
Now,
you brought up
the Moloch
in Bohemian
Grove,
and in
scripture it
says do not
pass your
child or
your children
through the
fires of
Moloch.
Now,
for researching
Moloch,
they had
various statues,
but they were
always very
large,
and they had
an open
hearth in
their belly,
and they were
typically made
of bronze.
And the ones
in that part
of the world,
at that time,
they were usually
in a seated
position,
and they
were made
of bronze,
and they
had a very
large belly
for a hearth,
and they
would build
a fire in
the belly,
and they
would stoke it
until the
whole statue
became bright
red,
and they
would tell
the people
to make
a wish of
prosperity
and place
the child
in the lap
of that
red-hot
bronze
statue.
So,
today,
you have a
character,
at certain
times of the
year,
he's got a
big belly,
and he's
bright red,
and children
are placed
in his lap
and told
to make
a wish
of prosperity.
Does that
sound like
anything
you might
have heard
of before?
Santa Claus,
oh my gosh.
I know.
Isn't that
one of the
discussing
or what?
See what's
going on?
Now,
here's the
thing.
The people
that know
about this,
actually,
the spiritual
world knows
about this
more than
the people.
See,
the people
are doing
things that
are making
enemies in
the spiritual
world.
When you
do this
kind of
stuff,
because we
are better
than that,
and we've
been duped
into believing
these things,
because it's
based on
belief,
not knowledge.
You can only
believe in
this.
You cannot
know this
and do
it,
because once
you know
what it
is,
are you
still going
to do
it?
Yeah.
You see?
People
say,
well,
that's my
religion,
I believe in
it,
I don't
care about
what you
believe.
Do you
know it?
Scripture
says you
shall know
the truth.
Here I
thought it
was always
just based
on drumming
up commerce
and funding
and stuff.
when you
read
scripture,
a lot of
people say,
well,
the Bible is
a commercial
document.
No,
it's not.
There is
commerce in
the Bible.
For example,
when you
read the
Bible,
commerce is
one aspect
of life
on this
planet.
There are
other aspects.
For example,
you have
agriculture,
stewardship,
you have
family,
worship.
In other words,
how do you
communicate with
the other
dimension,
the spiritual
world?
There are
forms of
healing
the body,
there is
a
judicial
ruling
in
scripture
that's
outside of
commerce.
It might
involve
commerce if
it's a
commercial
dispute.
The only
thing that's
in commerce
in scripture
is that
when you
do
trade
or sale,
make sure that
your measurements
are accurate.
Don't cheat
anyone.
Don't rig
your scale
so it's
not.
You must
use
substance
money.
If you
don't have
substance
money,
you can
use
credit.
But you
have to
live up to
your promise.
In other
words,
if a
corn farmer
is supposed
to barter
it with
a potato
farmer,
you can
give him
a note.
But you
can't
come back
and give
him another
note.
That has
to be
some kind
of
substance.
Instead
of
carrying
a ton
of
potatoes,
you can
bring
gold or
silver.
It's
much more
portable.
Economy
means
management
of the
house.
Ecos
means
house or
habitation.
Nomos
means
loss.
Economy
literally
means
management
of the
house.
When people
these days
say the
economy is
not doing
well,
I say,
what economy?
We don't
have an
economy.
What are
you talking
about?
They look
at me like
I'm strange
or something.
Economy
means
management
of commerce.
There's
no management
of commerce.
It's a
free-for-all
right now.
Or it's
management.
being managed
one-sided,
right?
So,
there's
your,
on the
occult
side,
what's
going on
is you
have the
supreme being
of the
universe
telling you
not to
do things
and you're
doing things
you're not
supposed to
do because
you don't
know you're
doing them.
Boy,
does that sound
confusing.
Well,
it's true
though.
We've been
taught everything
that's wrong
that we've
been taught
or brainwashed
to believe.
But what
happens is
after a while
those doing
the brainwashing
forget that
they're
brainwashing
and they
end up
doing it
themselves
also.
And they
don't know
what they're
doing
themselves.
For example,
you know,
if Henry Ford
started,
you know,
Ford Motor
Corporation
in his
garage with
a thousand
bucks,
right,
if you
take his
great-grandson
and today's
money,
give him
a hundred
grand,
let's say,
in a garage
and tell him
go start
a motor
company,
you think
he can do
it?
Probably not.
Yeah,
most likely
not.
So again,
it's timing
and people
are picked
to do certain
things.
You see,
there's a
very big
scope here.
So,
you know,
what's funny
is,
you know,
I'll explain
this to people
and they'll
say,
wow,
that's really
horrible,
you know,
the birthday
and the
dolls and all
that,
and I get
a call a
week later,
hey,
you want to
come to
his birthday
party?
So they
don't take
it literally.
Yeah,
like,
excuse me,
are you
taking a
piss right
now or
something,
so you
want to
call me
back later
maybe?
I mean,
you know,
sorry to say
it that way,
but it's
like,
how can
you ask
me that?
You know,
it's kind
of like,
I ask
people,
it's the
same thing,
we don't
have,
we're not
impeccable
with what
we say.
And if
you're not
impeccable
with what
you say
or with
words,
you can't
be impeccable
with how
you act.
Because you're
only as good
as your
word.
You know,
if someone
approaches me,
my kids,
I'm like,
you have
goats?
Well,
you know what
I mean.
I'm like,
yeah,
I know
what you
mean when
you say
kids,
it's a
baby goat.
I thought no
animals were
allowed there.
Well,
you know,
I mean
children.
So you
mean children
but you
say goats.
So your
word isn't
any good.
So if all
you've got is
your word
and your
word isn't
any good,
I can't
do business
with you,
I can't
trust you,
have you as
a friend.
So what
am I supposed
to do with
you now?
I think it's
just that we
don't take our
word as
strongly as
we should or
we don't,
you know,
claim it as
strongly or
take it as
literally as
we should,
maybe is the
proper way to
say it.
Everything is,
you know,
like,
oh,
it's okay,
it's not
that important,
it's only
words when
we should be
listening to
what we're
saying and
really listening
and understanding
exactly what
we're saying
because by
saying it,
by putting it
out there,
we're making
it happen or
we're causing,
it's like,
everything is
like a ritual
it seems like.
Yes,
and why do
they say
kids very
specifically?
Why don't
they just say
pigs or
sheep or
birds?
Why do
they pick
kids?
Because
a kid,
it's very
specific,
a kid is a
sacrificial animal
to the adversary
or people
call him
Satan or
the devil,
It's the
Azizel,
right?
So it's
very interesting,
you look at
it, there's
no coincidence.
You see
when people
say,
oh,
that's a
coincidence,
well,
the word
coincidence actually
means to
coincide with,
and for something
to coincide with
something else,
there has to be
a plan,
right?
So there is
no coincidence,
meaning the
way that people
use it,
right?
It's a
coincidence that
I came on
the phone,
on the show
tonight,
on the call
because I
knew that
around 6
o'clock I
had to
call in,
so I knew
that me dialing
on this phone
had to coincide
with that time,
so it was a
coincidence,
you see.
You see how
we're not
using words
properly?
And even
the most important
contracts are
only worth the
paper that
they're written
on if no
one's going
to follow
them,
they're just
words.
You know,
for example,
when someone
makes a
declaration and
signs it under
the penalty of
perjury,
meaning that's
done,
right?
This is a
done deal.
I can't give
you any more
than that on
paper,
right?
Can you?
No,
it's about the
ultimate promise
when you sign
under the
penalty of
perjury,
right?
Okay,
well,
if you don't
have paper,
what do you
do?
You say it
three times.
And,
you know,
recently I was
helping someone
with a project
and I said,
I'm about done,
and he said,
are you done,
done?
Meaning like,
you know,
you're really
finished,
you know,
versus just
finishing a
certain area
of something.
Yeah.
And then
when it was
said,
no.
See,
and then
I said,
when I'm done,
he says,
are you done,
done?
I said,
yes,
I'm done,
done,
done.
It's done,
right?
So it's
finished.
So three
times or
twice,
you know,
twice means
it's,
you know,
you have my
point,
you've heard
that before.
Sure.
We can
operate without
paper,
but can
we?
You see
how people
have been
trained a
certain way.
Again,
these societies,
for example,
that are in
power,
you know,
knowledge is
power and
the people in
power have
a certain
knowledge that
the common
folk don't
know because
it hasn't been
shared or
it's been
lost,
right?
So what
knowledge is?
It's knowledge
of the
spiritual world.
You notice how
very little of
the spiritual
world is
taught?
They
scooped it
under religion
and when I
say spiritual,
I think I've
done this with
you before,
but I
have a
spiritual
relationship
with everyone
on this call
and,
you know,
when I say
that to
people,
you know,
oh,
yeah,
that makes me
feel so good
or whatever.
Do you know
why I said
that?
They're like,
yeah,
because we
talk about
spiritual things.
No,
that's not
why.
It's because
I've never
met you in
the flesh.
It's
intangible.
Spiritual
simply means
intangible.
I don't
see anyone
or no one's
present,
but I'm
actually
imparting
information.
You know,
you could be doing
business with
someone in
China you've
never met
and you're
conveying
information
back and
forth,
contracts,
instructions,
business.
That's a
spiritual
relationship
because you've
never met
them in
the flesh.
Once you
meet them
in the
flesh,
now you
have a
spiritual
with the
body.
You shook
their hand.
You know
what they
look like.
You can
go have
lunch together.
Now you're
on the
next level,
you see.
So when
you read in
Scripture that
this is
spiritual,
that's all
it means.
It's very
simple.
But you
have, you
know,
the New
Testament
and all
this other
religious stuff.
Oh,
spiritual,
it's got to
be good.
No,
spiritual could
be pretty
bad.
You can
have a
general in
Washington,
D.C.
telling a
colonel in
Afghanistan to
put his
finger on
the button
right there
and launch
the missile.
Right?
That's
spiritual.
Never met
the guy,
but he's
giving him
instructions.
So we've
lost accuracy
to the point
where I'm
just amazed
anyone's here
on the planet
left and
anything's
functioning.
Every day I
wake up and
I'm amazed.
It's all
still here.
I'm like,
okay,
everybody's
still here.
Wow,
it's amazing,
we're
functioning.
You know?
Yeah.
Well,
that must be
for a reason.
Yeah,
and the reason is
when you start
reading and
you find
out that
the
scripture,
the Bible,
is basically
an appointment
book.
It's an
instruction
manual for
anything and
everything you
can do in
your life.
There's
nothing you
can do that
you won't
find in
there.
So,
there's 615
various
codes,
laws,
legal stuff
and statutes.
And I know
how a lot
of people
say,
well,
lawful isn't
legal or
all this
other stuff.
And I
say,
wait a
minute,
let's
hold on
here.
If you
want common
law,
everyone
agrees that
in order to
have common law in law you have to have an injured party right where's the
injured party right you can't injure a piece of paper can you you know so
there's no injured party there's no case right right but in common law you've got
this particular thing called treason and when someone commits treason it's a
death defense death penalty right right okay you know if you go to court for in
common law court for treason can you show me the injured party please where's
the injured party in treason there isn't yeah it's a legal aspect there's
legal and law are the same one but they're different one is legal actually
has to do with agreement because if there is no injured party no one can
testify but every people the authorities that be have to all be in agreement that
this man or woman did something that would prevent us from being proper
stewards in this nation and it would harm the population right like if you
were for example a spy and you were caught and you were giving information
that would jeopardize the safety of your country and the people in your country
could no longer be proper stewards you know take care of themselves be
vulnerable to losing everything you see it operates on many levels so that's why
in scripture there's a lot of stewardship how to take care of the land
you know where's the injured party when you blaspheme you know blasphemy for
example in scripture is a death offense right there's certain things that are
death offenses whether you won't find an injured party so what I'm saying is
there's a lot of a little bit of just because a little knowledge is good a
lot doesn't mean it's better right you have to kind of slow down and work it
through and really comprehend and understand what you're what you're
learning you can't do far forward and discernment has to be there and we've
all just pretty much taken for granted what we've been told and not looked it
up for ourselves or or even gotten curious enough to look it up it was like
it's not it's it's like nonchalant it's like no one made it that important yeah
we didn't come to that conclusion ourselves to make it that important to
look up every single word and understand exactly what it meant well during the
for our formative years you see education has to be completed at least
the bulk of it and then the discernment aspect during your formative years
meaning like you know when it when are you not really considered a baby anymore
it gets between like seven years old and 13 like at 13 years old they start to go
through other changes like puberty and you get you know changes you're not
interested in learning anymore interested in the opposite sex right yeah
you have to get the ball changes yeah if you've got to get the bulk of the
attention span and the learning done between 7 and 13 years old you've got a
five-year window you know if you're sitting there you're 16 17 18 in high
school and they're talking about something in class well you hear and
want want want want wine you're wondering who you can ask out on a date
for Saturday right it's too late yeah so you've got to get all your education done
between 7 and 13 years old and pretty much figure out what you want to do in
life by 13 this is how society operated for thousands of years up until recently
see so the human let's see here the people's bodies haven't changed the way
our brains are wired haven't changed but everything else has why I guess it's to
take us down into another direction when I say us I mean the collective us on
this planet now and everyone is so concerned you know about you know this
country or that country but everything that's happening right now is on a
planetary scale when I say right now I mean since 1998 till now in 1998 was
when the last age ended we're in the final or in the seventh age actually the
third age or the 7,000 biblical year it's the year 6,013 since Adam right so
that means you know we've finished the 6,000 completely we're 13 years into the
seventh millennium so there's a lot of specific things that are going to happen
how do you arrive at that you know when you read scripture you know you get
around chapter 5 and you start reading all the begats you know like Adam begat
Seth and he lived this long and he begat went on and he begat and he begat I call
it the begats goes for like two chapters and you're reading you're like why am I
reading this you know why am I reading this who cares if this guy lived to 800
or 600 you know so what you got to do is make a chart and follow that all the way
down at least to them when the Messiah was born and you'll know then the Messiah
was born exactly in the year 4,000 since Adam not since creation since Adam is
where how we're measuring time okay right now by the way a little thing for
you science buffs out there you know how we just talked about in the begats
you know like Adam lived till 900 and something and this other guy lived till
600 right and you read them and you're like this can't be right you know you
notice after the flood the the life expectancy came down right well for your
science buffs again you know how you watch you know oh even if you go to
university or television you know whatever they pull out this big skull or
you know and they say well this is Cro-Magnon man right and this is a
regular human skull you know this is a big difference in size you know they're
like you know these well we had homo sapien all this way they make up all
these terms and you have to claim them as yeah yeah yeah well what they're
actually showing you is someone who's lived many centuries because if you
study osteopathy it tells you that the longer you live the more your bones grow
right if you study what the study of osteopathy yeah actually sometimes the
theopathy I'll say it in Greek sometimes it's a Greek word yeah it tells you in
normal study you know like osteopathy 101 it tells you that the older you get
the more your brown brow bone and your femur bones your thigh bone grow
getting down cutting in and out my cutting out let's see say hello yes I'm
losing you you're getting kicked you're cutting out your battery or something
are you there Angela I'm losing you I can hear you you're breaking up really
bad I'm sorry I'm using my location again and say are you plugged in my cable
so I don't my in the chest and I'm breaking up so if I hadn't talked okay
are you but you can you can hear me right I like you know I my connection is
I'll keep speaking hopefully you'll remedy it well what's interesting is
things of are not as they appear as we've been saying and I guess when you
when you wrote on the description about prophecy I mean no one's called in to
ask questions we haven't allowed it yet but I mentioned earlier well actually
there's three people with their hand up waiting to ask the question you think
we should let questions go right now I'm fine with it it's up to you if you want
to continue on and ask questions later or take questions later and now it's up
to you oh I like to continue a few just a few more topics okay go right ahead
and the mindset is very important and I'm not trying to convince someone of
anything I'm just trying to show you another way of looking at what you think
is the same thing and when you look at it this way you'll say hey I what I was
the way I thought it was this thing doesn't resemble anything at all what
I've been told or taught and when you start researching it on your own you'll
say oh okay now I'm in limbo you know I'm really lost now and my my intent is
not to lose anyone but it's to maybe shed light or cause a higher sense of
discernment you know you ask why but the again many people who say they have
read the Bible actually have not with with the discernment that's required and
when I spoke earlier on the the main character in Scripture is the Christ or
you could say the Messiah the Savior that has been the focus of Christianity
Christianity and actually in Judaism as well and what they've put in front of
the world or who they've put in front of the world and both intent and imagery is
incorrect scripturally now I'm not saying it's incorrect if you want to believe in
it because you can believe in anything but what I'm saying is what I've
discovered in Scripture and what is being put in front of the world is not
the same thing at all not by a long shot so the who is the who is this Christ
figure who is the Savior they call him Jesus or Yahshua or you know all these
names and they've got images of him in churches and people wear crosses around
their necks and all this other stuff and I haven't found any evidence of any of
the descriptions in Scripture at all that resemble what's being taught to the
people and that was actually one of the scariest parts of researching Scripture
are you still there Angela yep I am here okay great so what for example when
you go to a church the first image they show you let's say when you when you
know they say they've just built this church and they open the doors you're
our first customer come on in right you look down the aisle what do you see at
the end typically see this this symbol looks like a large cross right and you
see a guy nailed to it with long hair and he's wearing a diaper and he's kind
of leaning the side it looks real beat up not too happening and that's supposed
to be the way the Messiah or the Christ was executed or killed or that was
supposed to look like him and so far the whole world has accepted that image well
I read Scripture and for example his execution started reading it it's in
the first four books of what they call the New Testament and each one has an
account of it Matthew Mark Luke and John and it's usually towards the end of the
book now if you read the account of how this execution happened in each of the
books and you actually take notes on each one because they each give a little
bit of information some have a little less information some have a little more
if you take notes on that and you've also read what's called the Old Testament
in the Law of Moses and all of the prophets and all the Psalms before that
because what they call the Old Testament is actually the introduction to the New
Testament and you've taken notes on that well you'll put you'll harmonize the
whole scene and you'll and you'll you'll get information put together
that'll say whoa where did they get this image what's this Roman what's this guy
doing on this Roman cross well what's going on you know why why how did Mel
Gibson screw up so bad you know that movie he did recently what is it called
the Passion or something like that right right yeah it's like well wait a
second you know they've made so many films and you always you know this man
carrying this long cross you know and and they set it up and you see a big
cross in the middle and there's a cross on his right and a cross on his left and
you know and in Jerusalem they sell tickets to where there's three holes in
the ground when the old city of Jerusalem you know this is where Jesus
died you know this is where he was crucified and you read the scripture and
you're like excuse me folks have you guys read the book have you read your
own book at least once do you know what you're doing here no no this is we don't
believe this is what we believe in you see this is our faith this is our
religion oh I see I see okay well I'll leave you alone to it then you just go
right ahead you know knock yourself out so what am I trying to say well I'll go
through the story very quickly you have this fellow he is the Messiah he's the
character of the Christ in Scripture and the leaders of Jerusalem or the leaders
of Israel at that time are under Roman occupation and the things that he's
saying and the way he's coming off as being an authority is indirectly
challenging the authority and the powers that be so they want him gone so they
can't figure out what to arrest him on but finally they do arrest him on the
charges of blasphemy because scripture says not to blaspheme and the charges
were brought upon him because he said you will see me sitting at the right
hand of the father and the priest tears his robe and says we don't need any
witnesses against him he just witnessed you know he just said it and what's
very interesting a lot of Christians are misled because there's a false witness
they're saying and he told the people not to pay taxes and a lot of people
say well Christians don't have to pay taxes and like yeah that's what the false
witness that was there said that he actually the Messiah didn't never said
that and at least document it and there is a scene where he actually walks into
a room with Peter and says look at this tax collector here isn't it isn't it the
law that tax collectors only collect taxes from foreigners and they don't tax
their own people? Taxpayer didn't say anything and Peter said yeah it says
well we don't want to be a stumbling block to this man so why don't you go
catch a fish and you'll find a silver piece in its stomach and why don't you
give it to him half a shekel for me you know half a piece of silver for me and
half a piece of silver for you because that was the required minimum tax half a
piece of silver for every man over 20 right so where does the Messiah say not
to pay taxes when he's paying taxes himself you see so people don't know how
to read I just wanted to interject that so people read that and there's someone
witnessing against him saying that he told the people not to pay taxes he is
one of the false witnesses that are spoken of saying the witness people were
paid to witness against him. Well to move forward you see because at the time
Israel and the leaders were kind of like a puppet authority because they were
under Roman rule Pontius Pilate was a governor over them really and you know
they were allowed to rule on minor things but major stuff they had to get
permission from the Roman government so so far we're in accord with a lot of the
movies and stuff they teach in Sunday school right right okay well we're going
to start this is where the diversion starts here well they bring them to
Pilate and they say we want to put a death sentence on this guy capital
punishment right let's say which is actually a Roman term also and Pilate's
wife has dreams and visions not to to leave this man alone and you know
there's things that go back and forth but ultimately Pilate says look I find
no guilt in this man that is worth of death and I've told you this three times
in other words I'm not going back on it I want nothing to do with the death of
this man no I'm not going to oblige you I'm not going to put him to death and
then if you keep reading Pilate says to the Pharisees you have a law you you
Israelites use your law and the retort back from the Pharisees is well we can't
run to Caesar's rule he says I'm making this one exception use your law but what
law of Israel supposed to be using at the time but what was the law of the
Israelites they get their law from Moses right so if you go to Deuteronomy 21
which was one of the five books of the law of Moses you will see in Deuteronomy
21 it says if a son acts a certain way and it's a death offense used to be
nailed to a tree and taken down before sundown so the land does not become
defiled and that's the law they used now the only involvement the Romans had
in this execution was to close off the streets and provide police protection
to keep the crowds back because it was showtime see the the this mosaic form of
execution hadn't been done since the Romans were had conquered that part of
the world so it was over a hundred years or maybe 150 years since they'd
seen something like this so it's showtime it's a parade so the Romans
closed off the streets just like today when you get a parade going right you go
to the local city and you tell them what you want a parade for and they say okay
we'll approve it and we'll give you the police protection to close off the
streets and whatever have your day but here's the thing if you read in the law
it says that all executions were to happen outside the city wall so it can't
be at the Golgotha or Calvary that they say he was killed can't be
because that's inside the city wall had it be outside the city wall well but the
question is how specific can you get on this you can get very specific on it
over and over and over in Scripture there's a metaphor using the almond tree
a l m o n d the seven-branched lampstand was the arm was to be the likeness of an
almond tree in Jeremiah chapter 1 he asked Jeremiah what do you see he says I
see a branch of an almond tree the Creator says yes I shall do it this is
do what you know I basically said do I didn't say that in the scripture in
Genesis Jacob is hurting some sheep with a rod of an almond and branch and
he peels the bark back to show its stripes and psalms that says through
our stripes we were healed right so we start to see if we keep reading further
on the Messiah is the center of the lampstand or they call the menorah which
is an almond tree and it has seven branches well you see the Messiah was
nailed to this tree in the Mount of Olives with two other thieves or two
other offenders right so you've got three people nailed to a tree with their
each having two arms up in the air and the center of the tree making it seven
because you have two times three is six and the center is seven so that's what
the menorah it's still used today they use nine branches or whatever and further
Hanukkah or whatever but the menorah the lampstand is the likeness of an almond
tree and the almond branch keeps coming up over and over and over so we know it
was an almond tree based on the prophets and the Psalms and being nailed to a
tree doesn't kill you because you have to be taken down by night so you have to
be hasty the method of execution in the Bible because remember they're using
their law Pontius Pilate said use your law the method of execution is not being
nailed to a tree it's actually stoning and if you read in Luke when he left the
Messiah or the Christ was leaving the temple he the people wanted to stone him
and he turns around he says twice you've tried to stone me already why so when he
was nailed to the tree the people were being held back and they were throwing
stones at him until all this flesh was ripped off of his body which is in the
Psalms as well and it's very important to understand that the Messiah the
scripture says and that the Messiah will explain everything to us and he
actually does and the Messiah says haven't you read Moses the Psalms and
the prophets they tell you all about me he didn't say wait for this new religion
coming around you know that they'll tell you about me no he says you have to go
to Moses the prophets and the Psalms so the keys to all this information is in
five books of Moses all the books of the prophets and reading the Psalms you'll
find great detail on how he was executed and he was front and center he received
all of the blows from the stoning the the other two offenders let's say one was on
his left one was on his right they received partial blows on their sides
that's why their legs had to be broken if you read it the centurion saw that the
Christ was dead and he walked around to the other and saw he was still alive and
he walked around to the other he didn't go from cross to cross so what I'm saying
is what why is this important to know you know to some it probably isn't but to
others if you actually research it and you find it to be true you will see
what's going on that this image that's being put in front of us as being the
Christ is not even close and you've got a lot of other groups I should say
Jehovah Witness or whoever else I didn't want to get into you know they all have
their own quote-unquote theories you know he was nailed to a stake you know or
something and everyone's got their own idea but it's not from Scripture well
what they you know the Greek word style Romano's or style girls they've
translated to crucifixion and Messiah said carry your stake there was a stake
involved it looked like a what would be a metaphorically a railroad tie because
you they didn't tell you to just get up on this ladder lean on the tree so we
could nail you to it it didn't work that way those executions were done they were
very brutal they would they would beat the person to be executed very badly and
nail him to a crossbar cross beam on the ground and they would have been nailed
the cross beam to the tree and then nail your feet to the tree and that's how the
execution was done I like to set up for the execution and then you were stoned
in that position so this is a very different account on what is being
taught and or celebrated and to me it's very clear by reading it in the
scripture and anyone who can read it forensically and and has read the law
and has read the dialogue between the Roman authorities and the the
authorities of Israel at the time will see it as plain as day now we can get
you know into the spiritual aspect of it you know a lot of things have been
branched off you know people say well you have to be saved and I asked them
what are you going to be saved from you know or I live under grace will you
define grace they can't define these terms these are things that people have
been told that are not scriptural whatsoever we have some people that
would like to ask questions all right I'll take some okay the first one is SB3
there you go go ahead go ahead did you have a question go ahead and ask your
question please I'm thinking that in the last show he said he was going to reveal
something you know let me mute my computer please okay yes he was going to
reveal something shocking and I'm kind of thinking what was it well as anything
that I've said tonight I mean move you in any way or did you know any of this
information or you aware of it or do you find I mean yeah in the most part in the
most part yes uh-huh does it shock you that the the birthday cake represents
human sacrifice I knew about that yeah okay you're one of the very few then
yeah I knew about that okay thank you thanks a lot thanks thank you okay we've
got straw man let me try to unmute straw man here go ahead straw man did you have
a question for the Greek guy straw man hello maybe you've got your phone muted
out you have a button on your phone or something or you fell asleep maybe straw
man are you there all right we'll just press star 8 again I'll let you back on
we're going to move on to Daniel Ray one go ahead Daniel Ray one Daniel Ray did
you want to ask a question do you have a mute button on your phone maybe Daniel
Ray one okay there we go okay I have three first of all why you catch colds
in the wintertime that's an interesting scenario on foods but also could be a
factor of sunshine where in the summertime we have a lot of vitamin D
production which saves off a lot of illnesses in the wintertime we don't have
much vitamin D could it be also a factor yes and no yes if you if we properly
look at what you is called vitamin D but no because there's really no such thing
as a vitamin okay what they've done is taken bodies non-living bodies dissected
them in laboratories look at the chemicals that are involved and said
let's call these things vitamins because every cell seems to have it and maybe
you need it and maybe we can actually bottle these things and and sell them in
other words measuring something changes that thing so what do if you look at all
of these for example chemicals or vitamins I should say like vitamin C well
vitamin C is ascorbic acid right well is it if you've ever worked with ascorbic
acid you wouldn't want that in your body and what they do is for example take an
orange apart you know and they kill it first right because you have to juice it
and heat it and separate all the parts out of it right and they say well look
this thing appears to be like ascorbic acid oh so it's in an orange let's call
it a vitamin you know well you know then if you read a lot of these medical
documents actually all of them they never tell you anything is they tell you it
appears to be so when you when you guys figure it out why don't you write a
document say hey we figured it out let me know you see when you go to science
class and any level of education they talk about theories or things appear to
be and I said well you have a conclusion you know for sure I'll buy that
information but in the meantime I'll just I'll be a little bystander on the
side okay nothing like having the real food food is it they don't they well
here's here's an example of how that aspect of science currently works you
know for example you know someone comes back from war and they say you know hey
man I've got shell shock and they say well well well you know I've got nothing
for I can't help you if you got shell shock but if you have PTSD and if you can
claim that I've got lots of things I could prescribe for PTSD but I've got
nothing I could prescribe for shell shock you see yeah how you caption it
see that's where they work is this see you know why you contract an illness you
know I've called you contract an illness because when you go there you get
inspected and he has all these books with legal bindings on them and it says
which one of these diseases do you want to contract with well that's interesting
way of putting it didn't it well is there any other way to put it I'm not being
facetious I'm just saying oh I hear you I am yeah in that way that's interesting
yeah so for example you know I've got a problem with fat I can't help you with
fat but I if you say if you sign here and say that I've diagnosed you with a
lipid disorder will it be this fat also now you claim that you claimed my
creation you've claimed my description well now you can be my subject and my
patient and I can legally prescribe it to you see yeah but for example you know
if you're a garbage man I can't help you but if you're a sanitation engineer if
you claim to be that my my description then I can help you that's how your
subject here so yeah I'll claim that one yeah I'll be that I'll claim that
description oh okay that now if you make this your description I could work with
you right because now you take full liability for it yeah I'm showing you
spiritual the spiritual cognitive side of it in other words being cognitive you
know being aware of what's going on hope I didn't lose anyone with this but when
you measure something that is living you will get different results and if you
measure something when if you kill it and then dissect it and process it and
fractionalize it it won't measure the state they actually the very process of
trying to measure something actually changes that as well you know the
vitamin vitamin part I never bought into and I just basically when people want to
talk about it say well there's no such thing as a vitamin I don't know I've
never seen a vitamin hanging off of the tree have you you know hardly on jumping
subject something you brought the other night gave me a reminder of some of the
hair the Greek heritage the story is it's when the children of Israel were led
out of Egypt thousands hundreds of thousands of them a second contingent
left the other way it didn't go across the they went to Greece they went to
Greece right as a matter of fact everyone left Egypt for a short time and
the modern Egyptian people actually the ancient Egyptian people are still
occupying some of the Caucasus area parts of Russia and Armenia and most of
the modern Egyptian people in Egypt today are actually of Canaanite descent
Phoenicia yeah then they went from the Greece they went down into Spain and they
traded with the Spanish and they fought with the Spanish and had difficulty
finding the Spanish gave them Portugal and they continued to contract and trade
with the Spanish and fought with the Spanish so they finally say well we got
to move again so they took their boats and then exploring up north along the
coast to the Green Isles and the gal the woman who is the the leader and his
wife and his wife was named Skoda and so he took all these people the majority
of them and went north to the Green Islands and that became the land of
Skoda or Scotland so the Scots to a great extent of the house of Israel of course
the Irish gave them suppose they gave them the bagpipe and the Irish claim
they still haven't caught the joke okay however the bagpipe also traces back to
the Egypt right and it's I believe it's once mentioned in scripture or something
like that so you may have you may have very close relatives in Scotland perhaps
I do that's the third item the third item you mentioned in the night was
going to talk a little bit about some of the future predictions right well the
more than predictions I can I can get to that pretty directly if you like to hear
it yes they're there they're going to happen for sure and the actual detail is
unfolds every day because the information in scripture is actually
very it's like a time-release capsule to use with people you know if you watch
television they've got these drugs now that are time-released right so you know
they don't all dissolve at one time one of the promises made by Daniel will shut
up this book until the time of the end and there's a patient that is required
for example when people say I don't do that old obsolete law anymore I said
what do you mean old and obsolete that Moses formally gave that in writing only
four and a half days ago two people are thinking in secular time which is four
and a half thousand years ago it was actually given only four days ago in
the spiritual realm it's not a very long time at all no but essentially the crux
of the matter is I was kind of hesitant to get into a lot of the prophetic
aspects because most people are what I call idiocentric and that's a Greek word
meaning self-centered in other words when people in America read the Bible they
say all the Israelites oh they're American Oh Babylon that's American Oh
Israel that's in America oh this beast is American Oh the Antichrist is the
president right someone in Japan reading it will say Oh Israel is
Japanese Israel is Japan the Antichrist is Japanese this is Babylon is Tokyo
right someone in Russia saying you know well the Israelites are Russian and
Moscow is Babylon and guess what they're all wrong no we know it's all Greek
nope it's not Greek either that's a good point so I am hesitant because people
want to debate and argue well the Israelites are not this and like I well
whatever but essentially what you're going to see happening temporarily after
1998 there are four seven-year periods plus one five-year period so if you add
that all together you get a pretty good idea after 1998 when you will have the
spiritual dimension I call it the fifth dimension enter into this fourth third
plus one or fourth dimension fourth being time now the two do these dimensions will
all meld together and the truth will be exposed but before that happens if you
read in Scripture there's one more world empire or what a lot of people call the
New World Order that will have to take place it will be in power for about seven
years and it'll be extremely powerful the most powerful world order or kingdom
this world has ever seen by a long shot in power and Dominion and this kingdom
is being formed right now it's a political world power it's military it's
judicial it's economic it'll be a world focus and this can be referred to as the
fourth beast of Daniel or the beast in Revelation is being formed right now as
we speak and it is actually going to be a nation a group of ten nations forming
a very loose Confederacy like it's like the EU for example the Confederacy of
Nations and it'll be in the Middle East the thing is one of those nations are
missing right now doesn't exist it's in Psalms 83 if you read Psalms 83 David
says these nine nations come against Israel destroy it well that has to be
prophetic something in the future because all through history Israel never
fought more than a two-front war and it lists all of the nations with great
accuracy and there's actually a group of three that have to be formed but there's
one that's actually missing completely and that's a Syria and at the end of the
psalm he says and a Syria will join them also so where is a Syria a Syria has
not been a nation for over 2,300 years it's in northern Iraq there are about
over a million of Syrians that live all throughout the world so when we look at
the occurrences and why the Iraq war happened from a secular point of view
you could say yes it was based on weapons of mass destruction which we know
was a lie and or was based on oil greed and power yes but yeah that that's been
going on for thousands of years but now you know the real reason the spiritual
world is in charge this nation had to be formed and this country was used to
form it and if you look a little bit deeper a beast power in Scripture is
defined by a nation that's able to wage war militarily against another so
America does qualify or the United States does qualify as one and the
characteristics the characteristics of this beast or the characteristics of a
beast in Scripture are always a predatory animal of some sort metaphorically and
what all predators have in common is that the the destroyer eat their prey
but they all do it differently there are different types of predators so this
type of beast system has a characteristic that whenever it goes
into a country most likely it divides it by two or splits it went into Colombia
and formed Panama over 120 years ago went into Germany made East West Germany
went into Korea split Korea went into Vietnam it split Vietnam what are the
chances of it splitting Iraq into two countries like nine out of ten very
very high chance and I've been saying this now for quite a few years and
recently I think in 09 an Assyrian Congress now when I say us Syrian it's
us Syrian not Syrian an Assyrian Congress was formed in Los Angeles and
they actually put together a small little Constitution and they said well
we don't have a country yet we'd like to have one but we've got everything ready
to go so you're going to see that forming and also you're going to see
the country of Jordan it's going to be divided into three and the current regime
the current king actually that's there now Abdullah I think it is they're going
to be ousted and that's very specific in Psalms 83 as well it lists the Jordan
as three separate countries and that is coming that is coming over the next seven
to twelve years now what does that have to do with what's happening here well I
just explained to you the purpose of the military involvement of this country or
the people of this country over there from the spiritual world from that other
dimension but the rest of it is not basically it's not even remotely
mentioned in Scripture or at least this country in any specific specific way
other than when all the nations are mentioned there are many places in
all the nations will do this or this will happen to all the nations such and
such but what you will see happening here is this country and Europe will be
playing second fiddle to this new world empire forming in the Middle East also a
few years ago I was saying to people the middle class will start to dwindle and
in fact be destroyed and you're going to see a lot of economic upheaval it'll
probably start late 2008 early 2009 I've been saying that's enough since
2005 2004 actually that's pretty accurate yeah well where do you where do
you get that from if you look at the time period in the book of Revelation it
gives you in the earlier chapters and by the way I read Scripture without chapter
and verse because those things are like speed bumps put in there there's a they
were never put in they were never in this scriptures the chapter and verses
recent edition and if you read the scripture without chapter and verse it
has a natural effect on the mind where you should stop and go so I'm not very
good at giving chapter and verse but in the book of Revelation the earlier
chapters it says a day's wages will be X amount of wheat or X amount of barley
but do not harm the oil in the wine Wow okay so who are wage workers this is
going to be their wage so you figure out how much wheat is given there and wait
and you go to the store and say see how much wheat costs and you're like wow a
day's wage is going to be around 20 some odd bucks wow that's not very good but
do not harm the oil and wine are the wealthy and who's doing this are the
horsemen who have been let out already and why is oil and the wine represents
the wealthy well because in order to produce oil and wine you need
infrastructure and that was typically something the wealthy did wage workers
and your middle class did not make oil and wine in order to make oil and wine
for example wine you need vineyards and you need labor to crush the grapes and
you need barrels and you're basically you have to have what's called what
discretionary income today right yep and also oil making oil was a big operation
takes a lot of olives to make a little bit of oil you need a lot of equipment
and storage so that's if you have a biblical mindset you could read that and
say well okay the working class will be pretty much decimated but the wealthy
will not and you can go out and say that for you know you can say that for
example if you preach group gloom and doom at any time during the history of
this people on this planet you'll always be right but can you do it with specifics
and timing no you can't do it unless you're actually following what's in the
manual so you got to look at the timing in there there is a book of Revelation
is four seven-year periods so then you know earlier I said there are four
seven-year periods plus a five-year period where does that five-year period
come from well it comes from Genesis because there are five days before man
comes on the scene right man was made on the sixth day and this is our day in
other words man system the number six six six is the number of a man in
Demetria which is you know when you figure out the name numerically but it
also is the system of man and two witnesses to the system of man it's
basically you know you want your system go ahead go for it see if you like it so
the six six six six basically means the system of man the system of man the
system of man but it also is the number of someone's name now a lot of people
run around and they say well this guy is the Antichrist and this guy is the
Antichrist and that guy's the Antichrist I'm like no and there's a
problem when you study script short scripture in the Bible or the Bible
accurately I tell people be careful of what you say because one of two things
will happen you'll either be laughed at by those who know it or you're going to
be misleading those who don't know it so when people go around screaming about
the Antichrist well is such-and-such or this guy the Antichrist mentioned in
scripture well no doesn't fit well the Antichrist is an Antichrist he's an
Antichrist so he is a he is a Christ or a character that comes out of man system
not of the divine and if you look at scripture very carefully man's number is
six and if you look at when the divine Christ was born his number is four he
was born in the year 4,000 he said I am the Elohim or the mighty one of the
Sabbath or in regular English didn't he say I'm the Lord of the Sabbath I made
the Sabbath for man and not man for the Sabbath remember that yep well the
Sabbath basically means week and how many weeks are there in a month or four
right so here he goes number four again if you keep searching scriptural through
it you'll see the Messiah in the fourth position he's got three on his left and
three on his right that's the number seven number four is directly in the
middle of the number seven so if the Messiah of the scripture divine was born
in the year 4,000 if we want to figure out who the Antichrist is he'd have to
be born in the year 6,000 right with scriptural logic well when was the year
6,000 that was around the fall of 1998 that would make him 13 years old see
yeah so it's not such-and-such and it's not you know the point is that how old
is he how old is this guy you're calling the Antichrist oh he's 52 they're too
old sorry bye wrong where'd you get that from well
somebody I read something that somebody wrote and that he read something that
somebody wrote yeah what's that yeah somebody channeled it yeah it's like
reading the cliff notes on the cliff notes on the cliff notes and anyway by
the way if anyone's taken English and you're supposed to read a book and you
read the cliff notes you never get better than a B or a C you've got her
you've got to go right to the source so but there's more detail in scripture
apparently this fellow is of Assyrian descent it's very clear in Isaiah and
other prophets they call him the Assyrian and we just spoke about a
Syria being formed so he's one of the people that don't live there or live
there and also it states very specifically he will have an injury and
lose his use of his right eye and the use of one of his arms okay so now we're
getting really specific do you see my point yeah so you've got all these
priests and pastors and quote-unquote religious people saying well this is it
could be good well what are you basing it on you know faith yeah or based on this
timetable that means that the 2012 year is not going to disappear either it's the
Mayan calendar oh okay 2012 I've got two letters and a number for you or I got
three words for the 2012 crowd you know what they are you know what that is
y2k get it yeah what happened during y2k remember all the I mean a lot of guns
canned food and generators were sold right I certainly did yeah but what
happened nothing obvious yeah okay so 2012 equals y2k real simple I mean if I
did fail they wouldn't tell us anyway well first of all there's no such thing
as 2012 and the real reason the Mayan calendar ended is because it was a
government funded the astronomers were were government funded and the
government ran out of money so that's home to wrap it up real quick
don't think no change yeah have you ever heard of Occam's razor the simplest
explanation is probably the most accurate and actually I did read
something about this oh about 15 years ago because they were talking about 2012
15 years ago and someone pointed out it says why don't you read about what they
wrote about this in the 1800s on how they reckon that time system and you'll
see that they just decided to end it for no reason at all
they talked about galactic centers and all this other stuff and it just doesn't
make any sense because the earth is always in the galactic center it's
ridiculous so they just made it up you know what an opportunist is right yeah
you ever go to a rock concert and they sell t-shirts outside for 20 bucks right
you know sure you know whenever you have a particular okay for example you know
we go to the movie theater pay 20 bucks for popcorn you know it's called
opportunism right but it's well-deserved I'm not telling anyone to not spend
their money preparing or not telling anyone to tell anyone not to prepare
this is commercial you know I mean it's you see you see commerce goes in luck
with lack of knowledge and lack of information do you see my point you know
there's a good film I suggest people go and get if you haven't seen it it's
called idiocracy I don't know if anyone's seen it surprised yeah it blows
away that people say we gotta see the matrix it's what's going on now matrix
it's like you could show the matrix to a million people and even then you know
like five will get it maybe but if you watch idiocracy in the first five
minutes you're like oh no this is what's going on right now it's so much better
than the matrix you know in these other films that you know they kind of sneak
in a little thing but they don't really tell it to you like it is you know being
like in the matrix you're plugged into this thing it doesn't really translate
very well but if you watch idiocracy you're like oh I'm living in it right
now this is happening so yeah we tend to romanticize too much but what's again
what's going to happen here is this country is going to be playing second
fiddle to that world economic system that's going to be forming there where
is there the Middle East Syria okay yeah so there's a lot more specifics I
mean we can get like super specific on time and what to watch for example you
know a lot of people I get our idiocentric the word idio is the Greek
word meaning same or self right like that's where you get through the Freudian
term id ego right from you know like the id and the ego and this other stuff
that nonsense they talk about right but this is the Greek word idio meaning
self the same self like the word idiot means someone who is just into their
self-concern like for example a prerequisite to being greedy as you must
be an idiot in other words if you're in just your own you're only concerned
about yourself that leads to greed we're not using these words we like for
example the word moron means infantile that's all it means it's a Greek word
morose or moron meaning morose meaning infant it's all see with a bit the
interesting thing about Scripture is that everyone has the same intelligence
the way how we perceive and act in Scripture is discerned by discernment it
says people have eyes yet they don't see and they have ears and they don't hear
it doesn't say anywhere in Scripture that one man is more intelligent than
another anywhere we all have the same intelligence it's that our perception
varies in great degree from blind all the way to full open eyes and open ears
and then you have wisdom which is discernment right that's why there is a
saying that you know a fool learns from his own mistakes and a wise man learns
from other people's mistakes well if that wise man didn't see the other
people's mistakes how would he learn anything so it's based on discernment
eyes and ears again right right so there's we all have the same intelligence
so that IQ quotient stuff intelligence quotient that's ridiculous why would
you let someone tell you how intelligent you are when scripturally the
instruction manual says we all have the same intelligence it's discernment right
that we don't have and that's the purpose of this call I want to somehow
maybe try to convey or impart something that will increase someone's power of
discernment well again how are these words being used and we know all of the
books have been manipulated so don't bother with these dictionaries go get
yourself an etymology dictionary etymology tells you the root meaning of
the word how are they going to mess with that you know yeah how are they
going to mess you know you can change the meaning of the word of person or
this or that but yeah go look up where that word came from you're going to start
messing with that I don't think so that's a big liability so we need to you
know we have all these dictionaries but they're really you know why does blacks
law have to keep changing why you know get an etymology figure out what the
word really meant I think I explained coincidence earlier it means to coincide
you see so you know like a real easy one is kid kid is a goat children are the
offspring of men and women period yeah would you like to take another question
yeah sure is that it for you Daniel Ray or did you want to ask anything else
that's fine thank you okay SB3 go ahead SB3 you must have your mute button on
or something I am muted you from this end they look like you were trying to say
something here I hear clicking say something SB3 SB3 1 2 3 did you want to
ask a question do you have a mute button on your phone maybe looks like you're
trying to talk I hear y'all sporadically say something yeah you're
unmuted on this end so I don't know something wrong with your phone maybe
looks like you're trying to talk from this from here say something talk say
testing 1 2 3 okay don't then we lost it's not work well now they're there
that's just and they're unmuted but I know they're having a problem with their
phone and maybe their mic I don't know how they're on but all right we have a
couple more questions Joanna go ahead Joanna oh wonderful okay thank you so
much what an idiot you know we get more stupid people on here it's like they
just can't stand it they can't stand it okay Charles Slackus yes go ahead yes I
was wondering how you spell that word of that dictionary oh etymology yeah yeah
that's just a term that means root of words it would be e-t-y-m-o-l-o-g-y okay
one more question what would be the proper Bible to study would it be the
King James or the earlier version that's a great question and I was waiting
for someone to ask that you want the short of it or the long of it
both well the best source right you always want to go to the source that is
preserved is the Hebrew and the Greek now I'm not suggesting the Israelites
spoke Hebrew or they spoke Greek it's just the father decided to preserve it
to our it all the way to our day in Hebrew and Greek almost unchanged now
when you get yourself a King James version it's a version well not a
translation it's not interpretation see an interpretation or translator or
interpreter has to be precise when you're the Japanese Prime Minister you
go to the UN you bring yourself an interpreter or translator whatever you
say he better say it to the T now the someone given the version of the story
may not be so so accurate but the wonderful thing about Scripture is that
it has an effect on mind that if the reader has power of discernment the
information that you're reading even out of the King James or an NIV or
something that's been really kind of messed with you'll be able to correct it
with your own power of discernment just like a digital information you know
transferred over a computer line it's all zeros and ones but when the
computer sometimes gets a corrupted signal it says I've got a syntax error
here because this doesn't make any sense you got to figure out what the problem
is so when you read in the King James for example my name is the Lord you've
got to say I've heard of that word Lord before and I know that it's an English
title of nobility and if I look it up there's about 400 of them in England
which one is it can't be right this is a syntax error because Lord is not a name
because these Lords in England got names like Lord Vicar Rothschild or Lord you
know Lord Michael Helmsley right right so and Lord cannot be a name it's
actually a title of nobility syntax error okay defrag time go back to the
original language of preservation what do they got in there so then if you're
reading in the Old Testament you're going to go into a Hebrew and if you
don't read or comprehend it you get an interlinear where it's got the Hebrew and
the English right under it and you will see that it doesn't say Lord at all and
there's a lot of errors in the in the King James because in the old in the Old
Testament you'll see it'll say well it was the eighth day of the fifth month in
this year then you get to the New Testament they're talking about you
know Easter Sunday well wait a second there Sunday was only invented 500 years
ago it can't be accurate because they weren't reckoning Sundays 2,000 years
ago so you're going to need power of discernment see in the digital world they
call that sampling rate when you send a digital signal there's some little a
board or another program that's always looking at the information coming in and
sampling it and saying okay this is good this is good oh this is corrupt right
here it's going to mess up your syntax and you get a little syntax error on
your screen you know so if you've got the power of discernment and you're a
word technologist you know what I mean you'll be able to pick them up I see I
consider myself to be a word technician so unfortunately if you're not a word
technician my best suggestion would be to get yourself an interlinear which has
got the languages of preservation in the English right below it now every full
unabridged Bible in the introduction will explain everything I just explained
to you an unabridged version of most Bibles that I've seen are anywhere
between 7 to 40 pages long and they say well we just changed you know the name
to Lord because if we didn't nobody would buy this book you know like they
say for publishing reasons and obviously you know it'll tell you the days
mentioned here didn't exist but we did it for publishing reasons so they'll
preface this stuff but unfortunately without the power of discernment and
knowledge of what existed and what didn't exist back then you're you're
not going to do well unless you're talking to someone like me and I'm not
really looking to tutor anyone or have a Bible study or anything like that but
there's plenty information and help online there's a program called eSword
and it's King James Version but if you hold your mouse over each English word
it'll give you the definition and the original word that was it was preserved
in now when I say Hebrew the the Israelites there I don't see much
evidence of them being Hebrews or speaking Hebrew they spoke Edenic the
people around them the Canaanites the Babylonians the Cushites everybody
around them were Kate were spoke Hebrew and that's why when you're reading the
off he says because you didn't drive the Canaanites out of your land they're
going to be a stumbling block to you and your children Wow wow yeah so now
you're stuck with you you're we're basically operating in the Canaanite
system you might have heard that before right yeah and but the father says I'll
give you what you did what you need and what you deserve and give you what you
deserve based on how well how well you find out what I want you to do and do it
I've been speaking to people lately about miracles and healings and they said
I found all miracles and all healings require had one basic requirement and if
you don't meet that basic requirement you ain't gonna get them and that basic
requirement is you have to be an obedient servant and every miracle every
healing what they all had in common was an obedient servant now when you're a
servant some you know it's let's say you you're living with someone as a roommate
and he tells you hey go do my laundry well thank your servant get up and do it
yourself but if you're living with someone and you say I am your servant he
tells you get up and do my laundry yes I will I may not do it perfectly but I'll
try to I might get scolded here or there you know I threw the red sock in with
the white shirts messed everything up but I try most people aren't even trying
you know if you look at all the miracles that the Christ performed with a water
and a wine those were obedient servants they ran out of wine and his mom his
mother said Miriam she wasn't married Miriam she said yeah he'll he'll make it
into wine and he said well you want me to show everybody who I am okay and she
says do exactly as he tells you to and they did exactly what they told him what
he told him to do and that water didn't turn into wine until the host put it
right up to his mouth to read it very carefully so there's procedure involved
in Scripture if you look at all the prophets there were obedient servants so
your King James Version is fine if you if you've got powers of discernment how
about the Geneva Bible was that a better translation Bible than the King
James no not much better very similar okay that's what I need but we're kind of
stuck we're living in a Canaanite society if you know what I mean right
and and yeah so it's a little more difficult like for example okay let's say
you got a you let's say you know we're used to certain things that are easy to
get like gasoline and batteries and things like that a real basic but if you
went out and lived in the bush in a village and you needed some diesel
batteries they'd laugh at you right right like where do you get those well
you see that's about 500 miles from here you know getting your seaplane and take
off and go get some batteries so these simple things that we take for granted
like we open a book to get information we're in the wilderness if you're in the
wilderness and you're out of batteries well you know by time you get those
batteries ain't going to be in the wilderness anymore might as well stay put
so in other words it's it's things that we consider to be easy tasks in our
lives like we should be able to open a book or get a program and have
information accurately conveyed to us we're not living in that time right now
unfortunately there's a lot of work see in scripture the father says he wants us
to be workman's in it a workman in the scripture he didn't mean like a
government job where you see one guy digging and eight people standing around
watching are you done yet he meant that you know everyone's got to work in it
and get a piece and share like potluck what'd you get let me see what you
learned so it's a constant it's it's but it is finite the message is itself is
finite because you can hold it in your hand from 400 to 900 pages depending on
the size of the font but the information contained therein is not finite it's
beyond you could study one verse out of the Bible for 50 years and just barely
get it because it's so multi-dimensional and a good place to start would be
reading Genesis chapter 1 verse 1 that's the first chapter that's been messed
with heavily and if it takes you more than a month to get past that less than
a month to get past that first verse you missed the point well thank you for the
information you're welcome okay that looks like we don't have any more
questions so if you want to go ahead and get into something well it's intense for
me because it's important to me and I can get into something that's very
specific if people are watching the news something that'll affect them
watching the let's say when when you do watch the news for example or get your
news online you will notice that in the past 10 years actually over 13 years now
something in the Middle East has been in the news every day consistently yeah
okay and that's for a reason now lately and I've been saying this since so 405
you've been seeing a lot of this nation-state called Israel in the news
almost every day as well online or maybe not as much as just the Middle East as
as a whole in general but lately Israel has been focused because of the let's
say unrighteousness or unfavorable things or unfavorable way that they've
been portrayed there's a lot of specifics in scripture on why they are
that way right now and how it is temporary and how it's all going to
change very very specifically now if the scripture doesn't say well this will
happen at 420 on May 15 2018 because there's no such thing as May or 2018 or
420 p.m. in scripture time isn't reckoned that way at all so the way it's reckoned
is by using landmarks and again one reason I don't speak on Israel and all
these other nations and peoples and basically the Bible at all in public
anymore is because everyone thinks it has to be the people here and it's not
but there are some very very specifics in scripture that will that do tell you
with great specificity what to expect and the reason Israel is mentioned over
and over from the Old Testament all the way to Jerusalem in the New Testament
is for another as for a very specific reason also see people don't want to
identify with that because they say well I'm not an Israelite I'm not Jewish you
know see there's nothing Jewish in the Bible there's no religion in the Bible
there's no Christian in the Bible there's no Muslim in the Bible the Bible
deals with hereditary bloodlines period there's no issue the word Jewish was
invented around 1500 it means these people do Jehovah's Wish Jehovah's Wish
Jewish real short has nothing to do with anything in scripture they they do
translate the word Jewish the word Judean which is one of the families one
of the lines in Israel as Jewish it's not accurate you'll see it as a Judean
but to get to the point if you read Isaiah chapter 1 verse 26 that's Isaiah
chapter 1 verse 26 it's a chapter that gives you a ton of information in just a
few words if you have scriptural discernment that's about a month's worth
of study and I can distill it down like this in Isaiah chapter 1 verse 26 he
says when I return you into the land which he did in 1948 I will restore to
you your former judges your judges of old and then you will be known as
faithful and righteous people there if a city but it can mean people as well
because in order to have a city people so he says when I return you back into
the land I will restore to you your former judges and then you will be known
as those faithful faithful and righteous city so let's look at that real closely
well after they left Egypt after machinations in the book of Joshua and
all that they get into the land and they claim the land they the creator
dispossesses the inhabitants allows them to win all the battles and they settle
in the twelve tribes and they're ruled by judges as in the book of Judges now
he said he would when he returns them back to the land he's going to return to
them their former judges the judges of old he repeats it twice well right now
modern-day Israel is being ruled by prime ministers a minister is a judge
they're ruled by head judges so it's a coincidence and and it says that and
then you will be known as that righteous and faithful people or city so
if it means what it says it says what it means are they going to be known as a
righteous or faithful people during the reign of prime ministers or judges in
modern time nope because you're going to have your reign of judges or ministers
prime ministers and then you will be known as righteous so when they no
longer have prime ministers they're going to be viewed as okay now they got their
act together and they stopped pissing off the rest of the world and everyone
around them well when is that going to happen well the book of Isaiah he tells
you I don't speak in secret I just tell you what's going to happen it happens
and it happens again so there's a repeat cycle there in prophecy so if you look
at the ancient judges of ancient Israel there were 16 of them if you count
Joshua the one that battled to get them in there you'd be 17 BC after they
settled in there were 16 well if you look at the book of judges in the
scriptures you'll see one two three four judges well up to the fourth judge
they're all men but the fourth judge in ancient Israel is Deborah a woman and
the only judge of ancient Israel and after that there were 12 more and then
there was a revolution or civil war whatever you want to view it as or a
change of government and they put Saul and they put Saul in as a king their
first king and then it was David and Solomon and so on and so forth if you
look at modern-day Israel with their modern-day judges or prime ministers
you look at Ben-Gurion okay you got one two three four Oh fourth one gold in my
air grandma Moses she's a woman also Oh coincidence it's repeating so how many
prime ministers is Israel going to have in modern day if they had 16 judges in
ancient times and it's repeating they're going to have 16 prime ministers
right now Netanyahu is number 12 so you've got four more prime ministers
before Israel flips flip-flops into another style of government and they
kind of flip-flop throughout throughout the entire world and they kind of leave
what's called the Zionist movement in the way that it's been done for the past
hundred some odd years you're not going to see them involved in as lawyers and
bankers and you know controlling interests and things like that all over
the world they're going to start focusing on on that part of the world so
it's very very accurate in terms of timing as a matter of fact this past
election with Netanyahu if you looked at it from a world news perspective TV
Livni a woman was was 90% in the polls against him and everyone's saying well
it looks like your prophetic thing may not work I said no it's going to work
you'll watch like last few days you know they'll put Netanyahu in she's going to lose
because there's only going to be one woman prime minister well there you go
well what are you psychic no I'm not psychic not at all let's read the manual
tell them what you told me about us not being a nation how we can't have a
nation how it's not possible that we have a nation oh yeah this country here
it's very difficult to call it a nation you see in order to be a nation all the
people have to be related in some capacity see Italy is a nation Greece is
a nation Spain is a nation Portugal is a nation China is a nation Russia is a
nation but America it's very difficult to call it a nation the reason why is
because if you go to Italy Spain Portugal or Russia or China 90% of the
people are going to meet guess what our Italian Spanish or Chinese they're all
related they could trace their roots back you know hundreds if not maybe a
thousand or so years bloodline thing yeah but here I mean I've got you know
neighbors German the guy across the street you know he's from Africa the guy
over there is Chinese what kind of nation is this I don't know they tell
you it's a melting pot it's so it's a frontier and if you read scripture
everyone's going to be returned to their nations the only nations here it's right
in front of our faces what are the Native Americans on reservations called
the Navajo what Indians no they're called Navajo Nation the Cherokee Nation right
oh yeah the Iroquois Nation you notice the only nation or only time the
legitimately use the word nation or outwardly is with the Native American
people right right yeah I'm part of the Cherokee Nation why because if you see
where they put us all we're all related right so it has to do with bloodline
what you believe in is not you if you say so what do we have here what do we
have here what do we have here in the United States of America if it's not a
nation what is it you told me the other day oh it's an outpost it's a gathering
it's a frontier it's an outpost of all the other places see this is the last
what we have here I don't remember what did I say other than an outpost I can't
see what we have here well what what what they're trying to do is make it a
nation by all of us going under the same father figure that's what the word
patriot means you all say you the word patriot actually means you all share the
same father the Patras you have an allegiance to the same father and there's
they made George Washington our father you see that's why they call it the
founding fathers not my I know who my father is I know who my earthly father I
know who my heavenly father is I don't know who these guys is a bunch of dead
guys by the way dead people don't make laws only the living make laws right if
you read the scripture he says I am the living one the Almighty I am living he
says that many times right that's why today the the current living peak men
and women in the legislature say well we make the laws that Constitution thing
that's just a piece of paper they're actually correct but the here's the thing
with powers of discernment what do they make they're passing bills what's a bill
you go to the restaurant and you have a get a service deck that's called a bill
right where you go to the cleaners they give you a bill when you pick up your
laundry right so they're doing you see it's a bill do you want to pay this bill
first time most of the time it's a bill we did not order well you kind of did
because you're George why you you're you know you've founding fathers right you
believe in the founding yeah okay well you're related here you go
not all of us it's wild isn't it like look in the Constitution it says we the
people of the United States blah blah blah blah blah and to establish justice
I read that I was like what everybody left Europe to get away from justice and
these guys are establishing it here this doesn't look too good yeah but explain
what justice is justice is a statue of a woman carrying scales she's not blind
but she's blindfolded and at her feet is a snake and under and under one of her
feet she's got her foot stepping on a book and if you want a more accurate
description of this go online or research DK D I K E it's not dyke it's
DK of the pronunciation D I K E but it sounds like it's spelled like dyke and
that is a Greek goddess and she was the basically kind of she interceded
between Hermes and Zeus to make sure that everybody was observing Zeus's
commands you see it's a goddess religion if you read scripture it talks a lot
about this goddess religion see justice is a goddess religion justicia is the
Latin aspect of it a lot of the Christian popes were named Justinian because they
served justice there were pagans that served this Babylonian goddess or Greek
goddess which actually originated in Babylon different form that's why you're
brought to justice you see and you serve justice or you there's a miscarriage of
justice when she has a miscarriage it's really bad Wow that's profound yeah this
is a religion that's why if you read a lot of comments like when they talk about
the Patriot movement these guys are bad they're they're radical or whatever it
says they don't they tell people not to believe in government oh we have to
believe Oh religion oh I see you've got to believe in it right it's very it's all
religious but the thing is again my stance is the Creator puts all of these
things in place basically everything you see in place right now around us is
there to accommodate us we don't want to steward the land the way he instructed
us to because well most people say oh that's the old law that's done away with
and you know those things we don't we don't believe in those things you know
he says every seventh year you were to let your fields go fallow don't plant
and you will eat what comes up naturally and I've tried that before and I get
actually more food when we do that you get a bumper crop the year before
actually the Israelites were dispossessed from the land because they didn't do that
and other things and because they sacrificed their children we went
through that already on the call what what modern ritual is so everything is
the way it is because it's supposed to be this way because we're the people are
making enemies in the spiritual world and the spiritual world controls the
physical world in other words the unseen world controls the seen world even these
scientists you know they'll show you that you know you know look at this
thing under a microscope Wow is that what it looks like you know let's go
even deeper and deeper and deeper but again I started the call I try to bring
up that man has been focused and man has been led to focus on the death side of
the natural world not the living side all of the technology all of the science
all of your medicine all of your whatever you look at cross broad
spectrum is focused on the death cycle not the life cycle you know look at
your automobiles you know an automobile consumes more air in four hours than you
do in a week and it gives off toxic chemicals your cell phones fry your
brain I mean you want to keep going I mean have you ever seen a prescription
drug that has not been taken off the market because it was dangerous which
prescription drug do you see on the market today that you don't think is
going to be taken off the market five years because it's dangerous all of them
what do you think is going on we're focusing on the death cycle yeah toxic
chemicals in the soil is fertilizer that the plants will love that oh you got
bugs in the water because you know the water is you're moving it through
straight pipes the water likes to vortex and move in you know swirl around but
no we'll force it through straight pipes and when the when the pathogens build up
we'll just put chlorine gas in there you know that'll make it better
yeah fluoride yeah but this whole thing see people lack the discernment so I
mean imagine you know we're operating on a very low level I think that's part of
the being dumbed down right yeah but the way you're dumbed down is by your
discernment being taken away or you're you're being taught that if you do try
to discern you're weird or you know again the reason why they put this guy
nailed to a cross up there is because you know if you do if you try to do
what he tells you to do that's how are you going to end up right that's
psychological right but all of this again is meant to see there's a time
period man we've been here we're going on the seventh day seven days is not a
long time but for us it's you know six thousand plus years now creation didn't
happen six thousand years ago that's ridiculous we're talking about there's a
new being on the block here his name is Adam I'm talking about not talking
about when the earth was made and all the other stuff that's a way before that if
you have the discernment to read scripture you'll see that for example
when you read in Genesis chapter 1 you know you have creation and then the
earth was you know redone and then you have the first day something was made he
said it was good he said well he made something he said it was good the first
day then he makes another thing he says okay it was good and it was the second
day and so on and so forth all the way to the sixth day well then you get to
chapter 2 and you know you see well well back again in chapter 1 man is made on
the sixth day and the plants and things are made on the fifth and so on for but
when you go to chapter 2 he's ready to make man and there are no plants yet you
know he says he has to bring water so the plants will grow you know there's no
man yet you know I mean there's no plants yet even though he's ready to make
man so what's going on it seems like things are out of order well if you
look at the style that Genesis chapter 1 is written in that is an affidavit of
evidence to be entered into a court case in chapter 2 is where the creation
really starts well chapter 1 is evidence to be entered into a court case what
where's the court case where's the trial yeah well book of Revelation the entire
book is basically a trial and it's unrebutted can't rebut it can anyone
rebut that you created the earth prove it this whole existence is a battle over
who's going to rule over this blue marble in space a man can do it legally I
mean legally I mean scripturally legal legally if he gets everyone on the
planet all men and women and children have to worship him as the creator has
to be anonymous unanimous if you have one or two or three or four people that
refuse to worship him as the creator he doesn't get the prize and that's why
when you read in Scripture there are two witnesses against him that's why when you
read in the book of Daniel Nebuchadnezzar it said he ruled the
entire world when it says that it means it but these three guys said no we're not
going to bow down to your idol and we worship the Most High and he has the
power of saving us from your furnace and if he decides not to save us that's
fine too but we're not going to bow down so they throw these three guys in the
furnace and they had to be saved because it wasn't time to give someone dominion
over the earth and they came out and Nebuchadnezzar said wow okay who's this
guy you said well you got it man he is the Most High I better watch myself so
this time is coming again you're going to have a character coming on the scene
that's going to usurp the consciousness this is a fight and a battle for your
consciousness and the people on this planet have been set up like this for
the past 6,000 years for six days however you want to look at it six days
not a very long time and one thing I want to say about time is you can you
know how the saying is it be here now yeah you're always here in the now but
you can never observe the now you can only observe the past or the future and
the only way you can observe the future is if someone has a vantage point from
the future that convey information back to you and the only way you can observe
the past is if you have a record of history the reason why you cannot observe
the now is well let's do a simple experiment okay let's observe this
second oh it's gone oh okay did anybody catch it no I can't see it oh we were in
another second right now here it goes oh you see it's called entropy okay but
let's look into the future I got this mason jar over here for capturing time
you're ready you ready Angela I got it open we're going to capture this second
coming you ready three two one I got it in the jar okay oh it's gone oh I didn't
quite get it let's get the next one you see how you cannot observe the now
you're always observing the past you see I miss this might sound a theory on some
people say well whatever you know but think about it on your own time so
here's the kicker man man's history is about the past but the creators history
is about the future when the creator writes when the father writes history he
writes about the future because he has a different vantage point like for
example the Messiah said the first will be last and the last will be first he
keeps saying that he gives parables about it and he said I am the alpha and the
Omega or the olive from the top the first and the last well if you look in
Genesis chapter 1 it says basically you know in the beginning God created the
heavens and the earth no it doesn't I mean yes it does but they left out a
very important part it actually says in the beginning all of him are the mighty
ones I don't like to use the word God but let's say God in this case for ease
communication it says in the beginning God created the alpha and the Omega the
first and the last right and then he created the heavens in the earth so
that's why in the book of John he says in the beginning there was the word and
the word was with God and God was the word well so he's standing there in
front of the Pharisees saying yeah this guy this convicted felon you guys just
killed by the way yeah okay let me show you where he really is you see Genesis
right here for Moses see him right here oh see the elephant on the Alpha Omega
right there that's him that's that's how you guys that's how you guys just killed
could you imagine what they wanted to do to John when he showed him that I wonder
he was on the lamb pretty serious stuff not religion so that's what Genesis
chapter 1 also Genesis chapter 1 each letter that's in there actually
represents something and it goes on there 28 letters well book of Revelations
got four seven-year periods what's four times seven 28 right right okay so if
the first is last and last is first and the Creator says in the book of Isaiah I
have declared the end from the beginning now everything in Scripture is a
declaration which book almost wholesale or holy talks about the end book of
Revelation so he tells you okay the last will be first the first it would be
last so the book Revelation is the first book of the Bible but where's your proof
like that I am the word right book of Revelation starts with the letter a
apocalypses word apocalypse by the way that they're using in the context
they're using this means to reveal oh really yeah and if you read in the
prophet he says well the Messiah gave us the law and everything well if you
read the book of Revelation he says this was written by the father given to the
son whoa whoa if all scriptures written by the Messiah this one's written by
the father to give to the son this is outside of the other one something
different about this one and the reason the reason people don't understand the
book of Revelation not even by a long shot is because the next verse says well
it says written by the father to give to the son to give to his servants
remember the analogy I gave before when you're living with someone as a roommate
you're not a servant right so how are you someone's servant they tell you what
to okay stand stand on one leg and put your hand on your head okay that's a
servant the non-servant say no are you kidding man that's outdated stuff man
that law is done away with we talked about that's not for me man no okay no
wonder you don't understand prophecy or the book of Revelation or anything it's
very simple obedient servant it's kind of like very simple instructions let's
go back to Genesis well where's Genesis Genesis second book of the Bible why we
said I'm the word well Genesis it's preserved first word is bed of sheep
that's the letter B second letter in the alphabet because by the way all the
alphabets go a B C D E and then they kind of fall apart you know well the
second word in the in the book of Genesis is but ah another B got two
witnesses this book in second position and then you go then you got to find out
which book is the third one fourth one go all the way to 49 books you got that
kind of time on your hands you'll be real successful with it or someone can
tell you how to figure it out do you see where I'm coming from this is this takes
so it's very technical and there's a lot of information involved and a lot of
again discernment there's no belief here I didn't you know do I did I say I
believe in anything you know I believe this is no there's no belief there's a
certain level of discernment that you need to follow through with you know I
was once speaking with a rabbi and he says you know if I told the people the
truth I'd have to get a real job I couldn't do this anymore people don't
want to hear this people just want to get away and come you know and just sit
around and and you know they want to hear a couple of nice things and tell
them you know whatever they are and go home they don't want to hear this I'm
like you know what you're right I better shut up people don't want to hear this
but there will come a time in the next decade that there will people are going
to want to hear it well people want to hear it now they're here listening I
know I know what I'm saying is it'll be the talk of the town there'll be an
event and they'll be we got to find somebody to explain what's going on
because these priests and these pastors and these are these guys don't know
what's going on they can't explain anything has anyone seen the Simpsons
movie by the way the Simpsons they did a film where you know the Simpsons you
know that that those cartoon characters right and there's a scene where they're
they're in church and this the granddad gets possessed by a spirit he's rolling
around prophesying and no one knows what to do and Homer Simpson picks up the
Bible he's paging through and he's like this book doesn't have any answers you
know he's paging through it really fast you know I thought that was very funny
because that's what's happening everyone's looking in Scripture and
they're like this book doesn't have any answers can't explain anything yeah
that's a jigsaw puzzle you have to put it together and you need discernment
like it was written in code yeah but it's written in code and it was great
it's hidden in plain sight but with with discernment like I spoke to the other
fellow before like a computer you know when it's just receiving a digital
message how does it know it has a syntax error zero and ones I mean it's just
zeros and ones you know syntax error what are you talking about you know so
we have a lot of errors in Scripture you know it's like my favorite one is I do a
test on someone if they want to start learning because you see there's no
such thing as a good teacher only good students right
you can't teach anyone anything but if someone wants to learn they'll just
watch you and pick up you know if they want to learn something so every
academic every professor anyone with a high college degree has failed this and
I'm going to give it this is the way it's a quiz I pop on them I said there's a
shed and it has a gable roof with a ridge on it you know it's like a shed
you know roof with you know the ridge on the top of both sides are equally sloped
okay a rooster a rooster lands on the ridge and lays an egg what side of the
roof does the egg roll off of roosters don't legs you got it you got it you
wouldn't that's great Angela you get a big gold star for that from my book every
academic I've ever spoken to engineers I'm talking about people that are like
designing stuff in the world you don't think about bridges and you know you
know high-level education I had one guy tell me well you really don't know you
know you should get a grant for that and research that project like where you
talk you see roosters if you're addressing which side the egg rolls off
of you missed you'd like to serve and they do yeah I have nothing to do with
your intelligence matter of fact I found out what they call intelligent
people are the easiest to fool you just make you write up something really
technical and you use real fancy terms about simple things and you get them to
claim those terms or claim those names and now they know that well because I
kind of claimed this thing sounds really technical I know a lot yeah yeah they're
really people are bullies right yeah you know here's the thing it's easier to
fool six billion people than to fool one I'll tell you why if you fool one
you've got five billion nine hundred ninety nine million nine hundred ninety
eight thousand nine hundred ninety nine that'll say hey dude you've been fooled
look at us we'll show you what's going on don't believe that all right they'll
still square them away but if you fool the six billion or most of them over a
long period of time if you get one or two that come out and kind of see what's
going on you got all this majority that's going to come out and say we see
those wackos right there let's put him in a room with some padding or something
or drug him up so he shuts up or whatever you know he's crazy so you've
got it you've got it always go after the the whole group and the only power that
can do that is the spiritual world only the spiritual world can do that and all
men in power positions or leadership positions are actually being guided by
the spiritual world and if you read about the spiritual world there was great
violence there a long time ago 2,000 years ago and a third of these beings
are rebelling against us or actually coming against us and rebelling against
the Creator not very good it's funny how you know how much demon position is
there in the Old Testament you notice very little not any but when you go to
New Testament there's a lot what's changed there's all these things are
temporal and you've got to comprehend time and it might seem difficult but it's
happening anyway I mean time is going to pass anyway but our comprehension of it
is lacking that's why in Scripture it doesn't give you specific measurements
of time it tells you when you see these things happening then this will happen
and then this and then you be ready it uses landmarks just like you would use a
landmark when you're traveling on the road so basically the prophecy part that
I would like to just settle in people's minds would be that this country is going
to be and the Western world is going to be playing second fiddle within the next
decade to 14 years to the Middle East number one I wouldn't be concerned about
a particular character like they call the Antichrist because he's 13 years
old and there's nothing you can do about it anyway Jesus was 13 years old
wasn't he when he started preaching in the temples and stuff yeah I was 12 mm-hmm
yeah so this this this particular character people know who he people
don't necessarily know who he is but he's a pretty popular he's going to be very
well-spoken very charismatic extremely bright for his age he's going to mirror
the Messiah in every way well in a lot of ways but not in every way I should
say because the the things that happen you see one thing that people don't
realize just as it's normal for us to see airplanes and automobiles around if
you brought an ancient here it would be really strange for him if you went back
into ancient times there were things going on then that would be very strange
to you there was people were more conscious and observant of the
supernatural events and what we would call supernatural things that just
shouldn't happen for example if you read very carefully in the scripture with the
prophets no one ever really questioned whether or not they were actually being
had gotten dictation from an angel about what to write down you know in
scripture well we've that became scripture later there was no doubt in
anyone's mind as a matter of fact there are many places where they would
approach like Ezekiel or Jeremiah or Isaiah people would say so what did he
say like how did they know because they were signs as a matter of fact there
were people in other nations that knew the spiritual world of the other
dimension was interacting with someone in a very specific place it was very
obvious I mean how I mean it could have been a light through the sky could have
been I mean you know there was a lot of supernatural stuff going on but if you
read it very carefully as if you're there almost like a screenplay you'll
say like oh well these people acknowledge him as a as a prophet that he's got a
message from the Creator and they want to know what it is well if there was any
doubt why would they be asking him right and if you keep reading in
scripture you you know said why do you ask for signs and wonders where you're
not going to get any now oh you mean we used to get those on a regular basis
mean those things you get on a regular basis we're not going to get those
anymore nope if you read that carefully Messiah says what sign will be the sign
of your coming he says there'll be no signs and wonders for you guys just the
sign of Jonah three days and three nights in the belly of the fish meaning death
by the way when Jonah was swallowed by the fish it wasn't a whale it was he
died in there and he was spit out on the third day and if you read it he looked
like a dead man got up walked up had a job to do so what we find to be
commonplace today would not be commonplace to them and vice versa
yeah I've never seen anyone pop out of a whale alive so yeah well it wasn't a
whale it was a fish you know he was swallowed by a dog a dog a DAG a DAG
sounds like a dog but DAG is a fish and a leviathan is is whale actually in
Hebrew you know a lot of for example you know people say well I speak English you
know it's like I don't want to learn Greek or Hebrew I'm not Greek or Hebrew
you know I want English oh really okay do you know there's really not much in
the English language if you take Greek and Hebrew out and if you take Latin out
I don't know what you got left can you tell me you really take all the for
example I say well what's that animal in the desert with that hump on its back Oh
a camel oh no you're speaking Hebrew yeah okay you know very easy I mean you could
look up the origin of the majority of the words in English they're from Greek and
Hebrew and Latin which is Greek and Hebrew like in Latin the the earth is
heirs and in Hebrew it's had it you know I mean there's not much of a difference
all languages come from Edenic's Edenic is the root word is the root of all
words and that's what Adam and Eve spoke and that's what most people spoke up
until 4,000 years ago actually in that particularly the Israelites I should say
not most people because there were divisions where languages change and you
can see it's very specific in Genesis here's an example in Edenic's like the
word Kelev means all heart and that's also the word for dog in Hebrew because
if anyone's ever had a dog you know dogs are all heart you know also from Kelev
you get the word wolf the LV sound or Kali you get the K-O-L-L-I right so the
more people that use a language and they live apart from each other the more
corrupt or the more changes letters like letter R and letter M will put in much
much later so there actually is some study called Edenic's you could look it
up online right now there are some people doing some really really good
work especially with the advent of supercomputers to analyze words and they
find that they all have the same root just like if you find out the truth of
DNA you'll find out we all have the same DNA actually and we all have the same
mother that's why when they find these old primates they tell the people you
evolved from they call her Eve you know we all came from her you know stuff
they're saying is just unbelievable again my purpose even though you said it
was prophecy there's a lot more prophecy to go but it's not going to help anyone
if you lack discernment so that's the main thing the sermon is the main thing
and you could go back and read it there's there's prophecy in there for
example Isaiah he says in the end they will mark their skins and pierce their
body okay well there's always been tattoos and body piercings but not like
now I have yet to run into anyone even I saw a grandma in her 60s get new
tattoos brand-new I was like whoa you know all over the place I mean it's
insane and it's like oh yes I know that's fine of the time some of these
people are getting piercings over their body I mean and they're putting hooks in
them and doing weird things again with the prophecy it doesn't say only women
or some people it says they they they is a majority usually right majority of the
people right I've never seen it's unprecedented unprecedented the amount
of tattooing and body piercing going on today it's unprecedented yeah yeah
within the next within the next 10 years it'll be really hard to find someone
who doesn't have it it's not a fad folks it's not a fad this is it this is how
it's going to be from now on at least for the next 25 years or so so when is
it and times actually going to be we're in it we're in the end is like the
beginning and if you want to know what's going to happen read the book of
Revelation it's very clear it's very difficult to understand unless you're
trying to follow biblical law I mean it's conditional in other words if you
want to understand the words in this book you have to be kind of obedient he gives
it to his people and he says my people will do my will if you're not doing his
will his people if you gain his people he ain't going to show it to you very
simple you just got to try it's I mean there's other people I think you've had
someone else on that tells people to do biblical law it's never been done away
with it has it everyone in the New Testament did biblical law I mean
everyone I mean the Messiah and the the Apostles they followed the law even Paul
followed the law now I tell a caveat if you read anything about the Apostle Paul
anything that he wrote Paul speaks on a PhD level you will be confused and you
will be distracted and he will be misinterpreting what he's saying stay
away from reading Paul until you start reading the first five books of the law
and read the books of what the Messiah said the Messiah said Pharisees will not
enter the kingdom okay you didn't go back and change that when he says it's
written in stone Paul says I'm a Pharisee okay Messiah says follow me and
be like me Paul says follow me okay keep all the different yeah you're gonna have
some problems serious you see that's why when you go to quote-unquote Christian
churches they only talk about Paul because well there's many reasons I can
get into but if you read Paul if you read Paul you're going to be confused if you
if you believe that you are Jewish or Christian or any kind of religion and you
read Paul there's a prophecy that says the father says that because they don't
want to do my laws I'm going to bring them straight a strong delusion I want to
start considering some prophetic verses on on the perception and the
discernment capabilities of the people in the end times he says that in book of
Dennis is the lawless will not understand or comprehend is he talking
about traffic law or codes and statues or what yeah he's talking about biblical
law well I think there's most of us are pretty confused about it as it is well
it's very simple just read what he wants you to do I remember a lot of those
things there is no temple to do a temple sacrifice and those temple sacrifices are
not for you to do there for the priests to do and there is no temple but you see
the Messiah said I've made you kings and priests for gaining knowledge right when
you when you speak to kings and priests do you sit there and talk about religion
no they're kings and priests they're supposed to go out rule the people
they're supposed to make sure that the stewardship is handled properly they
need knowledge they don't need religious gobbledygook you know if you're going to
start speaking and trying to impart knowledge to a king or a priest he
doesn't want to hear about Santa Claus of the Easter Bunny that man or it would
be in a position of power he's got bigger fish to fry in his mind he's got
stewardship issues there's there's there's people that rely on him he needs
knowledge not religion as a matter of fact the book of Zechariah father says
why do you people always want religion I want people so a good place to start
would be read the first five books in the Bible and just stick to it you know
when he says for example don't wear mixed fibers on your body he tells you
don't mix the wool and the linen and this and that okay when I read that I
was like what oh man I've got a 80% cotton poly you know it's 20% poly
shirt it's cotton upon no okay so don't wear mixed fibers all right that shirts
got to go I'm going to try it you know he says if you eat an animal with four
legs and two lives on the ground it should chew the cut and have a cloven
hoof let's see a pig okay he's got a cloven hoof but he doesn't chew the cut
okay no pig rabbit choose the cut but he's got a paw okay no rabbit okay a
dog he doesn't have a paw or to the car he's out won't eat that won't eat rat
won't eat a cat you see so you got discernment now any else okay it comes
out of the water says it should have fish if it comes out of the river the
ocean or the lake it's got to have fins and scales all right let's see I like
catfish but okay it's got fins but no scales okay catfish is out why because
he said so it's good enough for me I'm going to try it I'm going to try to live
the way he wants me to live and I'm gonna see what happens you get my point
yeah how's that work out for you works great it works great it works really
well and also says you do this because you you will be to be set apart and the
thing is don't expect everyone to do it because if everyone is set apart what's
set apart nothing like if I've got a you know if I'm an apple farmer and I just
harvested let's say you know a ton of apples well in those apples I'm going to
set a few apart that you know would be great a or triple-a or whatever maybe a
photographer needs a really good-looking apple or something you know then you got
the grade B ones with the scratches we'll make applesauce out of those and
you got the moderate ones that go to like you know school lunch then you got
the real pretty looking ones they're all bunched over there we'll sell those as
a you know yeah so but if everything is set apart then nothing is set apart
because you need in other words you don't have hot without cold right hey
you don't have black without white so he tells you you know well try to be set
apart and if you you know apart from the rest and if you want to be set apart the
way I'm telling you to do it I'm giving you I'm telling you how and you do it
you know he tells you you know for example if you happen to eat an unclean
animal to unclean but unworthily like a pig or whatever you you're unclean for
seven days you got to wait seven days before you try to do something that
requires you to be in a different state a clean state for example get married
what's that you wouldn't want to get married the next day yeah well it's a
prayer if you want to actually pray you want your prayer to be very effective
where it's carried by an angel to the heavenly realm if you're going to
present yourself to a king you kind of you know make sure you're you know what
the king wants you to be you know in preparation but if you're going to
present yourself to the supreme being of the universe and he tells you well
don't try to do anything set apart if you're not set apart yourself you got to
wait until you know that's the time of period until you're until you're set
apart again so I don't like to use the words clean and unclean because people
think it has to do with getting dirt on you you know it's a ritual thing that's
why a lot of the occult again I say knowledge is power and the people in
power have certain knowledge this procedure and of course anyone who
studies the legal system they understand this procedure right in the spiritual
world there's procedure if you want to start delving into the spiritual world
there's a procedure you can't walk in there like a bullet you can't walk into
a courtroom like a bull in a China shop there's certain procedure so the same
with the spiritual world you want to act like a bull in the China shop they'll put
a yoke on you and they tell you be a beast of burden in the spiritual world
he even says that he calls people he says a lot of people are going to be
basically acting like beasts of burden so you have to be set apart by look these
are this is the procedure these are the rules for example when you read in any
Bible or Scripture he says these are my appointed times the 14th day the 13th
day the first month okay and you've got the first day of the seventh month the
tenth day of the seventh month the 15th day of the seventh month those are the
biblical feasts right and he says these are my appointments that's what they
actually mean now if you don't know when he says the first month he's not talking
about January when he says the seventh month right it's not July and I was kind
of hinting that before September is 1770 we get a little closer now so when
he says these are my appointed times with you and you're not trying to do
them even if you're trying to do them if you don't get them on the right time
aren't you going to miss your appointment now how many times can you
miss your appointment with someone of authority when they don't want to see
you anymore how important is it how we talk from children you if you make an
appointment you have to be there okay so everybody we have the majority of the
people on this planet missing their appointments with basically the
emissaries of the Supreme Being and the Supreme Being himself he's telling you
what I want you to do on these days and these are appointments I don't see
too many people trying to do them where does it say that oh I don't see too many
people trying to do my son saying that no I mean what where does it say on the
14th day what what are the appointments we are supposed to be doing Oh where do
you tell you Leviticus Leviticus 23 the book of Leviticus chapter 23 the whole
chapter that is all about the appointments I thought it Leviticus
talked about what we shouldn't and should eat it's more than that it's also
what days you yeah well that's to prepare yourself what's more than just
eating it's there's six over 600 ordinances and laws in there about a
third of them a third of them are for the priests and the priests families and
because there are no priests and temple right now you can be conscious of those
and put those aside and also the age of those things happening is over that age
ended around 50 or 60 AD we're in a different age now so you keep them with
your intent as best as possible on the ordinances with the priest like for
example in the book of Kings when Solomon was dedicating the building the
temple when it was built took seven years to build David didn't build it a
son built it in Jerusalem when he dedicated the temple and they and you
know basically this what's called the second of the presence showed up
everyone stepped out and Solomon said this will be your dwelling place forever
well that's how it's translated in English but in the actual language
preservation the word Olam is translated to forever it doesn't mean forever all
on this for a set period of time meaning the onto the age or ages for
example in the Greek text when you see forever it doesn't say forever it's the
actual Greek word is a onion which is where we get the word eon from which is
a thousand or multiples of a thousand years so when Solomon said this is your
dwelling place for ever or Olam or unto the age if you knew about astronomy you
know food let's say you and I were there I'd give you a real sharp elbow on the
side and say Angela you'd say what I said you know what you just said I said
what you'd say what I said he just said that this temple won't be here around 50
to 100 AD he says why do you say that well that age is ending between 50 and 100
AD really Wow and now the Messiah comes here didn't he say verily I tell you
not one stone will be left upon another of this temple right here you remember
that you're saying that around 33 AD was anybody really shocked about that I
mean people that knew scripture I didn't see anybody kind of freak out over it
you know in the text they didn't accuse him of wanting to tear down the temple
they actually made at one of the informal trial places or accusations
they said and he said he would rebuild it in three days because that's what he
said after this isn't I will rebuild it in three days which means two thousand
years right and that's what they said well but he said he would rebuild the
temple in three days but no one complained about him saying it won't be
there because they're kind of new the age is going to end between 50 and 100
AD I'm using modern you know communication terms here that we can
communicate but the temple was actually destroyed around 66 or 70 AD which is
kind of like you know in the beginning of that era I just mentioned or kind of
like in the middle it's great accuracy here you know you know when Moses yeah
you see so right now this age ended in 1998 and it's the age of the water bear
when they asked the Messiah I said when we where do we do the Passach or the
Passover he says when you enter the city walls you will see a man bearing
bearing water and you will follow him to the upper rooms whoa right away a big
red light you come on and say wait a second I've been reading scripture all
the way from Genesis down to here water bearing is a woman's job now it's a man's
job here something wrong with this picture because all through scripture
it was the women that went to the well and drew the water for the camels and
the sheep what does it mean then well it means that this the bear this the
pouring out of the spirit is spoken of meaning that the truth will be poured
out by a man which is odd because it's poured out by a woman traditionally and
when you read about scripture this particular female entity known as
mystery Babylon she's pouring out her spirit getting all of the nation's
drunk with it and all the people kind of falling into this Babylonian system
I'm going to end it's going to end yeah the pouring out of the spirit and I was
going to be coming there's a different spirits going to be poured out you see
that's why she's holding a cup now I've said this once before people said you
just offended every woman on the call I'm like no I didn't this particular
being just happens to be a female gender like if someone you know burglarizes
your house and they catch him and you pull the mask off and it's a woman and
you tell someone a woman burglarized my house you know is that like you just
insulted women no it just so happened that this particular burglar happened to
be a woman right right we have to use discernment again I'm the reason I keep
bringing that up it's not really a sore spot but whenever I bring that up that
this woman is pouring out the spirit almost every time except for speaking
with you I guess you're in this call people said you just insulted women you
know it's like wow people relax and listen to what's being said or written
or you know I didn't think that at all I don't think anybody did yeah good but I
just want to tell you where I'm coming from and I'm starting to maybe qualify
things based on past experiences but that's okay too I think changing yeah
we're gonna do this again okay we've been on for a while like you have a
sounds like you have a lot more information sure well yeah and again I'd
love to just give the information out but again without the discernment aspect of
it you know big deal you know well we've had our lesson in discernment now
we need to go study that a bit and then come back on yeah we'll communicate about
that and again in the reason that I feel good about speaking on this call is
because there's a lot of legal discussion here typically yeah I find it
fascinating what you have to say well thank you and a lot of the legal
discussion is based on power of discernment right the words right usage
of words and I'm just trying to show people that the powers that be on the
earth right now are there for a reason they're accommodating the people because
the people are doing things that are making enemies in the spiritual world so
we need to reflect back to ourselves and see what we're doing kind of do you
know clean up our own act in our own homes in our own minds in our own selves
and we'll start to see things change around us in a positive light it's done
on an individual basis for one each one at a time so well thanks for having me
hello yeah no I'm here I'm sorry I had my mute button on we've been doing that
for about three hours and 38 minutes and I think we could probably go on for
another three hours but let's save it for another yeah we'll have to learn from
what we've been taught already and and and start to pay attention to what we're
reading and look into the like you said the etymology of the words right and the
thing is it's not what people are making a big do about what's called
government what's called law on the courts and all that but I just want to
say it's not just that it's every subject I have not seen a subject or
topic or a body of knowledge that anyone can subscribe to on this planet right
now that is not just turned inside out upside down and I'm saying this in a
very truthful way not to be sarcastic I've not seen anything that hasn't been
affected in a way where I can't say it's uncorrupted every field everything is a
lie and in the other some yeah well I wouldn't say completely but enough of it
in there that I wouldn't take it on face value nothing that's why I say I'm
just visiting this planet you know right now taking notes if you once you
really find the truth of all things here you don't really want to be a part of it
you know I mean you're in it but you're not of it you're just passing through
until you know that it's all corrected and man's not going to correct it it's
going to take this other dimension mingling with this one with real
authority real truth real knowledge real you see real science and then it'll and
then it'll all come together with that said blessings to everyone and thank you
for having me Angela oh thank you for coming on we appreciate it immensely and
we'll have to do it again thank you everyone for participating and
listening I love you all it's been fun and don't forget we have a show on
Saturday we're going to have David Clarence on and Mr. Greek person make
sure you come on too that should be interesting we'll learn from David
Clarence on his executor or executrix letter all right everybody good night
it's been fun I love you again I'll tell you I never get tired of saying I love
you and we'll see you on Saturday okay