They make X's and A's and all kinds of things.
Southeast Arizona, did you want to chime in?
Yeah, hey Angela, it's the Greek. How are you, sweetie?
Hi, I'm fine, thank you. How are you?
I'm doing fine, thank you. I chimed in...
What's new with you?
Oh, everything, everything.
I'd like to discuss one aspect,
to discuss what this fellow brought up with the Cloudbusters.
I let the cat out of the bag.
Recently, we ended the drought in Texas
and have been supplying cotton farmers around Arizona
helping them fill up their irrigation ditches
using the ethereal rain engineering technology.
No, I don't know about it. Tell us about it.
Well, the reason I chimed in is
I appreciate the fellow talking about the Organite
and these other things.
It has positive and negatives.
It doesn't really work for ethereal rain engineering.
It does mitigate some of the local magnetic fields and the EMF
and works a little bit on the chemtrails, like you said.
But the concept of it is, even biblically,
we were given everything on the earth to manage it
and completely use it.
But the thing is, the science that's taught
is so backwards.
Even on the highest level for the past 1,000 or 2,000 years,
everything is just completely backwards.
They teach that clouds and weather patterns
are formed by humidity and evaporation, and they're not.
When you look at a cloud, that is actually the cosmic ether.
It's basically neither matter nor energy.
It's a very primordial form of, let's call it energy,
that the earth is swimming in because space is not a vacuum.
And where the earth makes contact with the fluid of the ether in space,
it causes a swirling, just like if you were to pass a ball through water.
The water swirls around it.
And the moisture is attracted to the ether.
So when you look at cloud patterns and jet streams and things like that,
that is the ether flow, and it happens to attract moisture-forming clouds.
It also attracts other things, radioactivity, small particles,
different forms of energy.
So if you're trying to do weather engineering like they do
with cloud seeding with silver and iodine and things like that,
you're looking at the effect.
The clouds are not the cause of the weather.
They are simply the effect.
So everything is about dealing with the symptom, not the cause.
But once you understand the ether,
it's very, very easy to manipulate.
And it's so simple.
If you look at the work of Dr. Reich, he was heavily persecuted.
He used cloud busters that were water-powered.
And I'll just spill the beans.
A lot of people say you should keep this a secret.
But all that technology, the work that he did,
was a wonderful stepping stone.
Personally, I don't agree with the organite stuff,
which is the polyester resin with the metal shavings.
And you can go online.
It's like a big hit.
The problem is when you accumulate this orgo and energy,
too much of it is not conducive to health.
It has to be grounded.
And all of these organite devices and these polyester resin
with metal shavings in them, there's no grounding to them.
Sometimes there is some reference to grounding them.
But that's not what the ether is really about.
If you read the work of Wilhelm Reich,
he talks about it's interesting how all societies through history
have suppressed the reason for the orgasm.
The orgasm is not just the excretion of bodily fluids.
It's the discharge of the sepharic buildup of energy.
And once you understand the orgasm,
you understand the weather, you understand the ether.
And that's kind of like a roundabout.
Really?
Yeah, yeah.
When you say orgasm, it's like everyone's like eight years old.
Oh, orgasm.
It's a very specific biological function.
And all living creatures, even plants, have them.
And it's the release of the energy.
And once you understand the accumulation and the release of the orgone,
there you go.
But just to fast forward, just to affect the ether,
you don't have to make water-grounded codbusters,
which are all these pipes that are water-grounded,
or the organite with the polyester resins.
And I'm knocking the organite because I went through that phase.
Okay?
It's very popular right now.
The easiest way to capture the ether is understanding the way it flows.
Everything that's taught,
they teach you that everything goes from a high potential to a low potential.
Right?
So if you have a bucket of water, it's a high potential of water.
If you put a hole in that bucket,
and next to another bucket that's got low potential, no water,
the high will go to the low.
Same with electricity.
If you have a dead battery next to a fully charged battery,
the fully charged battery will always go to the discharged battery
and charge it.
Everything that they teach and everything that we are taught to observe
is high to low, high to low.
You know, your gas tank's full, it goes to low.
Right?
And then you've got to fill it up again.
Well, the ether is the opposite.
It goes from low to high potential.
So in other words, if you mastered the ether,
you would put a low battery next to a fully charged battery,
and whatever is in the low battery will give up to charge the higher battery even more.
And these lessons of the ether are given in the Bible as well,
but no one reads it, so they wouldn't see it.
Like in the Bible, it says, for example,
those who have little, that little will be taken away till they have nothing,
and those who have much, much will be given till they are full.
That's a lesson on the ether.
So basically, what you do is you take a cardboard tube,
like you can experiment with the little cardboard tubes you get out of a paper roll
when it's spent, right?
A longer one would be better, okay?
Like a paper towel?
Yeah, like a paper towel roll, right?
And get yourself some, go to a window tint shop,
and you know that silver film they use for window tint?
You know, when it's bright, it looks like a mirror,
and you know, it's like a two-way mirror deal?
Yeah.
Okay, and just put that on the back,
and then put a little red light on the back of it.
So if you look down the tube, you'll see right through it
because it's dark in the tube, and there's light on the other side, right?
But when you go through the tube,
the ether goes through the mirror because it looks clear,
and then it wants to reverse, and it sees a mirror,
and temporarily gets bounced off.
It still goes through it because you can't shield it.
So now you create a low concentration of ether in that tube,
and all this happens in millionths of a second.
It's like a pulsing.
So the ether goes through the tube,
and it doesn't reverse back because it's a mirror on the back side.
So that's why you want a longer tube to keep it really dark in there, right?
So what you do with this is you have the red light back on the back of it
because any form of light stimulates the ether.
That's why, for example, fog is lifted
when the sun comes up in California, typically.
People say it's the heat of the sun.
It's not. It's stimulation of the ether.
So what's interesting, to make a long story short here,
is you make a little device.
I have some that are quite elaborate,
and in other words, you spend several days
building ones that are more durable and more technical.
There's a lot of tough guys, like ex-Marines, gangster types,
real tough guys, right?
And you go out in the parking lot, and you say,
hey, you see it's a totally blue sky,
and you're going to make a cloud, and they all laugh.
And boom, you take the thing out,
and within five to 15 minutes, these clouds start to form.
And these tough guys are like little girls.
They want to crawl under their cars.
They're so scared.
Really?
Yeah, it's very interesting.
You got to have the right conditions.
You have to have at least 15 grams of moisture
per cubic meter of air.
What that means in English is you have to have
about 40% to 50% humidity to do that.
Well, that's not abnormal here in California.
Yeah, exactly.
But out in the desert, it's down to five or eight.
You have to sort of attract warmer moisture air,
and also warm air holds more moisture.
So is this what you did in Texas?
Well, let's say there's no more drought in Texas, right?
It was officially eliminated the end of February.
So these things can be, you know,
people talk about the chemtrails.
There's a lot of concern about the chemtrails.
Well, obviously, there should be, OK?
Yeah, everybody here has got a persistent cough
they can't shake.
And I've heard other people talk about it, too.
And it's not that detrimental.
I mean, it doesn't, you know, stop you from working
or doing anything, but it's like a cough
that's persistent in almost everybody.
Well, what they're doing is actually a mix
of very low-level technology, which is basically
a plane shooting some stuff out the ass end, right?
But it's also coupled with some really,
really high technology that people are,
shouldn't be discussed, by the way,
because it's basically a PSYOP.
Spider web technology?
Yeah, kind of.
The technology, well, involved with that, again,
they're not familiar with the ether.
They're doing it also to spend money, right?
You know, like the $1,000 toilet seats
and the $800 hammer, right?
Well, I think ultimately they're doing it
to, you know, cull the population.
Well, it's a PSYOP, like, for example,
if you go look at children's coloring books, right?
They have, like, the Columbus story
with the Nina, Tina, and Santa Marina, right?
You got to color it in.
And they got chemtrails with Xs in the background
of these ships from the 1400s, right?
Have you seen those coloring books?
No, I haven't seen that.
Chemtrails in children's books.
They're putting them in children's books now, right?
So when the time is right, it'll serve a purpose.
But you've got to do the food.
You got to eat their food, drink their water,
and breathe their air.
It's a tripartite thing,
so you can never blame it on just the chemtrails.
So if you shop at an ordinary...
Yeah, yeah, it's a three-part.
It's always a three-part mixture.
So you got to learn about cleaning up your water, right?
The best way to clean up your water,
if you have charcoal filters, even a Brita pitcher,
go get some zeolite, go to an aquarium shop, okay?
You know, down the aisle where they sell supplies
for maintaining your aquarium and stuff.
And you'll see zeolite,
or they'll call it like an anti-ammonia granular thing, right?
And you get a handful of zeolite.
You buy it.
It's like five bucks for like half a pound.
It's really cheap.
Or low-grade...
I mean, there's kitty litter that's made of zeolite,
but it's really low-grade.
It's too much clay.
Well, this particular zeolite is aquarium-grade
or fish-grade or pet-grade.
It's a type of clay that absorbs radioactivity.
It absorbs fluoride out of the water,
barium, lead, mercury, naturally, okay?
So even if you have like a baloney Brita pitcher,
it's made of acrylic or whatever.
You flush it out with baking soda really well.
You know where that filter drops in?
Just put a couple of handfuls of zeolite in there,
and that'll take out most of the stuff
that causes damage to the brain and the nervous system
and what they're hoping...
If you look at all the water tests,
they never show you uranium, strontium, radium in the water.
They never even test.
They lie.
They put zero.
They never talk about arsenic.
So learn about water purification.
All you need is a handful of zeolite in your water filter, right?
Well, truth here is...
Truth one is saying that it does not remove fluoride.
Brita does not remove fluoride, but...
Do the research on it.
Go do the research on it.
Yeah, well, I have an aqua rain machine myself.
The Brita itself may not remove it.
However, the clay that the gentleman talked is removing it.
Yeah, the zeolite will remove it.
The zeolite is a very specific type of structure.
It's actually an alumina silicate.
Not aluminum, but alumina silicate.
Each little particle has millions of little honeycomb cells in there,
and it also acts as an ion exchange for heavy metals, radioactivity,
which radioactivity is basically heavy metals,
and your fluorides.
It doesn't do all the halides, fluorine, chlorine, and all that,
but it does the fluoride pretty well.
It'll cut it more than 80%, 90%.
The reason why I say Brita is because whenever you see a water filter,
it's like people freak out.
I need a plumber.
You look at these complex.
What if I'm renting an apartment?
What if I live in an RV or whatever?
So you just go to your local store and get a pitcher filter.
You see them at Goodwill for $5, you know,
and just clean it out really well because it's an acrylic plastic.
It gives off nasty stuff.
Oh, it gives off what?
You got cut off.
It's acrylic, so it's got like cryosilane,
you know, the stuff that's in Krazy Glue, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
So what you want to do, these plastics are pretty nasty.
PVC is the worst.
PVC will always give off phthalates, which are estrogen mimicers,
but your acrylic, what you can do for,
this is, again, not the best way to go,
but it is a good way, you know, for under $30 or $40,
you can have a kick-ass water filter.
I mean, that really gets the really bad stuff out of the water.
So you basically get the Brita thing and get a box of baking soda,
put half the box of baking soda in it and just clean it out
without the filter, hot water overnight,
and do that for a couple of days.
Now, if you want even better filtration with the Brita,
water, see, those regular filters, carbon filters or what have you,
are not as efficient above 40, 45 degrees.
So if you get your water down, in other words,
if you want to put water in a Brita pitcher,
just put water in a regular pitcher overnight in the fridge.
So when you run it through the Brita, the water is near 39 or 40,
and that makes the filter like 99% efficient for getting out the stuff.
You know, if you filter, see, water at 39 degrees is the anomaly point.
That's where it's densest.
If you lower the temperature from 39, it expands, you know, again,
and, you know, that's why ice expands, right?
So water is its densest, and it's also its healthiest state at 39.
Like your blood, your body is 98.6.
If I raise your temperature or lower it, you don't feel good.
So water feels best at 39.
That's what's called its anomaly point.
So if you want to work with water at 39 degrees,
and coincidentally, most of the fridges are set at 39 degrees.
There's a reason for that, you know,
because everything is basically made of water.
So if you really want a real kick-ass water filter,
and I've done tests on this,
and you still have the minerals in the water.
The thing is, talking about systems, you know,
you just want simple as the best.
And the reason why the simple is the best
and the cheapest is the best sometimes
is because there's no commitment.
If you want to get something else,
it's not like you've invested a lot into it, right?
Yeah, right.
And it's very simple.
Yeah, just spread a filter,
clean it out with baking soda, hot water for a few days.
We keep repeating it to draw those things out
that are in the plastic.
Put it all together.
Whenever you pour water through the Brita,
make sure it's chilled water, pre-chilled, okay?
At 39, you could look up 39 degrees as the densest,
I call it the anomaly point
because any liquid, as you cool it, it contracts, all right?
As you lower the temperature, it contracts,
but water will contract to 39.
If you keep lowering the temperature, it starts expanding.
It's the only element that does that.
So there you go.
I mean, just get a handful of zeolite, you know?
I mean, you go to the aquarium shop and,
hey man, I need some zeolite.
Okay, here it is, you know,
a little package,
and just to make sure you have enough in the Brita.
Actually, you want to rinse the zeolite
because it is a type of clay also.
So you want to rinse it in a bowl so it runs quickly.
Yeah, it would be cloudy, wouldn't it?
It would be really cloudy.
You got to rinse it for a couple of gallons of water, you know?
Or just put it in like a stocking, you know,
like a cheesecloth in a bowl.
But is it a coarse texture?
Is it just a fine powder or what?
It's coarse.
It's like, I'd say, half inch minus, right?
Or typically, the reason I'm suggesting the aquarium one
is because it is coarse.
You're not worried about it clogging the filter.
Pool companies sell it.
It's coarser than sand but finer than kitty litter, right?
It would be like a 10 mesh minus.
But the stuff you get for the aquariums
will do the job for your little Brita thing
because the water,
when you do your pitcher filter deal, right,
you know, the water doesn't rush through right away.
It kind of hangs out.
You have a lot of dwell time, right?
You ever notice if you ever use one of those pitchers?
Yeah, you know what?
I'm getting a question from the group wants to know,
is there a website where we can get the info
for these tubes with the silver film?
No, you got it right here.
If you want to do some just general research on zeolites,
the benefits of zeolites,
look at some scientific papers, you know,
because most of this stuff, you know,
is dedicated to the third grade level reading
that you have in this country
for the people doing pool maintenance
and aquarium, you know, stuff.
But if you, there's a couple of websites
that are scientific papers that talk about
they're using zeolites for mitigation
of radioactive water, arsenic, heavy metals.
Weren't you making water?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Drinking water, I mean.
We synthesize spring water
using Victor Schauberger technology.
As far as I know, we're the only people on the planet.
Actually, there's one other outfit in Germany
that has replicated Victor Schauberger's implosion equipment.
We synthesize spring water.
And it's not something that you would drink all the time.
It's kind of like you would drink it like a good bottle of wine
because it actually costs as much as a good bottle of wine.
And you get high when you drink it.
I mean, it's great.
You know, have you ever had water from a mountain spring
at the source?
No, I don't think I ever have.
Yeah, it's really, to give you an idea
how important it is to Europeans,
I spoke to a fellow that's moved to Arizona from Germany
and he had the water.
So he reminded him of the Edelwasser
that he had 30 years ago in Germany.
When people go on vacation to the country,
they go to the spa, you know.
And these men would go up to the top of the mountain
and come down with black bottles
because you don't want to expose it to any light.
And they were paying 50 Deutschmarks per bottle,
which is about 250 bucks in today's money.
His family did, and his family was working class
because they knew the importance of real spring water.
And it was very difficult to go up there
because you had to be like a billy goat, you know.
You have to get the water before it touches the ground
when it comes out of the rock, let's say.
And a lot of people say it has healing properties
and things like that.
I just, I enjoy it because you get high from it.
I mean, you know, you get this lightheadedness
but exceptional clarity, a lot of energy.
You have to go to the bathroom often
if you're not used to it, you know, number one.
Wasn't Patrick Flanagan doing a lot of work with that?
Vortexing water?
Yes, he was doing a lot of work using
like directed energy pyramid stuff.
But not what, if you look up Victor Schauberger,
V-I-C-T-O-R-S-C-H-A-U-B-E-R-G-E-R.
That's a mouthful.
Victor Schauberger.
Yeah, yeah.
His work, he has what's called the repulsator.
Okay, the water goes into an egg-shaped vessel
and it's lined with gold and we use gold, silver
and it has a granite egg-shaped impeller.
And once the vessel is about three quarters full,
we pull a vacuum on it, about two inches of vacuum
and we inject some CO2.
And we still maintain about one inch of vacuum
so the CO2 never goes into the water.
And then the water is vortexed.
It goes up to a very high speed, very gradually
then it's reversed and it's all done at 39 degrees.
And what's interesting when it goes through
an implosion process, you'll see the vacuum
increase on its own and the temperature
increase and then decrease, increase and then decrease
as the water pulsates.
And then after about a half hour of that implosion process
it's decanted in a dark amber bottle
which is put in a foil bag.
So it gets absolutely no light and it's labeled
and it has to be kept at 39.
Can you spell Schauberger again, Stelios?
Sure, S-C-H-A-U-B-E-R-G-E-R.
Even if you don't spell it right, it's pretty popular.
There's been a big revival in his work
and a lot of people talking about vortexing
but no one's really doing it, unfortunately.
I found most of the people that get information
off the internet are more like armchair.
You know, they know a lot about it
but there's actually, they don't really do much with it.
There's so many websites, I'll tell you
they're doing all this stuff.
It doesn't really matter.
Water has to be in the dark, it has to be at 39
and it has to have a vacuum with the presence of CO2.
It has to be an egg-shaped vessel.
No one's really doing that, unfortunately.
There was a book about two years ago
called Secrets of the Soil.
It deals with topics and that is among them.
And Victor Schauberger's Peter Tompkins and Christopher Berg.
And it gives a lot of what seemed to be
magical techniques for use in agriculture.
Correct, yeah.
Never put iron, never use iron tools.
We also make copper tools for gardens.
When you put iron in the ground, it discharges
the electric current in the ground,
the biological current.
It also leaves iron trace elements like the rust.
And the soil relies on capillaries
and these capillaries dry out with the iron.
But if you use copper, it doesn't ground out
the earth's choleric current as iron does.
And the micro bits of metal that are left in there
transmute to magnesium and other elements.
Another guy to read is Louis Kervran.
K-E-R-V-R-A-N.
He showed that you never need to take potassium, right?
You know how they say eat bananas because it has potassium?
If you take potassium supplements or take potassium,
it just comes out in your urine.
Your body produces potassium from sodium.
Transmutation in the body.
All biological creatures have the ability
to transmute elements.
The elements are not empirical or ephemeral.
They're just states of matter.
So when you look at all the elements that exist
that they're showing,
they're only showing I think 90 elements,
but they're really 140.
Those are different states of matter.
There's no such thing as like the element gold,
or silver, or copper, or carbon, or whatever.
Those are just different states of the same thing
and it ties back into the ether
like we started the conversation with.
You can transmute materials.
The body does it.
Louis Kervran's excellent example was
he took chickens and fed them a diet devoid of calcium.
And they still produced very robust eggs.
So where was the, you know,
the eggshell is 90% calcium, if not better.
Where is the calcium coming from?
And they had no bone loss, right?
And he also did a wonderful experiment
and I met one of the folks that were part of the experiment
back in the late 50s, early 60s in the Moroccan desert
with the French military.
He made sure that no one had potassium in their diet
and fed them sodium pills.
You know, they took the sodium
while they were working in the desert
and their potassium levels increased.
And the sodium level was normal.
How did that happen?
Well, because the body produces it.
Your body produces potassium.
Right now my son is producing too much.
Lower the sodium.
The sodium would probably be key.
Do a distilled water for about a week or two.
You know, a distilled water is not good for you
but it could have therapeutic effects for a short time.
It could be for medication.
Well, the reason we're saying,
that's kind of complex.
Who's saying it?
You know, it's interesting.
You go to the doctor and they check for blood pressure.
They put a cuff on your arm and they inflate the cuff
and it cuts off the circulation to a certain degree
and then the blood builds up this artificial pressure
which doesn't exist and then blasts forward
and then they measure that, right?
That's how the blood pressure works, right?
It's completely artificial
because the blood is not pumped through the body.
The heart does not pump the blood.
It's the most ridiculous thing and no one's noticed it.
I mean, there's a guy named Frank Chester.
Unfortunately, he's an artist and not a doctor.
Otherwise, they would have killed him a long time ago.
He proved 15 ways from here to what they call Sunday
that the heart doesn't pump the blood.
It's physically impossible.
The bottom of the heart is 330 seconds of an inch thick
which is like the thickness of a plastic card
and you need 60 pounds of pressure to move the blood 4 feet, 60 psi.
So if you've got 2,000 miles of blood vessels in your body,
you need a 1,200 horsepower pump to move it
not even one-tenth of that distance.
It's impossible.
Well, then how does it do it?
How does the blood move through the body?
That's a big secret, Angela.
Do you want me to reveal it on a minor talk-shoot call?
Excuse me, this is no minor call.
Yes, tell us.
All right.
I'll just cut to the chase.
The blood moves through the body through the capillaries.
You've got over 2,400 miles of capillaries in your body.
The capillaries are what moves them through what's called peristalsis.
Peristalsis is that inchworm effect when you swallow, right?
Like astronauts before they send them out into low gravities,
you know, up in the space station or whatever,
they hang them upside down and they feed them
so they can practice swallowing upside down using peristalsis, right?
It's like an inchworm effect.
Okay?
So in order to put the peristalsis in your throat,
it's simulated by nerves and muscles.
There are no nerves and muscles in the capillaries, right?
I mean, when was the last time you cut a capillary and screamed, right?
So they just, what, contract and expand and contract and expand?
Yes.
They contract and expand due to the exchange of gases,
typically oxygen and carbon dioxide,
because it's a permeable membrane, the capillary.
Okay?
And it's a very easy experiment.
You could take a laden jar, a jar that has two ends on it,
and stretch a porous silicone tube.
Okay, but wait a minute, wait a minute.
When the heart stops pumping or when the heart stops beating,
Yeah, that's the effect.
That's not the cause.
When your heart stops, well, if you have a heart problem,
that is not the cause.
So wait a minute.
So you're saying your heart is beating
because your capillaries are constricting and expanding.
Yeah, well, that's what's moving the blood.
The purpose of the heart is to slow the blood down
so it enters the lungs.
Oh, so it's like a regulator.
It's a regulator.
The bottom of the heart twists, okay, when it beats.
Okay, first of all, they're telling you
it lays on a 45-degree angle in your chest,
and you take an x-ray, right?
But it doesn't.
It's actually, that's two-dimensional thinking again.
The heart lays in a spatial dimension.
You can measure it like a cube.
In other words, the same width, same height, and same depth
lays on an angle in your chest, okay?
It actually doesn't lay at a 45-degree angle.
It lays at a 36-degree angle
because the diagonal through a cube is not 45, it's 36 degrees.
Okay, and it's that specific angle.
As the blood goes into the heart,
the bottom of the heart, the whole heart seems to contract,
but it seems to contract because it's twisting.
Just like, you know, when you twist a towel,
it seems to get shorter, okay?
And when the blood goes into the heart,
only 70% comes out, 30% still remains.
So you're always mixing new and old in there, right?
And you see, when the doctors take out a heart,
they take the left, I believe it's the left ventricle,
they cut it off and throw it on the floor
because it's like paper-thin,
and they only look at the right side,
which is a one-inch-thick muscle.
This is your medical schools now.
This is what people pay $50,000 or whatever a year
to get this ridiculous training.
I think it's okay to knock doctors once in a while.
Oh, you have my permission to go right ahead.
It's just bizarre what they teach.
I mean, you know, so this is, you know,
okay, what's the problem, then, with the heart?
Well, if you go back and look at when fluorine,
bromine, and chlorine were introduced,
or fluoride, into food, into the environment,
and you did a graph...
When was that, by the way? Do you know?
Was it right after the war?
That was after the 50s, where they started it.
It really came in full force in the 70s.
And if you look at how much...
Like, brominated products are flour, right?
It's like, you know, if you go to, let's say,
a health food store and get some flour that's not brominated,
you're like, wow, what does that mean, you know?
Because all the flour products are brominated.
It's like a bleach.
The flour looks pure white, right?
Yeah, what does it mean?
Okay, well, this is what bromine is.
Bromine, chlorine, chloride,
let's say fluoride, fluorine, and iodine, okay,
like iodized salt.
Those elements are in what's called
the halogen or halide groups, okay, on the periodic table.
So iodine, fluoride, chlorine, and fluoride.
Basically, you can look at the halogen or halide groups
on the periodic table.
All those elements, they create a calcification
of soft tissue in the body.
And there's a lot of study on that.
So when they introduced, you know, the brominated flour,
the iodized salt, the fluoride in the water,
it starts building up plaque on the arteries.
I remember you telling me that we shouldn't take calcium
because calcium helps solidify cement.
No, well, calcium, you can't really use calcium.
I mean, you can, but the best place to get calcium,
believe it or not, is vegetable.
It's the most biologically compatible.
And if you need a shot of calcium,
obviously dairy products, okay, or a calcium supplement.
But the issue is the halide group elements
that I just mentioned, okay, the brominated flour,
the iodized salt, the chlorine in the water,
even from taking a shower, and the fluoride in toothpaste
and the fluorides in the water,
those elements basically create calcification.
I shouldn't say calcification,
but it creates a hardening of the soft tissue.
It also damages the pineal gland in the brain.
It damages and it shrinks the brain.
Any soft vital organ tissue,
and that's what causes most of what's called heart disease
from the research that I've done.
And I'll debate any heart specialist or any doctor
or any scientist on this in any capacity.
And there are many papers written on this,
and I've presented a few of them showing how this is the effect.
You know what they say?
Well, that's only for mammals.
That's not for humans.
That's what their answer is.
But humans are mammals.
You see what I mean?
It's like they play the word game.
It's like I can't look at that because if I look at that,
I'll have to put on an orange reflective vest
and a plastic broom, right, for a living.
People are asking how they can get in touch with you
if they wanted to.
Do you want to give out an e-mail or anything?
I haven't set myself up for being public.
I mean, yeah, I chime in to a talk show
or whatever once in a while or a radio show or something.
Yeah, I'm glad you came on.
I haven't heard from you in a while.
I met you when you were in California.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, I frequent there.
Yeah, one of these days I'll get to meet you in person.
But, yeah, that's basically this group,
and thanks a lot.
I chimed in because, you know,
my favorite part of it is talk about the ether and the weather.
And the chemtrails.
Well, no, I love it when you come on.
Well, thanks.
Yeah, the chemtrails, you know, you've got to just find out why.
It's a sci-op.
You know, someone from the inside is going to come out
and really give the information.
I believe there's plenty of information already out there,
but I gave you my take on it.
It's a three-part thing.
If you breathe their air, drink their water,
and eat their food, you're up Schitt's Creek.
Okay, so what about them, though?
The powers that be that are doing this?
Are they immune?
Are they lizards or what?
David Icke says they're reptilians.
Yeah, they exist, but they're not lizards.
No, they're not lizards.
But, yeah, are there lizards that stand upright
and can talk and kick your ass or whatever?
Sure, of course, but not here that you could see, right?
When was the last time you went down Ventura Boulevard
and saw one, you know?
Well, you never know.
Yeah, you never know.
I don't buy the David Icke stuff.
It's more the bloodlines than probably looking lizard-like, right?
Yeah, the bloodlines are the bloodlines.
If I talk about the bloodlines, okay, what about your bloodline?
You know, figure it out.
That's more important than someone else's, right?
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's all about bloodlines.
It always has been and it always will be.
Well, yeah, I mean the banking cartel family
is pretty much considerate and important.
The queen thinks it's important.
It's called pedigree, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, you know, but that's not, you know,
what does that have to do with chemtrails?
I don't know.
Well, what I'm asking is, well, I usually say this to people,
is we don't drink what they drink, we don't eat the food they eat,
and we don't breathe the air that they breathe, and we don't
because they have their own farms and their own ranches
and their own wells and their own airspace.
Well, look, if you could put two and two together, Angela,
let me just do a quick recap.
If the weather can be controlled with a stupid little cardboard tube
with some reflective thing and a red LED,
and your body transmutes sodium into potassium,
and the heart doesn't pump the blood,
could we actually have the power to transmute all those toxins
before we put them in our body simply with our thoughts?
I hope so.
I hope you're going to say yes.
Absolutely.
Are you confident?
Do you have the faith of a mustard seed, right?
Right.
Which means it'll take much once you learn it.
And what about eat anything, eat any poisonous thing
and it will not harm you?
Well, here's the thing.
The thing is, if you walk around every moment thinking about that,
it's going to make you crazy.
What you do is you learn how to transmute, okay,
just like riding a bike.
You know, it's tough in the beginning, but then once you learn,
you never forget, you just jump on a bike and go, right?
Right.
So you just do it all the time.
And just the thing is, you know, the way we'll finish off with this,
do you have interest in anything here in the way it is,
or do you have an objective reality that you're just visiting this place?
Personally, I think we are the artificial intelligence we strive to create,
and I believe this is one big giant computer simulation that we live in.
So don't ask me.
It's all artificial, and in order to be artificial,
the word means you need an artificer, which is an artist.
Someone made it.
Divine intervention.
Also known as divine intervention.
Yeah, but you see, divine, we've got it wrong, too,
because, see, man's kingdom is up and down, vertical.
You've got the king sitting up high and the street sweeper at the bottom, right?
But the divine kingdom is a lateral kingdom.
You're either on the left of the throne, on the right of the throne.
You ever notice how Eve came out of Adam's side, right?
Everything is lateral.
You're in or you're out.
Man's system is vertical.
You know, when someone says, you know, you ask a 5-year-old child,
where's God, and they point up to the sky, you know?
They don't point next to you.
You see, so everything is backwards.
I mean, absolutely, and here's the most ridiculous thing.
But they also say as above, so below, right?
Yes, as above, so below, right.
Now, is that vertical or is it lateral?
I guess it depends where you're standing and how you're standing.
I mean, if you're sideways.
Well, when you look above, here's the other big lie.
This is the big lie, okay?
You know, we always talk about the legal stuff and the banking,
but maybe taking a break is a good thing.
You know when they show you a model of the solar system?
They show you this thermonuclear sun in the middle,
all the planets in neat revolving orbits going around it, right?
Yeah, we already know.
It's like it's in a wake.
The sun is like a meteor, right?
Exactly.
And we're all, the planets are following in a wake behind it, right?
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
It's not thermonuclear at all.
It's a rock.
Nassim Harriman.
Do you know who Nassim Harriman is?
Someone once sent me a video back.
He doesn't quite have it all together.
He still thinks the sun is thermonuclear, I think.
Is that true? I'm not sure.
I don't think so.
I think he's more brilliant than Einstein, I swear.
Einstein wasn't happy.
Absolutely.
I went and saw him in person in Santa Monica.
He was an amazing guy.
No, he's a good guy.
Einstein was like Lee Harvey Oswald.
You know, Lee Harvey Oswald had 20 witnesses
saying he was in front of the soda machine
when the shots rang out, right?
Oh, I don't know.
I wasn't alive at the time, so.
Right.
It's all propaganda.
Einstein was just put in front of everyone
like everybody else is put in front of everyone.
Yeah, so we're trailing behind.
So if the sun speeds up,
well, you see the surface of the sun is like a comet.
So when you look at a sunspot,
that's like the eye of the hurricane.
The surface of the sun is black, right?
And it's not hot.
Yeah, I think he believes it's electromagnetic or something.
Yeah, it's inductive.
But here's the thing.
When the sun speeds up, it gets brighter.
If it slows down, it gets dimmer, right?
Now, due to vortex shedding,
you know, like something in something else's wake
spins faster when the wake speed increases, right?
So when the sun speeds up in the next 20 years
and it gets brighter,
the Earth is going to go from a 24-hour day scenario,
you know, 12-hour day, 12-hour night, basically,
to a 16-hour day scenario,
8-hour day, 8-hour night.
And it's going to get really hot for a few months.
Yeah, but will we really, will we,
I mean, it's so gradual a change.
Will we even notice it in our lifetime?
Oh, yeah, it's coming.
It's just around the corner.
And the powers that be try to hint, global warming.
They're not telling you which globe, right?
Well, I think that,
I think the sunspots and the,
the, what do they call it?
The GMEs?
Yeah, solar mass ejections.
They always come back.
You notice that they never show a photograph or a video of anyone?
I think those are what's controlling the weather here
and why we're having such odd weather.
No.
No?
Yes and no.
Both.
You have a vertical,
as we're trailing behind the sun,
it looks like we're like,
imagine a teardrop laying on its side.
The sun is on the front end
and the planets are all up until about the center of that teardrop
and the back half of it is all empty right now, right?
There's also a vertical vortex that goes through, right?
If you put your hand through water, right, to spiral it,
you'll notice there a vortex is going 90 degrees to the main,
you know, one, okay?
That's where the other objects come in from.
I'll leave it at that.
I know.
I'm trying to follow you there.
Say that again or explain it again.
The rest of the planets, aren't they the same?
Just look at basic vortex shedding, okay?
If you, let's say, run a basketball through water,
you get a wake behind it, right?
Right.
But if you look very carefully, right below that wake,
there's another wake going vertically 90 degrees to it,
not horizontal.
Lots of little ones, right?
Those are the positions of the planets,
and they also go up very far.
And that is like a vacuum,
so if you need to visit a solar system,
you want to ride one of those vertical wakes.
Okay.
Yeah, so interstellar,
I don't know if you want to get interstellar travel,
but basically everything they're telling us is a lie.
Absolutely everything.
Oh, I already know that.
I think we all know that.
And here's the thing,
the most degrading thing you can do to a man or a woman,
and their offspring, okay?
The most degrading thing you can do to anyone is grade them.
Think about it.
What do you mean?
Say that again, I'm sorry.
The most degrading thing you can do to anyone is grade them.
Right.
What do they do in school from kindergarten all the way up?
Oh, sure.
Well, yeah, and degrees,
isn't that all a Freemasonic thing?
No, well, I got no problem with the Freemasons.
I would join them in a heartbeat
if they weren't doing what they were doing
because they have keys to a lot of ancient knowledge.
But the problem is they don't know how to read these things, right,
because they went to these school systems.
But they're just a side note.
How do you account for your unusual perspective?
I'm sorry?
How did you slip past the brainwashing of academia?
Oh, well, they started moving me up through school,
and they finally kicked me out at a very young age,
and then they wanted me to go to these universities for free,
and I went there, and the professors told me,
what are you doing here?
You could teach this class.
Get out of here.
So I did.
I was always on the outside.
I asked questions since I was very young.
But in order to be objective, you can't take interest.
For example, people call me up and say,
oh, this basketball game is on.
And I'm like, all right, let me turn it on.
And I watch these guys in uniform chasing the ball back and forth,
back and forth.
I said, listen, guys,
I said, no, this doesn't make any sense to me at all whatsoever.
Because objectively, if I had to take notes and send them back home,
let's say, to another planet, let's say,
I can't say I'm into this team or that team.
I've just got to explain what these people are taking interest in, right?
So you just have to have objectivity.
You can watch your clothes there.
Say that again?
What?
Well, the movement in a basketball game is not a great deal dissimilar
from the movement of different colored clothes in a dryer.
Right.
Actually, watching the dryer spin is a little more interesting than television,
which I don't have anymore.
The vortex is more evident there in the dryer.
Yeah.
Everything is moving in a spiral, like a 364 degrees in a circle, right?
Because you can never draw a perfect circle.
You know, triangles, they tell you that should add up to 180 degrees.
If you add up all the internal angles, it's physically impossible.
Go out with a tape measure and lay out a triangle,
the internal angles will always add up more than 180 degrees
because you can't draw a straight line.
Everything wants to curve and spiral.
So once you get away from this linear thinking that they're giving you,
this two-dimensional thinking,
they have to wrap up everything in two-dimensional sense,
and there is no such thing.
They keep it two-dimensional because you can't interact with it.
It's just yes, sir, no, sir.
But the universe is one of scale, not of dimension.
In other words, if they're telling you planets are orbiting around the sun,
have you ever walked down the street or in nature seen anything orbiting around anything?
Never.
The universe is one of scale, not of dimension.
Dimension is an illusion.
The whole thing is part of a big computer program,
and we're being controlled by the moon.
Well, in essence, Angela, we are nothing more than God's thought emanation.
We're in someone's thoughts, and it's kind of hard to even conceive that concept,
and I'm not saying that as a fact.
This is maybe trying to be poetic.
I like it.
At some point.
Well, listen, look, this whole existence is more a lesson for all the other,
let's say, races, okay?
Because if you read the Bible, it's very clear.
It says the heavens, which are three heavens.
You have the sky, right, and then you have outer space,
and the third heaven is a realm that's not tangible to us.
The book of Isaiah says the heavens are inhabited.
It doesn't say there's just bacteria out there.
It's inhabited.
In order to be inhabited, you're in stewardship role, you're in creation role,
you're in, you know, we're being watched.
The earth is universe central right now.
Interesting.
And you've got time.
Time ended in 1998.
Everyone's like, oh, the end's coming.
What are you talking about?
It already ended, man.
You're in the credits version of the movie.
The movie ended in 1998 in the fall.
You're in the credits right now.
What's great about the credits is if you want to shoot a two-hour film,
you don't get two hours of film, you get two hours and ten minutes
because you've got to roll the credits, right?
And what's interesting about the credits is let's say you have a character
in the first few minutes in the first scene of the movie,
you don't see him again for the rest of the film.
He shows up one more time, doesn't he, in the credits.
So what you're going to see for the next, you've got about 20 some odd years left
in terms of the way things are.
You're going to see all these very unusual new ways of doing things
which are nothing more than things that are of ancient time.
Very, very interesting.
So you've got to know the history, but the real history,
not that, you know, Christopher Columbus discovered America.
How could that be?
There are already people here, right?
So, you know, you've got Adam, right, who's the new kid on the block, right?
Yeah.
So, you know, what's the deal here?
Well, learn how to keep time.
I think we spoke about it a while back, you know?
Yeah.
Learn your equinoxes, your months or your moons,
and your day starts at noon, period.
How hard is that?
If you learned it in school, you know, it would be natural.
Even the Naval Observatory, who is the timekeeper
on their Julian calendar date section of their website, says,
the day starts at noon for scientific and astronomical purposes,
but for the people and civil reasons, it's midnight.
What did they just say?
For those of us that, you know, want to pursue the truth,
the day starts at noon, but for the cattle, it's at midnight.
Keep us in the dark.
Yeah, midnight is an illusion.
You know, you have the day starts at noon, period.
Noon is when the shadow is dead on north.
You get no shadow to the east, no shadow to the west,
and it lasts for, you want to measure it down to a thousandth of a second,
you can do that.
And this is how it's been done forever, I mean, up until the 1700s.
You know, they used to do in common law courts a trial in the morning
and they hang you the next day if you were found guilty.
Right?
Well, they did the trial in the morning, and when did they hang them?
At high noon.
So, it's all over.
I mean, it's just that, you know, in Genesis,
it says there was evening, there was morning, the first day.
Evening is noon.
Evening starts at noon. Morning ends at noon.
How many times do people catch themselves, they say,
you know, good morning, you know, it's like 12.05,
and say, oh, oh, oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, good afternoon, you know.
Well, I think the point is to take advantage of sunlight, right,
and get the most you can out of the daylight hours.
I mean, you know.
That happens naturally because you always have 12 hours in the day,
no matter what, because you have the sky divided into 10 sections,
then you've got your first hour before the sun rises,
and you've got your last hour after the sun is setting, right,
after it's below, the disk of the sun is below the horizon.
In religious circles, they say, oh, yeah, you know, sundown, you know,
sundown, that's an hour, man.
There's no precision in that.
It's all in the Bible.
It's all in all the books, in the Koran, it's in the Bhagavad Gita,
the Mahabharata, Rig Veda.
Day starts at noon, period.
It's in your old scientific literature.
So why do we go to school and take everything that we are taught
or told as gospel?
Why?
Are we such inferior creatures that we don't have the inspiration
to double-check what we're being taught?
We're just so gullible.
It's like, why?
Okay, you ever see a chihuahua?
You know, put a chihuahua in a natural environment,
how long do you think it's going to last, right?
It becomes very dependent, and when you run into chihuahuas,
they've got a big attitude problem, right?
So, I mean, this is what I say.
I say there used to be people, men and women.
Now you have these creatures called human beings,
which are a subspecies of people bred by bad food and bad education.
Yeah, instead of evolving, I think they've devolved the population
down to inferior status, really, because...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And it's all...
No one put a gun to your parents' head to send you to school
or eat whatever, or, you know, not you, but anybody.
It's a slow cultural thing because people don't want divine law.
And it's a small group of people that have led the group away.
That's why you have shepherding, right?
You know, if you have an evil shepherd, the flock goes to its demise.
If you have a good shepherd, the flock prospers, doesn't it?
So you've had a pretty evil shepherd on this earth.
That's why I say this whole thing, I mean, no hard feelings,
but this is as much of a lesson for the spirit of man and woman
as it is for the other ethereal beings out there.
So, you know, that's why I keep saying this is universe central
in terms of the attention that we're getting.
And it's going to get really, really harsh.
I mean, if anyone...
I mean, there's no hope at all in what people know.
In other words, you know,
oh, we've got to make the environment better.
We're talking about the environment.
The environment is your water, your river.
We're hypocrites.
If you see a society talking about the environment,
you go down to their rivers,
and if their rivers are running like a sewer or they're dried up,
hypocrites.
The river is your environment, period, your water.
You know, everything is just backwards.
It's just completely...
There's no hope in any system right now on the planet,
whether it's alternative.
Yeah, solar and wind.
Yeah, my foot.
You know, that's ridiculous.
You know, that's so ridiculous.
I mean, in the New Age movement,
all the religions, I mean,
there's no hope in any of that.
You're going to have to wait until the veil is lifted,
and I'm sure that's a common terminology.
Just have hope in yourself.
Look to yourself.
Don't look to anybody else to do anything for you.
Well, here's the thing about hope in yourself.
You just got to be flexible to the point where
relieve yourself of arrogance, rebelliousness, and stubbornness,
because if you read the scriptures,
it says people are so stubborn,
you have to kill them twice, right?
That's why there's the second death.
So anyway, I don't want to get into that,
but the thing is we're just too stubborn,
and we're too...
as a group, unwilling to change,
and it's got our mindset, you know, too much.
And everything that people are calling good is actually,
if you read it with some comprehension,
you'll look at it, and you're like,
ooh, this is pretty benevolent, you know?
And there's no hope in what people see being put out there,
whether it's mainstream or not.
In it, there's no hope in it.
In other words, you can't rely on it,
because it's all going to fall apart at the seams.
It already is, you know?
And you got to understand also the Elohim,
the Creator God, and His crew, okay?
Because I consider myself part of the ground crew, okay?
Because if I could get off this rock, I would.
That's cute.
Right?
That's what Nassim Harriman says.
We need to get off this planet.
Yeah, you need to get off it if you can.
That's my first suggestion.
They're very, very efficient.
You know, when I used to run construction sites,
I told people, if you're not efficient with something,
God's going to take it away from you.
Okay?
So they're very efficient.
So if these beings showed up now,
people would be so afraid.
They would board themselves up into their houses,
and they would starve to death better than opening the door.
That's how scary it would be if they showed up right now.
So what do they do?
They set up, he allows things to go to pot,
and this Antichrist figure comes in,
this one-world government, one-world ruler.
He creates a very highly regimented society,
reduces the world's population down by, you know, 75%, 80%,
especially when you look at the natural disasters
and the two asteroid hits we're going to get near the Mediterranean Sea.
And then you've got this situation.
Okay, so then the Antichrist declares himself as God.
So what happens?
God comes in, kicks him in the ass,
throws him in the lake of fire, boom.
Now you've got a society already set up, okay,
in a highly regimented order, and you start all over.
These are beings of very high efficiency.
You know, it's not the
if you look at all the religions,
what the religious figures are portraying in these things, man,
I mean, it's like, you know, please, you know,
tooth fairy department, save me.
You know, if you read the scripture, the crisis,
I didn't come for any of you all.
I came here to do a particular job.
They only had 12 people around them.
Even out of those 12, one of them couldn't handle it.
He had to go to the other side.
So, you know, it's kind of ridiculous.
I mean, I find the people on this planet to be pretty ridiculous.
I mean, I'm sorry.
Except here.
Except here in our nice, neat, little, tidy group.
Yeah, yeah, but I mean, in general,
the reason why I say that is because it's like, you know,
you can't tell anybody anything really
unless they're ready to hear it even then.
It's not even a matter of
the reason why it's important for my opinion,
people to wake up,
it's not so we could sit here and take windy walks
and talk about these things.
It's because I want to know what part of the equation
they could bring to the table, you see.
Because if someone's not awake,
what are they going to bring, you see?
So the reason why you want people to wake up,
because everyone's got this exceptional talent
that they each, you know, bring something in,
and then that's how you develop and go to the next level,
like in a video game, in a way.
Dr. Joe McCord.
That was weird.
Dr. Joe McCord, huh?
Well, that's very interesting.
You always have so much interesting stuff to say.
Okay.
It's been a while since you've been on.
I'm glad you came on.
Well, thanks.
Yeah, again, I heard this stuff about the ether.
Chemtrails, yeah.
Yeah, chemtrails, you've got worse problems than chemtrails.
You've got worse problems,
which I'm not even going to get into, much worse.
But yeah, yeah, but that's also in the scripture.
Look up, you'll see signs in the sky.
Don't be afraid.
Yeah, I guess that's just another thing.
You've got worse, much worse things than chemtrails.
I mean, and what's amazing to me is
it's right in front of everyone, and people don't see it,
and it's just like, wow, you know.
All you've got to do is put two and two together.
What's worse than chemtrails?
Nuclear war?
Oh, you're already in nuclear war.
You already have a bunch of nukes being used on this country,
and broad daylight, three of them,
ten years ago, and no one said anything.
Well, what are we going to say?
Yeah.
What is anyone going to say against,
you're talking about, you know, the powers that be.
We need to go directly to the powers that be.
We need to freeze their assets,
string the suckers up,
and eliminate all their bloodline families.
I'm sorry, but that's the only way.
Well, here's the thing.
Marco Polo, there's a book of travels of Marco Polo,
conquests of Marco Polo, whatever.
Okay.
So, you know, there's dinosaurs,
and I think it's in chapter 14,
you know, what they call dinosaurs,
these giant lizards, you know,
that were pulling the emperor's chariot,
and these villagers went up to the mountains
to get away from this snake
that was like 50 feet long and 6 feet in diameter, right?
Okay.
So, they found out that if you look at all the counties
throughout Europe, especially in Austria,
the county records going back five, six hundred years,
there were these giant lizards.
They call them dragons, okay?
They would come in and eat people
because people were expanding and encroaching on their turf.
Just like today, if there was a grizzly bear in downtown L.A.
that ate a mother and a child,
everybody with a rifle would be there in 15 minutes
and it wouldn't happen again for a very long time, right?
So, but not everyone's got that kind of firepower.
So, what you do, well,
people that didn't have the ability
to fight these creatures off,
they found out what their feeding habits were,
and they just cut them off from their food supply.
Yeah, well, that's what they're doing to us, I think.
You know, they've got us all brainwashed.
What are the powers that they feed on?
Well, they feed on your signature, right?
Okay.
They feed on, you use credit, you know, the whole thing.
Forget about 10 to 1,
it's more like 980 to 1 now with the signatures.
So, like I said, just fend for yourself.
Don't rely on them for anything.
Don't use anything that they've provided as a convenience
or a benefit or privilege, right?
So, what's old is new.
How did people live thousands of years ago?
Well, you know, I believe the car,
the automobile is a wonderful invention
because if you had a horse,
whether you use the horse or not,
you still have to feed him, water him,
and groom him every day.
If you have a car and you don't use it,
it just sits there.
It's cheaper than a horse, right?
So, I mean, there's certain things, you know,
just, you know.
Somebody else wants to chime in here.
Hey, Jay Horses, what did you want to say?
Well, he brought up a good point about not signing anything.
And, boy, when you're in court,
they try so hard to get you to sign all kinds of stuff.
And they try to extract your birth date out of you.
But as I told you last week, there, Angela,
I was going into court,
and you wanted me to call you and tell you about it.
So, that's kind of what I'm going to do.
Oh, okay, good.
I'm going to sign out.
Thank you, Angela.
Okay, but stay on, Gregg,
in case, you know, you want to pipe in again.
Okay, thanks.
Thank you.
All right, hey, Jay.
Very interesting stuff he had, the other guy there.
But, anyways, I had kind of an incident,
actually, a week ago.