Great, Angela, thanks very much for persevering for all this time.
I came on about an hour and a half ago, as a long-time listener and a first-time caller,
and I just want to thank you personally for what you're doing.
And my purpose of calling...
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Thank you.
Great, and I'm calling because I share the same heritage as the fellow, I think his name
is Greg, the Greek?
Yes.
That's on?
And what's interesting, I came on the call about an hour and a half ago, and I was listening
to your explanation of your history and past, and just on a personal note, very quickly,
I've traced my lineage back to Titus, and actually one of the family names in my lineage
is Apostolakis, which actually means descendant of the Apostle.
And I've awakened about 10 years ago, finding out what's going on, and I've been a student
of the Bible, and I got into it because of law, and then I found out pretty much everything
in it is true, and it's not a religious document whatsoever.
And I've been studying and teaching Greek and Hebrew, because it's very easy to learn
those languages.
If you look at the Greek and Hebrew, most people are afraid of it, but all you have
to do is download a coloring book for four-year-olds, color those letters for a few days, and they'll
be familiar, right?
And you can actually end up reading it in a few days, and that's an organic way of learning.
You're not going to learn a language from Rosetta Stone.
I speak five different languages, and I've taught myself in just a matter of days or weeks,
by just downloading a coloring book or a child's primer in that particular country, and that's
the organic way of doing it, because that's how you learn a language, unless you brought
it up in the jungle, right?
And I just wanted to also see if there's a way to get in touch with you.
I have a lot of information regarding prophecy and proper interpretation of Scripture.
Is there a way to get in touch with you, to perhaps lend you this information, because
a lot of it is not for what I call public consumption.
Sure, sure, yeah.
My email address is my initials, gptruth, for Greg Pappas, and it's at gmail.com.
gptruth at gmail.com?
Right, and my family name is Papavassilopoulos.
Oh, okay, Papavassilopoulos, that's the father of the king.
Right.
So, on a personal level, am I allowed to speak Greek?
Poly-legal, very little.
Okay, okay.
You can teach me the Greek that I never learned.
I dropped out of Greek school when I was a kid because I pissed off the priests, okay?
Oh, that's fine.
I hope you were never a kid, because kids are goats.
You mean a child.
When I was a child, I rebelled against the formalities of religion.
My first name, Gregory, obviously means watchman.
My whole life, I've always had this propensity to find answers, and for some reason,
all the kids I was in Greek school with at the Greek church just drove me crazy,
and I couldn't get out of there.
And they were all so petty, little.
You start knowing that there are certain people that are more of an indigo nature
than others that didn't understand that concept back then,
but I now understand those that are on the spiritual path
and are seeking the truth no matter where it leads them
are a little bit different than the average guy out there.
Thank you, and again, this call has been very long.
And something for your listeners, Angela, I just wanted to say to everyone,
we need to look at the cause, not the symptom.
I like listening to a lot of the calls, but they're addressing the symptoms.
And on a very quick note, the cause is based on this.
Everyone understands that knowledge is power.
So that means that people in power have a certain knowledge
that others don't, correct?
And that knowledge is that we do not live in a universe.
We live in what I call a multiverse.
There are many layers to it.
And they have knowledge of the spiritual world that is not taught.
And this outline is in scripture.
I don't want to say the Bible, and I heard Greg say earlier
that they've taken the divine names and turned them into titles of English nobility.
I've done a lot of research.
Here in Arizona, we have a library in the university that's a lot of books
that were bequeathed by wealthy sunbirds that came here.
And no one reads them.
And I found some very interesting books.
And I can tell you, after 10 years of research,
everything that can be known was known over 200 years ago,
or I'd say about 150 years ago, in science, math, physics, and all this.
And the stuff has been buried away, and everything's been convoluted.
And along this path, I found out how to understand the meaning of words.
And by listening to the callers, and they use words like justice, for example.
When you read the Constitution, it says they wanted to establish justice.
Well, not to offend anyone, but this might be news to most, not to some,
justice has nothing to do with law.
Justicia is an ancient religion.
It is a revival of an ancient religion.
It's a statue of a woman carrying scales and a sword.
It has nothing to do with law.
So beware, people.
Justice has nothing to do with law.
It's in the name of law.
It is a different type of law.
In short, I tell people, if you do not understand the relationships
of cannibals, birthdays, and dolls, you will not understand this society.
People say, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
And when I explain it to them, they are floored.
And if I do explain it on this call, it might offend some people.
And the intent is not to offend, but inform.
And this is the knowledge that is being held.
What they are doing, they understand we live in a multiverse,
and the spiritual world affects the physical world.
Just like, for example, there are very toxic gases
that are odorless, tasteless, and colorless.
And you can put that in a room of people, and everyone will die.
And no one will even know.
The spiritual world operates on that level.
And really quick, what cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common
is in the ancient Mesopotamian societies about 5000 years ago,
during the times of Noah, let's say, for those who have read scripture,
it was a primarily agricultural society.
And when things didn't go well, they had these guys called,
they had a little idol called Baal, or Baal, that people were told to worship.
And the priests of Baal were called the Qahans of Baal.
And they told the people, if you wanted prosperity,
you brought a young child to us.
And what they did is they put him up on an altar,
and they killed the child. They sacrificed him to Baal.
And everyone, including the parents, partook in the ceremony,
and they each ate a little piece of flesh and drank a little bit of blood.
That's why eating of human flesh is called Qahan Baalism.
In other words, cannibalism. Just take out the H.
Now when the parents went home, all the other children would say,
where's our brother? Where's our sister?
But the altar boys of the Qahan Baal, or the cannibal,
made an effigy of a child, which is a small doll.
And they said, give this to the other children to play with.
And they'll forget about the child.
So now you know the history of dolls.
And if you ask a mother, why do you give a doll to your child,
she doesn't know.
But the Puritans and the Quakers, when they first came here
and they saw a family giving their child a doll,
they knocked on the door and said, we're going to raze your house in 15 minutes.
In other words, we're going to burn your house down
because you're involved in human sacrifice.
You can either choose to stay in or leave, but we're going to purge you from here.
So now you know the history of dolls.
It's very macabre.
The powers that be worship the adversary, and they feed on negative energy.
And they don't care whether you know it or not, as long as you do it.
Now, obviously, that's not going to bring you prosperity.
So next year, you come back and you bring another child.
And if they keep taking all the children, someone's going to figure it out
and they're going to run them out of town, which they were run out of town many times.
So the Qahan Baal, the priest of the Lord,
that's why in today's churches, the priest tells you to worship the Lord, which is Baal.
Again, not to offend anyone, but we have to be very careful what we're being directed here.
Well, next year, again, they bring the child back and the Qahan Baal, accountable, says,
you know, instead of taking this child, why don't you go home and put him in a tall chair
and give him a pointy hat like we wear and bake a loaf of sweet bread
and put candles in it, ask the child to make a loaf, a wish of prosperity,
to blow out the lights, which symbolizes taking the life out.
And then everyone eats a piece of the sweet bread, which represents the body.
And to show that this wish of prosperity works, everyone attending the ceremony has to bring a present.
Now, if that doesn't sound like a birthday cake celebration to me, I don't know what does.
And I read this in a little tiny book that was published in the 1820s.
Now, what do you, what do you, I think this book escaped the incinerator.
Now, what we're doing is absolutely, we are a sick society.
And if you read scripture, you know, voting doesn't matter.
The Creator puts the leaders in and he says, I will put the leaders in based on how evil the society is.
So if you see a society that has a horrible leader, that is a very evil society.
And I'm not saying this to offend anyone. I'm just saying it to inform.
And now, the thing about the truth is it doesn't have prejudice.
In other words, the truth is the truth.
And if it offends anyone, it's not meant.
But again, in scripture, someone who knows the law cannot be offended.
Right.
Right, because if, you know, you got a big bump on your head and it looks ugly,
if someone says you got a big bump on your head and you know it, well, thank you for telling me.
Or if you didn't know, you thank them because now you know.
Instead of saying, why are you making fun of the bump on my head or something.
So these things, I've done a lot of research I've got.
I can have reams of information and I can take up 14 conference calls on things that I've discovered.
And sitting here, very few people want to hear this kind of information.
Oh, you'd be surprised.
You'd be surprised.
Yeah, I want this.
This is ancient.
Now, when you read the scripture, it talks about mystery, Babylon, the revival of an ancient religion.
Very little is talked about the times of Noah.
Now, whether you believe in scripture or not is irrelevant.
You'd have to go back to the epic of Gilgamesh King first.
Well, here, this is my perspective.
I'm one of the few people that I know that has a very accurate perspective and interpretation of prophecy.
In other words, very specific stuff.
And I see it and my track record is impeccable.
And this is the logic behind it.
The future minus the past equals the present.
So you don't know where you are unless you know the future and the past.
It's basic math.
So, you know, everyone's going around scratching their head and I'm saying,
well, this is going to happen, this is going to happen, and this is going to happen, and it's happening.
You know, when I go out and speak in public on this, I'm just this crazy guy that everyone's wondering what I'm saying is true.
Just like a prophet.
Nobody will call you crazy in our groups.
So this is, I can go into some real interesting detail.
I know that people would like to hear it, but here's the other kicker to this.
This information, this kind of stuff, you can't, from a spiritual level, unless you're prepared and you walk a certain path,
you don't pick it, it picks you.
You have no choice in the matter.
See, ten years ago, if you gave me a Bible, I said, what?
That's written by Shakespeare.
Throw that away.
God, what are you talking about?
Creator, what are you, delusional or something?
So I went to a seminar here where someone was explaining there is no money and this is a mortgage is a fraud,
and I was like, what?
No one ever told me this.
He says, well, man makes statutes and codes and the creator makes law.
And I'm like, wait a second, where do I get law?
He says, you've got to go to the Bible.
I said, no way.
That book?
You've got to be kidding.
So I read it just for the law and then I started reading that everything the scripture,
pretty much all the information contained was contrary to what man was teaching.
Now, man was teaching contrary to scripture.
Now, if you're seeking the truth and you have two different opinions or bodies of information,
only two things can be true.
Either they're both wrong or one of them is right.
So I put them both down and I started researching man's system and then the scriptural system.
And I've written many things and, for example, the creator's economy is different than man
and the adversary's economy.
When I say economy, it's a Greek word meaning the management of the house.
That's literally what it means.
Eko means house and nomos means the rules of the house.
In the father's economy, you have gold and silver and substance for trade, balanced scales,
no cheating, you have certain laws, you have certain ways of cultivating your crops.
One of the reasons this country will never prosper is because they don't let the fields go fallow
every seven years.
They just keep farming and farming and farming.
This is a very small example.
That's not even one hundredth of one percent of why.
I can give you 10,000 reasons why we're in deep doo-doo.
Don't have to be, but we are on a very practical level.
And another thing, just to segue a little bit of information,
because I don't want to get into things.
There's a million websites following the creator's law,
but the stuff that I've researched and I have stored up information,
there's nothing on it online.
Absolutely nothing.
And I'm not about to put it on online right now.
It's not ready.
The time isn't right now exactly.
It'll be ready in seven years.
I hate to say that, but I wouldn't mind coming on a conference call and giving it.
You should do it.
And because, you know, what you said, you said a great number of very profound things,
and the history behind everything.
And you said something that really got me.
You're compelled.
I've been compelled to this thing my whole life.
I was in Vestal in 1983, and I was visiting a friend up on the top of the hill above the city,
and I was staying at a hotel down on the port.
And we spent 12 hours together going over why it was that I needed to come to Greece
and work with this ministry at the time that was with Campus Crusade for Christ,
and they tried to convince me why I needed to be there.
I had already applied to go to seminary when I got back in August,
and I got to Greece on a variety of things that happened.
It was a very strangely orchestrated thing by the creator.
I would not have been there otherwise that summer.
Anyways, the long and short of it is that I'd been asking, ever since I was a kid,
for the revealing of the answers to me, that I'd understand what's going on,
how does this world work, and what are we all here for?
Are we all here to be somebody else's slaves?
Are we here to be free?
Is this a growth process?
I knew it was something beyond what religion taught,
because religion within the Orthodox and the Protestant tradition was, to me,
largely designed to keep all the slave workers in line
and not to allow us to rise to the level that we're supposed to be.
I never took a regular job.
When I got out of college, I applied for corporate jobs
and saw how horribly miserable these people were
and didn't take a regular job and sought out to find the answers to life.
When I went to seminary, I never actually ever said I was going to be a pastor
or a missionary or anything.
People kept asking me,
well, what are you going to be when you get out of here?
I said, I don't know.
I'm only here to find the truth, not to become anything.
I just want to know the truth.
You're not going to find it in seminary though, sorry.
I know, I quit.
I quit seminary halfway through.
I went out and started my own study.
I've studied philosophy and I'll direct people to de-philosophers.
I've studied a lot of things.
I understand that we are one with each other.
I understand that we're one with the universe.
I understand the power that's in us if we just wake up
and figure out what our pre-life purpose was before we got here.
Anyways, I put out a big question to the Creator,
and I got an answer.
I'd like to contact...
I'm going to interrupt.
I'd like to contact you and maybe give you some of this information.
Some of it is so profound that if I did speak it on this call,
some of the people might go and throw up,
and a whole bunch of other people might just freak out.
It's that kind of information.
Have you seen the movie The Fifth Element, anyone?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
That's my life.
Who's in it?
That's what's going on.
It's very close.
There's some stuff going on that...
My purpose is not to go to the average person on the street
or, let's say, on a call,
not to belittle or try to remain humble.
This information has to go to the leaders of the world.
Yes.
Because this is very specific.
I'm talking about...
For example,
the people are so brainwashed that the clock on your wall
and that calendar is totally false,
and I'll prove it to you right now.
It's so simple.
If you really want to wake up, even though it's been four hours,
this will be like drinking four espressos in a row.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Sept is the prefix for seven.
Oct is the prefix for eight, like octagon.
Nov is the prefix for nine,
and dec is decimal, meaning ten.
So why is...
If December is the tenth month,
why are they telling everyone it's the twelfth month?
Why is November the eleventh when it's really the ninth month?
Why is October the...
You see, it's right in front of your face.
September is the seventh month.
It's right in your face, and no one...
is saying,
wait a second, this is erroneous.
This is more erroneous than the straw man.
Give us the punchline.
Okay, the punchline is we don't even know how to keep time
with nature.
This is a multiverse.
When you read about prayer
and scripture,
that is a technology like someone setting up an antenna.
Yes.
And there's timing in there.
Now, if you're reading scripture,
if anyone's ever read it,
it says, these are my appointed times.
These are my appointed times, yes?
That's how they translate it in English.
It's moed and moedim in Hebrew.
Right?
If you read it, it says, these are my appointed times.
How many times can you miss an appointment
with someone when they kind of, you know,
say, well, this guy's not serious?
Yeah, really.
Do you see my point?
Now, again, knowledge is power,
and this kind of information is held by those in power.
But they're doing these procedures,
there's procedure involved.
And they're doing it for another character.
Now, I'm going to drop maybe,
with Angela's permission,
can I drop a bombshell of information?
Oh, please do.
I did some research on this ancient religion
that existed 5,000 years ago that was wiped out.
It was revived partially around the 4th century
and it's been revived in earnest in the past 50 years.
When I mean in earnest, I mean with turbochargers on it.
And this religion, for lack of a better name,
is called science.
Now, let me explain.
Let me explain why it's a religion.
The way they drag you in is by receiving a benefit.
A cell phone, a computer,
TV, you know, nanotechnology, whatever.
But that is not the purpose of science.
The purpose of science,
you know the white lab coats on the stethoscopes?
I've traced that back to 5,000 years.
There was a group of people that wore,
they tried to mimic the temple priests,
but I don't want to get into that detail.
Science basically teaches that man and woman
once was godlike.
And in that godlike state,
this is an ancient religion that's revived now.
In that godlike state,
they were hermaphroditic, meaning they had both sexes.
Or they were asexual, no sexual gender at all.
And what science teaches
is that in order for man to attain that godlike state,
what you need to do is have male with male unions
and the males become fertile and become drones.
And you have female with female unions.
And the females become emasculated
and they procreate children without man.
And the procreation,
the product of that female with female union,
will be hermaphroditic or asexual child.
So I just gave you a little bit of prophecy
that you're going to start seeing this
happening within the next decade.
So you know where you heard it here.
What's your name?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
What is your name?
My name?
I don't know if I want to disclose.
Actually, a lot of people did know of me.
Well, if I want to get in touch with you,
would you email me or something?
Well, I'll message you an email and you'll give me a name.
How's that?
Oh, that would be wonderful.
I think you will like it.
I can have so many,
I don't know if the science was really a bombshell.
I was holding it back.
I do have some bombshell material that,
I don't know if people want to be woken up.
Yeah, I want more bombshell stuff.
But hermaphrodite would then reference,
you're not talking about a female,
some of these people that have been born with genitalia.
Yeah, that's what he's talking about, yes.
Actually, when I started teaching this,
exposing this,
there was a man in Britain
that actually legally is considered asexual.
He went from a man to a female sex change.
He wanted to go back to a man,
and they botched it up,
and he can't be neither.
In other words, they hollowed him out completely.
So he legally is genderless.
There is one genderless person.
What's that?
You're saying that both parts worked?
No.
There's a genderless being,
a legal genderless being right now
recognized by the British or English.
The English and British are not the same
as most people know.
Right.
There's a registered genderless
status being in England.
You could go look it up.
But what I'm saying,
this is a product of what I'm talking about,
but it's not going to happen that way.
It's going to be through birth,
or being born.
You're going to see this in the near future.
Well, there's many a hermaphrodite
that have been born already.
Yeah, but what they want to do
is produce a society of that.
Wow.
And this is coming,
but this is,
that's actually,
there's other stuff.
A lot of the bombshell stuff is,
you see,
people complain about the government,
but they don't know
who the government really is, really.
You know, it's a corporation.
You think they're aliens.
We know it's a corporation.
It's an organized crime syndicate
is actually what it is.
Yeah, yeah.
It's in name only,
but let me drop something on you,
and you're going to think about it.
It's going to cause a little bit of thinking.
Okay, let's say you've got a country
with churches,
and you have a particular religion entrenched,
right,
like Protestantism or Catholicism in Italy,
right, let's say.
Now, the government is overthrown,
what people call the government,
and they get a new government,
just like that old song,
and here comes the new boss,
same as the old boss, right?
Right, right.
And it goes over and over,
and the cycle keeps going.
That's why it's a revolution.
It goes over and over and over.
But everyone fails to notice
that these churches and cathedrals
are still here,
and it's the same thing.
They are the government.
Right, they are.
The religion,
when the religion,
for example,
you know how they painted the Muslims
as, you know,
hating the Jews
and hating the white,
you know,
Western culture or whatever?
I read the Koran,
and there are verses in the Koran
that tells, commands the Muslim
if he goes against anyone
that is of Israelite descent
or their land,
they're going to be cursed.
And I know some Muslims,
and I read these verses,
and they say,
and I ask them,
where does this come from?
And they're like,
I don't know.
I say,
this is from your own book.
You don't even read it?
And these imams
and these priests,
you see,
I had a business
and another business next to me
sold sporting goods,
and I walked in one day,
this was years ago,
and I said,
hey,
how many of those baseball bats
do you sell every month?
And he said,
I sell a lot of them.
I said,
okay,
how many of the baseball bats
that you sell
are actually being used
for baseball?
He says,
you know,
I never thought about that.
You know why?
Because baseballs
make a great club.
I mean,
baseball bats
make a great,
inexpensive club.
People put them
in their backseat.
Every store owner
has got one.
Old ladies buy them.
Okay,
that's how they're using
the Koran and the Bible.
The Koran actually
was written by Hebrew rabbis
at night.
I'm not going to get into that.
But the scripture,
when you see someone
walk into a room
wearing black,
carrying the Bible,
he's using that on you
like a baseball bat.
He doesn't know
anything in there
at all.
That's right.
It's an intimidation.
It's all intimidation
to the ignorant.
You got it.
If you study Christianity,
that was born
around 400 AD
by a man
named Constantine.
325.
And it wasn't
the Romans
that threw
the Christians
to the lions.
The real history
in that
is that the Christians
were throwing
the Bible
and the followers
to the lions.
Christians have been around
for a very,
very long time.
I've clocked those guys
back to 3500 years
already.
It has nothing
to do
with the scriptures.
And Constantine,
around 300 to,
you know,
386 or so,
when they had
all these councils,
he was the Walt Disney
of his day.
You know how you have
Pixar pictures
and all the special effects?
That's how he got
people in.
For example,
again,
not to offend,
if you read
the Bible
forensically,
in other words,
you haven't watched
those gifs
of the movie,
the conference is
scheduled to be
broken down
automatically in
5 minutes.
To extend the time
by 60 minutes,
press star 8.
Uh,
I don't know how
Oh, sorry.
Angela,
I'd like to shoot you
an email
and maybe we can
speak and I'd love
to speak with Greg
as well.
And I've got some
stuff that maybe
shouldn't be said
right now.
Oh,
this is the time
for all these
things to come out.
This is the time.
Yeah,
contact me
and we'll set up
a call.
Well,
I'd love to
and I'd love to
also tell you
why I think
something shouldn't
be said.
And then you might
say,
hey,
you know what,
maybe you're
kind of right
about that one.
Or,
if you're
uh,
unintimidated,
if you feel like,
you know,
you want to just
go all the way,
I don't mind.
I've already been
down this rabbit hole.
I've been studying
for 10 years.
And I'm going to,
so you won't be
dropping any bombshells
on me,
but I'm always
willing to have
other people
wake up to,
I mean,
it's like part of
the deal,
you know,
learning this
esoteric stuff
is part of the deal.
You always wind up
on these paths
when you're
researching government
and the truth.
We've got to break
the image training.
You know,
you read the
Constitution,
I read that thing,
the first thing
that pops out of me
is to establish
justice,
holy crap,
what are they
talking,
this is horrible.
And then they
say the operation
of this document
is the law of nations,
that's merchant law.
And then it says
there are no more
slaves,
just U.S. citizens,
okay,
so instead of
calling you stupid,
I'll call you ignorant,
how do you like that?
That's exactly right,
even in Article 1,
Section 9,
Paragraph 1
talks about
the migration
and importation
of persons,
which is slavery.
It's right there
in the Constitution.
And there's some people
that I fed some
information a couple
of years back
and I showed them
about the
Uniform Slave Codes
of 1760,
because they wanted
Uniform Slave Codes,
because, you know,
if you had an
escaped slave
from one state,
it was death penalty
in one state,
not in another,
so you needed
a Uniform Slave Code.
And it actually
states that
when a slave
leaves 15 miles
beyond the plantation,
you need the passport.
Well, now you know
why the International Line
is set at 15 miles.
Yep.
Okay,
then it says...
Let me try to...
The slaves were white.
I'm going to
disconnect
and come back on
to see if that
does anything.
Maybe that'll
extend the call,
I don't know.
Otherwise,
it's going to
turn off
any minute.
Well, that's fine.
Either way,
I will try to
get in touch
with both of you.
Actually,
tonight I'll just
shoot you an email
and I'll bring up
the subject matter.
I'd love to...
Please do.
That would be great.
I've been sleeping
on this stuff
for almost a decade,
so I think it's time.
It sounds like
both of you
and Greg, too,
you're just like
bursting out
with this information.
That means it's
got to come out,
so I'm always
willing to facilitate.
If you say so.
It's your call.
Again,
I'd rather discuss
some of these things
with you first
or email them
and say,
hey,
maybe we don't
want to talk
about this one.
I think,
listen,
we're all
big boys and girls.
Those of us
that don't want
to hear it
can hang up.
I think the majority
of the people
want to hear
what you have to say.
We're all
wanting to
find the truth
and we have
an open mind
and we'll listen.
If we don't
agree,
fine.
If we do,
all the better,
right?
I agree.
Yeah,
it's time.
I'd like to
just preface
very quickly.
I want to talk
a little bit
about prophecy
that will astound you.
I'm not talking
about generalities
like all the crap
you see on television
or the Internet.
The Internet's
full of rubbish.
99% of the stuff
on the Internet
is rubbish.
I think everything
is foretold
in the Bible.
It's like instructions
on how
to carry them out.
The formula is
the future
minus the past
equals the now.
So if you're
missing the future,
you don't know
where you are.
And when man
writes history,
he writes about
the past.
When Yahweh
writes history,
he writes about
the future.
It's backwards.
We project
everything we see.
Right,
and also your intent.
The multiverse
operates on
several levels
and I'm not going
to give you theory
and opinion.
I'm going to give
you stuff that
on the call
you can try
and it works.
I'm talking
about here
now stuff,
not the
material seminar
stuff,
or you got
to come
into my,
join my group
or something.
Right now,
if we do a call,
this second,
I'll show you
some technology
verbally that
you can do,
a four-year-old
can do,
and you will
see the effect
immediately.
It's like
pushing a spring.
When you have
a spring at rest,
when you have
and you push
down on it,
when you let it go,
it actually expands
longer than it was
at rest.
It actually creates
something that
shouldn't be
happening.
In physics,
it's called
period movement
and all that.
I'll show you
how to push
on this thing
that's in
tension,
just waiting.
I'll show you
how to push