Hey Day, I'm out.
Talk Sheen.
Recorded live.
Hello everybody, it's January 16th, 2011, 8 o'clock p.m. Eastern Standard Time.
Welcome to the Divine Mind Group community call.
We have a special guest speaker called The Greek.
If you could give a little bio about yourself a little bit or what you're going to talk about,
we'd be more than happy to hear it.
And anybody else on the call, if you're not muted, please dial star six to mute yourself,
and it's obviously star six to unmute yourself when the guest speaker is ready to take questions.
So out of respect, please do that.
The floor is yours.
Thank you.
In terms of bio, I have pretty much the same biology as everybody else, no pun intended.
I'm just visiting this planet, taking notes is the perspective that I have on it,
and it's been quite a journey, quite a visit to this wonderful earth that we're on.
Started this journey about eight years ago, and still on it.
And finding out stuff every day, and I'm finding out things are not exactly how we're
either perceiving them or told about them or even see them in many cases.
So I started sharing this with people and getting mixed results,
but I kind of stayed on the path and kind of kept everything to myself for a while,
and occasionally I'll speak out and occasionally I won't.
And when I say kind of stayed on the path, at some points you have to focus
and go narrow and deep into a subject instead of being wide and broad.
But without that wide and broad view, you don't get bearings of what you're good at to focus on.
It's like we all have natural talents and natural things that we're drawn to.
So we've got to focus most of our energy on what we've been given in the talent department,
but also we can't be limited and we have to look around and look at other things,
because that's what I found, the generalities and general statements and general ideas
generally get us in trouble.
So with that said, I do have the floor, but I'd like to maybe run it the other way around.
I've done some public speaking, and whenever I've done public speaking,
I look at my audience, I look at their eyes, and I'm wondering if they're actually listening to me
or they're thinking, when is he going to shut up so I can get the microphone?
So with that said, are there any questions at this point?
Yes, I have a question.
Okay.
I'm James Gibbs's brother.
And my question to you is, he said I could ask you in regards to bankruptcy.
Okay.
All right.
I'm not an expert in economics or anything like that.
I don't know.
Is he on right now?
I think he might have you confused with someone else.
Yeah, I really think the call tonight is not really Frank or Brian Collins
or even Michael Joseph and David Merrill.
Now, it's possible that MJ and David will be on next weekend, but not necessarily.
It may be the week after.
Now, we've had Frank O. Collins and Brian Collins on.
But tonight, Greek is really going to kind of go into etymological terms,
where many things come from.
It's not necessarily an economic background, but more of, wow.
It might be scriptural-oriented type terms and things that we've roped into
and believed into.
And the etymological roots might give us great insight into what has happened
in the political and the religious perspective paradigm that has helped bring us
into this roped-in economic predicament that we have found ourselves in.
I think that might be more the order of this particular call tonight.
Is that fair enough for you, young man?
Yes, sir.
When I was speaking with my brother today, he was saying that we are all slaves
to the pope and money has no value.
He was probably telling you that.
I'd like to address that, Gary.
If you just hold onto that question for maybe 20 minutes or so,
I might be coming around that even sooner.
I just also want to mention, I do have some notes on my computer.
My computer is not working well, but I can go off of memory.
But if the fellow that's asking the question, if you just sit back,
maybe, like they say, enjoy the ride.
See, maybe I'll answer your question from a different angle
or a different point of view, and maybe I'll give you a way to look at it
that you'll be able to answer it yourself.
Okay. How long is this call usually? Is it about an hour?
No, we can run up to about three hours just about without even popping a whip,
if you know what I mean.
Okay. And you're also available on Skype, I do believe, if I'm not misunderstood.
I don't know about the Skype business,
but we'll figure out how in the hell to get to your program.
You got a handle on that?
You bet. Thank you.
Thanks.
Well, thanks. Thanks for clearing it up for me, Gary.
Go ahead, brother. You got the floor.
Throw the rope on him. What are we going to get?
What are we going to get for him? Run him on through and bring him on by.
Go ahead, Brother Groot.
You guys ever heard of dihydrogen monoxide?
This is a rhetorical question. It's a chemical compound.
And when you start thinking about dihydrogen monoxide,
you could look up what dihydrogen monoxide is.
It sounds pretty intimidating. You got the word monoxide in there.
We know monoxide's not good.
And dihydrogen monoxide sounds pretty volatile.
A lot of people scratching their heads saying,
what the hell are you talking about? What's this dihydrogen monoxide?
People say, what do you do?
I say, well, I work a lot with dihydrogen monoxide.
And they're like, never heard of it.
Well, dihydrogen is two hydrogens and monoxide is one oxygen.
So it's H2O.
So it sounds very intimidating when you call water dihydrogen monoxide.
And I'm going to get to the computer because, you know,
most people, when you give them a bit of information,
they run to the Internet, which is actually a wonderful thing.
I mean, you've got millions and millions of books and files
and things like that on the Internet.
That is much easier to access in the library.
So if you put in dihydrogen monoxide in the Internet search
and you go to one of the most popular references on the Internet,
it's Wikipedia.
Now, when you click on it, Wikipedia there,
it's going to say the dihydrogen monoxide hoax is a deception
that involves the use of an unfamiliar name for water.
Okay, then by listing some negative effects of this chemical,
attempts to convince people that it should be carefully regulated,
labeled as hazardous or banned.
This hoax was designed to illustrate how the lack of scientific literacy
and exaggerated analysis can lead to misplaced fears.
And I could have not written that better myself.
When I found that recently, I was just jumping up and down
and saying, finally, a simple way to explain what's going on.
So you say, well, what's going on?
Okay, I'll give you a simple example.
You ever notice when someone comes back from war,
they get shell shock and they can't sleep at night.
They just can't take the trauma and the battlefield experiences.
They just can't reckon with it once they get out of that environment
and go live back at home.
So it's been called shell shock.
And I remember growing up and meeting World War II vets
and Korean War vets and Vietnam vets.
See, a lot of them would go to the doctor to get some treatment.
But today, if you come back from war and you've got shell shock,
you go to the doctor and he'll tell you, I've got nothing for shell shock,
but I can treat you for PTSD, which is post-traumatic stress disorder.
What's the difference?
It's the label.
Okay, and if you start looking at how things are being labeled
and what they really are, you might get a much clearer picture
on what's going on in your world and the world around you
and in your thought perception area.
Because that's the thing that can be cleaned up.
A lot of people talk about being brainwashed.
Well, how about just washing your brain?
Think about the term brainwash.
It's very negative, but just washing your brain sounds a little different.
Same word.
So what are we being...
What's shown as being real scary?
And I like to use Wikipedia because it's simple to read.
It's not the be-all, end-all reference
because there's a lot of funny business going on there.
But once we learn how to read, we kind of see things a little clearer.
I've been hearing a lot of things about viruses lately.
So what I do is I go to...
Okay, you know, you see they're telling everybody everything.
These viruses are really scary, you know,
and you've got to be protected against them.
So I just go to Wikipedia and hit virus, okay?
So, you know, you're just visiting this planet,
so you want to make things easy for yourself.
So you just look at what everybody else is looking at,
and you want to look at information that's easy to get to.
So, okay, virus, you know, you go to etymology,
you know, they give you the whole thing,
history, origins, microbiology, classification.
Scroll down. Okay, etymology.
Wow, one of my favorite subjects.
Okay, the word is virus.
It's from the Latin word virus referring to a poison
or other noxious substances.
You know, first used in English, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, history.
Here comes this guy, Louis Pasteur.
Okay, we know a little bit about him, so let's go down.
All right, origins.
Viruses are found wherever there is life
and have probably existed since living cells first evolved.
Operative word, probably.
Okay, so these guys don't know either.
Okay, so viruses, okay, then you have the regressive hypothesis.
Viruses may have been once small cells
called whatever parasitical large cells.
Okay, wait a second.
The operative word viruses may have once been,
so they don't know anything about that either.
They're just, you know, still searching.
Then you got the cellular origin.
Some viruses may have evolved from tiny bits of DNA.
Okay, so there's that word may again.
So they don't know.
Okay, then we go to the coevolution hypothesis.
This is also called the virus first hypothesis
and proposes the viruses may have evolved.
Okay, so they still don't know what they are.
You go to life properties and microbiology.
It says opinions differ whether viruses are a form of life
or organic structures that interact with living organisms.
Okay, so they're just telling me they don't know
and maybe this might be that.
All right, so we keep going down this long, complex article
and you'll start seeing that they really don't know.
They'll just show you certain observations.
But what they do know, we scroll back up to etymology
and they got the operative word here is.
This is the word is from Latin referring to poison.
Okay, so the only thing they know about viruses
is that it's a poison.
All right, so if it's a poison, well,
then we're in the virus category.
We put that aside for now.
Now, what do poisons do to a living body?
Because I have a living body.
And what category would that be?
Well, maybe that's toxicology, right?
So we look up toxicology and let's go back to Wikipedia.
And, you know, because that's common
and it's written on a modern day 8th grade level
or 100 years ago a 3rd grade level.
And we go to toxicology from the Greek word meaning toxicos
or poisonous.
Okay, so I guess if they know viruses are poisons
and toxicology is poison,
well, I know I'm at the right place here.
So we go to history.
Okay, and you start reading about, you know,
when they've been working with poison
and they know a poison.
But, you know, so I'm wondering, you know,
they got chemical toxology
and they got toxicity of metabolites.
Wow, okay, well,
these are things that are organic and, you know,
metabolic in nature, let's say, right?
So let's start reading that, see what it says.
I'll skip around and you'll see how
what's being disclosed to us
and we're not picking it up.
So many substances regarded as poisons
are toxic only indirectly.
Okay, indirectly, that means that,
all right, it's not direct.
So maybe I've got a way of getting it out of my body.
But okay, let's go back to the text.
An example is wood alcohol, and you go on,
formaldehyde, formic acid,
okay, things in the liver.
Okay, they're talking about, okay, as for drugs,
many small molecules are made toxic in the liver.
Okay, they're not telling you maybe,
they're telling you they are in the liver.
A good example being acetamiphen,
especially in the presence of chronic alcohol use, okay.
Genetic variability of certain liver enzymes
make the toxicity of many compounds differ
between one individual and the next
because demands placed on one,
here it is at liver again,
one liver enzyme can induce activity in another.
Many molecules become toxic
only in combination with others.
A family of activities that many toxicologists engage
includes identifying which liver enzymes,
here's that liver again,
convert a molecule into poison.
What are the toxic products of the conversion
and under what conditions and what, okay,
so you could keep reading.
So what they do know about toxicity
has a lot to do with the liver
and when poisons get into the liver,
certain poisons,
the liver has enzymes in it
that will change those poisons
into different poisons that will harm you,
but they do know that
and they keep using that liver
over and over and over again.
So now that we know that viruses,
they know that viruses are poison
but they don't know a lot about much of it,
they just propose or maybe.
I'd rather go on what they know
than what there may be.
So if it's a poison,
it has to do with your liver.
So if you've got viruses,
what do you know about cleaning out your liver?
Do you see how simple this is?
If I just came out and say detox your liver,
would you have gotten it
unless I took you through this long road?
But it was actually,
it wasn't a long road at all.
There are people that pay 100,000 bucks
to get a degree in this stuff.
So that's just one point.
Now I'm not saying what,
this is the be all end all,
I'm not a doctor
and I haven't gone into their labs
and researched it,
but this is what they're putting out
on a very basic reference.
That's correct.
If you detox the liver,
then you make the body live longer.
So what you're saying makes absolutely perfect sense.
Deep hammer down, go ahead.
Well, you see what I'm saying?
I just basically,
all this was,
I was just reading from Wikipedia
and they're telling you
viruses are poison
and then poisons develop in the liver
and the liver actually
turns some things into poison.
You can take something benign.
So what's going on?
Why is everything so scary?
Why are we being,
you see,
if you look, okay,
from a political point of view,
let's look at what's going on right now.
It's real simple,
real simple.
You can deduce everything
and the thing is,
I do want to get to,
to show also the various layers
of what's going on
and I guess I'm starting at the bottom,
but sometimes it's,
that's the best place to start.
If you look at what's called
the democratization of the world right now,
okay, and you know,
some people think it's a good thing,
some people think it's a bad thing.
Well,
why does everyone have a different opinion on it?
What does that word actually mean?
Okay, so
let's go and look at the suffix.
It's a Greek word.
The suffix craci,
C-R-A-C-Y
in an etymological dictionary
is simply,
means state
for a government
or a form of rule.
But the demos part,
now,
a lot of these dictionaries,
you know,
when you do a lot of studying
and law and stuff,
don't they tell you,
well,
you got to get an old one
because they've changed
the most recent ones.
Yes, they have.
But they cannot completely hide it,
the use of words,
because we're actually using them.
So,
how do we find an old term
or definition for the word
D-E-M-O?
Now, another thing I want to mention
is
words are phonetic,
so the spelling changes.
Like, for example,
shop in this country is spelled
S-H-O-P,
but in England,
it's S-H-O-P-P-E.
And the same with theater,
it's different over there,
but if you,
it's not really how you spell it,
it's how it sounds.
So you can look at it...
Robert Fox.
What's that?
Robert Fox was a guy
I met in Texas in the 90s,
hell of a fine guy.
And, man,
he was deaf on buying
old dictionaries,
like
the three-volume Bouvier,
was it 1906 certified,
1868 or 28 Webster's,
going back to Black's Law 1,
I mean, things like that.
Yeah.
And I don't know,
but I got a sniff out there
and I kind of think I smell
that guy in the background,
but
you keep going
because you do it real good.
I just kind of want to acknowledge
because I really appreciate
what you're doing.
So if they're hiding something,
you see,
I think conspiracy theories
are overrated.
I think everyone's getting caught up,
like a dog chasing their tail,
wondering what are they hiding here?
What's the Vatican hiding?
Who are they hiding here?
What information is being hidden there?
I don't think they're hiding anything.
If we learn how to discern,
we will find...
Well, I shouldn't say
they're not hiding anything.
They are hiding some stuff
and maybe later on in the call
I might explain what it is,
at least from what I have perceived.
But
if we want to look at,
go back to the
democracy
or what the word means,
it's obviously a Greek word.
Well, if it's not obvious, it is.
And you could look up the suffix,
crossy meaning government or state.
And the word demos is usually
translated or
in dictionaries as
of the people
or masses.
Right?
But, you know, that's a nice way to sell it.
But the root word, demos,
you can find it.
It's either spelled D-E-M-O-S
or D-I-E-M-O-S.
Well,
the most common usage of the word that
I would consider to be most accurate
would be the two moons of Mars.
So, if anybody wants to just research that on their own,
I'm not going to get into it right now,
what that word actually means.
What are the two moons of Mars?
Just look them up.
You got Phobos, which means fear.
And what does demos mean?
D-E-M-O-S
or D-E-I
or D-I-E-M-O-S.
You can look that up on your own time.
And that's your head,
the meaning of that.
And your tail is your crossy, which means state.
You see?
So, once you figure out what that word really means,
look at the two moons of Mars,
what the definitions of those moons are,
Phobos and Deimos.
Go ahead and put crossy on the tail end of Deimos,
and that'll just paint you a clear picture
on what's going on.
It washes away all these conspiracy theories.
It kind of reminds me of Beau Gratz.
It's called head-up rectus, in a sense.
Could be.
Let me just throw this in.
Okay, I'll just say it.
The moons of Mars are Phobos and Deimos,
meaning fear and terror.
Yep.
Does that make any sense to anybody?
Yeah, and Mars would be called the hill of war, wouldn't it?
Yeah.
So, you see what's being put in front of us
essentially can be called the whole truth
and nothing but the truth.
It's just that we can't see it.
So, you know, one thing that got me started
on this journey of what I call critical thinking,
it might be my own brand of it,
but I do share,
if you start going on a road of critical thinking,
you're going to find there's a lot of other people
you can jam with on it,
you know, just like musicians jam, you know?
Oh, yeah.
And everyone's going to bring a piece,
a new piece to it,
and you're going to end up making music,
which is really neat.
Yeah, we got to kind of go to the woodshed,
do a little wood chopping.
Yeah, and it's not only people,
but you'll see that entire societies and cultures
have been given a piece of it, right?
Right.
And what got me going after the truth
or the use of words and communication and language
as a technology
was when I found,
someone once told me that man doesn't make law,
he makes codes and statutes.
So I said, where do you get law?
He said, you go to the Bible for that.
And I said, the Bible?
What are you kidding?
That's written by Shakespeare.
You know, so I was like, well, wait a second.
You know, how do you knock it
if you don't know anything about it, right?
So I went and got one
and started reading just the law parts of it.
And I was like, wow.
And as you start reading the law parts of it,
you're like wondering,
how come I wasn't told any of this?
And then you might start running across words
like Lord and God and playing.
Wait a second.
I was watching TV the other day
and there was a Lord right there in England making a speech.
They can't be, what's going on with this L-O-R-D stuff?
Then you look a little deeper
and you look a little deeper.
Now, before I picked up the Bible,
I was looking at books like the Bhagavad Gita
and the Mahabharata.
And those are the books of the Hindu culture.
People that call themselves the Hindu religion.
And by the way, that word's not in that book.
And when I started studying it,
I was looking at it and saying,
wait a second.
They're not really doing what I read.
They're not really.
I mean, they're saying they're not eating meat.
And here, well, yeah,
it shows you the ups and downs of not eating meat.
Okay, whatever.
They want to do things a certain way.
That's fine.
I just thought it was very odd.
They weren't following it.
Then I read a book called the Koran.
And I knew some Muslim people
and I go up to them and I say,
hey, you're Muslim, right?
How come you're doing that?
I mean, I'm going to read you some verses.
What book does this,
what book do these verses come out of?
And they're like, hell if I know.
I said, it's your own book.
You never read it?
And the same thing with Christians or Jews.
I said, you know, why are you guys,
I've read your book, right?
Theoretically,
they're supposed to use the Bible, theoretically.
And I asked them,
how come you guys are doing this thing to your,
you know, I don't see any amendments or addendums.
What's going on?
So for a period of about two years,
I thought I was losing my mind.
And I was like, oh, wait a second.
I got to catch up to the program.
Nothing is as it seems.
No one's following any rules.
At all.
No, they just kind of make them up as they go.
And they make them up as they go.
And here's the wonderful part about it.
You ready?
When you read their own books,
when I say they,
meaning the religions of the world,
and what they're using as the base
for their religion,
just like the base for money should be gold and silver,
they've completely debased
what they're doing.
It's like having money that's not backed by anything.
Does that sound familiar?
Oh, yeah.
So it's completely debased,
and they're operating on some kind of weird
spiritual credit system.
And I started looking at it a little closer
and finding out the meanings of words,
and it got, you know,
I found out that
every level's got it,
the lie changes on every level.
So when you think you've got one aspect of it
and that's the truth,
and you look at it a little closer,
you put it down, come back,
look at it a little closer,
you're like,
wait a second,
this can't be right either.
And you just keep going,
peeling that onion away.
And so I found out that
pretty much everything is debased.
You know,
I spoke to a nurse recently,
and I said,
well, you know,
how is it working there?
She goes, basically,
you come in,
and, you know,
you go to a doctor,
and it's basically,
we got hair treatment,
penis enlargement,
antibiotics,
and painkillers.
Okay, we do that really, really well.
Do you get my point?
So, I'm thinking, wow.
I do.
We need to check out the computer
and see what your symptoms are
so we can know what we can tell you.
Yeah.
So it's really some,
I'm seeing this everywhere.
You know,
I'm starting to see this
on every level.
I started seeing,
you know,
in the,
in what they call,
I call the Holy Writs of the world.
That's a simple way to communicate
to the everyday guy on the street
and say,
I'm reading about Holy Writ.
Now, everybody on,
you know,
when you say that,
they go,
well, you're reading about the Bible?
I say, well, no,
there's a lot of Holy Writs that the world has,
and guess what?
They're all in agreement,
but you guys aren't.
They're all in agreement.
You know,
if you start looking at what
is written in the Bhagavad Gita
and the Mahabharata,
which is the Hindu text,
it's called the Hindu text,
it is in complete agreement
with what's called the Bible.
And if you read the Koran,
it is in complete agreement
with what you call the Bible.
Yes, it is.
And if you start reading, let's say,
the Egyptian Book of the Dead,
or the Book of Osiris,
it is in agreement.
Yes, it is.
They're all talking about
this third-dimensional physical existence,
and it's information about
things that we do not see.
It's information about
things that are
the way things should be
and the way things can be.
Period.
Yes.
And they all say the same thing.
Now,
when I first started finding out
about all this,
how no one follows the book,
I would go out
and start telling people.
You know?
Yes.
And using their own book
as a reference.
I'm saying their own book,
you know,
it's not their own book,
but what they subscribe to
as the base.
You know,
what's backing up
your quote-unquote belief?
And by the way,
look up the word believe,
it's the word belie,
which is
it's a lie.
That's why I say,
well, you know,
I believe, I say,
listen, brother,
I don't care about what you believe.
Tell me what you know.
I want to know what you know,
not what you believe.
Yes, it's kind of like Hindu.
Hindu is a British term,
but yet it really meant
in you is to do,
but that was not
what the Hindus
really called
or knew about themselves.
Entirely different.
I agree with you 100%.
Well,
yeah,
go look at how many times
the word Christians
actually,
even in your King,
in King James,
they've really,
I might get into that
a little bit later
or actually maybe
sooner than later,
but if you look
at the original text,
though,
the word Christian
is used twice
and it's not
in very good light,
if you know what I mean.
One,
in one way,
it's not very good
and the other way,
it's very ambiguous
and you keep going
and the word Muslim
used,
I mean,
if you want to just
research that on your own,
anybody could plug in
these terms
and if you have a question
about any of the holy writs
of the world,
you know,
there's some pretty good
search engines out there
that I was not familiar with
when I was doing
this longhand.
So,
if you've got a question
like, for example,
you know,
why don't Hindus
eat meat or something
or why do Muslims
hate the Jews,
for example,
and put that question
in a simple query
and you'll get
a lot of perspective
on it.
But you're going
to have to read
it very much
the same way
that I gave
an example
earlier about
describing the virus
as a poison
in the liver.
Now,
that's just one way
to look at it.
I'd like for someone
else to look at it
another way,
but don't come
showing me something
you saw on television
or something written
in an advertisement.
Yeah,
because it's all been
a public mindset
reformatting
much as Bernays,
the nephew
of Freud did,
and then they
picked it up
and they've
massaged it,
shall we say,
and now we've
come up with
all of these
modern terms
and Michael
Tessarian has
exposed a heck
of a lot of things.
But you're doing
a real good job
kind of getting
in that deal.
Go ahead and
pull the slats
out of it,
Greek.
I mean,
just put the
hammer on.
I mean,
we might as well
just blow their drawers
off while you've
got the opportunity.
so here I've
been running down,
again,
knocking my head
against all
people that
have,
they believe in
something,
so I don't
believe in
what you do,
and I'm like,
well,
what do you
believe in?
And they'll
give me a
particular
flavor or
brand or
religion,
and I'll
pull out their
reference and
they'll say,
okay,
well,
this is not
to challenge
them,
maybe hopefully
to enlighten
a brother or
a sister,
right?
So I've
gotten,
it's strange,
this is the
response you
get,
and I actually
printed it out.
It says,
looks like you
answered it
yourself.
However,
my personal
opinion is
that I really
don't believe
what it says
anyway.
Do you see
where, so
have we lost
our minds?
Oh yeah,
because they really
don't believe
what the hell
they're reading
anyway.
Yeah,
and I think
they might,
you know,
be losing
the ability
to,
the cognitive
ability or
reading comprehension,
and also the
different layers
and the
translations.
So one
thing that I
found speaking
to people and
looking at what's
going on in
the world is
it's real,
real,
real basic.
You know,
I started,
you know,
all of us
pretty much
got,
noticed that
computers became
commonplace within
the last ten
years.
Very common.
So if you
start looking
at your
computer,
okay,
you know,
it's got some
real basic
stuff,
and you
could actually
download how
a computer
works on a
small YouTube
video,
and it'll
show you.
And I'm
looking at it
and I'm
like,
wow,
that's exactly
how our
mind works.
That computer
is a mirror
image because
we assembled
it.
That's some
real,
real basic
stuff.
a hologram.
Well,
it's got some
hardware,
okay,
we've got
hardware,
it's
fleshy,
okay,
you know,
we like making
machines now
because we don't
care about
quality.
You see,
years ago,
there were human
computers.
You'd go and
talk to them.
Their names
were like
Socrates and
Plato,
and you've
got,
in your
holy writs,
you've got
your human
computers there.
You go
forward,
you've got,
you see,
and also the
ancients,
you know,
they didn't
use,
they knew about
factories to
mass produce
little trinkets
like they do
in the world
today,
mass production,
but they found
out that
machines made
of metal
using
electricity
did not
produce a
high enough
quality product
than a
machine made
of flesh and
blood and
fat and
water than
breathed.
Do you get my
point?
Oh yes,
I do.
A machine
that is
made of
flesh and
blood will
always produce
a higher
quality item.
So they
said,
okay,
let's put
these machines
making machines
away and
we'll have
just people
making what
we need.
And it
was always
of higher
quality.
You know,
no one would
buy a
Faberge egg
if it was
stamped out
of a
press,
right?
Right,
it didn't have
that quality
to it,
it didn't
have that
personal touch.
That's right.
So today,
years ago,
people had
nannies,
today they
put their
children in
front of
the TV.
Okay,
it doesn't
matter how
much money
you've got
these days,
that seems
the way
that things
go.
Okay,
so I
started looking
at this
computer and
I went out
and got
one,
I plugged
it in,
and plugged
everything up
and it
prompted
me,
hey,
lights are
on,
but nobody's
home,
I need
an operating
system.
So there I
got this
disk,
you know,
give a plug
to Mr.
Bill Gates,
it was a
Microsoft disk,
right?
Yeah,
sir.
Put it in
and started
downloading this
operating system.
If you've
ever downloaded
an operating
system,
it's not
lickety-split.
It takes
a little
while.
And then
it hit
me.
Oh,
man,
we get our
operating system
from our
deity.
Yes.
We get our
law from our
deity.
I'm not
talking about
traffic law,
I'm talking
about how
you reason,
what you
eat,
wear,
how you
keep time,
do commerce,
how you
raise a
family,
everything
comes from
your deity.
Absolutely.
In this
symbol,
I shall
conquer.
One side
is theocratic
military,
I mean,
correction,
monarchical
military.
The other
side is
theocratic
religious.
And so
when they do
the crossing
of the hands
of the Pharaoh,
what they're
doing is
that they're
giving you
a Sir
Bill Gates,
a knight of
the queen,
and therefore
that operating
system is
a system that
is dictated by
the queen of
rule.
Is that a
copy?
You can look
at it that way
if you so
choose to
download that
operating system,
but you've got
to look at
them all,
right?
Absolutely.
You've got to
understand where
they're coming
from.
Right.
So you get
your law from
your deity,
and here comes
somebody who
says,
well,
I don't have a
deity.
Okay,
you don't have a
deity.
All right,
that's fine.
Then do you
believe in the
laws of the
state?
Yes,
I do.
Well,
the state is
your god,
and April
1st is
your holiday.
Thank you
very much.
Next.
You see,
and I'm not
saying don't
believe in the
laws of the
state,
because you
can't really
believe in
anything.
You have
to know
them,
remember.
So what
happens is
if you read
your holy
writ,
all of them
pretty much
say,
if you
don't want
what's in
here,
we're going
to appoint
men,
and you're
going to
try
man's
law,
and see
how you
like that.
So when
you hear
about conspiracy
theories,
or man's
government
isn't,
you know,
what it
should be,
or they're
cool,
they shouldn't
be there,
they're not
legitimate,
this runs
the full
gamut.
Wait a
second,
they're
accommodating
you.
We,
as a
society,
worldwide,
have
abandoned
acknowledgment.
Forget
about following
any form
of rules
that come
from a
spiritual
nature.
We've
completely
abandoned it.
Total
apathy.
The opposite
of love
is not
hate.
It takes
a lot
of energy
to hate
someone.
The opposite
of love
is apathy.
We're
living in a
world where
the majority
of the people
are apathetic
to their
own scriptural
references.
I'm not
talking about
religion,
I'm not
talking about
going down
to the
temple,
or the
mosque,
synagogue,
or the
church.
Because
I've
never
gone to
mosque.
I've
never
gone to
the
mosque.
I've
never
gone to
mosque.
I've
never
gone to
the
synagogue.
And
I've
never
like
I've
never
gonna
do
it
like
that.
I've
never
gonna
teach
femininity
to
a
girl,
because
she's
and Yeehawks start seeing in this country they have a sacred document, okay?
Now, if George Washington is your deity, that's fine,
because if you go to the Capitol Rotunda and look up,
guess who's looking right back down at you sitting in a heavenly throne?
G.W., himself.
And if you don't believe me, go look it up.
You go into the Capitol building and it's a big round open area Rotunda
and you look up, there's a big painted dome.
And you got George Washington sitting in the throne with angels around him
and he's looking down at you.
Yeah, see, we can't even qualify as a nation in this country
because a nation is matriarchal and it means they're all related.
But now that we've got a damn father figure,
it's mama's baby but daddy's maybe.
So now that we got daddy's maybe,
we don't know who in the hell is part of this country
and so they call us a mouse and pot.
Right, now here you go.
We don't know anything anymore.
It's probably, you know, two years ago we spit shine jump boots
and we used what they call Lincoln boot polish.
And now you might as well call it shinola
because people today don't know shit from shinola
and I'm just going to say it plain out for you.
Now you take it and run with it from there.
Well, here you go.
If you read the document, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
and to establish justice.
Now hold on a second.
You got to go through this with a fine tooth comb.
You know, I mean, you're on this planet for what,
60, 70, 80 years?
People say, I don't have time.
Well, you're born naked and you die naked.
What do you got in between?
Time.
Don't ever let anybody tell you, especially you little ones,
you ain't got time for something.
That's all you've got in this particular incarnation.
Now, look at this thing called justice.
Just go look it up.
I'm not going to get into what it is,
but you will find it's a woman with scales
and it goes back to the Greeks.
They called her dike, D-I-K-E.
It spells like the word dyke.
Right? And if you could look at all,
you know, how you're brought to justice.
You have to serve justice.
Oh, yeah.
Now there's also a miscarriage of justice.
See, things, I mean, they're building everything up
and that's why you go to court.
They're praying.
If you ever read a private lawsuit,
the attorneys are praying to the court.
They're praying.
Now, but hold on a second.
If you keep reading the document down there,
keep getting in there, flip a couple of pages,
and it says the operation of this document
is the law of nations.
Now, when you go to the, let's say, for example,
they say we use the Constitution and the Bible.
Doesn't the ever living say?
What it, well, let's say, let's say this
without getting specific right now.
That don't do what the nations or the law of the nations.
Who are the law of the nations?
They usually translated the nations as Gentile.
It's the word goyim.
Or the Gentiles, another way, might be pagan.
In other words, the creator was frowning down on it.
Now, I'm not frowning down on anything that's written
in that particular document.
Because it's simply accommodating the people's perspective.
But we need to understand and comprehend.
Actually comprehend, that word understand
is a totally different subject.
But what's going on is we're not examining things closely.
You said earlier about the mother.
Okay, what do you know about DNA?
You can go through pages and hundreds of pages of DNA.
And I regret ever doing that.
And all you will find is all they really know for sure about DNA
is that we all have the same mother.
Okay, so mama seems to know something
that daddy doesn't know on earth.
So, you know, there's a family.
Mother, father and a son.
Son was growing up around 22 years old.
And the parents, you know, mama and papa said,
hey, you know, he's 22.
We've never seen him date a girl before.
I think it's about time he did.
You know, go out and meet someone to get married.
So father goes to the boy and says,
hey, actually young man in this case,
I want you to go out and meet yourself a nice girl.
Bring her here because it would be nice for you to get married.
And he says, okay, I'll do that, papa.
So he sends him out. He comes back a week later.
Brings in this nice looking girl.
Sits her down on the couch in the living room.
And, you know, daddy comes in.
He says, oh, no, son, you can't marry her.
He says, why not, daddy?
And he says, well, you see,
you can't marry her because she's your sister,
but your mama don't know it.
So don't tell your mama.
Okay, so sends her off a week later.
Comes in, another girl comes in.
He sits down on the couch.
Father comes running down.
He says, daddy, I brought another girl I'd like for you to meet her.
And he says, oh, no, son, you can't marry her either.
He says, why not?
He says, you see, she's your sister,
but your mama don't know it.
So, you know, he sends that girl off again.
And then the other girl off.
And, you know, a few days go by and mother asks him,
she says, what happened to those two nice girls you brought home?
And he says, oh, mom, you know, I really can't tell you.
You know, daddy told me not to tell you.
And he says, well, what did he tell you not to tell me?
And he says, well, he says I can't marry them
because they're my sisters and you don't know it.
And she said, oh, you go ahead and marry either one of them
that you might like the most,
because he ain't your daddy and he don't know it.
So, things are not as they appear to be.
Yeah, that's true.
At all.
Anyway, that was kind of maybe a long joke with a short punchline.
But moving forward,
your law comes from your deity.
And what I mean by your law, it's a reference point.
You know, who would go hire a carpenter who said,
I cut this board twice and it's still too short?
You need some kind of reference
and you need to know what you're doing with that reference.
People say, well, I don't believe in that.
And, well, I'll do whatever I want.
I say, okay, I'm building a house
and I need a countertop exactly 62 inches long.
You could call up someone on the telephone
and relay that information across the country
and they'll send you the countertop at 62 inches long.
Based on you having the same reference.
That your tape measures are all the same.
And what I found out is that all of these holy writs
that were from the deities of the world
all say the same thing.
So, when you start looking at the spiritual definition of these things,
there's a lot of confusion.
A lot of confusion.
I ask people,
what is the body, what is the soul, what is the spirit?
And I still haven't gotten a straight answer.
I ask someone, they say, okay, well, all right, hold on a second there.
You're telling me I have to be saved.
Can you tell me what I have to be saved from?
And if it's more than two or three words, you probably don't know.
Okay, well, you need to live under grace.
Okay, can you please just define grace?
Oh, okay, you don't know either.
They just can't define it.
So, if you start looking at the way these original texts were translated,
you're going to find out that there's a lot of confusion
even in the way they were translated.
And that's where I believe things were done on purpose.
Because if you have fleshy bodies here that know
there's more to what we've been told,
all you need to do is switch around a couple of concepts
the most basic ones, they'll take it as being,
well, that's the way it is, and they'll never figure it out.
And it's really, really, really simple.
And I've looked at all the texts, well, the three that I mentioned were four,
and they all share the same thing when you go to the original languages.
Now, when I say original languages, I mean the languages of preservation,
the way they're preserved today.
Before they were translated to English and all the other languages.
And the one that I've looked at and spent the most time on
is what people normally call the Bible or the Scriptures.
And I focused on that for a very simple reason.
It was the only one that I found that had the most detail.
When I say detail, people, places, and things.
And it also had the most law.
It was just pretty simple.
So that's why when you, for example, look at what Hollywood does,
they make movies about the Bible.
They make movies about, you don't see, well, you know,
supposedly it's a religious offense to make a movie about the Koran
because there are not supposed to be any images.
Okay, fine.
It just so happens that we're getting all these images of the Bible.
We're getting stories. Everybody's involved in it.
Hollywood, print media, I mean, it's about the Bible,
but they're not really, how accurate is it?
Well, you could read the text yourself.
And that's why I emailed you, Gary, and I said,
hey, how about we do a thing with the Strongs?
But we might do that, maybe not.
But if we start reading these texts and we see what we're being told about them,
it just ain't so.
Well, see, that's, I agree with you.
It's kind of like if you took Lothar Shalmapoose Cardinal,
elected Pope 600, called Muhammad,
and you went to his original teachings,
even prophesied in the Talmud of Emanuel, spelled with a J,
you would see that what he taught and done was entirely different
than what we know of as the Quran today.
Translated, basically, what, 60, 68 years after his death.
They always spin, twist, and turn everything
because we're dealing with a business model.
And we can go back to Luke 2, even in their King James,
and Tiberius taxed the whole world.
These yo-yos don't know.
They've been under tax and tribute,
and they want to go back and act civilly, Roman civil law.
They don't even understand the root of where in the hell they come from.
And so what I really wanted you to do was to get in here
and kind of blow their underwear off, you know?
Well, it's about time, but here's a simple thing.
You know, people talk about jurisdiction.
You know, jurisdiction.
Okay, jurisdiction.
Okay, and how it's gained.
It's gained in your mind.
Yes, it is.
It's gained in your mind, and here's the funny thing.
I was speaking to someone the other day,
and they're saying, well, you know,
well, you got to tell the people why they don't get it.
You know, and basically the conversation started out,
and I was like, okay, the people that don't get it
are the ones saying Happy New Year two weeks ago.
Yeah, they don't know when the time of the year is.
They were saying Merry Christmas a little bit before that.
You go on a lot of talk show calls, turn on your TV, newspaper,
go out your door, look how quiet it is on those days.
Say, I don't know what these people are using as a basis for it.
It's some kind of credit system they're running on
that I do not understand.
I do not stand under it.
I'm familiar with it, and in order to communicate with them,
for the past few years, I've raised some eyebrows.
When someone says, hey, are you going to meet me on Friday?
I said, well, yeah, I'll meet you on the day you call Friday.
But see, it rolls.
It's set by the sun, it's set by the moon,
and it's by the wobble of the planetoid aspect called the Earth.
Yes, I'm going to get into maybe a little bit of that aspect,
but the thing is, you know, I had a call,
and I'm on this call on a day you call Sunday, I tell people.
Okay, it's not Sunday.
No, it ain't.
There ain't no Monday, there ain't no Tuesday.
Now, here's a good example.
The timekeepers, the priests of time,
because you see, back in, through all your scriptural references,
when I say scripture, I'm talking about all of them,
your priest was managing your time.
So if somebody says they're managing time,
they're a priest by default.
If you read your scriptures,
and you had a physical ailment and you couldn't figure it out,
you went to the priest.
So if you go to someone today that, for a physical ailment,
by default, they're your priest.
You got the white robes.
Now, that's why I talk about something called image training.
You're controlled by images, like flashcards.
Whenever you see a doctor on TV, he better be wearing a white robe.
They always dress him up that way.
Now, okay, so now you're going to go and look at all your scriptures,
all of them, throughout all the cultures.
And if you got a problem with law,
or you don't know, you can't really, it's a real gray area,
you go to your priest.
So if you go to someone for law today, by default, they're your priest.
Now, this doesn't sound pretty,
because people are going to start saying,
well, wait a second, they're just this, they're not a priest.
Like, okay, so then what's a priest then today?
What's he teaching?
Well, the real priest is really their courthouse,
because that's where their law is rendered.
The yo-hoo, uh, yay-hoo, uh, called a cleric,
a, uh, minister, a, uh, uh, shit, a preacher,
is down there teaching them the bullcrap
that they want to hear to tickle their damn ears.
Well, hold on a second.
These people don't understand that no more.
They don't know what in hell they're doing.
And then if they need a healer up there, a putae,
they don't understand that this cat don't believe in that.
He doesn't believe in healing, or curing.
He believes in symptomology,
because there's more damn money in treating symptoms
than there is creating a cure.
He don't know nothing about the bomb of Gilead.
Right. Now, hold on, hold it right there, hold it right there.
When you read about the temple,
the function of the temple,
now, I'll tell you about the one in the Bible,
the one out there in Jerusalem.
Yeah, that's big talk.
What I found out about that,
it served one function.
It had two functions and three functions.
And there was a fourth, but it was minor.
Oh, yeah, but that...
The functions were, it was the court,
it was the place where you went to record a document,
and it was a university.
Yes, it was.
And alongside that center,
okay, were small little rooms that if you wanted to pray,
you would go and pray in private by yourself,
or your wife, or your husband,
or one other, or two other,
in private.
They had all these little rooms going around, hundreds of them.
Now, today, if you take the courthouse,
the records at the university,
and put them in one building,
you've got a temple.
Now, most major cities,
and even smaller cities,
have those features, but they're divided.
So, if the body is the temple,
and we're living in a place where the temple is divided,
do you see how this confusion comes in?
Oh, yes, because they're divided in their mind,
they cannot prevail.
Yes. Now, Christ said that the kingdom of heaven is within you.
Now, that word endos,
endos, E-N-T-O-S, is phonetically within you.
Technically, in Greek, that's not what it means,
within you, within your body.
He really, technically, the way it was preserved meant amongst you,
meaning it's fractional.
It's in pieces.
In other words, the things to come.
The temple that was there at the time had lost its usefulness
because the people's hearts were not made of flesh,
they were made of stone.
And the irony there is this.
How many people today know
that halide group elements on the...
These are chemicals, periodic table of elements.
Halide groups would be fluoride,
bromine that's used in your flour,
and chlorine that's used in your water, all those groups.
Go look at your halide groups.
Those things calcify the blood and harden the arteries.
Now, isn't calcium a stone?
Our hearts are being turned to stone as we speak.
Yeah, and your pineal gland...
And your gland...
...that's the angel at pineal.
It's calcified.
Now they do not have the doorway, the gateway to the Creator,
which is in their own brain.
And they don't understand that.
And if I may be single, they have to open that aspect
because rods, cones, and water, vitreous humor,
is in that one pineal gland,
not the blamed-ass two eyes that they got in front of their head,
in front of their ears,
because they don't understand what's really in their head.
They have 22 letters.
So putting chlorine in water ain't got nothing to do with bugs
because the bugs come back, and so does the bromine.
You kill certain bugs,
and you give rise to others that are more dangerous.
Yeah, because it's the way they think.
Right, and the fluoride ain't got nothing to do
with making your teeth stronger.
No, it doesn't.
Even though Deep Smith County...
Go ahead.
Okay, so what I'm trying to make a quick reference is,
is these biblical references, just for simple terminology,
are trying to give you a hint.
And when you go through the Bible,
you'll see the same thing is being repeated over and over
if you pick a topic.
And you will see what is meant by a heart of stone.
You see, and you start saying,
how are our hearts being turned to stone?
And I just wanted to give that example
because if you're reading a holy writ, no matter what it is,
if it doesn't have a practical use in your life,
it means nothing.
Absolutely. It's got to be a living thing.
It's got to be living.
A language, if no one is speaking a language,
that language is considered dead.
Yes.
I can't take and heal until I step inside of them,
see what's wrong with them,
and initiate an electromagnetic flux
that will cause a change in their physical body
and they'll understand it with their comprehension.
My wife had run across a book I was reading one time
and Steve would give it to me
and it said how to screw any woman out there, whatever it is.
And boy, she was upset as hell.
I mean, she said,
what are you doing?
What are you reading this for?
I said, I screw them all.
She said, what?
She said, what do you mean by that?
I said, how in the hell do you think I heal?
If I do not implant the thought of healing in their mind,
how in the Sam hell do you expect me to cause them to be healed?
I fuck them all.
I just don't do it according to the laws of the king.
Well, the restrictional aspect...
She understood what I was saying
and so I've been screwing them all, as the fellow said, ever since then
because that's how I heal.
And I teach them to do that.
I mean...
Well, look at your water for a second.
...yourself.
Do not limit yourself
or what the hell your preacher, your minister, your judge,
your whatever in the hell come up with.
They don't know shit from Shia LaBeouf.
One of them, you get it on your feet,
get it on the carpet,
your wife will whip your ass and run you down the road.
One of them, you can polish your boots and they'll look damn fine.
Now, I realize that's not the normal way of looking at it,
but since you want to get in this game,
I'll bust the door open for you
because I'm just an ass-kicker from the get-go.
Go ahead.
Hey, well, when you look at water,
water's got a spiral in nature.
In German, your spinal column is called the spiral column.
In German.
It's not the spinal column, it's a spiral column
because everything in nature follows that mode of geometry.
Why is everyone so impressed with a bunch of acid
in a spiral form in the nucleus of a cell?
They call it DNA.
Ooh, this DNA.
All these things are going to happen, I'm going to change your DNA.
Ain't no evidence of that.
It's just acid, you know.
Why do you think they say you've descended from monkeys?
Because, see, you descend, you're lower than the monkey.
Do you get the language that's being used here?
Yes, I do.
You keep going, brother, I just...
You have similar DNA to a monkey,
which is now dinonucleic acid,
whatever fancy name they're putting on that.
There's a fellow named Lipton that does a lot of work on that
and he got in some trouble.
I don't know if he's doing all right,
but he has actually mentioned they've taken DNA out of cells
and the cells are just fine.
Yeah, Bruce Lipton, that's who you're talking about.
Yeah, okay.
So, I mean, what's the big deal about that?
Now, they're missing the part of water.
You know, water is not H2O.
And you tell that to people
and they run around screaming in their head,
well, take some water with electrolysis,
you know, they use that for breaking up water into hydrogen and oxygen.
And go ahead, try to reduce all that water into hydrogen and oxygen.
You can't.
It never, no one has ever succeeded doing that.
It ends up turning into deuterium and tritium
and other compounds of water
that are very effective in absorbing radiation.
That's why they use it in their nuke plants.
So, now if you take the, let's go the other way.
Let's take some hydrogen gas and some oxygen gas,
put it together, bam, you get a lot of energy being released
and you get some water vapor.
When it condenses down, that's water.
Okay, well, do me a favor and drop that on a concrete sidewalk
and come back in two hours and tell me what you see.
You see a hole in the concrete.
So, water is not H2O.
It appears to be H2O.
So, how do we keep the water healthy?
Well, if you don't want to study that, I tell people,
if you don't want to study what water really is
and you don't want to get on the technical aspects
or the engineering aspects, go get yourself a chicken.
Go grow a garden.
Go stand by a natural river or a natural stream or a brook and observe it.
And what you will see, if you have the ability to see,
you will see things that cannot be described.
And this information is not being held by the high priests
in your academic centers,
because if you go to your academic center right now,
if you don't worship at the altar that they built,
you're given the boot, if you get what I mean.
All of these academic centers build an altar and you bow down to it.
If you don't bow down to it, you're not welcomed.
What you will find when you look at nature is that fish don't swim.
Fish are swum.
Birds don't fly. Birds are flown.
In other words, these natural living creatures
are made a certain way that when they react,
they change their environment around them.
They move around them to a frictionless state
and they simply move into a vacuum.
If anyone wants to do some research on the way one can think along these lines,
do you ever see some, for example, in the news,
you know, the Chinese or the Europeans just built this 300 mile an hour
monorail maglev train.
Wow, that's so fast. It's so wonderful.
Okay, if you think that's so fresh and hot,
go research this guy named Beach and it's spelled just like the sandy beach.
And he was one of the founders of Scientific American.
And back in 1864, he built a tunnel underground in New York
and he built a train that was designed to go 700 miles per hour.
And this is in 1864.
And they did succeed with the design.
I don't know if they ever got it up to 700 miles per hour.
But what they did was they made a round tunnel
and a round train car with a one inch gap.
And the way they powered the train or moved the train through the tunnel
was using a steam turbine to create a vacuum on one end of it
to suck the train forward.
And why did he do that?
Because he knew that air enters a vacuum at 700 miles per hour.
So when you have a fish or a bird,
they're actually creating a vacuum around their bodies
in the medium that they're in and the inverse square rule does not apply to them.
Inverse square rule basically with airplanes is that
if you want to double your speed, you need four times the energy.
So how about making an airplane or a boat that creates a vortex
with a little bit of suction in front of it so you have no resistance,
so you're actually being sucked forward.
And this technology exists today, but people don't know about it.
So the water acts the same way.
It's healthiest in certain conditions.
Water at 39 degrees or 4 degrees Celsius is at its most dense state.
If you lower the temperature, it starts to expand.
If you raise the temperature, it starts to expand.
That's where it's healthiest state.
Now if you start vortexing the water
and you start doing it in the proper fashion
as it's done in nature with the absence of light and the absence of air,
and you get your velocities and you have your geometries being,
for example, an egg-shaped vessel,
when that vortex in that temperature of 39 degrees or 4 degrees Celsius,
which by the way, coincidentally 39 degrees is what most refrigerators are set at,
if you get a high enough velocity at that temperature,
you'll notice that oxygen becomes aggressive at high temperatures
and hydrogen is passive.
But at low temperatures such as 39 or 4 degrees Celsius,
oxygen is passive and hydrogen becomes aggressive.
So now if you've got some chlorine in the water or fluoride or anything like that
and you've got your vortex kicking,
the hydrogen becomes aggressive, bonds with your chlorine and you get HCl,
which is hydrochloric acid in a small amount instead of chlorine.
And you can buffer that water and now you've got a way to get rid of toxins
and poisons in water without using other chemicals
or large amounts of filtration equipment you have to throw away.
So if you want to do something to your water
or you want a very simple way to filter water,
is you can go get yourself two Brita pitchers,
there's no plumbing involved, those pourable pitchers,
and go ahead and pour your tap water into one pitcher,
put it in the fridge till it gets to 39.
And when it gets to 39, you get yourself,
you pour it out of that first pitcher into the second pitcher,
so now you're filtering it at 39 degrees.
And then you store your water in an egg-shaped vessel.
And the easiest way to get an egg-shaped vessel would be a flower vase,
one that has a flat bottom on the outside but it comes to a point on the inside.
Go ahead and store your water in there and when you put your water in there,
do me a favor, get yourself either a copper rod or a wooden spoon
and go ahead and spin it up to the right, let it vortex to the right
and then go ahead and spin it up to the left, both directions.
And if you want to do stuff with a tuning fork or put some stuff in there
or minerals or whatever, you do it then.
And what you've done is you've restored water's natural body.
You see, what happens is man ignores the way things move in nature,
so he says, hmm, let's just pump the water through a straight pipe.
The water wants to meander.
See, that's why rivers meander left and right.
When the water hits the right turn bend, it folds over to the left
and you get a longitudinal vortex,
which is a fancy way of saying a tornado laying down on its side.
And that's how a natural river processes the elements,
just like I mentioned earlier.
When you start straightening out your rivers,
you start getting a standing wave, the temperature goes up,
the oxygen becomes aggressive,
it starts eating away whatever the material of your pipes are made of or your canals.
And it also grows pathogens.
Now, you know you're doing water, let's say for example spring water,
from a natural spring, if you were to freeze it,
look at it under a microscope, it would seem very amorphous in shape.
It would just look like a frozen amoeba.
But if you take water that is oxygenated, for example,
and ready for breeding pathogens and you freeze it,
you'll get these beautiful crystal snowflakes.
So do the research on your own and figure out what's really going on
as opposed to what we've been told.
Because the alternatives that are put out in front of us
are not really alternatives, they're part of sometimes the main agenda.
And the main agenda actually is the alternative to the natural,
because we don't want to observe the natural seemingly,
or it's been hidden for so long we forget.
Wood is another wonderful substance for using as a pipe.
The National Hydrological Society has done research
with wooden stave pipes versus plastic and metal,
and they found that the degree of pathogens and the resistance of the water
was always less in the wooden pipes.
That's why sometimes you'll read in major cities there's a water main break
and they'll pull out a wooden pipe that's 150 years old
and everyone's laughing saying,
Oh, look at those people that were so dumb making wooden pipes.
Were they really? Water has to breathe.
So if you study Victor Schauberger,
you might get some really good insight in water.
You see that everybody's got a piece of the puzzle.
The kingdom is here, but it's in pieces.
The kingdom actually, the world will be redone,
but most people are not ready to hear how things are going to happen
and when they're going to happen.
Because when you read things, for example, in a holy writ,
you will see that you're entering into a trust agreement
and it's a private trust agreement.
That's why, for example, if you know a Native American,
he will say things to a certain point.
If you know, for example, someone who's a Denali,
people refer to them as Navajo here.
And I'll ask a man who is of the Denali,
Dinele means people.
He'll say, Tell me what you know and we'll get to a certain point.
And he says, I can't tell you about this
because I haven't gotten permission from my elders.
Wow! So this secret, this ancient knowledge is in a private trust.
Do you see where I'm going with this?
We've heard a lot about these trusts all the time.
Oh, yeah.
Information from the spiritual world is usually held in trust as well.
Look at your prophets and your prophetesses.
And what usually happens when a prophet or a prophetess
goes out and speaks to people, they want to kill them, right?
So when you're speaking to a group of people
and they like what you're saying, you better stop and say,
Wait a second, I better check myself. Maybe I'm not saying it right.
Anybody ever stop and think about that?
It's called ear-tickling. People want ear-tickling.
I could hear someone in the background.
So if you're speaking about spiritual matters
and people are reaching to pull out a gun and shoot you
or run you over with their car, you're probably doing it right.
It doesn't mean you are. And it's a very tough place to be.
But I want to go back maybe to the spiritual aspect about it.
I wanted to interject that about water,
because go look up what water really is.
And you'll start learning about geometry and how we've gotten away.
And this is all because we've lost contact with what the creation is.
And if we've lost contact with the creation,
how are we supposed to get even to the creator?
He's got beings around him to stop you before you get there.
If you look at anyone in power, there's layers that you have to get to.
If you're messing up the creation, how are you going to expect to go to the creator?
So here's the message that I'd like to give so far,
is that law comes from your deity.
Now, I've chosen the ever-living the way he is described in the Bible,
and the message that he gave through that.
And I explained the reason why I've chosen to study that
is because I found the most amount of detailed information there.
It doesn't make someone else's work invalid.
But if you choose anything else to study,
you must prove that what is written in that holy writ
is workable in your life and is workable in time.
Absolutely.
You've got to live it, you know.
Now, one thing I've noticed in the spiritual world,
that 1,000 years of our existence is one day for them.
Absolutely.
So when someone says, well, that's really old stuff,
and you look at, you know, it was given, let's say, 3,000 or 4,000 years ago,
how is it old when it was just given to us four days ago from their perspective?
What makes it so old?
They're not used to looking in time like these people look in time.
And this is the thing.
I teach people to heal because it's a formula.
It's a law.
And once you understand the law,
there is no time, there is no space, there is no damn distance.
It's instantaneous.
But these people don't believe and understand and think that
because of the bullshit that's taught by these damn frappin' ass preachers, ministers, clerks, etc.,
because they don't want you to know who and what the hell you really are.
You don't know.
You're never going to be the deity that you are supposed to be in matter, space, and time
because you cannot identify with it.
You can't ascend to the heavenly realm because your ass don't even know you come from there.
Yes, that goes back to the notion of what is the spirit, what is the soul, and what is the body.
We have those three aspects.
And I have yet to get a straight definition,
and sometimes you just got to lay it out and let people see it for themselves.
Oh, absolutely.
And this concept of heaven and hell.
There's a lot of talk about heaven and hell, I've noticed.
And even in the translations from the Bhagavad Gita, the Mahabharata, and the Koran are not correct.
And especially your KJV or your NIV or your whatever.
How can it be so blunt in your face,
and they go ahead and translate and put a word in that is not there?
Yeah, it's kind of like somebody made a statement.
Way too much anger.
Well, you better go back and read about your Messiah, your teacher.
He braided a cord, whipped their ass, and run them out of the temple.
And the scripture does say, be angry and sin not.
I can whip your ass and straighten you up and not violate the law if I understand it.
Because if I can do that, then I can wake your lethargic ass out of your damn sleep,
and you can be the sleeper that awaketh.
Oh, hallelujah.
It ain't frustration, it's the damn application of the formula of instigation.
You gotta handle all that, young folks.
You know what, I think they're drinking too much milk of amnesia.
Oh, we're on the same page.
I just love being a butt kicker.
That's why in the hell I was sent here.
We're on the same page.
Yeah, it's milk of amnesia.
So, you know, if you look at what's going on, this concept of heaven and hell,
you know, here's the thing.
I run into these folks all the time and say,
well, if you don't accept Jesus Christ, you're gonna burn in hell.
And I said, wait a second, wait a second.
I just ran into another fellow a few minutes ago, and he says,
he said that Jesus Christ said that I could do anything I want
because he washed away all my sins with his blood.
Okay.
And then I just ran into another fellow over here who said that, you know,
well, you know, you've got to see my point.
How many of them are there?
You know, if you start reading scripture, you're like, wait a second.
Where did these folks get this stuff?
Yeah.
Where did these poor folks get this stuff?
So that's why there are special, if you read Malachi chapter two,
you know, you're going to get quite a sense.
I've had, I used to be on some conference calls a few years ago,
and some pastors would call me in private and say,
I want you to come and speak to my congregation.
And I said, whoa, why?
He says, because you know a lot about the Bible.
And I said, are you sure you want me to come and speak to your congregation?
He says, absolutely.
We're going to fly you out to Dallas and this and that.
We couldn't teach them in their congregation.
Yeah.
So I tell these guys.
There ain't no way in hell for me to tell the secret to the masses.
Yes.
Well, this is the point.
And I say, well, I asked the pastor or the priest or whatever.
I said, do you have a Bible?
And they laugh, of course, you know, because how could you be a pastor and not have a Bible?
I said, well, I want you to do me a favor and a promise.
And he says, okay, I'll do what you tell me to do.
And I said, well, I want you to read Malachi chapter two.
What verse?
Just start reading Malachi chapter two.
When you had enough, hang up and call me back.
And then we'll make the arrangements for me to come out.
And none of them have ever called me back.
None of them.
No, because when they read Malachi, they know it's talking about them.
It's talking.
It's very, very, very, very specific.
You can't get more specific than that.
So that's what I'm saying.
I've stopped speaking to people that adhere to a particular belief.
When someone says to me again, well, I don't believe what he does or I don't believe what you do.
I say, I don't care about what you believe.
Tell me what you know, because what you believe cannot help me.
But what you know might.
I agree with you.
What you know, what you are doing.
Just like they're telling you.
Well, I don't believe this.
I don't believe that.
So what do you want to die?
You don't want to or do you want to get well?
Well, I want to get well.
Well, I don't do what you believe.
And if I do what you believe, your ass is going to die.
Now, if you'll listen to me, I'll tell you and I'll show you and you'll get well.
Which one do you want?
You know what they always tell me?
Show me what it is you got.
And so I do and they get well.
And then they go back and they say, I know you did it.
I just don't understand it.
I said, well, which one do you want to get?
You want to learn?
You want to understand?
You want to live?
You want to be healed and healthy?
Or do you sorry ass want to die?
They got a graveyard out there and there's three or four cats as well and dig a hole.
And they ready to shove your ass in there.
Now, which one do you want?
You know, it's amazing how much of an attitude adjustment they get.
Well, again, you go to your deity and if you're doing it right, there's going to be provisions.
And what you're going to notice is it takes a gift.
For example, when the Christ turned the water into wine, did he really?
If you look at the story very, very closely, he was told to do that.
And he said, wait a second, if I do that, they will know what I'm able to do.
So they're all in agreement.
So what actually happened, his mother said, okay, he agreed.
So do exactly as he tells you to do.
So they were obedient.
They would say, okay, tell us what we want done.
Exactly as he tells you to do.
It's not this mystical, magical stuff that nobody knows.
The clerk, the Roman church, the damn government tells you, it's do what he tells you to do.
Oh, God, I just love you.
You see the deity aspect of it.
So what they did was they went and fetched these large cisterns of water.
And there's still water.
And they poured it into a cup.
It's still water.
And they give it to the host's mouth.
They're still bringing him water.
He puts it to his mouth and now it's wine.
And he says, wow, typically we bring out, you see, the best wine.
You see how the story goes.
So there's something going on here.
That's why I tell people, if you want to see what's going on, it's all, you've got all the equipment.
You just don't know how to use it.
It's six sparkings of water.
Six sparkings.
Six is the number of man tripled.
Outer court, middle court, motosa court.
Six is the number of the feminine bab aspect.
And until you impregnate her with life and possess her, as the creator told us from the beginning,
your sorry ass is going to die because you're just an ignoramus.
It's just that damn simple.
All right, here's the other thing.
When you read in any of the scriptures, where does it say to keep women down?
Nowhere.
Matter of fact, Little Al found a research paper today.
And I sent it out to everybody on this call.
And it was talking about Mary the Magdala, Magdalene.
She was really the chief apostle because the men were so damn upset that the woman understood.
But yet the woman, feminine, female, iron male, is symbolic of wisdom, Sophia.
She could not find a place among men, the male aspect of the Vatican, the political aspect.
But she was the teacher of the house.
And our women have got to go back to being the witches, the wise women, the true teachers.
And when they get off their ass and raise up and start teaching, then our children will raise up.
And then when our men understand what those women are, instead of beating and brow-beating and trying to beat them down,
then damn it, we will all rise up.
Because it is a two-fold aspect that creates the third aspect.
Well, the man does this.
I said, have you ever seen a rooster spread his wings and protect the chicks?
He said, well, no.
I said, well, what does?
He said, the hen.
I said, she spreads her wings and protects the brood.
That's right, hen.
That's why she's called the nail, the hook of the tent.
And when you get your head out of your ass, rectus, as Bograts would say it,
get a plexotomy so you can see, you'll understand, you'll quit beating these women down like this damn Roman cult has,
and you'll come back to power.
Our women are worth something.
Well, the Christ even said, I would like to be like a hen spreading her wings over her little chicks to the Pharisees,
but you would not let me.
Well, if you read in Psalms 111, wisdom is what?
A she.
If you read in Ecclesiastes, wisdom is what?
She is wisdom.
Okay, shekhinah.
She-khinah.
The feminine spirit aspect in nine applications.
Seven chakras revealed.
Two hidden.
Oh, my.
She's called the Holy Ghost.
They tried to make a damn man out of her, but she is a woman.
Yeah, it ain't got nothing.
She is a teacher, the tent, the nail, the hook of the tent called the valve.
Go read it in the book of Jasher in case you people don't get a grand on it.
Well, why do you think this earth is in the milky way?
The gal, galactic, literally means milk.
Gal in Hebrew, gal in Greek.
Oh, shit, I love this guy.
You're in the milky way, the galactic galaxy, that's all milk, milk, milk.
You wonder why we're on the milk?
We're on the land of milk and honey.
Maybe later I'll tell you what I found out about honey.
But the aspect, we have so, we've become apathetic.
And again, I've got nothing against the powers that be.
They're simply accommodating the people.
Yes, they are.
They are simply accommodating them.
It is up to each one of us.
If we say something, that word believe or to believe is a killer.
It is a killer.
And there's examples of that in scripture as well.
While I was on another call and I was more sober, so to speak,
on the aspects of the information,
and I always bring up the Exodus on Cecil B. DeMille,
all the movies that you see of Christ being crucified, for example.
Oh, yeah.
Those things, when you read scripture and go look at those movies,
I'm not talking about glancing at it.
Or having it read to you.
When you actually sit down and read it,
you're going to say those things never happened that way.
And they didn't happen for those reasons.
You know, and that's why I mentioned to have a,
if we wanted to go down that path,
you know, I could show you, for example,
the various different things that are just right there that we just don't see.
Okay.
Can I interject?
You see, there's some of them that don't understand that in this country,
Elisha is called a male.
But over in other countries where they have not cornered this information,
Elisha is a woman.
Just like Micah is Micah.
And they don't understand that these women were great prophetesses.
But they have left out the teacher, the tent of wisdom, knowledge, and understanding.
A child was raised and trained up in the tent of his mother.
She taught him the law of the impregnating aspect of the creator,
the male aspect called father.
And these people don't understand this.
Washington is not the father of a great nation.
Hell, the old idiom.
Mama's baby.
Papa's maybe.
Well, they provide a mama.
It's called Columbia or Liberty or Justice.
And they're providing both aspects of it.
But if you start researching the history, the secular history,
and the structure of what they're providing the people,
and you go way back,
go to a university that's got some old, old books,
and look up your Chaldean Hebrew history,
back in those Mesopotamian days,
and you will see the rituals of human sacrifice that they did back then
are still prevalent today.
And they're disguised in holidays and birthday celebrations,
in toys.
And we're focusing on the death aspect.
Nature has both sides.
You have life and you have death.
You have life-giving energies and you have death-giving energies.
When you look at the life-giving energies,
the big end always comes out first.
And when you look at the death-giving energies,
you have a sharp point.
Case in point, in the death side,
which most people only know,
a snake has teeth, a viper fangs,
and they're hollow and a fluid is ejected once it goes under your skin.
Like a hypodermic needle.
Do you see a spear?
It has a pointy tip.
What's the purpose of a spear or the point on a sword
or the point of an arrow?
I'm not talking about using it to tickle your back with.
You see, the bee's got a stinger.
It comes to a sharp point and it's like a hypodermic needle.
You see the reference?
Okay, now let's go to the life-giving aspect.
The big end always comes out first.
When a woman bears a child,
what is it called when the head doesn't come out first?
Boy, we've got problems.
We've got a break.
Yeah, we've got to have...
Okay, when you plant your garden,
you get your seeds in the right depth,
nice and cozy, and you water it.
What do you see popping out the sprout?
You see the big end come out first, right?
Right, the head always comes out.
Now when a chicken lays an egg,
the big end comes out first.
When a raindrop, a drop of water, is falling through the sky,
the big end of the drop is going towards the resistance.
I see it.
See, so in life-giving energies, the big end goes first.
You can look at the male anatomy.
You can look at the female anatomy.
Yep.
Okay, if a woman's uterus is in the shape
of an egg, okay?
Now here's the thing.
They put out all these things, for example,
just to test you.
It's in society all the time.
Just to test you to see if you're getting information
and you're sure.
And when I say getting information,
not what to believe in.
They got this thing called
what came first, the chicken or the egg?
And I've seen academics use that.
So we don't know.
It's like the chicken or the egg thing.
I'm like, that is the most foolish question
I've ever heard once I started reading scriptures.
The chicken came first.
How do you know?
Well, if you show me a blue egg,
I'll see that's not a chicken egg.
That's a robin's egg.
And if you show me an egg that's so large
it fits in the palm of my hand,
well, that's got to be an ostrich egg.
Do you see how simple?
You know, why did the chicken cross the road?
Because someone built a road on the darn farm?
You know, or what came first,
the chicken or the egg?
Well, today would be the chicken farmer, wouldn't it?
Because chickens won't do too good in the wild today.
No, they won't.
Okay, so here's the other thing.
I want to go back to time.
Okay, so here are your months, all right?
They've got all their pagan gods
and here we get to the seventh month
and they're calling it September, which is proper.
Septim means seven.
Octo is eight, like octagon.
Novo is nine.
December, decimal, deca is ten.
So how do they get off calling December the 12th month?
November, you see, the 11th, when it means nine.
October, which means eight.
They call it the 10th month.
And September is seven.
Yeah, they go back to them.
They're calling it the ninth.
What did Caesar and Augustus do when they screwed time?
Well, this is what they did.
They were following the sun.
There's a certain aspect of if the sun doesn't rise,
we're all screwed.
We're all going to die.
So we've got to focus on the sun.
And go ahead and look at your friends
that everybody thinks they're your friends, your Mayans.
Oh, they love the Mayan calendar.
These guys worked on a base 20 system, OK?
It was completely different.
And as a matter of fact, go study their society
and look at what their pyramids were used for.
You want to go down that line?
OK, fine.
That's OK.
I don't know much about them, and I don't
want to know much about them.
Well, in reality, in reality, let me take that for them.
That's why I'm bringing this up.
I'm playing it.
There's a wheel within the wheel.
And Ezekiel is telling you about that because Ezekiel's
grandmother, an Aaronite Levitical priest himself,
his grandmother was Maya.
And that's the Temple of Maya.
And if you take that temple, it is the exact layout
of the Book of Ezekiel.
It's ankle deep, knee deep, hip deep, and water to swim in.
His daddy was a cat called Buzi in the Book of Ezekiel.
You know him as the Guatama Buddha.
He walked in the middle path.
He understood the three aspects of the cross
and Golgotha, the place of the skull,
the 22 bones of the cranium.
And he knew that the right and left hemispheres
had to be brought into subjection to the higher aspect
of divine law.
And that is what they are not teaching in our scripture.
And our damn preachers don't know shit from Shinoah.
Well, that would be a different aspect.
One way to look at it, and that would be, again,
I'm sort of adhering to the text because I see
a straight flow through it.
And your interjection is,
I've got nothing.
If that works for you, that's fine.
Well, it does, because I can't heal if I don't understand it.
Correct.
Now, back with the time...
To do the same thing, I have to teach them to do it.
Okay, so when you look at your time...
Nature means something.
And nature has a law.
And nature is under a higher law.
And when you understand that law of creation,
there is nothing that will be withheld from you.
Now, we're rising to that level.
And you're damn good at what you're doing,
because with the etymological references,
oh, man, I wish you'd get into all the stuff
I heard you on Angela's call.
Okay, well, all right.
So when you look at the time...
It'll make them go to thinking.
That's why I love you,
and that's why I really wanted you,
is because you're gonna make these people think.
And if they don't think,
they will not lift their lethargic butt
out of the place of destruction.
They've got to learn to reason.
And that's why you were so unique.
And that is why I wanted you.
And that is exactly what Angela was telling you.
Get in there, click butt, and take some serious names.
Hell, you got the program?
You the sniper, start popping the cap.
Wake the folks up.
Let's do maybe a little bit on time.
We need the meat instead of the milk.
We need something we can chew on.
Well, do you want me to give a quick proof
on what time is in terms of keeping time?
Or do you want me to show you how to define
what the soul, the spirit, and the body really is?
Yeah, get it on, Bubba, get it on.
All right, let's go with time.
Get out there.
You know, we're able to stand up and, you know, it's not a big...
All right, here you go with time.
Okay, so they're telling you right in front of your face.
Now, if you start going out screaming
that September's really the seventh month,
they got a place for you.
You know, it's either behind bars or in a bar.
You know, and these things I see in a way,
they're left in place to kind of see who's waking up.
Because, see, when you hold a big hammer,
everything looks like a nail, right?
And the nail that sticks up from the floor gets pounded down.
So these things are going to be revealed to everyone.
Everyone will know these things,
but it's still right in front of us.
So if we start looking at time,
and you want to look at your functions of time,
you've got your years and your months,
you've got your weeks and your days.
One of the core elements to kind of see what's going on
is get your months down.
Because once you get your months down,
you get your weeks down.
And then the days and the years are much simpler.
So when you look at the word month, okay,
if you look at the etymological roots of it,
it came from the Germanic word mund, M-O-N-D-E,
which sounds very much like moon.
Now, if you ever heard the Latin term, the fin de mund,
which means the end of the world,
they're not talking about the end of the world
because the world, there's a different name for the world,
it's terra, is the world, I mean the earth.
The world means society when they say the end of the world,
and your society is based on the moon.
They're saying the moon has something to do with it.
And you hear about all this title research and all this stuff.
Okay, well, so when they say fin de mund,
it's not the end of the world, it's the end of the moon.
Okay, so what's going on?
Well, the creator says the seventh day is to be set apart.
That means that one-seventh of your time
is no commerce, no work.
When I say work, I'm not talking about mowing your lawn,
I'm talking about going to what you do for work.
And the priests were exempt from this,
because when you're a priest, there's a fellow saying,
well, you know, I'm having a problem keeping the Sabbath.
I'm like, didn't he make us kings and priests?
What day did the priests take off?
Oh, you're right, I see.
You see, so when you take that priestly or kingly position,
you're working all the time.
But the Sabbath, everyone understands that,
okay, we're supposed to take that day off.
Okay, well, when does your month begin?
Now, a simple example would be,
well, let's look at the Battle of Jericho.
Okay, now they get out of Egypt,
and they go all the way around.
If you look at all the zigzag paths they took,
they took the long way to get to that part
of what was called Canaan.
And they approached it from the east, all right?
And they marched around it for seven days.
And on the seventh day, they attacked.
And people say, well, see, that's a biblical anomaly,
because attacking is work.
And they basically pillaged it.
So you see, there's a Sabbath anomaly there.
I said, nope, there isn't.
Because they started on the first day of the month.
Now, the first day of the month, in reference to Scripture,
is the first day of the month, period.
The next day, or the second day of the month,
is the first day of your first week.
So when they started on the first day of the month,
day two is day one, and so on and so forth.
You see, day three is day two of the week,
but third day of the month.
That's why when you read in Scripture,
it says on the 11th day of the fifth month.
That has nothing to do with your weeks.
Your month count is your month count.
Your first day of the month is the first day of the month.
And you get 12 or 13 first day of the months.
So they marched on the seventh day,
was the sixth day of the week, but the seventh day of the month.
It was the seventh day of the second month.
So they attacked Jericho, besieged it,
and then they had their Sabbath.
So when you see the new moon,
and I'm going to explain what the new moon is,
because it ain't what you think, scripturally.
The new moon is your first day of the month.
The next day is the first day of your first week,
but your time is measured by saying,
by using the day of the month, just like they do today.
And here's a simple anomaly.
When you look at your calendar, let's say,
pick a day like, you know, September 15th.
This year it might be on a Tuesday,
but last year it was on a Wednesday.
Next year it might be on a Thursday.
What's going on here?
Is September 15th a Tuesday, a Wednesday, or a Thursday?
It's neither.
Now who is your timekeeper here?
Who is your priest in this part of the world?
Well, if you look them up, it's called the Naval Observatory.
You go to their website,
and they'll tell you we only count days off of the Julian calendar.
And you can go to the website yourself
and research Julian and Gregorian calendars
on the Naval Observatory,
and they will tell you that we only count days,
and weeks, and months, and years
are nothing but arbitrary notions.
Oh, so your rulers have done away with Sabbaths,
and months, and years, and everything.
It's right there in front of you.
Just go.
There's no specific link or anything.
Anybody can search the Naval Observatory, Gregorian,
or Julian calendar, and you shall see that.
Now, if you read in...
So when is it the first day of the month,
and what is the new moon?
Well, real simple, when you say new moon,
you go to the Naval Observatory, and it's that dark moon, okay?
It's new.
Well, is it really?
And if you look at what's called the Jewish or Hebraic calendar,
they'll say it's the dark moon.
But is that scriptural?
He says in Genesis that he created the lights in the heaven
for keeping the monads, the times, the seasons.
Okay, then he made the lesser one and the greater one,
one to rule the day and one to rule the night.
They're both the same size.
It's just one is the 2 million watt light bulb,
the other one's a 200 watt light bulb,
if you look at it in your Hebrew.
And I was going to go over that strictly in the text,
but I might as well just say it forward.
Now, the eastern, the golden gate is facing the east.
And Ezekiel, he says, when on the new moon,
you open the eastern gate.
Where does the full moon rise?
In the east.
And it's exactly the same size as the sun.
The disk of the moon when it's full
is the same size as the disk of the sun when it's rising.
And it comes up on the opposite gate depending on the season.
Where the sun rises in the winter,
the moon rises in the summer.
And they switch places gradually through the year.
And that's another way of getting into your equinoxes.
But your full moon is your new moon.
And here's your other way to look at it.
When they left Egypt,
they left on the 14th day of the month,
going on the 15th, okay?
So, when they left Egypt,
it says very specifically in Exodus
that he gave them a pillar of smoke by day
and a pillar of fire by night to give them light.
Now, in the middle of your month,
every month for me,
around the 15th or 14th of the month,
the sky is dark.
Now, why would you give them a pillar of fire
to give them light if it's a full moon
in the middle of the month,
if you use the dark moon as your new moon?
That just doesn't make any good horse sense to me.
And if you're reading your Psalms,
I think it's 81,
he says on the new moon,
the full moon blow the trumpet.
So, it's the full moon because you see
he doesn't work in the dark.
He brings things out into the light.
So, you wonder why everybody's doing the opposite
and you wonder why we're having all these problems.
So, now, what you will also see
what lines up really well
is your first Sabbath is your first quarter,
your first half waning moon.
Your second Sabbath,
your first Sabbath being on the eighth day,
then you get another seven days.
Because the first Sabbath is on the eighth day
because you got the first day of the month plus seven.
Your second Sabbath is on the 15th,
which is what they call the new moon,
which is actually the dark moon.
And your third Sabbath
is on your waxing half moon.
And your fourth Sabbath comes right before
your full moon.
Because also you'll see the Sabbaths,
when the Sabbaths are over,
they're either going to be half full
or precisely black or precisely full.
So, the way you would do your count
is if it's the first day of the month,
it's the first day of the month,
second day of the month,
third day of the month and so on.
But the second day of the month
is when you start your week count.
Now, you go all the way down.
So, your Sabbaths are on the eighth of the month,
the 15th, the 22nd and the 29th.
Okay, here's the 29th day of the month.
This is the last Sabbath.
But it doesn't mean you're going to have
29 days in your month.
You might have 30, you might have 31
because it's observational.
He wants you to observe it.
It's all by observation.
So, you see how it's not 28 point whatever
or 29 point whatever?
How they show it.
And everything works out in a neat little package
once you get to the equinoxes.
And then you need a little more
information.
But before we get to...
And see, that would figure out your year.
When spring, when you find the bead,
your first month, your reference point.
But before we jump to that,
I want to go simply back to the day.
Well, when does the day start?
Well, everybody knows the day starts at midnight.
That's what they say.
Well, what happened before you had those clocks
and what if they took all the clocks away?
How would you reckon when the day starts?
Well, when you look in Genesis,
he keeps saying over and over,
there was evening, there was morning,
the first day, there was evening,
there was morning, the second day,
so on and so forth.
Now, he only has to say it twice
but he knows we're so thick and stubborn
that he's going to have to say it
at least six times.
So, what does the word even mean?
Well, if the scales are even,
what does it look like?
You've got the left and the right side
equal parts.
So, if the sun travels through the sky
from east to west,
when do you have equal parts of east
and equal parts of west?
When the sun is straight up and down, right?
Straight above in the middle.
Noontime.
Noontime, right,
but not noon with your mechanical clock.
It's observational, you see.
Now, let's jump back to this world now
because we're talking about the way
this is the spiritual message.
If we jump back to this world,
let's look at it real close.
In banks, when you deposit a check afternoon,
don't they count it as the next day?
Okay.
They used to do that before ATMs.
If you go to your naval observatory again,
look up Julian calendar or Gregorian calendar
and start reading about what they're reckoning
and they will tell you verbatim
for everybody knows
and also the scientific community
that the day starts at noon.
But for civil purposes,
the people have been told
it starts at midnight.
Isn't it real easy to weed out
the haves and the have-nots that way?
Yes.
Do you want to know who doesn't know?
Everybody who stands around Times Square
watching that ball drop at midnight?
Do you want to know?
Those are the people who don't know.
I agree.
Do you see where I'm going?
You know, he talks about 7,000.
Okay, he spoke to Elijah in the cave.
Don't worry, there's 7,000 more.
Well, look at it real carefully.
Were there 7,000 or is there really 7,001?
There are things that you see.
Also, we work on a base of 10.
Our numerical system of 0 through 9
make all the numbers base 10.
The Babylonians worked on a base 60.
Computers work on base 2.
The Bible works on base 7.
I just want to throw that out there
because that might be another call on numbering.
But, you see, your day starts at noon.
Now, if you go to Nehemiah around 13,
he says, look,
and it became dark under the gates of Jerusalem.
Now, wait a second.
He doesn't say it was dark in Jerusalem.
You see, they got the people in certain religions
believing that the day starts at sundown.
Ain't so, because sundown is a very ambiguous thing.
So, in Nehemiah, they say,
well, it was dark in Jerusalem.
Okay, it says here it was dark under the gates.
Now, do you know what the gates of Jerusalem look like?
They have these walls that are anywhere between 8 and 16 feet thick
and there's an archway about 30 feet high
and you walk under it.
And that's how they let you in.
It's kind of like you're crossing the border today
or going through an airport, you know.
They inspect everybody going in and coming out.
And he says it was dark under the gates.
That means the sun has to be overhead
because if the sun is not,
if it's on an angle in the sky,
the shadow migrates and you get some light coming into the gate.
And Nehemiah says, why are you letting the people in?
It's the Sabbath.
What are you doing letting them in?
See, it's busy out there because everyone, you know, it's busy.
It's midday.
See, and another, if you go to, I think, chapter 7 or 8,
he says, wait until the gates get really hot before you let them in.
Well, how can it be at sundown or midnight
when the gate's done cooled off by 4 o'clock, 3 o'clock?
The gates get really hot by noon.
So it's right there in your scripture.
And you don't have to go as far as Nehemiah.
There are many other examples.
If you look at the New Testament, you see the same examples.
When you start looking at your times, when your days were.
You know, how can you be sitting around the shores of Galilee
and the next day you get on the boat,
you're sitting right there and you go across.
You see, it's noontime.
It's when the next day is counted.
That's why there's so much confusion going on.
But is there really confusion?
Because if you go out today and tell people the day starts at noon,
they're going to say you're nuts.
Look at your old common law courts.
They had, a man steals your horse, he's guilty.
You have your court in the morning and you hang him the next day.
That's how they did it in the West.
But they always hung him at high noon.
Yes.
You see, so that was the next day.
Not 12 midnight or sundown.
So these things are right in front of us and they are organic.
Okay, and we learn organically.
You know, some people say, well, how do you know so many languages?
And I'm like, real easy.
Well, it's not real easy, it takes work.
Go download a coloring book for children.
Start coloring in those letters and words.
And you will not forget them as a grown man using a coloring book.
Those things will be absorbed much faster maybe.
For some people, slower than for others.
But that is the simplest way to get familiar with a language.
And once you start getting familiar with that language
and you're familiar with scripture,
you will see that not only individual people have been given pieces of it,
but entire cultures have been given pieces of it.
And they use them every day and they do not know what they're doing.
I like how you use that analogy of the coloring book, Chris.
I mean, that's how we taught our kids.
Yeah, that's how we taught our kids.
So you just basically go and do how you would teach a kid.
You do it to yourself and you can learn it.
I don't mean to give you a hard time,
but I used to give people, you know,
I hear them talking about the problems in the world.
I said, hold on.
And they're like, why?
I said, we have no future.
And they say, why do you say that?
I said, because all of our children have been turned to goats.
You see?
I understand what you're saying.
Yeah.
I just wanted to point that out because, not on you,
but the thing is, we can get very, very subtle.
And a lot of people say, well, you're a real nitpicker or whatever.
And I say, well, we've got the simple,
let's look at the simple stuff first.
The very simple stuff.
And we're all trying and we're all working with each other.
And that's the point.
But again, with the time aspect,
I just wanted to reveal those aspects of it.
Now, to get into the year and when you determine the year,
you basically use your equinoxes.
And when you start, you've got your moons to count.
But there's things called intercalation where your moon,
sometimes you might have a 12th month.
In a year, sometimes you'll have a 13th month
based on your equinoxes.
And that can get pretty complicated to explain at this point.
But basically, your full moon after your spring equinox
is your first month.
That's an easy way to do it.
What gets hard for people to wrap around their minds
is that your year number changes in the seventh month
during the time of ingathering.
But it's not New Year's just because the number changes.
Well, imagine like today, they go from January through December.
And on December 31st at 1159.59, they change the year number.
Well, how about you just change the year number in September,
but your New Year's is still in January, let's say.
That's one easy way to think about it, your celebration.
So you actually have two New Year's in a scriptural year.
You have the month that you change the year,
which is the ingathering.
He says in Leviticus, at the time of ingathering,
that's the end of your year.
But how can it be the end of the year at the seventh month
when we're still way down the line from the first month again?
Well, that's when you do your tallying in.
You're accounting for the year.
You see, they're using this kind of stuff today.
The moon, typically the end of the month was when you settled accounts.
That's why you get a monthly bill today.
The same thing, you're still settling accounts before the moon,
but it's not the creator's moon, it's their moon.
The one that you have to get by buying a calendar
or they actually give it to you on the phone
or whatever electronic device you've got to kind of plug it in there.
Because that just seems to be the standard today.
That's just the way things are.
And again, when you start getting into scripture,
you get a very deep sense of comprehension on why things are the way they are.
And it becomes easier for you to see that the things are the way they are
because they're simply accommodating the people.
The people do not want to follow any form of ancient knowledge
or the way things should be.
And it's even in their own paperwork.
It was quite shocking to go to the Naval Observatory
and see on their website them mocking society
by saying that scientists know, we know the day starts at noon,
but for civil use it's at midnight.
I mean, to me that's kind of a mockery in a way.
I agree. That's why we can't trust, I guess,
the leaders of the powers that be sometimes.
They're accommodating the desires of the people.
Now, here's the thing.
Is it because they've held back education?
Well, how have they held it back?
I mean, I found it. It's right in front of me.
But it's kind of a catch-22 because you go out teaching this,
you're viewed as a threat.
Oh, what are you, going against our system?
You see, so that's where the wisdom aspect comes in.
Well, these things are not going to last very long.
And, you know, when I tell people
the Gregorian calendar is purely fiction,
they say, well, it's been around a long time.
I'm like, yep.
You know, you don't start showing someone that says that something
about what is really going on.
Just because, you know, you put an ad in the paper for a carpenter
and someone comes up to you and he says,
well, I have 20 years' experience.
Most people say, oh, that's great. It means you're good.
No, it just means he has 20 years' experience.
He could have been doing the wrong thing for 20 years.
I agree.
Experience, you know, we need experience.
Okay.
So that's the aspect of your time.
So, yeah, your day of rest.
Now, here's the kicker, okay?
When you go research, I think there's a scientific term for it.
It has to do with your metabolism and your heart rate.
They've got a lot of documentation on how your heart rate is affected
by the phases of the moon.
Go imagine that.
Where scripturally, each quarter is your Sabbath.
So maybe the quarters and the phases of the moon
having an effect on the way your metabolism works
is a coincidence.
And if you look up that word coincidence,
it really means to coincide with.
So what is it coinciding with?
Do you see my point?
Yes.
Coinciding with the truth in time.
So we're not...
Believe it.
We're out of sync with the true phases of the moon
and we're coinciding with what they set up for us to follow.
Well, yeah.
I mean, you mean the people?
You mean in general, the they or...
Yes, because we don't...
I mean, like you were talking about...
He wants you to be more specific.
He's more British.
I understand, but what I'm saying is we've been taught a certain way
and we don't know the true phases of the moon
or the first day of the week.
We only know what we've been taught.
I know, yeah.
Yeah, so what do we do?
I mean, you know, the sharing, perhaps?
You know, here's the thing.
You know, the things I speak on, it's not because I believe them.
You see, I've observed them and I'm just sharing an observation.
And once you observe it as being correct,
because there is right and wrong and correct,
you got to share it and you know it and you've got to live it.
You see?
There's many aspects to it.
Now, there's people that know this information
and don't do anything with it.
They don't live it.
So maybe that's another aspect to it.
You've got to live it.
I agree, but they're also keeping that from us.
I mean, by all this other things they're making,
keeping us busy, so to speak,
where we don't have time for nothing else.
To really find out the truth of many things.
Yeah, if you go look at a lot of societies in history,
Stalin put in a 10-day work week and an 8-day work week.
There was some funny business going on in Egypt back in the days.
There was funny business going on in China back in the days.
I mean, if you go look at all your societies,
everybody's trying to be their own deity, you see?
Because the way you keep time, like I said earlier,
you get it from your deity.
And one easy way to make it more revealing
is you get law from your deity.
Law is not just civil law or traffic law or tax law or whatever
like people have been taught.
Law is every aspect of your life.
It's your operating system.
It's what you eat, what you wear,
how you do commerce, when you do commerce,
how you keep time.
And one easy way to make it really see how in your face
they've managed us is every time you see the word law
in anything, substitute it with the word god or deity.
So let's go down the line.
You've got commercial gods.
You've got civil gods.
You've got gods of nature.
You've got Ohm's God, right?
Like Ohm's Law, right?
You've got the god of thermodynamics.
You've got Einstein's God.
And if you start substituting the word law with god
or your deity or your L,
it's going to paint a very clear picture.
And then all of a sudden when you go back to your scripture
and you start seeing about don't go after all these other gods,
substitute when you read your scripture that word with law.
Reverse it.
And it'll be as plain as day to you.
What's going on?
Because that's the nature of your deity.
That's where you get your law from.
When I say, okay, what you eat, all right,
how you keep time, what you wear,
well, there are things in there about that.
For example, what you eat.
He says if it's on the earth and it's got four legs,
it better chew the cut and have a cloven hoof.
Okay, done.
All right?
If it's a fowl, it better have a crop.
Okay, fine.
If it comes out of the water, it's got to have fins and scales.
That's, I mean, how easy is that?
Okay, what you wear.
He says my people do not mix the wool and the linen.
Do not mix the wool and the cotton.
Do not mix fibers on your clothing.
Okay, when I read that, I looked at myself and I said, oh, no.
I got through my closet and I see 80% cotton, 20% polyester,
really nice shirt.
Okay, got to go.
I see this.
Okay, it doesn't mean that you can't have a wool jacket with a silk liner.
It just means don't mix it within the same garment.
You can have various different fabrics on layers
as long as they're not woven together.
How easy, I mean, how difficult is that to do?
Well, you might feel kind of, you know.
Go ahead.
Okay, that's not difficult to do.
And, you know, the priests are to wear,
okay, the priests are to wear linen that is bleached white.
Really?
Okay, that's interesting.
It has to be bleached white.
Has anyone ever done any research on linen fibers?
Take a linen fiber about six feet long, okay.
Now, anybody that's into radio engineering or communications
that builds antennas and stuff, in their rule book,
well, basic rule of thumb in engineering for antennas,
if anybody knows about this, they'll see it.
They say never make an antenna six feet, exactly six feet long.
Now, six feet long is your average, you know, length of a garment
if it was going to go above, woven from around the shoulder
down to your feet, all the way down, okay.
Now, anyone in antenna and radio engineering will tell you,
never make an antenna exactly six feet long.
Why?
Because you're going to be picking up all this kind of weird ethereal energy
and you're going to get a standing wave
and you could blow up your radio set eventually.
Pretty wild stuff.
So, take yourself a wire exactly six feet long, stretch it on something
that doesn't have any conductivity and put a copper plate and a zinc plate
or a copper and an iron plate with a resistor, a coil and a capacitor in between
and watch what happens with your voltmeter after a few days.
And you'll get a reaction going for about three to four weeks
and then it will stop.
So, let's take a linen fiber and make it six feet long.
And make it taut and resonate it.
Pluck on it, measure it, run a current through it, pluck on it, measure it.
Take that same linen fiber, bleach it white using sodium hydroxide,
a lye type of bleach, not chlorine or fluoride or bromide.
And go ahead and check its resonance again.
You're going to see a drastic change in resonance.
Just plucking on it and just bleaching it.
The same amount of mass there.
In fabric design, it's called mercenization of cotton,
you know, where they do certain processes to it.
I don't want to get into the results.
It's a whole spin-off.
It's very subtle but yet very powerful.
How many straight fibers do you need to make a garment?
A lot of them.
So, imagine thousands of these fibers all over your body bleached white in linen.
And this was for the priests.
I mean, I can go off on a whole other aspect of the scientific real science
of what's going on.
You see, in science, they always teach you theories.
But in the scientific principle, you have a hypothesis, a theory,
an experiment, and a conclusion.
And I'm noticing a lot of people going into debt for hundreds of thousands
of their credits to learn theories.
So they say, well, what about this theory?
I'm like, I don't want to look at that theory.
When you get a conclusion, come back and tell me, right?
We've got this theory.
We've got that theory.
We've got this theory and that theory.
Well, it's a theory.
Is that good science?
It's incomplete.
You see?
Yes, it's incomplete.
Yeah, I'm going to take you out for some theoretical lunch.
How do you like that?
You think you're going to leave that lunch hungry?
More than likely.
Yeah.
So why would you spend $20,000 a year learning theories?
That's true.
And they're supposed to be there looking for facts.
Conclusions.
Or conclusions.
Yeah, let's finish this deal up, right?
What's the conclusion?
In other words, you have to believe in a theory, right?
You know, to belie, believe.
I don't want to know what you believe in.
I want to know what you know, because I can't use what you believe.
I can use what you know.
I agree.
You know, I tell people, you know, if you take really hot water
and put it in the freezer with a stopwatch,
and you put really cold water in the freezer with a stopwatch,
you'll notice the really hot, almost boiling water
will freeze faster than the cold water.
I don't believe you, they say, okay?
And they go and do it, and they call me up,
and they say, hey, it worked.
It does.
The hot water always freezes faster than the cold water.
And I said, okay, well, I didn't ask you to believe me.
I'm glad you went and proved it, you know?
Okay, but, you know, what else is going on?
I knew that, you see?
Well, I'm glad, you know, I was able to inspire you, maybe.
It's like, well, how did you know that?
Well, you ever work on a farm in Minnesota where it's like 20 below
and go milk a cow, and you got that hot milk,
put it down for five minutes, come back, it's solid like a rock.
But the cold milk isn't frozen.
It's got a little skin of ice on top of it.
You see, they knew these things, you see.
Go to a university where they teach dendrochronology,
the study of trees, and pull aside, you know,
your biggest rooster, you know, your highest priest
from the department there, and they teach people about trees, right?
And you say, okay, I'll take your courses,
but before I do, I want you to explain to me
how one blade of grass grows.
And they're teaching on trees,
and they don't know how a blade of grass grows.
And I had an academic that got real...
I once asked this question to an academic,
and he turned around and said,
how dare you talk to an academic like he's an asshole?
Excuse the French.
Didn't address it.
So I'm like, well, before you go,
I'll tell you what trees really are.
He said, well, you know.
I'm like, well, it's pretty simple, isn't it?
It's pretty obvious, right?
I said, well, what are they?
I said, they're gates, they're valves,
like a valve on your faucet.
He's like, well, you look at them, all pretty and stuff,
but they have a very simple function.
Their roots are in the ground and their branches and trunks
and leaves are in the air.
They exchange what's produced in the air
with what's produced in the ground.
They pump the ethereal energy that's in the sky and the air
and they pump that into the earth.
And whatever's produced in the earth,
the roots pump up the trunk and it's released through the leaves,
pump it back into the atmosphere
and it goes back out to outer space and feeds the sun.
He's like, well, how did you learn that?
Just by looking at it.
They teach the people the sun is millions of degrees.
Yeah, sure it is.
You ever notice that when you heat or cool your house,
the heat always goes to the ceiling
and the cold always goes to the ground?
Yeah.
Whether you're running the heater or the AC or whatever,
the heat always goes up.
You make a campfire, the heat always goes up,
cold always goes to the ground.
Okay, that means that all year round,
you've got a hot head and cold feet.
That's the worst health condition, isn't it?
Now let's step outside through the seasons
and look at what's going on out in nature.
And when we're at sea level,
it's real hot in the valley, let's say,
where do we go to cool off?
Hey, honey, let's get in the car and go up to the mountaintop.
Get in an airplane, they've got de-icers on the wings.
You've got an airplane take off from the Sahara Desert
or Hawaii or near the equator.
It goes up and it's freezing up there.
Okay, so on the earth, when you're on the earth,
on the terrasphere, the closer you get to the sun,
the colder it gets.
Go figure.
Right?
Yeah.
And if you're at sea level and I'm at 1,000 feet high,
aren't I 1,000 feet closer to the sun?
So if the sun is so many millions of degrees hot,
shouldn't I be a little bit warmer?
Just a little, maybe?
What if I go 20,000 feet higher than you?
Now I'm 20,000 feet closer to the sun.
If it's so darn hot, shouldn't I be just a little warmer?
But what's happening?
The opposite.
Yes.
Nathan, when you go into outer space,
your body would literally just break apart from being so cold.
Well, it can and it can't depend.
You know, space is another...
Think of space as the ocean.
It's another...
Here's another way to think about it.
You know, they tell everybody, you know,
let's go to the moon, let's do this,
let's go look at outer space, look out there,
but they're not talking about what's happening
at the bottom of the ocean.
Well, what do you call people that are not focusing on themselves
and focusing on somebody else?
Somebody else's business, you know?
You know?
It's like, why are you mining that way?
And, you know, why aren't you putting stuff back
the way it was before?
Well, mind your own business, right?
They don't know anything about the earth.
Well, they do.
There are some people that do.
And they're always looking away.
It's a distraction.
You see, when you read scripture,
you got, for simple vernacular,
you've got pagan and non-pagan.
Okay?
And you start looking at this, you know,
okay, pagans have no rules,
and the non-pagans do.
They have a sense of right and wrong.
Okay?
So, okay, what's the purpose of paganism then?
It has nothing to do with worshipping the earth
and all the stuff they teach you.
It has to do with what's going on today,
when no one's following any kind of holy writ
in their scriptures.
Then what's the purpose of it?
Why isn't anyone following?
Why do people have no law or no rules in their lives?
Well, it's to hide a theft.
How am I supposed to take from you,
if you're well organized and you know
the difference between right and wrong?
But if you teach people there is no,
you know, the law is done away with, you know?
Oh, there's no, you know, you see,
there's no real right or wrong.
That's your opinion.
It's real easy to steal from them.
I'll give you an example.
Like, a non-pagan thief, okay,
walks into a store and he's got a long trench coat
and secret pockets, and he wants to stuff stuff,
you know, put stuff in his pockets,
and hopefully no one will see him.
You know, that's like your traditional,
classical way of stealing, right?
Okay, but a pagan thief doesn't operate that way.
He creates a distraction.
He walks in and three, four of his buddies walk in.
They have a fight in aisle six.
Everybody goes to see what's going on,
and he just grabs everything in the cash register,
waves goodbye in plain sight.
When you create enough of a distraction,
people will not see what's going on.
And if people on this planet are not distracted,
I don't know what they are.
There's many aspects to that.
I wanted to say something before for your other thing
when you were talking about why it's cooler
and the higher you go.
It's all dealing with pressure and how fast the air rises.
Okay, that's a good point.
Thank you.
That makes it cooler.
It's basically when, during the day,
when the sun hits the earth,
the sun basically heats up the ground, obviously.
Basically, the ground acts as an insulator.
Right, and the cold air becomes,
instead of cold air becoming heavy,
it becomes light and it rises very quickly.
Almost at the speed of air entering a vacuum.
That's right.
So in nature, the heat becomes dense
and it goes down,
and the cold becomes rarefied or light and it rises.
But when you heat or cool your house,
the cold becomes dense and goes down,
and the heat becomes lighter and it rises.
Now, why?
See, why is what man is doing
opposite of what nature is doing?
That's a very large discussion,
but I can give you the basics of it.
Earlier we spoke about life-giving energy
and death-giving, okay?
Again, in life, the big N comes up first.
You have coolness, contraction, implosion.
With death, you have a sharp point in the beginning.
It cuts, and it's expansive, and it's hot.
So both of these energies work together.
And when you are plugging in your electric heater in your house
or your electric air conditioner,
or you're using natural gas or oil or wood to fire your stove,
you're using the death side principle of nature.
What you're doing is you're creating chemical decomposition
to get energy.
And the energy that comes from chemical decomposition,
the heat rises and the cold goes down.
When you're using energies that are life-giving
and life-producing and implosive versus explosive,
you have the reverse pattern happening.
You have a cool rising and the heat going down.
Again, from experimenting with high-speed vortices
under vacuums and without getting into the technical aspects of it,
if you were to open one of these vessels
and put your hand over it while that vortex is cooking,
and I'm talking about in the tens of thousands of RPMs
with the absence of air, if you were to open that sucker
and put your hand over it,
you will feel a shot of cold air right from the middle throat shooting up,
almost like a cold blow dryer.
And the bottom, the very, very bottom tip where you exit,
where you just open it, will start to warm up.
So these energies can be produced and can be created.
And they can be used.
Like I gave the analogy earlier,
the 700-mile-per-hour underground train was invented in 1864.
So how impressive is it now that you're getting 300 miles per hour?
A hundred and what, 60-something years later, 150 years later?
What's going on here?
You see, go research a man named Nathan Stubblefield.
Nathan, as it sounds, and Stubblefield will be S-T-U-B-B-L-E-F-I-E-L-D.
And you will see the cell phone was invented before the telegraph.
So what's going on? Some strange stuff.
Now, I'm not talking about a cell phone like, you know, your iPhone or whatever.
It was a wooden box, you know, and had a little antenna.
No battery.
That's why it never took off because there was no battery involved.
Now, the other aspect of the spiritual realm I wanted to speak of,
I don't know if anyone has any questions on time.
No, I don't.
Okay, it's a very simple thing, but it's very difficult
because if it was taught when we were in kindergarten, it would be natural.
The other thing I tell people is if you want to be an expert on any field,
you can do it within a year or two with your own study.
In less than three to five years, you can be pretty much very well versed
in any subject you want to learn within your range, like within your town or your city.
And if you study it for five or six years, you can be on a world expert level with it, any subject.
If you go to a university library and read what they've got in their libraries
or storehouses of information and then see what they're putting in their textbooks,
they're not in agreement.
And I'm talking about the textbooks that get republished every year.
Now, I'm not saying don't go to school. That's fine.
I'm just saying be aware of what you're learning.
I once was speaking to someone and they went and started asking questions.
The university gets a letter saying,
we don't think you're academically fit to continue here, 19-year-old man.
The other aspect I would like to speak on is there seems to be a lot of confusion
about what a soul is, what a spirit is, and what the body is.
Well, the body, not so much, but it's all intermixed.
You've got soul music, oh, you're so spiritual, or you've got the body, the flesh.
The body seems to be pretty clear on what it is.
By looking at all of the holy writs of various cultures,
I find that they're all in agreement, but their translations are not.
And the believers of a particular brand of religion that may or may not have stemmed
from that particular text do not know the difference between the soul and the spirit.
And if you look in your Strong's Concordance, in the Greek, for example,
when you look at the definition of soul, they're giving you the definition of spirit.
And they also tell you that it can be a soul or a spirit.
It's like they don't know.
When you look at the definition of spirit, it's the same thing.
It could be either one, they're telling you.
Well, it can't be. I can't go into a dictionary, look up cat,
and the definition says, well, it can be a dog.
Then I go to the, look up dog in a dictionary, and it says,
well, it could be a cat.
Wait a second, I'm not, you know, that ain't going well for me.
It's got to be a publishing error.
But if everyone's buying it, I don't buy it.
So you dig a little deeper, and you look at the Greek word for soul,
and in Greek it's pnevma, right?
So phonetically, in English it would be spelled P-N-E-U, right?
So you are a living soul, so the word soul, P-N-E-U, let's see,
that has to do with breath. You get the word pneumonia from that, P-N-E-U?
Or P-N-U-E? And you get the word pneumatic,
like a pneumatic tire has to do with air or breath.
When you're pumping up a tire, it's basically a pump breathing into the tire.
Or when you blow up a balloon, that's pneumatic.
So the breath is actually your breath. Your soul is actually your breath.
Simple as that.
So in order to be a living soul, you need to be breathing.
That's right, so you go to Genesis, and he says he made them a living soul.
And if you look up in Hebrew, it's nefesh, and nefesh means breath.
He breathed life into them.
Okay, so what's this thing called the spirit?
Well, you go back to the Greek, and you look up the word spirit,
and you will see in Greek it's psyche, P-S-Y-C-H-E.
Well, that's where you get the word psych from, like psychologist, or psychic,
or psychological. And whoa, that has to do with issues of the mind.
So the spirit must be the mind.
So you go to Hebrew, and you look at the word for spirit, and it says ruach.
And the ruach has mental attributes, obviously. It's of the spirit.
Okay, so what do you do with that? How does that affect you in your life?
Well, maybe you need to be made more practical.
Okay, I've seen someone lose their soul, and we put it back into them.
Very simple.
Swimming in a pool, they bumped their head, they didn't come up.
We pulled them up, they weren't breathing.
Give them CPR, hit on their chest, give them more CPR.
They took a breath, and that big gasp, and they vomited all this water.
Well, for a little time there, they didn't have a soul.
And we put a soul in their body, that's your breath.
Well, we allowed it, we created the conditions for the soul to start working.
It's simple as that.
Now, your spirit is your mind.
It's information, it's your personality, it's your character.
And if you start looking up your scripture, where the word spirit is being used,
and soul, they've messed it up, they've made such a fine mess of it,
that unless you go through it to know what the words are in the original language,
even in your Sanskrit, if you go to your Bhagavad Gita, Mahabharata,
do the same thing.
I've seen scripture in Bhagavad Gita, where they write the word soul,
and you go back to the Sanskrit text, and it's not even there.
Well, they use the spirit in a different way, and there's something going on,
where they don't want you to know what the soul and the spirit is.
So if the soul is your breath and the spirit is your mind,
it's not the brain matter, it's your personality.
What makes you you, the way you think, your character, your mind, basically.
Now, why can't we see that? Well, here's an example.
It can be used and it can be measured, and I always say,
well, if we can't measure it, we can't manage it.
So it's very important to be able to measure it.
But let's look at it this way, a little more tangible.
Let's say I get a DVD of The Matrix, the movie.
Okay, it's this round, you know, looks like a CD, right?
And you give it to a materials analyst, and you give him a hundred bucks,
and you say, I'll be back in a week, tell me what it is.
He'll give you a bunch of sheets of paper, it tells you it weighs this much, 19 grams,
it's this thick, it's this wide, it's made out of this plastic,
it's got metal film, it's got ridges in it at this dimension,
and you're like, wait a second, did you see that this is a movie of The Matrix?
And he says, no, I can't see that in my lab, I can't see that with my...
The way I observe materials here is just don't see it.
Do you have a DVD player or a computer?
Put it in there and play it and see it's a movie.
Well, I can't measure that.
You need to have the specific device to run that information.
So what happens when you die?
Your body dies, and so does your soul,
because if you're still breathing, your body's still alive.
And it says your spirit goes back to the L, back to the boss, right?
So the Hindus, they say you are reincarnated.
Okay, not over and over and over,
or you were conscious of being here before all this.
It doesn't say that, it's just not in the text, sorry.
It says you are reincarnated, means you're put into meat again, karne.
That's what it means.
Actually, it doesn't say that in Sanskrit,
but you are put back into a body, flesh,
and then a bunch of stuff happens.
Or there's a point there where you're entered into a different type of body,
and a bunch of stuff happens.
But after you are reincarnated into a body again,
there's a little trial that goes on, and then you get your spirit body.
And then there are others that just go right into the spirit realm.
They don't get reincarnated, but they still exist.
And they're conscious, they get a light body.
Now if you read, let's say, the Bible,
okay, you are resurrected, everyone is resurrected,
and you are put back into a body,
or you are resurrected into a spirit body.
And the ones that are just put into a regular body,
you have a little trial, and then you get your spiritual body.
Same stuff, you know, there's just more detail of it in the Bible.
And that's why when people say,
well, you've got to be saved, and they can't tell me what I'm being saved from.
So if I want to play a joke on them, I say,
what are you talking about, you want to go to heaven?
Everybody goes to hell, and nobody goes to heaven,
because heaven is coming here.
And they're shocked, and they run, or they freak out on you,
or you better have a getaway car if you're in a Bible study saying that.
Because they've taken the word grave and translated it to hell.
Dante's Inferno.
There is no hell that you go to.
Everything happens here.
And all the texts, they all say the same thing.
Now there's a place that's called the Lake of Fire,
and that's not, you know, it's here on earth, but it ain't burning, it ain't hot yet.
I'm watching it, there's weird stuff going on around it.
Okay?
Big sinkholes there, you know, I think about a year ago,
a tourist, you know, fell into it.
And they're just putting signs around it now, telling people to stay away.
Because it's heating up.
Not for a while yet.
And these things, you know, you don't share them out in public.
You don't give people specifics.
I've done it before on another call with Andrew.
I just, very nonchalantly, just started throwing out specifics and stuff, you know.
And you can never put dates on these things, or days.
They're all by observation.
But the observations become so clear that when you look at the pattern,
you know, that's why when you look, for example, in the Book of Daniel,
the Book of Revelation, notice they're just day counts.
What happened to the months?
Seems like the months are gone.
It's just day counts.
And if you're reading the Book of Enoch, it says,
the moon will err in the last days.
It means it won't become, it won't be reliable.
But these day counts will be.
These things are very, very specific.
And the Book of Daniel and the Book of Revelation ain't got nothing to do
with what people I hear talking about it on the Internet,
or the Bible studies, or TV, or talk shoes, or all that stuff.
You don't have a clue.
Your first clue is someone comes on and says,
well, Happy New Year.
And it's January or whatever, what they call January or whatever.
And they start talking about the Book of Revelation or Daniel.
It's like, okay, let's just hear what they got to say anyway.
Or this or that or whatever.
You can't mix the two.
It tells you not to mix.
You ever wonder why mules are infertile?
They just don't mix.
So the soul, the spirit, and the body are so distinct.
And once you start seeing the procedure that they're telling us,
things that are going to happen,
you know, okay, I covered the spirit, the soul, and the body.
And there's no hell. Hell is translated as the grave.
But there is a place called the Lake of Fire, and it's on Earth.
So what about heaven?
Well, okay, if you look at the Book of Revelation,
there is a spot there where it tells you the new heaven descends, right?
Okay, this thing is pretty large, but what's its shape?
And it's very clear when you read in Isaiah,
the shape of it is a pyramid.
You ever wonder why all societies and cultures
throughout the world have built pyramids?
Were they all just, was it a coincidence?
Absolutely it's a coincidence.
It coincides with certain bits of information.
It's an incredible story.
And the thing is, most of the information, when you start to see it,
not just in the Bible, when you start to see it repeated over and over and over,
and the Bible has the most specifics on it,
you're like, whoa, this thing is held in trust.
This is a trust.
And there is a time in all of them where people will start speaking out,
but you see, timing is everything.
You've got to know when this information has to be given out.
Not too soon and not too late.
And that's why, again, I mentioned to Gary,
if you guys, we did have the time,
I could go through some stuff real quick with you
and your translations to maybe show you how to fish,
instead of giving you fish.
Please show us.
Please explain.
Okay, well, what I usually like to use as a reference
is what they've put in front of you.
And what have they put in front of us?
You see the Cecil B. DeMille movie?
Everybody's watched the Ten Commandments on TV, right?
When I say everybody, I'm painting everything with a white brush.
And what do you see?
You see Charlton Heston, okay?
And you've got a bunch of people lined up
towards the middle of the movie.
And you've got Yul Brynner as Pharaoh with his chariot.
And Charlton Heston says a bunch of stuff, lifts up his staff.
And the waters open up.
They actually used Jell-O for the special effects.
You know, they just fast-forwarded it, you know, stop motion.
And then you see all these people walking down
and walking across the bottom.
You know, the waters, you know, kind of shimmering left and right,
you know, on their side.
They cross over.
Now, here come the Egyptians.
Here comes Pharaoh, because actually,
Pharaoh is the proper Egyptian way to call this.
Pharaoh comes.
And actually, Yul Brynner's on the shore.
Actually, in the text also, he doesn't go.
But his troops go, and the waters collapse,
like anti-gravity all of a sudden gives out.
And they drown.
And that's the way the story goes on TV.
But the interesting part is that Cecil B. DeMille knew.
Now, I'm not going to hold him to it.
I believe, there's that word believe again.
Maybe I should say it appears that he knew what was going on.
Because if you read in the text, if you go to, for example,
if you open up to an e-sort, it's right in front of you.
Go to 14, just hit somewhere around verse 9.
You go to, there's a book on the upper left.
You click on Exodus, and you go to chapter 14.
Let's just hit verse 1 and then just start scrolling down.
Well, if you read in other parts of the text,
he says, not a one of them that left Egypt was crippled,
maimed, or weakened in any way.
And Cecil B. DeMille kept showing two or three times.
They would edit the scene, and they would focus
on someone being carried in a stretcher in the movie.
Now, right away, if you read the text in Scripture,
it said none of them were infirm or crippled.
They all walked out.
And here he is showing you several times in your face, close up,
of a man being carried in a stretcher.
So you know right away something ain't right.
So if you go to the text, let's say chapter 14.
Let me see which verse to really, okay.
All right, if you go to Exodus 14.21,
and he says, and Moses stretched out.
If anybody could see that, it says like,
if you hold your cursor over the green part,
it shows you the actual word that was there.
And you'll see there's an 853,
and that's not being translated at all.
It says ep.
But anyway, keep going.
His hand over the C, and the L-O-R-D caused the C to go back.
Well, you see back right there is italicized,
and it's even in print italicized,
and there's no Hebrew word attached to it.
That means that was put in.
That was not in the original text.
Can you see that?
Anyone?
It's in Exodus 14.21.
Okay, and then it says, by a strong east wind.
That's there in the text.
And all the night, and he made,
okay, there's that 853 again.
It's not being translated, but keep going.
Forget about that for now.
And he made the sea dry land, and waters were divided.
But wait a second.
L-A-N-D, land there is italicized,
and there's no Hebrew word attached to it.
That means that there's no Hebrew word saying land.
So it should read, and Moses stretched out his hand over the C,
and the ever-living caused the sea by a strong east wind all night,
and made the sea dry, and the waters were divided.
There's no land there.
And even if you have a King James in print,
you will see it is in italicized.
That means it is not in the original text.
You go to Exodus 14.22,
and the children of Israel went into the midst of the sea upon the dry waters.
It doesn't say ground.
If you hold your cursor over ground, the word ground,
it's italicized, it's light gray in this program,
and it has no corresponding Hebrew word.
That means that it's...
And if you look at a print KJV, which I have several of them,
it's always in italicized.
It's not in the original word, original text.
So, okay, and the children of Israel went into the midst of the sea upon the dry waters,
and then it says a wall onto them on their right hand,
and a wall on their left.
Because you see W-E-R, there's no corresponding.
So that was put in as a conjunction there.
Okay, so, and you keep reading,
so the Egyptians pursued and went in,
and after them to the midst of the sea all of Pharaoh's horses
and his chariots and his horsemen came to pass.
And you keep reading, reading, and the waters returned,
and they covered them.
Okay, if you keep going to the rest of the chapter.
So it seems like the story ends there.
But then there's an interjectory aspect to it.
And if you go to Exodus 15,
go to the next chapter,
just click one, verse one,
and then saying Moses and the children of Israel,
okay, let's pass those verses and get to the meat of it here.
Okay, you get to Exodus.
Well, actually, Exodus 15 is interesting.
It says the ever-living, or it would be Yahweh here in the original,
or Jehovah, they have it,
is a man, or an ish, I should say, of war.
So, okay, and Yahweh is his name.
And then you go to Exodus 15.4.
Pharaoh's chariots and his host has he cast into the sea.
His chosen captains also are drowned in the Red Sea.
Well, it's actually the Sea of Reeds.
That's fine, that's reasonable,
because in chapter 14 it said that that's what happened,
if you keep reading through it.
Now the depths have covered them.
They sank into the bottom as a stone.
Okay, so something's going on here,
because in the movie it showed them walking across the bottom.
And in the previous chapter I showed you
that they did not walk on dry land,
they walked on dry water.
Well, wait a second.
If they walked on the bottom like it was in the movie,
how would they fall to the bottom like a stone?
Well, it's not finished here.
If you keep reading, he says,
and with the blast of their nostrils,
the waters were gathered together.
The flood stood upright as a heap,
and the depths were congealed.
If you hold Kafa, you see the word congealed
is to shrink, thicken, curdle, frozen, congeal,
in the heart of the sea.
The heart, labe.
Okay, if you keep reading down,
in the middle, in the middle,
not the whole sea, just the middle of it,
the midst of the sea.
So what do you call water that's congealed or made hard?
Okay, and also the blast of his nostrils,
if you go to Exodus 14,
it says that an easterly wind blew all night.
Now you stop there for a second and say,
wait a second, this sounds a lot like ice to me.
Could it possibly get that cold?
You know, especially here when he says,
and the flood stood upright as in a heap.
And that's what it says there.
If you hold it over the number, it's 5067.
It says, in the sense of piling up a mound,
that is a wave.
So obviously the wind was frozen.
Obviously it was frozen.
But he said in the previous chapter,
he's blowing with an easterly wind.
Where were they? Near Sinai, right?
So you go to meteorological reports in Sinai, Egypt.
It's pretty easy to do.
Do a Google search on meteorology of Egypt, Sinai vicinity,
or it actually would be outside of Egypt at this point.
And you'll see meteorological reports
around the time of springtime at night.
It goes down to 22 degrees at night.
As a matter of fact, last year it was down to 15 or 16 degrees Fahrenheit.
Or minus 8 degrees or 6 degrees Celsius.
Now, earlier I mentioned that, you know,
the warm water freezes faster than cold water.
In the desert, in the sunlight, even in the spring,
the water is warm.
So we have a selective wind over a certain section.
Now, before I give you some more evidence,
let's look more and see what happened.
Because he says it fell to the bottom like a stone.
But if you keep reading,
you go down to, let's see,
where it says it fell to the bottom like lead.
If anybody sees that, what verse would that be?
Fast forward.
And Miriam the prophetess, the sister of Aaron,
took a timbrel in her hand.
See, there's a prophetess there as well.
Let me see where it gives you a second witness
that they fell to the bottom.
I don't believe I can't see it.
If you read the whole chapter, you'll see a second witness there.
Just for economy of movement,
you'll see there's a second witness there
where they fell to the bottom.
They sank to the bottom like a stone.
They sank to the bottom like lead.
Again, if they're already walking on the bottom,
how can they fall to the bottom?
And it doesn't say anything about clearing the bottom of a sea,
which is a very, very nasty place to walk on.
And the silt would be at least knee deep.
Now, also, if you read these two chapters very carefully,
you'll see that there's confusion.
The Pharaoh's chariots went into confusion.
If you've ever gone fishing on a frozen lake
and that lake starts to crack,
you leave everything on there and you run.
Now, he says here in 15 and 14
that with the blast of your nostrils,
the waters would gather together and frozen.
So if you go, for example, here a little, there a little,
if you go to...
Let me see if I can... I'm trying to find some notes here.
Psalms. All right.
If you go to Psalms 147.17, click on the top.
You're at Exodus now on that book,
so you click down to Psalms
and you go all the way down to 147.
Then you click on 17.
147.17 says,
He casteth forth his ice like morsels,
who can stand before his cold?
Okay, so they weren't standing when the ice was broken
like pieces or morsels.
And then 18, he says,
He sendeth out his word and melteth them,
he causeth his wind to blow, and the waters flow.
Okay, but if you also look in Scripture,
it says the morning came,
and the morning in the desert is very hot.
Well, actually not very hot,
but the heat in the desert, even in spring or winter,
the sun is definitely warm enough to melt,
even in the morning before you get to the desert.
But if you get to Job,
go back up to the book
and on the top left of the program,
click on Job,
and then go to 37.
Click on chapter 37,
and then verse 10.
You say,
By the breath of G-O-D,
E-R-L,
frost is given,
and the breath of the waters are strained.
And the breath here would be Rahab,
which is literally the whiff.
Not the entire length,
but the width of the waters,
which is my aim,
are strained,
narrowness.
So there's another witness to,
through by his breath,
frost is given,
which is also mentioned,
he blew an easterly wind.
So a little bit here,
a little bit there,
and it's pretty well established
that they walked on an ice bridge.
Now, when you're walking on ice,
you're walking on water, aren't you?
Haven't we heard about walking on water
in other parts of the Bible?
Jesus.
Yeah, you see how things get pieced together,
and they get pieced together
in a way that the book gets smaller
and smaller and smaller.
You'll start noticing links.
Kind of like neurons in your brain,
these things have to be linked up.
Or a jigsaw puzzle.
Look, you've got a jigsaw puzzle,
and you dump it on the table,
and you start assembling all the pieces.
And the way they're assembled
is each piece interlocks
very specifically and tightly.
And actually, when you start forming
that jigsaw puzzle,
each piece is so strong,
you can lift up the entire piece,
the entire puzzle from just one piece.
But it's really hard to assemble that puzzle
without a picture.
You usually look,
you always use the picture on the box
of that jigsaw puzzle as your reference.
So the problem is,
we've lost the picture that was painted.
Or it's given, actually,
in other parts of the scriptures.
And every scripture has
very similar attributes to it.
But the Bible is extremely unique
that it has the most detail.
So that's why, again,
I've gravitated towards this.
Another aspect of it
is if you go to your e-sort,
and go to the book part,
and you go up to Genesis,
go to verse 1, chapter 1,
and you just look at that verse,
you see 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Which is, in the beginning,
G-O-D created the heaven and the earth.
That's 10 words in English.
But in the original,
if you look at just the green numerals above,
you'll see 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Let's see, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Actually, they've left out one
in the beginning,
which would be bed of sheep.
So this is not even totally correct.
There are actually seven
in the text of preservation.
But by the way,
how do they get from six
of the original words
in the language of preservation
to 10?
Okay, so they've added some.
And also, if you look,
if you hold the cursor over 853,
you notice they didn't translate that.
And it's E-T-H or F.
Or Ate.
So this is the first verse.
When you first see someone,
like in the Dinalee language
or Navajo,
when you're greeted,
they say,
Ya Ate.
What a coincidence.
They left the Ate out.
Why aren't they translating that?
And they give you this really lame excuse.
Well, what is Aleph Tav?
Apparently contracted from HG 26.
Okay, apparently.
So that means it's not.
What is Aleph Tav?
Well, Aleph is the first letter
of the Hebrew alphabet.
And Tav is the last letter
So it's the first and the last.
And it's a word.
Now, in Greek,
it would be the Alpha and the Omega.
And it's actually in the form of a word.
And it's the first and the last.
Wasn't there someone in Scripture
that called himself the Alpha and the Omega,
the first and the last?
I am the Word.
How about in John,
where he says,
In the beginning was the Word,
and the Word was with Elohim,
and Elohim was the Word.
Are we supposed to go to the beginning,
maybe to Genesis,
and see that they left out
the first and the last?
And if you do a search on that,
go ahead and copy that.
Highlight it and right-click copy.
Go to where the binoculars are.
Click on those binoculars.
You bring up a search engine
within the program.
And just go ahead and paste that
H853 in the search.
And go ahead and click on that.
And you're going to see,
zero verses found.
You've got to wait,
because there's hundreds of them,
hundreds of places where it exists
in Scripture in the Hebrew,
and they left it out.
And you can click on each verse,
and you can see,
okay, Genesis 1-4,
and Elohim, or G-O-D, saw,
and then you see the H5-3,
the first and the last, again.
And then the light.
Okay, that was good.
And then Elohim divided, you know,
and they have another word there,
which is divided, badal,
is to divide.
Okay, but what's that word H996?
They're not translating.
Well, if you look at it,
it says properly constructed
from an otherwise unnamed noun,
okay, but actually ben, or ban,
means sun.
Not as in sun as in the helial sun,
the body of light and space,
but as a father and a son
from the darkness.
So you can do your own research,
and you start looking at,
click on each verse,
all throughout Scripture,
where that 853 is.
Click on it, and you'll see,
stick that in,
for example, Genesis 37, 11.
And his brethren envied him,
but his father observed
the first and the last saying.
So that first and the last
starts taking on a new meaning
when you start looking at
the original language.
So, I mean, that's enough
of maybe just a quick way
to use that search engine,
and you'll just look,
even leisurely or recreationally,
what's being left out and why.
Any questions on that?
Maybe I want to show
one more thing.
Are you folks familiar with
the Vatican?
It has a statue of Moses,
and he's sitting,
it's a marble statue done
by Michelangelo.
Is anyone familiar with that statue?
You can just do
statue of Moses in the Vatican,
go to images,
and it'll pull it right up.
That's right, Angelo.
I just turned on the chat.
Yes, he has horns.
Does anybody else see that?
That Moses, the statue,
has horns?
Oh, he has horns like Ayatollah.
Hold on a second.
Don't spill the beans on me now.
Okay, now he's got horns,
and people look at that,
and they're like,
they're up to no good.
They're doing something, okay.
If you go to Exodus 34,
let's say verse 29,
and it came to pass
when Moses came down from the mount,
Sinai, with two tables of testimony
in his hand,
but he came down from the mount
that Moses was not,
that the skin of his face shone
while he talked with him.
And when Aaron and all the children of Israel
saw Moses, behold,
the skin of his face shone,
they were all afraid
and came nigh to him.
Okay, Moses called on to them,
okay, but if you skip down
to 34, 33,
till Moses had done speaking with them,
he put a veil on his face.
But wait a second.
The scripture tells us
who lights a candle and hides it, right?
So if his face was shining,
why would he cover it?
But if you hold the cursor where,
let's go back to 34, 29,
he came down from the mount,
the skin of his face shone,
that's the word 7160,
which is Quran,
the primitive route to push or gore
or to shoot out horns,
figuratively raised.
Is there a big difference
between shooting out horns
and your face shining?
I think one has nothing to do with the other.
Do you see what's going on here, folks?
It's right there in your text.
It's not in your translation.
But if you go back to the original,
you got the tools to do it
or get yourself a Hebrew interlinear.
You pull out a Hebrew interlinear
and you'll be reading
the English on the bottom
if you don't read Hebrew
and you'll notice that,
wait a second,
why is that word italicized
and what does that word mean in Hebrew?
So Michelangelo actually knew the scriptures.
Do you wonder why he had such a hard time
getting along with the Pope
and why the Pope said he would have killed him
if he wasn't such a good artist?
He just went ahead and did it anyway.
That's why, you know,
the Vatican is completely overrated.
They're not hiding,
they're not hiding scripture from you.
They're hiding parts of it,
but you can get those parts.
They've put in parts
and you can figure out where they are
if you really want to be a workman in it.
And it doesn't mean like a government job
where one guy is digging
and eight people standing around saying,
are you done yet?
You need a group of people to do it,
to cut through the stuff.
So they're not hiding.
Okay.
Do you ever hear the term, for example,
have a nice day?
Okay.
You want to go find yourself a nice church?
You want to find yourself a nice girl to marry?
Or you got to find yourself a nice boy to marry?
Well, you didn't say that wasn't very nice.
Anybody ever look up what that word nice actually means?
You know?
And I'm going to tie this in
with what I'm talking about,
the Vatican being overrated.
You go to the online etymology dictionary,
excuse me,
and the ones on the internet are about 80% good.
There's another,
there's a part of them that's lacking.
But go ahead and click down
to where you find that word nice.
You know, people always wish,
well, that wasn't very nice.
Or, you know, you've got a nice jacket on
or it's a very common word.
So you go, I guess it's page eight,
page nine,
and on this online etymology dictionary,
which seems to have creeped up
in several positions on the internet.
Anybody want to read the definition of the word nice?
If you've got it?
Bully, stupid, senseless.
You got it.
And if you go down there,
there's Jane Austen making fun of people,
saying, I'm sure, cried Catherine,
I did not mean to say anything wrong,
but it is a nice book.
And why should I not call it so?
Very true, said Henry.
And this is a very nice day.
And we're taking a very nice walk.
And you are two very nice young ladies.
And oh, it is a very nice world indeed.
It does for everything.
Do you think she knew what the meaning
of that word nice was?
Absolutely.
Okay, so the Vatican,
wasn't that formed by what?
The Nicene Council?
Somebody already got it.
Thank you, guest 77.
It was formed by the nice,
the very nice people at the Nicene Council.
It didn't come across someone's head
that these men that put this stuff together
didn't know what they were doing?
That it coincides with hiding stuff in plain sight?
It's just right in front of us.
You're talking about from the Latin, right?
And Old English, or Old French.
Nice, simple, silly from Old French.
From Latin it says,
N-E-S-C-I-U-S.
Ignorant from N-E-C-I-R.
To be ignorant.
That's what they actually said.
Yeah, so the Nicene Council.
Okay, so I think they're overrated, man.
They're telling us they don't know Jack.
Now, if you ever look at the history
of Constantine and those guys,
they were into forming a uniform state.
Like the UCC is the Uniform Commercial Code.
They were trying to form a set of rules
that if you want to create a state,
because there's a lot of land that needs to be reconquered,
because the Babylonians had once conquered the whole Earth.
It's in Scripture.
They wanted to reconquer it.
They wanted to go back out and take it again
under the Greek system.
And also, if people are not familiar with this,
it says Roman Civil Law.
This is Roman this, Roman that.
Where did the Romans get that from?
Greeks.
You're under the Greek system.
It's in your Scripture.
The third beast is the Greek.
And the system was divided into four.
It still stands today.
You've got another system coming here,
right around the corner.
I've got a quick question, Ashton.
I'm going to cut you off.
Everybody's asking about your website.
Do you have a website?
No, I don't.
I've done a lot of research in things that,
if I had to do a website,
maybe I was thinking of doing a blog.
I don't want to put the time into developing it.
Yeah, you just want to be able to post this stuff real quick.
So, yeah, you might want to do a blog.
I don't mind.
I've got a lot of notes,
and I've got a lot of stuff on many subjects.
And if someone wants to go that route,
set up a blog.
There's a lot of free ways,
and I don't mind pumping information that way.
But I know there's some wisdom that
if you know you're not going to do something,
and you're not going to succeed in setting up a website,
why even start it?
You know?
Anyone who has a website knows that it's a lot of work.
Oh, yeah, trust me, I know.
So Romans got it from the Greeks, I think you said.
You got it.
Where'd the Greeks get it from?
Oh, interesting.
Okay, it's in your scripture.
The Greeks got it from the Persians,
and the Persians got it from the Babylonians.
And the Babylonians got it from their forefathers.
That's why when you read in Genesis,
these were the men of old, the men of renown,
the men of name.
Whenever you read that word name in your scripture,
it doesn't say name, it means shem,
which is actually your character.
Just like when you meet someone,
you know your name is, let's say, Tom Smith.
Oh, someone in your family must have been a Smith.
Or Michael Baker.
Well, someone in your family, you guys were Bakers, right?
Your name is your character.
So we're talking about some real tough cats back in those days,
and if you start going through your scriptures,
you'll start seeing things ain't the way they seem.
But the Greeks, basically,
if you've got to study your genealogy,
it's in your Genesis, too,
where'd the Greeks come from genealogically?
Right?
And you've got to look at the kingdoms.
Your secular history does have a lot of information
regarding your question, by the way,
where the Greeks got it from.
The Greeks got it from Egypt.
The Greeks got it from Persia later on.
But initially, your people that left Egypt,
there was a mixed multitude.
Most of them went east,
and some of them went north.
And some of them went east,
and kept going,
and then they kept going north across land.
And then west.
For example, if you look at a lot of your Greek terms,
and you look at a lot of your Egyptian terms,
they're pretty much the same thing.
Like the word, how do you say chemistry in Greek?
Pretty much kimi, or kime, right?
And Egypt is the land of chem, kime.
Right?
Okay.
If you look at the etymology of a lot of Greek words,
like if you look at the etymology of a lot of English,
it comes from Greek or Latin.
You look at the etymology of a lot of Greek,
if you're studying within the Greek technical aspects of it,
you'll see it came from Egypt and Persia.
And a lot of it was inspired original form of speaking.
Some of it came from Cyprus,
which means copper.
And northern Phoenicia, northern Canaanite.
It's a mishmash.
But they're really tough.
I mean, they were pretty tough.
Even today, their battle strategy
and their political strategies and their economics,
not so much their economics,
but I would say political, science, medical
is still dominating the world today.
Who are those folks over at the Land of Nod?
The folks over at the Land of Nod.
I don't know the answer to that one.
Not much said about them.
Now, before the exodus, there were people
who had either won their freedom or just left
to go into other nations.
Is that correct?
There's a mixed multitude that left with them.
So they apparently took the same route,
but they divided later on
based on the etymology of what I see in the language,
you see.
But there's a lot going on, you see.
I mean, how has the world been faring
on this Greek system?
I don't know.
I think I gave the etymology of a democracy
at the beginning of the show.
The word democracy doesn't mean what you think it means.
Look at the moons of Mars.
Phobos and Deimos.
Fear and dread or terror.
Terror state is literally what democracy means, right?
Yeah.
Some people say demonocracy.
No, no, no, but look at the timing.
I'm trying to show you timing.
What do you see in the news every day?
News about what?
Ism. T-E-R-R-O-I-S-M, right?
All the time.
Is there a timing aspect involved here?
All things will be revealed in the end?
End of what?
The end is not like what people think.
Well, ultimately, the end is a new beginning.
Right.
You got one more system coming in.
You got one more system,
and this system that's coming in is going to happen so fast
and under the radar,
and everyone's going to fall into it.
And it's got nothing to do with the New World Order
everybody's preaching and teaching and running
that we have to get rid of
on all your conspiracy websites.
Now, Angela says it's the age of Aquarius.
You got it.
It is.
But look at how your ages transpire.
There's always argument about that.
Well, is it exactly 2,000 years?
Is it 2,150?
It's neither. It's observational.
How do you know what age we're in?
Well, you go out
in the beginning of the year in spring,
your equinox,
around your first of the month,
and you'll see what set of stars you see in the east
before the sunlight washes your ability to see the stars out.
And you'll see the water bearer, Aquarius.
But he's not fully... He's there.
Pretty much fully there, I'd say.
Well, not fully, but mostly.
And that's the time of the pouring out of the Spirit
by a man.
Now, biblically, the pouring out of water,
water bearing, was a woman's job.
All through Scripture,
the camels were watered and the sheep were watered by women.
So there's going to be a change here,
but it's going to be the reverse.
So you have
the way these things are happening here changing.
You see, the thing about that Gary was talking about
in the beginning about women.
If you want to raise the level of education...
I don't like using the word education
because it means the training of animals.
But if you want to raise the level of consciousness,
perception,
and true knowledge of a society,
you must raise the consciousness
or maintain the high level of consciousness
and knowledge amongst women.
It's the women that raise the children
during their formative years,
from when they're born to eight or nine years old.
If you dumb down the women,
you dumb down the society.
If you take the women out of the house,
Do you see what's going on
with women going to work with this woman's lib backfiring?
Oh yeah, that puts the children in the hands of the state.
Yeah.
They've taken the mother who is
bearing...
She has the...
Her ability to interact with those children
and pass down the wisdom
and knowledge and consciousness
and perception and training to children,
both young boys and young girls,
during their formative years.
If you eliminate that,
you're doing irreparable damage to those children.
Why do you think they want all the women at work?
The women's lib and women going to work
has nothing to do with women's lib.
That's all propaganda that was done.
Just like when they took down that statue,
let's say, of Saddam Hussein
and all you see is a crowd of people.
They paid 100 people 50 bucks or 200 bucks each
to go stand around here.
Oh, look at this big... Everybody says this is the way to go.
You pay a bunch of women to go out and burn their bras
and do this and do that and women's rights and this and that.
What do you mean women's rights?
Women run the house.
Women run the household, period.
They do the economy,
the maintenance of the house,
the scheduling of the house,
the child raising,
the education of the children.
Well, again, the knowledge impartment to the children.
But it's all going to backfire.
Nothing is going to be the way
people are thinking it's going to end up.
I mean, look, you got people running around
saying that you're going to burn in hell forever.
That's another thing.
Go find the word forever in your King James,
in your e-sword.
Find that word and go ahead and hold the cursor
over either Greek or Hebrew.
Doesn't matter.
Well, if you do it in Hebrew,
you're going to get the word olam.
And keep reading the definition
and it'll tell you for the age.
And if you hold it over the Greek word for forever,
you're going to get the word eon,
which means for the age.
So this concept of forever just ain't there.
That's something that's this new concept,
this new idea.
You know, an indefinite period of time.
You know, when it says ages of ages,
you got eon times eon.
Well, how long is an age?
It's a pretty long time for us.
So we start putting these things in perception.
Okay, let's go back to your Bible.
Okay, it says something about the second death.
Well, wait a second.
If you die, okay,
and you either go to heaven or hell,
okay, you'll be in eternal hell fire
or you're going to be up in heaven.
Where's the second death?
What does that mean?
What he's trying to tell you is that people are so stubborn,
you got to kill them twice.
But everyone gets the same thing in the end.
It's just what level you're going to be at.
Everyone gets a spiritual light body.
It's just that, you see, one thing people don't want to hear,
again, is that there is a chain of command in the spiritual world
just like there is on the physical world.
And all the scriptures say,
as it is done in heaven, it is done on earth and vice versa.
So if you see a chain of command in a military style,
now military has nothing to do with what you think a military is,
waging war in this map.
If you want to know what real military is,
which is the way the military here and there is done,
but it's not portrayed to the people in their schools or anything,
go read Sun Tzu, The Art of War,
which is taught to all students of military academies,
all officers and generals.
It's required reading.
Lao Tzu, Lao Tzu, The Art of War.
It's also taught to students of economics, right?
It has nothing to do with what you think war is.
Okay, so the military has nothing to do
with what they're putting in front of the people
with tanks and bombs and killing people.
The chain of command, because if you look at,
even at times of peace,
a standing army is to be held in every culture.
And if you look, oh, Tibetans, they're so peaceful there.
Yes, they do.
They do have a standing army in there.
Not with modern equipment and all that stuff,
but if you look at their culture and tradition,
the Japanese have their samurai.
I mean, however you view it,
there's always some form of chain of command with enforcement.
What good is a dog that has no teeth?
So there's always a chain of command,
whether it's in the spiritual world or in the physical world,
and there always will be.
So get over it.
Just the way things are.
Again, like with the water.
In nature, the water meanders left and right.
So it folds over and forms a longitudinal vortex,
which is a tornado laying down on its side,
to transmute the elements
and also to carry sediment and keep itself cool.
But what does man do?
No, we're going to force it through straight pipes.
Rebellion against the natural world.
How's that working out for man?
Not very good.
You cannot solve the problems of the world,
meaning society,
with the same mindset that created them.
You cannot solve the spiritual problems
that people have of the mind
through the same people that created them.
You see?
Again, like moving forward,
again, what deity do you follow?
That's where you get your rules and you stick with it.
You don't vacillate.
Okay, when you read the Bible, it says,
okay, there's a time when you go into Egypt
and there's a time when you come out of Egypt.
And you could see there's an oscillation.
You go in, they went in with Joseph,
to save themselves.
They gave up all their possessions to Pharaoh.
They basically sold their bodies to him
and they come out.
The Christ goes into Egypt and he comes out.
Okay, people always thought going to Egypt
was always going to save them.
And Jeremiah, the Babylonians, come,
we're going to go to Egypt.
He says, no, if you go to Egypt,
you're going to die either by the feast,
the famine, or the sword.
And they didn't listen.
And those that did, did, let's say.
Okay, well, Egypt is Chem.
That's where you get the word chemistry.
So that was saying better living through chemistry.
How's that working out for you?
Right now you stay out of it.
Later on, if you read in scripture,
you go, he forms, he says,
Egypt again will become, be my people.
And there'll be a highway between Egypt and Assyria,
which doesn't exist right now, but it's coming.
So you either follow what your,
you know, whatever program,
or, you know, you don't mix back and forth.
So, you know, I've got nothing against knowledge,
Egyptian knowledge.
I've got nothing against culture,
or ancient, or current, or all in between.
I just leave it alone, because right now
is the time to stay away from it.
That's fine. It's good enough for me.
There's a merit in there.
When you look forward into the New Age,
Aquarius, between now and then,
do you see any possibility of a severe
continental slip, and or complete loss
of the magnetic field spectrum?
Yes and no to both.
Yes, continental slip, no.
But yes, not the way you think it's going to happen.
And the magnetic is not going to happen
the way you think it's going to.
It's taught by science or anything like that either.
And it's a lot to get into, but I could give you
the shorthand version of it.
What I see in some of, and sometimes,
like I said, this information is held in trust,
that if you give the information too soon,
I may have incomplete little pockets
and not convey it properly,
because I don't have all the information yet.
Or it might just seem so ridiculous
and unbelievable according to what
the standard thing is being taught,
it just gets sloughed off.
And there's things in scripture
about casting pearls, right?
We have to be very careful.
So maybe, let's say, maybe I might know something
and tell you I don't know,
and maybe I really don't know it.
But the point is, there's a subtle balance between it.
And if you want, I could tell you
what I think is appropriate to say.
But it's an ongoing project.
It's not information.
As we go more into the day,
these days that we're in now,
that started roughly 1998,
more information is being revealed
that's been there the whole time,
the perception of it.
So the magnetic field aspect of it,
well, you asked about the continental part first, okay?
The way that the continents and the oceans,
the relationship between the sea and the ocean
and the rifts in the ground and the continents,
and the way that it's being taught
is very similar to how it is in scripture.
But it's hard to give a good bearing on it.
So I would say, no, the continents
are going to be just fine.
You're going to have, let's say,
someplace that is underwater.
Let's say the East Coast or places like that,
they're going to be, you know,
far enough underwater that, you know,
you won't be able to live there.
We're talking about 90 or 100 feet underwater.
You're going to have islands being underwater.
Okay, and then they'll be recovered again.
And that ties right into
the polar magnetic aspect, which, you know,
unless you're living under a rock,
you don't know that there's a lot of weird stuff
going on with the magnetism in North Pole right now.
There's a lot of havoc going on with it.
What's going to really happen with that,
I don't have a major amount of specifics
that I could share publicly,
but there is going to be a polar shift.
The Earth is going to shift from its axis right now
where it rotates, let's say,
the North and South Pole are actually like an axis, right?
That axis is going to change.
And the Earth is not going to be rotating
on the axis that it is right now.
It's going to be rotating, let's say,
imagine a line going through the North and South Pole, right?
That's the axle and the Earth is the wheel.
Well, the axle is going to move.
And the axle is going to be somewhere in the Middle East,
the North Pole, and it's going to shoot through,
come out the other side of the Pacific.
That would be your South Pole,
but it's not going to be the way,
it's kind of difficult to explain.
It's going to tumble and then it's going to come back.
But that's not for now, that's much later.
But you see, when you're talking about something
as large as the Earth,
these large things don't happen overnight.
Some do, but they're gradual warnings and gradual signs.
What you will see, let's see,
what you will see though is a rotational speed adjustment.
What does that mean?
Think about something for a second.
You know when you put clothing in the wash cycle,
you get centrifugal force, right?
And it dries out your clothes, right?
Yeah.
And the faster it spins, the more water comes off,
the water goes to the outer parts,
and the slower it spins, the less it does, right?
Yeah.
Sea level is relative.
If you look at the Panama Canal,
look at which side is higher, right?
One side, one ocean is higher than the other,
that's because of the rotation of the Earth.
Sea level is relative,
meaning that the relative sea level near the equator
is higher than the relative sea level near the poles
because the rotational vectoring,
the rotational velocity is a little bit greater.
Even though they all rotate at the same time,
there's more centrifugal force at the equator.
Now if the Earth speeds up,
the shorelines become larger, right?
The water seems to recede.
If the Earth slows down,
that 40 to 70 feet peak of water
that's near the equator starts to lose its steam
and starts to settle back down
and you get your flooding, right?
Uh-huh.
Okay, so that's maybe a way to look at it.
So one thing to do is go do some research
and see if the Earth is slowing down
or is the Earth speeding up?
The Earth's speeding up.
It's slowing down.
Okay, so that means you're going to have water coming inland, right?
Uh-huh.
Because that rise
near the equator is going to start less momentum working on it.
It's going to start to level out, okay?
Now right now what's happening in the Nile
that's not reported is the farmers are having a really hard time
because they're getting effluent water, salt water,
coming in up the Nile.
Never happened before like this.
And it's coming down really deep into the Nile.
We're talking about a lot of miles down into Egypt.
Can't grow in salt water.
Or brackish the way that you can,
but not the way they're farming.
And it's evident all over the world.
But remember, these things come...
Nature has a rhythm.
The nature of rhythm is the rhythm when you...
The higher the energy in nature,
you end up oscillating in four-fifths time like a waltz.
The slower oscillations, the larger ones,
are one to three.
I mean, yeah, one to three.
You have four parts.
So you have one part in and three parts out.
One part in, three parts out.
So you'll have one part slowing down,
three parts speeding up.
One part slowing down, three parts slowing up in four-fifths time.
Like a waltz.
And I'm just telling you this information without any background,
but what I'll tell you is you will start seeing things becoming strange,
but I can't put dates on them.
What I can see, if we're having the same conversation,
let's say, ten years from now,
I'll be able to give you more specific time periods.
Because this is how prophecy works, okay?
If it's a thousand miles from me to you,
all right, so I get in a motorized wagon.
It's not an automobile because I have to put gasoline in it.
If it was an automobile, it would just go on itself, right?
So I have a motorized wagon.
And I get in it, and I set the odometer at zero,
and I hit the gas, and I go.
Now, if you're a thousand miles away,
when I get to the 500-mile mark on my odometer,
that means I'm halfway there, because 1,500, right?
That's two, that's halfway.
Okay, that's all well and good,
but as soon as my odometer hits 500 miles,
and I look over to the side of the road,
and I see a sign,
500 miles ago to your house, like a landmark, right?
Okay.
I know I'm accurate, right?
Right now, we have certain landmarks that are taking place
for a spiritual prophecy to take place.
And those things, when you find those landmarks,
and you go back and reckon it with what's written,
it is so precise that it'll raise the hairs off the back of your head.
But if you start trying to put days, and years, and dates
on stuff that you don't have a landmark yet,
which usually gives you...
He gives you a 2,000-year landmark gap,
he gives you a 100-year, he gives you a 7-year, 14-year, 28-year,
he breaks it down to months, weeks, okay?
I've gotten the landmarks correct on several prophecies,
and they are so precise,
I mean, you could set the news to it.
You know what I mean?
Instead of setting your watch, you could turn on the news,
and, you know, my wife and I, we turn on the news sometimes,
we hear stuff that shocks people, and we're like,
oh, we knew that was coming, very specifically.
We're not psychic or anything.
We have psychic abilities, but we don't use them for that.
He tells you he's going to turn off all the psychics in the end,
they're going to be talking with a jabbering lip.
Nonsense.
And from what information I've been getting from the intelligence community,
that seems to be true since 2005.
It's lights out.
So I'm talking about these big...
I'm not talking about, you know, what you're going to have for lunch tomorrow.
I'm talking about these large, major events, earth-changing events.
Well, you remember when they had that big tsunami,
and they came on there and said that
that day was incrementally shorter than it would have otherwise been.
So that would indicate even enough to have to adjust the atomic clock to it.
Yeah, atomic clocks are a joke.
You take them on an airplane, they don't work.
If you set them at sea level, and vice versa.
Yeah. Well, anyway, incrementally shorter would mean that
there was a speeding up from just a wave rolling.
Slowing down, and the earth expanded a little bit.
Think of a skater.
When she wants to spin faster, she brings her arms in over her head.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
If the day's getting shorter, the earth is a little larger, or it's slowing down.
I'll tell you this, though, if you want to hear little pieces of prophecy,
I could give you very specific things.
I can't tell you when it's going to happen,
but I could tell you very specifically what's going to happen.
One thing, since we're on the global situation.
You know how you reckon 24-hour days with your clock?
Yeah.
Well, you're going to be reckoning 18-hour days with your clock.
In other words, you're going to get a one-third acceleration on the earth.
Instead of having 18 hours to go around its axis with your clock,
24 hours, it's going to go around in 18 hours.
That's going to freak some people out, don't you think?
And that's due to the expansion of the earth or speeding up?
Oh, it's going to speed up by 30% for a short while.
Yeah, it's going to wreak havoc.
I mean, no one's going to work that day.
That in itself right there would, in my mind, that in itself right there
would shut down the electromagnetic field as we're operating with it.
You're going to have problems with that before that.
Little hints here and there.
This is what I mean.
You know how earlier I said this new kingdom's coming on?
It's going to come in under the radar and everyone's going to accept it?
Right.
Do you know that if I got the newspaper today and made, let's say,
a tape of all the news for, let's say, the past year and assimilated it
and went back about 40 to 50 years and showed it to the people back then,
they'd be pulling the hair out of their head?
Yeah.
Do you see what I'm showing as a reference?
But the thing right now, see, entropy is increasing.
Entropy is the decay cycle.
And you've really got five seasons.
You don't have just four seasons, but your fifth season could last a week,
two weeks, a month.
It's called the rotting season.
And folks on a farm are familiar with it.
And even if you don't live on a farm, you'll notice at certain times of the year
that your milk goes bad faster than other times of the year.
And it has nothing to do with the temperature of your fridge.
That's the time of year where in Norway, people go out and when it rains,
they see these little white worms that fall on the ground.
And when the sunlight comes out, they dissolve into a liquid.
And they don't know what kind of DNA or they don't know what these things eat
or drink or how they reproduce, they know nothing about them.
And the scientists are telling the people,
oh, the wind picked that up from the ocean and dumped it over.
You know it didn't. Those are little critters living in the sky.
Space is like an ocean.
When I mean space, I mean, once you...
For me, when I study and you read scripture and you do science, let's say,
real science, that's the stuff they're teaching.
Space starts four to five inches above the earth, the terrasphere.
You got the atmosphere and the terrasphere.
There's a layer between the terrasphere and the atmosphere
that's anywhere between a few inches thick to a foot thick.
I don't want to get into all that stuff, but...
That's where space begins and you go out from there
and you go out as far as you want to go.
And it's just like the ocean.
You know, if you're in shallow water in the ocean,
you go to the real deep ocean, it's like being in another universe.
But you're still in the ocean.
Anybody ever stop and think that...
You ever watch that Space Shuttle STS tether video
when they, about 15, 20 years ago,
when they're putting out that 11 mile long tether
and it got zapped because of all the electricity
and shorted it out, but these huge disks several miles wide
showed up all over the place?
Yeah, I saw that.
Yeah, okay. You know, everybody said,
oh, those are UFOs, motherships.
You ever stop and think that space is like an ocean?
If you went down... Imagine the people that first saw
some of these deep sea creatures down there.
You think they were calling them UFOs?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Okay, so you...
You can see huge living creatures in space.
I'm going with that.
Yeah, and it's not like what you ever see...
And there's many levels of it, like a shark in the water.
You ever see how a shark is swimming
and he's got little fish following him?
Yeah.
And some of them, you know, he lets them,
they go into his mouth and they clean up his mouth
and he doesn't eat them, you know, he kind of lets them go, you know.
And, you know, sharks get a really bad rap on land, you know.
Everybody's been taught that sharks are...
You know, if you know what you're doing with a shark,
you could put him to sleep.
And I'm not talking about violently,
I'm just talking about just touching the right part of his body.
They paint a really bad picture, a picture of these animals.
So what I'm saying is what's going on out there
ain't what we're being told.
Well, actually, they're pretty immune on the subject.
Have you ever seen an academic subject on life in space?
The multiple varieties of life in space?
I haven't.
If you even start bringing up anything like that, it's ridiculous.
You know, then it's like you're going to be laughed at it, you know.
Okay.
You know, look at how they date dinosaurs.
I'm serious.
I want to maybe get my computer and pull something up.
When they find dinosaur bones, you know, they don't date the bones,
they date the rocks that the bones are in.
Okay.
If you do some research on dating of dinosaur bones,
you will see that they have a particular science
that dates the rocks, not the bones.
So if you fell in a ditch and died,
and we pulled you out, let's say 20 years later,
and we dated those rocks,
we'd say this is a 4 million year old man, isn't it?
Right.
And were you listening to when I showed you guys how,
do you remember the virus, you know, how you go to Wikipedia
and look and see how they're describing the virus?
They really don't know, but they do know that it's a poison?
Yeah, I caught that.
Yeah, go use that same frame of mind,
what they do know about all these creatures on Earth,
living, dead, past, present, or whatever,
and read it with that frame of mind,
and you'll see how little they really know.
What they're telling you is what they want you to believe.
They do know.
They know what's going on.
Look, one thing I've explained,
a lot of people come to me and talk to me about,
what about this, what about this,
this project here, secret project,
I'm like, look, this third dimension,
this dimension is fleshy dimension,
you know, when you walk into a wall, it hurts?
Right.
Okay, you know, plywood is really strong,
and we use it because of the different layers
that are glued together,
give it a multiple strength,
where you can't crack it across one grain
like you can a standard board.
So we make plywood,
so it's strong in every direction.
You ever come to think that this physical reality
is like plywood held together with glue?
What happens to plywood when you take the glue out?
You got little thin pieces of wood, right,
but not very strong at all.
Right.
Okay.
So the thing is, if you want to see what's going on
with this physical reality,
instead of knocking your head against a hard piece of plywood,
why don't we start looking at what's holding it together,
what kind of glue, you see?
And maybe if we just peel back
or find a way to release some of the glues
certain periods of time,
we'll be able to find out what this free energy thing
that people keep talking about,
because nothing's for free, it's coming from somewhere.
I always wondered if free, F-R-E-E,
is an acronym from revenue emanated elsewhere.
Yeah, that's a good one.
You see, you know, is it? Of course it is.
Where are you getting it from?
You know, and they got everybody sort of zero point.
There's no such thing as zero.
So they're sending you down what they used to call
the primrose path.
I don't know if people are old enough to remember the,
you know, you don't want to go down the primrose path.
It's right in front of you.
So...
Yeah, go ahead.
If you can see, and I can see,
living entities like that in space,
can you see them with an intelligence?
I'm not saying we're real smart,
but at the level at least that we're at
or maybe even above or...
Different, just like you'd have to reckon that intelligence
using a reference point.
And the only reference point I would use
is the balance that I spoke of earlier
between the properties of life and death.
Are they part of a...
In other words, how well are they adapted?
On which end of the natural cycle are they?
Are they a cleanup crew?
Are they like a snake's fang or a bee's stinger?
Or are they a sprout coming out of the ground
or a fish going through the water, you see?
Or are they a shark? I don't know.
I don't see them...
I've never thought of it that way.
I don't know how to reckon it.
I just know they are.
It's pretty...
Well, I shouldn't say it's pretty obvious.
That's not a good thing to say.
But they're out there.
Well, back on Earth, there's stuff going on here
that we need to suss out.
And again, your law, one thing comes from your deity.
And if you pick one, you pick well.
I'm going to read you something out of...
If anybody's got a Bible,
you know, you ever wonder why they have people swear on the Bible
when the Bible tells you you're not supposed to swear on it, by the way?
You know, why do you think they know?
Well, not the ones telling you to do it,
but that was set up to show who knows and who doesn't.
You're not supposed to swear on anything.
So, and they do stick in there, I affirm,
if you don't want to say swear.
But if you go to the book of Joshua,
chapter 24,
if you go to verse 14,
I'm going to read this out of a Scriptures translation I have,
which tries to stick to the original text,
but it's not really... It does a pretty good job.
But if you read the book of Joshua, verse 24,
I mean, chapter 24, verse 14,
the setting there is
they're ready to go into Canaan
and sell the land.
And this is what he tells the people.
And now, fear Yahweh, serve Him in perfection and in truth,
and put away the mighty ones
which your fathers served beyond the river and in Mitzrayim,
and serve Yahweh.
And if it seems evil in your eyes to serve Yahweh,
choose for yourselves this day whom you are going to serve.
Whether the mighty ones which your fathers served
that were beyond the river, he's talking about the Nile,
or the mighty ones of the Amorites,
right, it's north of them,
and in whose land you're going to dwell.
But here's the kicker.
But I and my house will serve Yahweh.
So he's basically, he's not condemning or judging.
He says, you've got to serve someone.
You're either going to serve these deities
or you're going to serve this deity.
But you've got to choose, you see.
So someone said earlier, even when you're not making a choice,
you're making a choice, and it's harsh.
And one thing you will learn about serving these minor deities
and the deities that man is acting as,
is you will find extreme cruelty in those systems.
That's the difference.
And you could look it up in scripture,
and you could look it up in secular history.
Go look up the Baals, do research on the Baals,
the lords of the Phoenicians.
Every historian will say,
these were some very, very cruel rituals,
cruelty beyond belief,
based on what we consider cruel today.
The Baal, by the way, is lord,
translated to English.
And if you read in the book of Jeremiah,
he's going to tell you, they will replace my name with Baal.
Well, what's lord translated to Hebrew?
Baal.
What's Baal translated to English?
Lord.
Well, well.
Isn't that prophecy nice?
So, you know, when someone starts reading scriptures,
they say, I don't believe they're using Lord for his name.
I said, wait a second, don't get upset at them.
You ain't going to change them.
Look here, come over here in Jeremiah.
Let me show you something.
And he reads it, and he says,
they're going to change my name for Baal or Lord.
What's Baal Lord?
I say, oh, there's your prophecy.
You know, that was done a long time ago.
You ain't changing nobody, son.
Now, Baal,
okay, Lord in English,
you got two choices.
It's either an English title of nobility.
That's it.
Okay?
Or it's an ancient Hebrew demon.
I didn't say this is multiple choice,
and you got two choices.
Don't start, there's no third one there.
Now, you want to start making up your own fairy tales about it?
Go for it.
So every dictionary, every,
all your unabridged Bibles have that in,
have it in your,
in your introduction.
Go get yourself an unabridged Bible,
and you've got anywhere,
they got introductions telling you why they printed it that way.
They tell you we're using God and Lord for publishing purposes.
What is in the,
what's a publisher?
It's a business, right?
What's a business for selling, right?
Have you ever heard of a light bulb factory
that made light bulbs that didn't burn out?
You know, you just make one and then close up shop.
If you start printing Bibles that started, you know,
putting words like, you know,
how they're supposed to be from the language of preservation,
you know, you can't go to church after you read that.
You know?
Scripture says you pray in,
you pray, there's an agenda here, by the way.
Scripture says pray in Matthew 6,
there is somewhere around there.
It says when you pray, you do it in private.
Don't do it in public like the hypocrites do
so they get attention from people.
And then he repeats it.
He says go to your private spot.
That's it.
Okay, so if you go to King James,
you know what word they put there?
They said go to your closet, go pray.
Now, wait a second.
Why did they choose the word closet
when that word actually means storehouse or private room?
Because nobody wants to go in a closet.
That's where they keep the skeletons, right?
Skeletons in your closet, right?
Psychological.
Because if you go into your closet,
you're going to come out of your closet.
Whoa, that's not good either.
So, no, we don't want to pray in the closet,
so let's go down to that nice church.
Remember that really nice church?
Remember?
You see?
Uh-huh.
They're using...
Okay, now, the Creator says,
my covenant with you.
All right, so, you know,
they're saying, well, that's done away with.
I'm under grace.
Okay, I wonder why.
I wonder why they keep saying that.
So you go to your...
find that word covenant in your strongs
and look it up,
and it says the cutting of flesh, the cutting.
You're like, ooh, no, man, I don't want no covenant.
Get away from me with that covenant.
You see?
I don't mean to intervene here,
but the call might automatically try to end
when it gets to four hours.
It's three hours and 52 minutes.
Well, let's maybe just wrap it up.
I'd like to say, I didn't realize it was on this long.
It kind of feels like I'm sitting around a campfire now.
Well, I'm just saying that it'll cut off
and automatically end the call itself,
and I have no control over it.
Okay, but you see, there's a psychology being used
there, but if you actually look at the word covenant
in the Hebrew language of preservation,
it's berit, B-R-I-T,
and if you look at the wonderful thing
about that particular language is that
you don't need a dictionary.
Each letter means something.
So the letter B-R-I-T, which means covenant,
B means house, R means the head,
but actually there's no I.
There's just B-R-T, berit.
So B means the house, R means the head,
and the T means the sign or the seal.
So to go into covenant means you're getting
a sign or seal from the head of the house.
How do you get cutting on from that?
Cutting on yourself.
How do you get that?
Or cutting on, cutting open.
You know?
Because it doesn't sound good.
So is that berit if covenant man?
That's kind of an urban myth.
You can say that because if you look around you,
but the British really was, in Old English,
was with a P, which was the pritim,
or the Greeks had named them the pritish,
or the pritim.
That's why pretty women are attractive.
They're pretty.
But yeah, I guess you can make that connection.
There's a lot of connections you can make.
Here you go.
I'll make one more connection before I go.
Oh, we go.
Okay, so earlier we were talking about fear and terror, right?
Yeah.
Do you want to make a connection to the British in that?
In scripture it says if you run from fear,
you're going to fall into the ditch or the pit,
and then when you come out of the pit or the ditch,
you're going to get caught in the snare, right?
Right.
Yeah, that's in Isaiah.
That's also in Jeremiah.
It's a very popular term.
You can look it up.
Run from fear, fall into the ditch,
come out of the ditch, get caught in the snare.
Now you know what a snare is.
Most people, if you don't know what a snare is,
it's a very cheap trap that catches an animal around the neck,
and it's ruthless.
So okay, look what's going on.
So right now you've got fear and terror going on,
and what's a ditch?
Isn't that a recess?
Isn't that a recess in the ground?
You dig a recess in the ground to flow water away, right?
Okay, so you've got a recession going on right now
from currency, water flow currency.
Now you come out of the recession, right,
and you get into a recovery.
You know, when a trapper sets a snare,
he comes back to recover his prey, doesn't he?
He's got to check on it every day, doesn't he?
Yeah.
Do you see what's going on?
He's talking about recession and recovery.
The ditch, the pit, and the snare?
I mean, there's so many levels.
If you want to play with words and scripture,
you could spend a lifetime with 100 people writing stuff up,
but that's not the way I look at it in my studies,
or I like to really impart information that way.
Even though it exists, you can see it.
Like, what is this recess, you know,
what is this pit and snare thing going on?
You know, but that's yet to come also.
There's many levels to it.
See, that's the wonderful thing about the divine.
The spiritual realm is your source.
You know, and that's why I came on Angela's call
and I told people, if you don't understand what birthdays,
cannibals, and dolls have in common or comprehend,
I don't want to use the word understand for that,
you won't comprehend what's going on around you.
And I'm not going to go over that now.
I know you go to that call somewhere back there in the past
and Angela's the Greek and forward.
Well, again, maybe we should say goodnight.
I sure hope you'll come back.
Yeah, it's been a pleasure.
I mean, I don't mind you keep talking,
I just don't know if talk show's going to kick it.
Last time we had a call go this long,
when I got up to four hours, they shut down the call themselves.
Okay.
Well, again, I read that last verse in Joshua.
Just to show you, it's also in all of your various,
what I call, holy writs.
They all say the same thing.
And the reason I've been studying the Bible
is because it has the most detail on time and law.
And there's a deep sense of irony
when you see the whole world is using it,
but no one's reading it.
They're using it like baseball bat.
That's why people say, you know, you're a Bible thumper,
if you start saying anything about the, you know, scripture.
But very often I tell people, be careful what you say,
because if you start saying things as absolutes,
you know, and they're not, you're going to get in trouble.
And, you know, you're going to either be laughed at by those who know,
or you're going to be misleading those who don't know.
And there's a lot of, there's more misleading
than being laughed at going on right now.
You know, and when I say laughed at is when you say something
and you actually negate what you just said in the same breath,
that's a laughing matter, you know.
So we have to be very careful.
So what, you know, I'll leave you off with a couple of more tidbits
and maybe I'll keep going.
One thing that's going on is,
you ever wonder when you pick up an English translation of the Bible
and you read from Genesis to Revelation,
you ever wonder if they have the books in the right order?
They're not.
Pretty sure they're not, right?
And if you want to do some good study on that,
there's a fellow named Ernest Martin,
and it's spelled just like it sounds.
And he's put it together, he spent his whole life
using history and clues in the scripture
to put them in their correct order.
Now I read his stuff and he's right on the money.
Because I was able to confirm what he told me.
Just like the fellow, I said,
you know hot water freezes faster than cold water?
You know, I got a big guffaw and a laugh, you know.
I got laughed out of the room.
A week later he calls me back and says,
I don't believe it's true.
I said, well, you're not supposed to believe it.
I'm glad you did the experiment.
So I went ahead and looked at his stuff,
and I just kept working on it.
And I took it and seeing what is this?
Ernest Martin did a lot of work
combining secular history of the order
and also the spiritual hints,
you know, the way that it was penned
by the prophets that were inspired to write it.
The prophets were basically secretaries.
And you know when you're reading Genesis,
you've got to keep in mind,
that was penned by Moses
2,500 years almost after the fact of Adam.
That's a recap.
When you're reading Genesis 1, that's a recap.
You see, but spiritually,
what's going on in the spiritual world,
you're going to find out there's another higher order
that is established.
You see, because when,
you notice that they talk about the scrolls.
You got the scroll.
Okay, what is a scroll?
Well, if you look at it on the end,
it looks like an axle of a cart.
And when you unroll it, it's like a wheel.
You got the axle,
the axle and radial aspects of it.
So if we look at the hints in scripture,
it's taught as a scroll
that can be written on both sides.
And it's sweet in the mouth like honey,
but bitter in your stomach.
And there were several prophets
that were fed this particular scroll.
So what's being said there?
Well, to get to the short of it,
if Christ said, I am the word,
and all the prophets say that he wrote all the scripture
and gave it to us,
and I am the Alpha and the Omega,
I am the first and the last,
and then he gives all these parables
that the last will be first and the first will be last.
He keeps saying that.
And if you're one to take a hint,
you're going to say, but wait a second.
If the last is first and the first is last,
let me go to the first book,
which they give us, Genesis.
Okay, that starts with the letter B,
because in Hebrew it's Ben-Ashid.
And if you go to the last book,
it's Apocalypse,
it starts with the letter A.
Because Apocalypse ain't got nothing to do
with doom and gloom and destruction,
like they tell you in English.
Apocalypse just means to reveal,
completely, no holding back.
So Apocalypse is A,
and he also says that it starts with the letter A,
but not only that,
it's written by the Father given to the Son.
The other one's all written by the Son.
Wait a second, this could possibly be
the first book in the spiritual realm.
And the first is last and the last is first.
Hmm, some interesting stuff going on here.
If you want to operate on that level.
No wonder it's very difficult
to have a rational discussion
with anyone on the book of Revelation.
We may be getting cut off here any second.
You spoke about a Bible called the Scriptures,
and you said it was the closest to the original text.
Where do you find that,
and what really are you asking for?
You can just research it online.
It's got about 200 and some odd mistakes.
Look up the Institute for Scripture Research.
They're printed in South Africa,
and they distribute it somewhere here out of Kentucky.
It's about $20 for a soft cover.
It's pretty good if you're tired
of looking at L-O-R-D and G-O-D
and Sunday and Good Friday
and all that other stuff.
If you're tired of looking at that,
because when I read that it's like,
you know, I just can't read it
for any length of time.
I have one of the, I think they call it
the Ratherdam Bible or something like that,
where they left the original Yahweh in it.
Okay.
Yeah, there's also one called the Jerusalem Bible,
which is the Catholic Bible.
It has some apocryphia in it.
They still use L-O-R-D, though.
Then there's another one.
If you could get your hands on it,
it's a Jerusalem Bible printed out of Jerusalem,
and they only printed a few thousand of them
about 30 years ago. I have one.
And it has the original language on the right
in the way, not the original language,
but the language that it was preserved in.
Now, here's one thing.
I'll give you another little nugget
to think about.
Did the Israelites speak Hebrew?
Or did they speak an Israelite tongue
that no one is familiar with today?
Or very few are, and we don't really know about it.
And is the modern Hebrew text,
actually, when they show you Paleo-Hebrew,
that's not Paleo-Hebrew, that's pre-Hebrew.
And the modern Hebrew text,
the actual paleo to that is
the cuneiform that you see on clay tablets.
If you do your own research,
you might find some interesting stuff.
And also, if you go to Jeremiah,
I think chapter 15, verse 5,
somewhere, or I might have reversed it,
but Jeremiah 15, I think,
he'll tell you that he's going to send,
he says, I'm going to send a people over here,
and they're going to take you over,
they're an old nation, renowned, powerful,
and you don't understand their language,
and you don't speak their tongue,
you don't know what they're saying.
He's referring to the Babylonians.
Okay, I think it's 515, Jeremiah.
Or I got to open it up.
Okay, now hold on a second.
Go into your encyclopedias,
and look up Hebrew.
You'll find that it's a Chaldean or Babylonian language.
It's also used by the Canaanites.
Now, he also tells them,
because they're going to be a stumbling block to you.
But here's the thing.
He chose that language to have it preserved in,
to our day.
And the wonderful thing about what the Babylonians did,
let's see, 515,
is that they were operating on a totally different number system
and their letters were extremely precise.
And if you ever get some time,
do some research on the cylinder seals of the Babylonians.
And I'll give you an example why.
Let's say we're taking a stroll through the desert somewhere out there,
and we find some Babylonian cylinder seals.
And we start talking about it.
You're going to have black helicopters and special ops people
coming at your door, taking everything you got,
no questions asked.
What's so important about those Babylonian cylinder seals?
Think about it.
If you read...
Okay, here, Jeremiah 515.
See, I am bringing the nation against you from afar,
O house of Israel declares Yahweh.
It is an enduring nation, it is an ancient nation,
a nation whose language you do not know,
nor do you understand what they say.
Nehemiah, when they came back from Babylon, he said,
why are you guys speaking that language?
What's wrong with you?
You know, we're losing it here, we're losing our culture,
our people, our language, everything.
And if you read in scripture later, he says,
I'm going to restore to you your language.
You didn't say I'm going to give you a new one,
I'm going to restore it.
Well, you know, when the colonies were gathered together
and we decided to become a nation,
that they voted on the national language
and Hebrew lost by one vote.
Okay, you mean in modern days?
Yeah.
Yeah, because they have Greek and French and English now.
Well, Hebrew is extremely precise,
it's one of the only languages that you don't need a dictionary for.
If you learn, if you get yourself a Hebrew coloring book
and you learn those letters and what they mean,
you could pretty much get familiar.
I mean, it's slow going,
but they can't fool you on the definition.
But they know most people aren't going to do that kind of research
so they could put anything they want in Strong's.
Right.
You know, but it's so simple.
And whenever you see something in Strong's
or an etymological dictionary
where they tell you of unknown origin
or unknown root,
they're lying.
What was the last time you walked in
and looked at a carpenter's toolbox
and you asked him what that hammer and saw is
and he said, unknown.
You know, it just don't happen.
It just behooves the mind.
I mean, what do you mean unknown?
Look here.
This letter means this, this letter means that.
Look how it's being used. What do you mean?
I know they've gradually changed the Strong's.
I waited a long time to get an old one.
Well, even the old ones.
It's still in the old ones, too.
They'll give you these really long, long, long explanations
and they're just taking you off.
Oh, I know it's not great by any means,
but better than the newer ones.
Oh, yeah, the new... Well, here's the thing.
You know, if you read...
I was telling this to someone, you know,
it says, I got to be saved.
They said, okay, all right, hold on, I got to be saved.
And right here in your own...
Give me your Bible, and I like using their Bibles
because when you show them a verse in their Bibles,
it seems to have like 70% more impact on them.
I don't know why.
Then they're sure you don't have a trick deck of cards.
Because they're carrying it around, you know,
and they think they know it.
You know, they don't know anything in there at all.
And I show them some verses and it just shocks them
because, you know, if you show it to me out of your Bible,
you know, it can't be true.
It can't be the only true one.
So you show them out of theirs, you know.
And it says that...
He says, the Christ said,
the gospel will be preached to the whole world
and then I will return.
I said, do you see it around right now?
Nope.
I said, well, then that means the gospel hasn't been preached yet, right?
Very simple.
And the word gospel that you're looking up
is not gospel in Greek.
It has nothing to do with that.
That comes from the German term,
Godspeak or Gotspiel.
The Greek word is Evangelo.
The EU prefix in Greek
is usually used with prefixes in words
that have to do with healing and health.
And the second part of the word, Angelos, means messenger.
So what it is, it's the message of healing.
It's what it literally means.
And they've translated that into gospel.
Or Godspeak or Gotspiel.
Do you think that's why a lot of people aren't being healed?
Or not, you know?
Their whole perception is wrong.
Now, who am I to say it's wrong?
Well, according to the way I...
the deity that I follow,
he gives me what's right and wrong.
Right?
I don't need CNN or...
Harvard or...
you know.
And why it's important to pick something to follow
that is of ancient times
is because it's your reference.
It's your yardstick.
I mean, there's things that are not in scripture,
but I always use them that I find throughout my life.
But I use that as my reference.
How does it measure up?
In Ecclesiastes, he says,
there's nothing new under the sun.
Everything that is, was,
just knowledge of it has been lost.
So you start hearing about all this high technology stuff,
now you want to know what's being hidden from you.
Why? Why are they hiding knowledge of high technology?
Because, let's say,
you lived in a common society
three or four thousand years ago,
and you knew how to use electricity.
Do you think that would give you power over the people around you
if you didn't share that information?
Absolutely, wouldn't it?
Just like you were talking about before,
the cell phone being created before telegraph.
Yeah, go look it up.
Nathan Stubblefield.
Go look up Beach.
The guy who established Scientific American.
And the wonderful thing is he built this tunnel in secret.
No one knew he was even building it.
And those trains were designed to go 700 miles per hour,
underground,
because they were being drawn by a vacuum.
And air enters a vacuum at 700 miles per hour,
and this is in 1860s.
And now we're supposed to be impressed with a 300 mile per hour train
150 some odd years later?
It doesn't impress me.
Because you're talking about the machines making things instead of people.
Yes, the ancients knew how to make machines that made things.
But they found the quality of those things were not as good
as if you had machines made of flesh and blood.
Do you know what I mean?
Another word is a slave or a worker.
Right. Well, that's what everybody is here.
Yeah. Well, when you get all that stuff from China,
a lot of that stuff is handmade, but it's made so fast
and it's not competent.
I'm not saying it's not competent,
because they will build anything to specification,
but the specifications they give those folks over there
is how cheap can you make it?
That's exactly right.
So when people say stuff from China is cheap and not good,
it's because the people here are giving that as their main specification.
I've seen stuff made in Chinese factories
to very, very, very high specifications.
I was just going to elaborate on that.
I actually have talked to a lot of Chinese manufacturers out there,
and they said they'll do it to whatever spec I give it.
And they gave me some examples,
and like you said, they'll put whatever chip you want.
Whatever spec, and you know what's wonderful about what they do?
If they don't have the equipment to do it,
they'll go out and get the equipment to do it.
Here, if you go to a company and what you want exceeds their spec,
we don't have the equipment. Sorry. Go down the road somewhere.
So you wonder why all the business is going there.
I have seen from doing design work in audio equipment,
a company, they went to design.
We designed a tiny little amplifier, Class D, very high power.
And it was a multi-billion dollar corporation that they went to,
and they didn't have the specific wave soldering tools
and machines to make these little things.
And they just went out and spent $150,000
when they were giving us the bid, just so they could make the prototype.
When do you have an American company go out and spend $150,000
to make you a tiny little prototype without charging you for it?
In other words, they were so happy to be a part of something.
Here we shopped it around all over, TI, Texas Instruments,
all these other places, and they were like,
no, no, no, no, no. We don't even want to deal with it.
So a lot of times, the manufacturers and designers
have no choice but to go to the East.
So the ancients had technology.
Today, in the current era that we live in,
if you find a cave or an opening in the ground, it's illegal to go into it.
They have federal laws. You can't go in there.
You're not supposed to go in there. Why?
Because for the past hundred years,
people have been going into caves, pulling out artifacts that just shouldn't be.
You know, oh, the ancients, oh, they were so poor.
You see, we're more advanced. Sure you are.
You know, what end of the circle are we on?
So it's all being stored up for some show.
You know, the next show, the bread and circuits.
Okay, so the technology that I'm looking at right now,
this computer knowledge, is really very ancient technology.
What's the possibility in your mind that some of that ancient technology
from way back when, what you're talking about,
is still in somebody's hands and that machine is still operating?
Okay, all right.
Think of it this way. Let me see. I'll just come out and say it.
Imagine a piece of metal.
Okay, you found something really, really old
or you know something is really, really old.
Okay, I'm talking about we can't date it.
I mean, it doesn't resemble any modern technology.
A piece of metal, okay?
Okay.
And you look under a microscope. It looks like aluminum.
It's kind of heavy for aluminum, but it's got properties of aluminum.
And you look under 200X, which is, you know,
you need a good microscope for that if you're going to get any resolution.
And you start to see stuff that looks like crushed animal crackers
or little circuit boards, microcircuit boards,
all through the metal, in and out.
And it's not an accident. It's deliberate. It's logic.
That doesn't resemble anything you see in your computer today
because when you see your computer today,
you've got this plastic, they call it a box in the computer industry, right?
And you've got the motherboard and you plug these circuits out
and you see these circuits that are, you know, chips and stuff soldered together.
Imagine a computer that's actually part of the metal.
Whatever you're casting, let's say a hammer, you know,
or part of a tool or a machine,
and it's got the computer integrated in with the material.
They have stuff like that.
They have this film that they've created,
but they're not going to release that. It's too expensive, they say.
Yeah, right. Well, you know, we're talking, okay,
the Babylonian cylinder seals and the plywood.
This reality is like a plywood.
Tesla found out if you hit enough voltage,
the right voltage and the right frequency at the right current,
you started seeing things that just shouldn't be there, you know?
How about this?
Let's say about 15 years ago, there were some hikers out in California,
up there in Marin County,
and as they were walking through a suburban neighborhood
parallel to the park, one of these high-powered transformers blew up.
And, you know, oil and noise and sparks and everything went everywhere.
And all three people that were there witnessed a civil war battle in front of them.
Oh, my.
Okay? And then it just went away.
So was that the time when...
The people in the battle appeared to them as ghosts,
and they appeared to the people in the battle as ghosts.
So is that a simultaneous time situation?
Yeah, high energy.
I tell people if you want to learn your science and you got a TV,
all their documentaries and history is your science fiction
and your science fiction is your documentary.
Oh, exactly.
They always tell us in the movies what's going to happen.
They do. Why do you think when they bring this high technology
in the science fiction, they call it a wormhole?
Why? Because psychologically it messes with you.
Because what's in a wormhole? A worm, right?
You're not a worm, so you can't go in a wormhole in your mind.
They're not wormholes.
That's why they tell you in school you descended from apes.
How does that make you feel?
I look at them and tell them they're stupid.
But it's a psychological dig in your mind subconsciously.
If the people that are saying that want to accept it, fine.
But it's not my truth.
Yeah, you know, why do they teach little children
rock-a-bye baby in the treetop?
Now tell me who puts a baby cradle in a treetop?
And then lets it fall.
And then it falls, right?
Yep. It's stupid.
Yeah, but these are all, they always...
You see anyone here?
Yeah.
So you're saying that that explosion caused,
for lack of better words, a psychic time warp of reality
into the past and they actually saw the past.
Is that what you're saying here?
What they saw appeared to them as a ghost.
But it was two-way.
They also appeared in the other reality and they looked like ghosts.
Let's take this the other way.
It leads back to the question about the machines still operating.
If I took a nickel out of my pocket
and I was able to take that metal
20 years into the future and bring it back to present time,
it would not start the nuclear disintegrate
or you couldn't even scratch it.
It wouldn't age until it reached that point in time to which I'd taken it.
Not necessarily true because it's not the same quarter.
I'm going to share some stuff that's been shared with me.
How's that?
About this subject.
Okay, that quarter.
Okay, go ahead and put that quarter in front of you
if you're sitting down on your desk, let's say, right?
Or on the floor.
Right?
Okay.
And now that quarter in your hand,
that's got a time-space, a space-time coordinate.
It's a quarter.
You can give your material science on it.
And it's got a coordinate in space.
Okay?
You could GPS it or whatever you want to do.
Longitude, latitude, or, you know, on a big scale,
on a universal scale, beyond what the satellites do.
Beyond the Earth, okay?
If you take that quarter and move it three feet to the right,
is it still the same quarter?
It aged.
Hold on a second.
Most people would say yes because it's right in front of me,
but I'll tell you mathematically it's not with this type of math
because the coordinates of where it is in space are different, right?
Thus, it's a different quarter.
That's due to what I call nuclear disintegration.
Yes, it's constantly bleeding.
But if I stop that process, take it into the future and bring it back,
it will not start again until it reaches that point in time
at its present position or whatever position there you put it in around planet Earth.
Okay, but the other coordinates beyond the planet.
But, yeah, I see what you're saying.
Yeah, essentially we're talking about the same thing.
But when I say nuclear disintegration,
I don't know, I don't know.
It's something to think about.
Go on your astrophysics and they have discovered,
even until today, that the Earth is the only planet in the solar system
that has radioactive material like, you know, plutonium, strontium, cesium,
uranium, all that other stuff, right?
So they say.
So they say those really large atoms.
And if you actually start seeing that the chemicals
or the elements on the periodic table are not empirical but ephemeral,
meaning that everything came basically from hydrogen all the way to carbon,
combinations thereof,
and if you look and see that hydrogen is not really the first element but the eighth,
it's the beginning of the second octave.
And you'll see that the primary octaves end around gold and platinum
and around mercury they, you know, they start going radioactive.
Okay.
And you got the lanthanide groups in between.
You're going to start, and then you just go back and use, let's say,
what the ancient principles of yin and yang are.
The opposites attract, hot and cold, positive and negative, skinny and fat,
dark and light.
If you could categorize those elements in the yin and yang concept
or opposite polarities in character in a spiritual way,
because spirit means character or mind,
you will see that amongst the octaves most of the organic material that we have
was formed between hydrogen and carbon.
And your elements after that are different combinations
of all the elements between hydrogen and carbon.
Here's an easy example.
When you take water and you warm it up, the oxygen component becomes aggressive.
That's why if you want to rust metal fast, put hot water on it in the sun.
But you notice that if you keep, get a nail or a piece of iron
and put it in some cold water, 39 degrees, and you'll see how long it takes to rust.
It almost doesn't.
Because oxygen becomes passive near 39 degrees in water,
which is its anomaly point.
But hydrogen becomes aggressive and it wants to bond with other things.
So if you take water and you vortex it, I'm not talking,
I'm talking about high speed stuff here, high energy.
But once you get it going, it kind of runs itself.
And you put, you have it in a proper shaped vessel and you evacuate the air
and you put in carbon dioxide.
While that vortex is going, the hydrogen becomes aggressive,
wants to bond with the carbon and you start forming carbohydrates in the water.
When you had no carbohydrate bonding or anything going on before.
Another way to look at it is if you take two carbons in the atmosphere
and you put some electrical current through it, carbon rods, let's say,
and you touch them together and the air is cold and the carbon rods,
I'm sorry, the carbon rods are cold and the air is warm.
Every time you arc that, you're going to see an arc
and a little piece of carbon is going to be blown off, right?
Right.
But you'll notice that when you start collecting this carbon dust at the bottom,
it's magnetic.
It's iron.
And if you look at the chemistry of it, you'll see X amount of oxygen
and X amount of carbon makes Fe.
You get an Fe56.
And if you start playing around with this,
well, there was originally iron in the carbon.
All right, okay, if you say so, fine.
I'll go out and get some 999 fine carbon and do it with.
And how come 20% of my residue is iron?
And if you use these basic principles,
you'll see with the right amount of electricity
and the right temperature on the right element,
you start making stuff happen.
And this was known to the ancients.
And that type of iron won't rust
because when it goes from carbon and oxygen,
you'll see it'll go through silicon and nickel for a very short period of time
before it gets pinned at Fe.
So alchemy is real.
You can transmute the elements.
You can grow gold biologically.
You can take copper,
the right amount of temperature, pressure and electricity
and take it to silver and then take a portion of that silver to gold.
This is not science fiction.
There are actually people on the web doing it right now on the internet.
Just research transmutation of copper to silver to gold.
You'll see a couple of people ready to go into production.
So the elements have been conquered over and over and over again.
The space-time continuum has been manageable and hidden from the people.
Like you were giving your analogy of going into the future with the quarter.
The way I was told that it works
is that your space coordinates and your time coordinates,
just by moving location, it's not the same object.
So if you go back and you know the right type of math
and the right type of energy,
you start, okay, well, let's do the coordinates the other way.
Work the equation the other way.
Let's say we change the time and space or space and time
and that makes the quarter not correct.
What if we want to keep the same quarter and just change the space and time?
Oh, now we've got some serious actual teleporting type technology,
if you know what I mean.
Yeah, that's basically what I was getting into with it.
It has nothing to do with Star Trek
where they disintegrate your atoms and assemble it somewhere else.
That's not how it's done.
It's actually done by loosening some of the glue in the plywood,
if you know what I mean.
So in that, there is a possibility of a very ancient machine
or machines still operating today.
You betcha.
You betcha it's operating.
More than just operating.
Can I ask you a question, Gregg,
about the signs that we see in front of us basically all the time?
What about the exit that's always in front of us?
We always see the exit sign, we see the entrance sign.
Right.
Yeah.
So, you know, what is the exit?
Is that the tin, the deca?
What is it showing us?
Do you have any idea?
I don't know.
Okay.
Good question, thanks.
Yeah, you're welcome.
But again, if I were to make one point is,
again, like Joshua told them,
you have to pick who you're going to serve.
Where's your reference point?
You know, railroad, the standardization of railroad tracks
is what made the train so prolific.
So, and I don't mean between,
I'm talking about between you and society,
I mean between you and your creator.
You've got to find a set of rules and you've got to stick to it.
And you can't get that without studying.
And when you study, when you go along that path,
you're going to dig up meanings of words
and start seeing things in a, let's say, different way.
You know, and the word believe or beliefs
will not be in your vocabulary.
You're going to strive for precision and accuracy.
So, yeah, I mean, I'd love to eventually,
as time goes on, I know I will happen to be just like,
you know, meet more people just like a musician.
When you play an instrument, you need others to jam with, you know,
to make music, you know.
So, but at the same time, those musicians,
they make a living by being music teachers too, you know.
Or they, you know, they go on stage or something.
But at the same time, within their time,
you need others.
See, everyone's got a piece.
And it's not only the men and the women individuals
and the children, but it's also in cultures.
You know, there are entire cultures
that hold a piece in their language.
And it's as clear as day.
I'd like to give an example of that.
You know, the scriptures talk about the keys.
Where are the keys?
You know, what are the keys?
Okay, if you go to any Spanish-speaking man or woman
in any Spanish-speaking country,
ask them, how do you unlock a door?
What do you use to unlock a door?
They're going to tell you, we use the llave.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm glad you got that.
Because it's just right there, right?
I mean, it's not, it's a coincidence.
It coincides with, do you see how it's in,
it's right in front of us?
I don't mean to cut in, but I'm going to have to give you
a couple more minutes.
I've got to get up quite early.
And if I close it down, it's going to shut the call down.
Okay, well, I'm surprised that we're still on.
I am, too.
I'm guessing it might be the fifth hour.
Wow.
Well, okay, let's...
Maybe they're listening and they find it enjoyable.
Sometimes.
It's just that I have a couple appointments tomorrow
and I have a computer that I still got to clear up.
And it's filled with malware
and I have to work with other computers.
Oh, I agree. I do the same.
And another reason, again, why I got into time
and all that, because when you read in Scripture
around Leviticus 23 and other parts,
he says, the Creator says,
these are my appointed times.
And they actually do mean appointments.
So if you don't know how to keep time,
how are you going to meet your appointment?
Because he's talking about appointments here on Earth.
Right? And he's got seven of them.
And when he says on the first day of the seventh month,
he's not talking July 1st.
You see? When he says this time,
you can't go to a calendar.
Because, you know, that's just so fake.
It's faker than fake.
I don't know if there's a word that's worse than fake
without using cow dung, you know?
So you're missing your appointments with your deity
if you're not in sync with how they want you
to keep time on Earth at the moment.
That's another reason that got me to strive.
Wait a second.
First day of the seventh month?
It can't be. I mean, what's going on here?
It can't be September 1st.
So that's another thing.
You'll notice in all your holy writ,
through all the cultures, there's timekeeping.
Now, I mentioned earlier the phases of the moon
are your Sabbaths.
Well, you know, the Buddhists do that.
Go study the Buddhist culture.
They're kind of eliminating it right now,
but they consider the new moon the full moon
and the rest, they don't work on each quarter.
So there's another culture that has a piece, you see?
There's no reason to be fussing and fighting.
We just got to look around and learn.
They consider the new moon the full moon.
The full moon is the new moon, yeah.
The Buddhists know that.
Go look up Buddhist cultures and what days they take off.
They go by the quarter of the moon.
So what do they call the dark moon?
That's the middle of the month.
The dark moon is the middle of the month
because the middle of the month always comes around
the 14th or 15th of the month.
So when they were in Egypt, leaving around that time,
he gave them the pillar of fire so they had light.
It says it very clearly.
Now, if you reckon the new moon as being the dark moon
by the middle of the month, you've got a full moon.
So it doesn't make any sense to use that.
So why would you need a pillar of fire for light?
And also if you look at the Egyptian culture back in those days,
it was a bad omen to leave your city during the dark moon.
You had to wait for it to get out of that phase.
So they broke the cultural thing that they were looking at.
They didn't have flashlights and beacons.
No, you had a light.
The light was the light of the fire.
And in the desert, can you imagine?
It was very dark.
There were probably shadows with the full moon.
Here's the thing.
People, life today, these signs have been shut down on a large level.
And Christ even said that you will have no signs,
just the sign of Jonah, which is the fish.
But in the end, which we're rolling into it,
there are going to be these signs again in the heavens,
and you've got to look up.
No one's looking up.
Everyone's just looking around,
within five feet in front of their nose, and that's about it.
But these things are going to start coming back.
Not exactly how they were, but you're going to have signs in the heavens.
Jeremiah 10 tells you that.
Don't be afraid of the signs in the heavens.
The people with no covenants will.
They're going to be scared.
You know what?
Is that also considering like clouds and things like that?
I don't know about everybody else,
but I see a lot of signs in the clouds all the time.
Yeah, the Hopi's got the web weavers, they call them.
It could either mean the railroad tracks or up above.
Now I'm talking about major stuff like stuff in the stars,
just like Abraham went to reckon the stars,
and he reckoned well.
He reckoned a particular female set of stars, Virgo, very well,
which shows up in Revelation 12,
which happens to be the reckoning of the day that Christ was born.
Pretty accurate.
Seventh month, too.
Yeah, it happens to be around Tabernacle.
It's when the moon is at her feet and the stars are at her head,
and she's cloaked with the sun,
and it ends up being September 11th, 3 B.C.
You know, that we know.
Number 11, there's no such thing,
but if you reckon it in the Gregorian calendar,
it's September 11th, 3 B.C.
It's when the Christ was born,
and that was shown to Abraham in Chapter 15,
and if you look later,
he sends 12 of his sons to the east with the bullet.
The conference is scheduled to be broken down automatically in...
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
5 minutes.
I don't know how to press star 8.
I don't have star 8.
I think we need to...
Anyway, because I know...
Yeah, I got to do some stuff.
I mean, it's been a pleasure, and thank you for the...
Hey, J.D., let us know...
Thank you for coming, Greg, J.D.
Let us know when he's coming back, send us a mail,
because this is real good stuff.
I definitely will.
Yeah, maybe I can connect...
Yeah, you can connect with Gary
and find out when we can get him back on.
Yeah, if you could shoot Gary an e-mail,
and then we'll schedule you in.
It's been a pleasure, and thank you for the knowledge.
Sorry we couldn't extend it longer.
Hello? Hello?
Is it dropped?
I don't see him. Dropped.
Mr. Greek, you still on?
Are you, Larry? Is that you?
Yeah, can you hear me?
Did you guys hear that call from TalkShoe?
Did it beep on your end?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, maybe that was his Skype phone.
I don't know.
No, it said that this is TalkShoe.
It'll be ended in that many minutes,
press star-8, but I don't have no star-8
or an extension on my end,
because I'm on the actual web interface.
Okay, well, his telephone dropped
according to my computer screen.
He's still on.
Kat.
Everybody, you have a wonderful night,
and we will reconvene here next week,
next Sunday, I think the 23rd.
Right. Thanks, J.D.
I'm sorry it's late for you.
Yeah, and then we have these,
I need to talk to TalkShoe,
because there's some guests that come in here,
and I might have to have everybody register,
because they put their name down
on certain things,
and they post stuff in the chat
that's inappropriate,
and it keeps on coming in over and over again.
So they're not really part of our group, so to speak.
No, it's just a young kid,
so I have to keep on constantly doing it,
because they put vulgarity,
and I have the ability to block guest participation,
which will make everybody forced to register,
then it's easier to block the people
that cause trouble, you know?
But I don't want to limit the same time
with the people that don't have an account,
but they probably need to just go
and sign up on the TalkShoe website,
and then they have their account and log in,
and it's just easier that way.
Well, you have a great weekend.
You too. Everybody, thank you very much
for being a part of the show.
Thank you, J.D. Appreciate what you do.
I try.
Thank you, J.D., as well.
This is Robert. I've never met you before,
but thanks for putting this call together.
No problem.
Thank you for joining the show.
If you have time, go and look at the prior calls
on the TalkShoe site.
I'm going to.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Everybody have a good night,
and God bless you.
Shalom, prosper, and be in perfect divine health.
Yes.
Good night.
Yes. Amen. Bye-bye.
Bye.