Everyone's asleep. Everyone but me. And I can't help feel like I'm doing this all by myself.
We took the long road, they had enough. Walking on seashells, my feet are cutting, I'm home. Another planet now.
No time for females, I'm out of love. I'm making up details, don't give a f**k and I'm alone. I'm so frustrated now.
But everyone's asleep. Everyone but me. And I can't help feel like I'm doing this all by myself.
Another morning, I'm feeling rough. Don't get too on it, I'm getting up and it's so, so complicated now.
It's time for my work, baby, oh. Set off the fireworks, baby, oh. Cause everyone's asleep. Everyone but me.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to the Vinnie Eastwood Show, broadcasting live on Americanfreedomradio.com and, incidentally, the VinnieEastwoodShow.com.
And my producers found out yesterday, looking at Alexa.com, that out of the 150 million websites in the world,
the Vinnie Eastwood Show's only been around for, well, less than two years, and it's now in the top 1% of websites in the entire world.
So I'm doing not bad, hopefully. Hopefully. Maybe it'll get better. Maybe it won't. Maybe people will just go, you know what, Vinnie's getting too big.
He must have sold out to the New World Order. He must be a Zionist shill. I'm pretty sure that'll happen.
Okay, today we are hoping to have a guest called The Greek call in. So if The Greek is listening, the phone lines are open for you, mate, and you can call right on in any old time you please.
In the meantime, I was going to talk about the New Zealand situation with regards to these asset sales and the Trans-Pacific Partnership Agreement.
Because I think this is actually probably one of the most scary, scary things that's happening to the country right now,
is that you have these New World Order trash, you know, working for the banking interviews, working for the banking cartels and what have you,
that come in and get elected, and nobody's ever really heard of them.
Like, I'd never heard of Mitt Romney before him starting to run for the Republican nomination and everything like that.
Never heard of Obama before he came in and started running for president and all of that sort of stuff.
It's just like, these people kind of almost come out of nowhere.
Like, their background is completely unknown to any of us because we don't actually get involved, right?
You know, we're not at politics every day. We don't go to Congress. We don't protest outside a lot of the time.
And even if we do, we're not naming names, shaming shames, and what have you.
Basically, these scum fracks get away with it because we don't know who we're dealing with.
And if you don't know who your enemy is, how exactly are you going to fight them?
If you don't know what their tactics are, how exactly are you going to defeat them?
So dig this. Here's the tactic of the enemy.
Manipulate people with the media to tell them that there's a big economic crisis.
Then when they react to that big economic crisis, they will willingly get anybody who says that they can save them into power.
That's how easy it is to manipulate our society.
Most people don't think about anything at all, at any point.
I forget who it was. It might have been Winston Churchill who said the best argument against democracy is a conversation with the average voter.
And I hold that to be 100% true because I have talked to many average voters and they don't know Shiite Muslim about anything.
They can't define anything. That's the thing. You've got to ask them to define right wing, define left wing.
They can't do it. Define economics. They can't do it.
So you have a whole bunch of completely uneducated, manipulated, totally brainwashed, mind-controlled slaves who are willing to destroy their own country for no good reason.
And it's just the thing, they're completely unaware.
This lack of awareness, wholesale, doesn't matter what country you're in, we all experience this massive lack of awareness, do we not?
And it's not my fault that everybody's not aware. It's not your fault. We're the ones going out there trying to tell the truth.
It's not our fault when they don't listen to us either.
It's not our fault when our countries get sold out.
It's not our fault. It's not our problem.
We're not the ones who created it. We shouldn't be the ones whose sole responsibility is solving it.
And more to the point, solving such a massive problem, let's say if I did take responsibility for saying, oh, hold on a second, the whole country's fracked, I have to do something.
Many activists do this and they find out very early on that it's not easy to do it on your own.
If anything, it's nigh on impossible.
That's another thing that I found out about all the activists in New Zealand.
Whenever any of them are in trouble, they always know other activists within their movement or in other areas or something like that, and they always come out of the woodwork to protect each other.
We really do have an opposite mechanism starting to work here in the truth movement.
Let me just try and break it down.
Media, assets, government, social.
These are the three things that I think probably really need to be defined for people in the truth movement.
Media, assets, social.
Media currently manipulate everybody by telling them lies and whatever.
Cool.
Who do they get to do all the commentary?
They get paid shills and what have you.
What does the truth movement have to do?
Get unpaid shills.
I'm a shill in some way, sense of the word.
I am shilling the truth all day long.
I'm shilling counseling and truth and ideology and what have you.
So technically, yes, I am.
Except I'm doing the exact opposite of what the current media do, and that's all that needs to happen.
You just have a look at whatever the establishment is doing, do the direct opposite, and you're most likely going to be right on the money.
Okay, it's pretty simple.
Do the direct opposite of whatever they want you to do.
Assets.
They want you to sell your assets.
Ergo, you have to keep your assets.
Very straightforward.
They want you to sign massive trade agreements, which take away your country's sovereignty and give evil companies like Monsanto the capacity to sue your company
without legislation stopping anything that would make them a profit.
For instance, if they wanted to come and dump toxic waste in the middle of Queen Street, for example, main city.
And the government said, you know what?
Dumping toxic waste in the middle of our main shopping areas is going to cause a lot of damage to the local population, and it might dampen the local businesses and everything like that.
So we're going to pass legislation that makes it illegal to dump toxic waste in public places.
Monsanto will go, you know what?
We're going to have to take you to court then because you're threatening our fracking profit margins.
And I'm not kidding.
I'm making a really insane example to just kind of show you exactly what they are capable of doing.
If they wanted to, they could do this under this Trans-Pacific Partnership agreement.
And if you're in the United States or in Japan or anything like that, any massive scum fracker corporation will be capable of doing this to you as well.
We are all going to be exterminated in terms of economics by this type of treaty.
Now, the United States has already suffered under NAFTA and GATT, so they already know what we're talking about.
They know what happens when you do these big, massive trade agreement deals.
People in the economic community know what happens when you join massive economic communities.
You're basically putting all your eggs in one basket.
Okay?
Now, everybody knows that putting all your eggs in one basket is an incredibly stupid idea.
Because if you stumble in any way, shape, or form, you're going to lose the lot.
And that's precisely the agenda.
Tie everybody together.
Right?
Not entirely dissimilar in a way witches are tied together and burned at the stake.
That's what's going to happen to our economies under this sort of stuff.
Okay?
Who benefits?
Not you.
And not me.
Not our countries.
Not our sovereignty.
Not our personal liberties.
Not our economies of any kind.
It's not possible.
It's not their real intention for this.
If the intention was to do any good, the agreements would not be secret from the public.
People would be able to look and say, ooh, I don't like that little bit there.
Maybe we can actually do something about it.
But no.
Doesn't work that way.
And the last aspect I wanted to explain is social.
Okay?
New World Order wants you to not be social.
Wants you to not hang out with other truthers.
Wants you to feel alone.
Wants you to withdraw into yourself.
Wants you to lose your mind and start becoming drug dependent and everything like that.
Well, look at it this way.
What's the normal aspect of a normal person's life?
We've got the Greek calling in now.
I'll come to you in a sec, mate.
You know how you go out before you became a truther and you used to go out drinking on Friday nights with mates or something like that?
You go around to their house.
Maybe you watch a movie or something like that.
Hey, still do that.
All right?
Except go around to a truther mate's house instead of watching some mindless movie.
Watch a documentary together.
So it's the same methodology.
Go and have dinner with a truther.
In fact, I have Tiff and Dan, two listeners who came around to my house the other week and invited me and my girlfriends here around for dinner tonight.
Okay?
We're going to go around.
We're going to have a nice chat and be friendly and all of that sort of stuff.
That's what you're supposed to do, man.
Okay?
Don't stay alone.
It's a bad idea.
At least I think so anyway.
You know, everybody's really cool in the truth.
Well, not everybody.
There's plenty of cool people in the truth movement.
Let me rephrase.
And by all means, if you're tired of hanging around with slaves talking about stuff that doesn't matter, find yourself a truther mate.
Email me if there's a truther that I know in your particular area or your particular state or whatever.
The video would show a social network.
I'm going to be launching this.
God knows when.
I just want people to send me emails with their current location and maybe what their interests are or anything like that.
And what I'll do is I'll send you the email addresses of people in your area, not so you can just chat with them on Facebook, but so you can actually meet them.
You can actually talk with them.
Okay?
That is the most important thing that you need to realize in life is that you are not alone in this.
I'm 10,000 miles away.
I can't be there with you at all times.
All of you listeners, on the other hand, you can be there for each other.
You really can.
And I'll be there for anybody who needs me.
All right.
The Greek.
Welcome to the show, mate.
You're on the air.
Greetings, Vinnie.
Thanks.
Thanks for having me on.
Well, it's good, man.
We've got you here for a good two hours.
And I was explaining to my friend Jono last night, Greg, about you.
And he said, well, who's he?
And I say, well, imagine that you were put here by an alien civilization.
And your task as a trusted science laboratory researcher for the civilization is to explore, research every single aspect of this planet and the universe from the human conditions perspective as a subjective sort of experiment.
And you need to know everything about atomic structure, about how plants really work, how the body really works, how the universe truly rotates and everything like that.
If you know everything from the micro out to the macro, that's basically the knowledge base that the Greek has.
And every single time he's called into the show, I have learned something radically new that has changed my perspective on everything.
Wow.
That's about as good as a intro as I can probably get to you, mate.
Oh, man, I might as well hang up because I don't know if I can live up to that now.
Well, let's start off by calling you Dr. Vinny Eastwood because laughter is absolutely the best medicine and you do prescribe it often.
Yeah, I do.
And I'm wondering if there's going to be any overdoses of Vinny Eastwood show laughter and somebody will have a bad reaction and go shoot up a school or something like a Prozac.
Yeah.
Maybe me calling in is a side effect.
Yeah, it could be.
It could be.
I mean, was it voluntary?
Okay.
Well, let's start off with the normal question that we asked all the guests.
Tell us a little bit about who you are and what it is you do.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, golly.
You give a pretty good explanation there.
I like to take the position that I'm just visiting here and trying to be objective and a little referral to that movie.
K-Pax, your produce is not so great anymore.
Yeah, I don't think it is.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
It is possible, but to get good produce here.
But, yeah, pretty much what I do is I'm observing and I'm trying to basically gather enough information and compare it with people's belief systems,
what they say is true, what they actually do versus what they say, and basically how the inhabitants of the earth are interacting with their environment and each other
and trying to form a body of work that would distill basically the current state of the situation
so it can be easily described and outlined to someone who wanted to know more about what's going on here,
which actually happens to be the inhabitants themselves in some cases, and you call it the Truth or Movement.
So, hopefully, in that case, I believe that in many aspects of what we look to explain as what is the truth,
a lot of people go into long-winded discussions and very, very narrow and deep topics,
but I believe it is possible to form a very general outline, let's say with bullet points and marks,
that one can go into depth later and it covers the entire field of existence on this planet.
Now, thinking about this, because that's one of the main aspects that you talk about when you talk about mainline, massive philosophical discussion,
what's the meaning of it all? Have you come up with a working hypothesis for what the meaning of life is?
Oh, yeah, absolutely. Well, you have to define life, and it's very difficult to define it using the conventional bodies of knowledge
that people usually subscribe to, science and religion and philosophy, because the mainstream teaches that we live in a dead universe.
We're nothing more than chemical substances, products of explosions and random effects.
But as we look a little closer...
We're coming to break, unfortunately, so we'll come back to you just in a few minutes.
The Greek is my guest, ladies and gentlemen. We'll be back in just a few minutes after the break.
You can join us in the chat room at TheVinnieEastwoodShow.com.
And also check out the other stuff at TheVinnieEastwoodShow.com. Lots of info there. Back in a minute.
Jamming like it was a thing of the past.
Brinding on through the universe at breakneck speed, transmitting out to the distant star clusters of the scumbaggery universe.
And we have a very special guest, the Greek. He's trying to explain to us what his working hypothesis is for the meaning of life.
The Greek, welcome back.
Hey, man, thanks.
Yeah, as you were asking me the meaning of life, well, there's several meanings to it.
Depends on your level of observation.
And again, we were saying that they do teach everything's pretty much a dead substance that somehow has coalesced into something living.
So from using that as a foundation or a basis to explain the meaning of life...
Well, let me just digress for one second.
When Sarah Vaughan, a great jazz musician, was asked what makes a great jazz musician, and she says it's the audience.
So the truth in one aspect, based on who your audience is, will be shunned and laughed at, and sometimes they'll even want to kill you for saying it.
Other audience will be indifferent, and other audience will be pretty susceptible to the information.
And not only just listening to it, but actually doing a little bit of homework and applying it practically and proving it out for themselves.
So I just wanted to make that a caveat, you know, based on what I'd like to say about it.
What is the meaning of life?
Well, I want to just tell you what I found out in terms of the summary.
If you look from a secular point of view, secular meaning scientific, mathematical, cultural, philosophical, even religious, yes, because religion is secular.
Most religions have nothing to do with the divine writing that they supposedly are subscribing to.
You will see there's been so much misery, strife through the ages, that the purpose of actually being here at this particular stage that we're in is to taste it.
There is absolutely nothing to learn from this experience.
And I know I might catch some flack from this, but there is nothing to learn.
There's nothing anymore to learn than if you've never had an apple before in your life, and you didn't know what it tasted like, and you tasted it, now you know what an apple tastes like.
What did you learn from that? Well, you learned that it does have taste, and it's a particular flavor that you can identify with an apple.
And that is the meaning of life at this point, where we are right now.
And I can gather this based on roughly 6,000 years of recorded history.
Well, that's a good pool of evidence, as opposed to mainstream science, which has a pool of evidence of, like, what?
A couple of dudes who invented some stuff and told everybody else what everything's about, and everybody else believed them because they were too stupid to disprove them.
What do you mean, in terms of the age of the universe and matter and planets and things like that?
Well, you know, I was more thinking about modern science and how, basically, if you have a look really deep into any scientific principle or mainline theory that everybody just kind of takes as an axiom and uses that as their scientific basis for their whole career and everything like that, like the Big Bang Theory.
Like, here's my summary of the Big Bang Theory.
I thought it was quite interesting.
Nothing exploded, and then suddenly there was everything.
That's the Big Bang Theory.
Right.
Nothing was there, and then nothing exploded.
Yeah.
Who was it, Mark Twain, who said that to say that everything that came from a random explosion is the same as saying that Webster's Dictionary is a result of an explosion in a printing factory?
You see, it doesn't make any sense.
We were talking about micro and macro, and I find that everything on a micro scale is exactly the same, like modeled on everything in the macro scale.
Like, I think they took a picture of the universe, or rather, and it kind of like was a sort of a cluster in the middle with sort of streamers sort of coming off of it, and then they took a picture of a human brain cell, and it's a cluster in the middle with streamers coming out of it.
So it's like the whole universe is just one other organism's, just one giant brain cell that we can only perceive, and it's all inside us, and it's all outside us at the same time.
Like, everything's built upon each other.
There's nothing that's disconnected.
Yes, exactly.
It's all connected, and there's many levels to it.
For example, when you look at all the divine texts of the world, the major ones would be the Koran, what they call the Bible, and say the Mahabharata or the Bhagavad Gita, which would be the Hindu text.
If you look at the storylines in there, and I mean the correct translation and interpretation, you'll see they are all in agreement.
But the actual religions that subscribe to these texts are not in agreement.
And when you approach any of their leaders, they'll say, well, you know, we don't go by the text, we go by tradition.
It's the same thing with the scientists.
I noticed on the chat, you know, you pointed out how they explained that nothing exploded and turned into, you see, that's how ridiculous they are.
But if you question the methodology, they'll say, well, who are you?
Where's your degree?
Where's your PhD?
So they could never directly address the information.
Well, you know what I'd do?
I'd tell them that my degree came out of nothing.
Yes, that's a good one.
One way to get people's molecules rearranged, let's say, is to just, I kind of do this sometimes, you always have to wonder what kind of shock value someone can handle.
But those that can handle, let's say, a medium shock value, I ask them, do you know what the most degrading thing you can do to anyone is, especially a child?
And they say, well, no, what's that?
It's to grade them.
Well, why is it to grade them and degrade them is the same thing, okay?
It's just different.
Wordplay.
Yeah, what it does is it paralyzes your ability to rationally think, and rational thinking is a whole other topic almost.
But you go into a learning environment, and they present to you that you will be graded based on your responses, based on how well you respond.
And now that's paralyzed your ability to rationally think, and now your incentive is operating under the threat of penalty.
Right?
So now you're operating under the threat of penalty instead of being inspired by doing the right thing.
So you've triggered, you know, how many children are growing up in a household, I can imagine, that say, mommy, daddy, why do I have to go do this?
Because if you don't do that, you're going to go to jail.
Or if you don't do this, you won't be able to get a job.
But they could never address the subject matter directly.
And now we have a society, I'm using the corporate way, that you have a society on the planet right now that is motivated by penalty,
which has actually disabled certain functions that allow it to, for example, exercise critical thinking and develop it like a muscle.
Exercise objectivity.
Exercise a healthy emotional expression.
And you force them to go into a state of armoring, you know, an armored emotion where things are kept back because of fear of penalty.
You see, so the school, what they call the school system, the education system, this is really funny.
When you look at all departments of education, you know, on the surface of all the countries,
they're not formally known as a department of education.
They're always known as a department of public instruction.
So you will do what we say or else, right?
Yeah.
Because doing anything else is verboten.
There's an old saying, I think it was the Bolsheviks in Russia, when they would have their meetings,
and they said, everyone, once we install this new form of government, everyone will enjoy beef for dinner and strawberries for dessert every night.
And it sounded great to most of the people.
Someone in the back raised their hands and said, what if I want to eat beef or have strawberries for dessert?
They said, you will do what we tell you to do.
You see?
So it's very interesting.
The whole point of life is to not tell other people how to live theirs.
It's to allow them to live it the way that they want kind of thing.
And it's like everybody benefits when everybody's getting exactly what they want.
You know, it's called a reciprocal relationship with the universe, I think.
That's basically what it's supposed to be.
I mean, no star wanders around solar systems knocking out planets because he's jealous of their curvature or anything, does he?
Yeah, all the time.
Yeah, if you look at the scientific model, if you want to just look at that real quick,
you know, they show you a solar system with a thermonuclear sun in the middle and all the planets going around in needle elliptical orbits.
That is the same thing as saying the Earth is flat.
It just does not happen because this is a universe of scale, not of these discrete phenomenon.
I mean, have you ever seen anything orbiting anything else?
Actually, you look in your home or outside or talk to anyone that's seen anything orbiting?
It just doesn't happen.
Occasionally I have a cat orbiting me.
Well, it doesn't last very long and it's a temporary position.
So, you know, as we look at it, everything is a universe of scale.
I was on another show in American Freedom Radio giving more in-depth explanations.
For example, if you take, let's say, an atom, the smallest form of material that we can handle of hydrogen or carbon or iron or whatever,
and you made it the size of the sun or the size of a planet, is it still, let's say, a hydrogen atom or is it a planet now?
And if you take a planet and shrink it down to the size of an atom, is it still a planet or is it an atom?
So the way we discern things is by its scale, its size, and where it is in the state of equilibrium.
It's because we want to define things.
We want to put things into boxes, categories, because that's the way we can make sense of them.
And what's interesting, though, is the more boxes and categories we try to arbitrarily put into things,
it actually limits our understanding because we're not actually in that box with it really looking at it,
really feeling it, really understanding it.
We're simply putting it on a shelf somewhere and ignoring it and saying, that's in that shelf, cool.
Yes, it is.
But the thing is, if one were to address the problem with the inhabitants on the Earth right now,
it would be something that would appeal to their direct intelligence.
And what I mean by that is also that everyone on this planet has the same intelligence.
The difference is their ability to perceive.
In other words, you can put 7 billion TV sets somewhere.
It's the ones that have the aerial antennas or hooked up to the cable, let's say,
that are going to get the best reception.
But if you hook them all up and allow them to flow, in other words, if they were properly connected,
they would all operate almost the same way.
So this whole idea of intelligence is flawed.
We all have the same intelligence.
In other words, if you go out and buy a computer that has a certain specification,
if there's another million of those computers with specific memory, let's say,
they will all operate pretty much the same.
The ability is, is it connected?
Is it able to process the information?
And do you have an operating system downloaded?
In other words, when you buy the machine, the computer that is, and connect it,
the initial prompting on the screen is,
well, before we perform any of these functions as advertised,
you need to download the operating system.
And just to go out on a limb,
the purpose of all of these divine scriptures of every culture in the world is that operating system.
These are aspects of law, aspects of history, aspects of science.
And when I say law, I don't mean traffic law.
I mean how to be a steward of this planet.
This triggers a remembrance in my mind of Sumerian culture.
And it was essentially like, almost like the Big Bang.
First there was nothing.
And then all of a sudden there was this really sophisticated culture with law,
mathematics, architecture, and philosophy, and all of this other stuff.
And it's like, where the heck did it come from?
Well, you have to look at, well, again, remember we said it's universe of scale.
That culture on a global level is very much like the culture today.
People had free access to travel.
You'll find that people got around quite well throughout the entire planet back then.
And you will find, there's a couple of really good archaeologists out there that do cryptoarchaeology,
and they'll show that from that culture that you just mentioned, the Sumerian culture,
you'll find artifacts that they have all over the entire planet,
dating from that golden age, let's say, that you, I think, alluded to, all over the planet.
And it's just not disclosed.
And the same thing with the Greeks, the same thing with the Romans.
They were everywhere.
It's just history has changed.
I mean, look at how history has changed just in the past 10 years.
Give it a few thousand.
If you wanted to prove to people in, let's say, 10,000 years' time that you were here, right here, right now,
you'd have to go through a heck of a lot of effort to even build something that would even last that long,
let alone be able to be visible still, let alone actually be recognizable as something that was man-made, right?
At the moment, there's pyramids all over the world that don't look like pyramids.
They've been eroded and what have you, and people don't even recognize them as pyramids.
They just think they're big hills or whatever.
And then you take a look at them from aerial shots, and it's like, oh, my God.
That 900-foot hill comes down on all four sides in perfect angles,
and it's covered with bush and trees and all this sort of stuff,
and it's like in the middle of Yugoslavia or something.
Oh, my God.
That's a giant pyramid.
Somebody left that here, and not to mention they're all over the place.
So think about this.
If culture and that download, as you were talking about, had the capacity,
would it even be able to be downloaded today from that technology being left behind?
I'm thinking of just an interesting question, and we'll come back to that after the break,
and we'll also bring you up through Skype, Greg, so you just hang on the line there.
And also we have a caller coming in, Cecilia from Montana,
and we will be getting to you just after the break in a few minutes.
Join us in the chat room, ladies and gentlemen, at TheVinnieEastwoodShow.com.
Back in a sec.
...
Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome back to the show that's all about shining bright.
sending out these light ray thingies all the way through the universe we've got
our caller Cecilia in Montana I'll come to you in just a second I said something
over the break that I think was quite a good analogy and wanted to repeat I love
repeating my own analogies it's like let's say for example you're an
enlightened individual okay I'm not claiming that I am I'm not claiming that
anybody else's or whatever it's all up to your perspective oh he's in like
doesn't matter okay if you want to spread knowledge okay let's say I'm
broadcasting from this radio station right here okay and you're listening to
this think about this I'm a Sun okay I'm the center of my own solar system
and I shine in every direction okay the vast majority of my light that goes out
will fall upon nothingness okay in other words deaf ears empty space okay
because space is cold it's 240 below zero or something like that
as a great tell me and the only time when that light or information is of any
use to anything is when it hits a planet ie you your mind or whatever and only
the planets are capable of turning that light into heat and energy and actually
sustain life so if I give you information light and you receive it the
energy the heat and and everything like that you can then use it right but if I
was not shining there would be no possibility of anybody even a small
amount of planetoids within within my light radius would ever benefit from it
whatsoever and so that's what each and every single one of us is I think is our
own little Sun beaming out the light and the Enlightenment to other people trying
to you know keep them thinking and stay alive in the head and in the heart that
kind of thing at least that's how I look at it anyway I could be wrong so we've
got a caller now I want to go to her Cecilia in Montana you're on the air
hello Vinny great to talk to you man this is great that you're like 10,000
miles away and here I am way over here talking to you it's like your sunshine
is reaching 10,000 miles and remember that that star could be seen from light
years away it doesn't have to be that close right and then someone looking up
at that light from light years away it's a great conversation I really uh
that's why I called up but was thinking about like what you're talking the other
guest you have there uh was talking about the atom you know like the Sun
being an atom and you know and the atom looks like the solar system when you look
at it under a microscope and there's a out in the middle of the desert in Peru
there's a six mile by four miles spider that's made with rocks right only could
be seen from like a thousand feet up in the air and the one leg and the one leg
on the spider is a little bit longer that it uses into in copulation with a
female spider but the only way that you know that you can know that that long leg
is used in copulation of that spider is under a microscope in a cave in this
spider is very very rare it only lives in caves deep under the ground and to
see this spider copulate you gotta see look under a microscope to observe that
one little longer leg on the right side in the same spot on the same spider
that's six miles big and four miles wide and you got to see it from a
thousand feet up just like if he was in a big giant microscope looking down and
this thing is something like 4,000 years old
hmm well it is like that and and it's and that's not the only site that
implies a tech hmm I think civilization took a long civilization took a long
turn I think we turned away from earth we think that we could create our own
existence we forgot the knowledge of nature just imagine the world we could
have a civilization joined with nature and I think you know there's a lot of
people across the earth now that realizes this you know and this is the
big tug-of-war I think you know the capitalists want to keep you know
everything working the way it is so they can make their money but the real
true capitalists that want to work with the earth and the technology together and
make it work good for the people and forget about the profit of the
capitalistic idea with the true capitalistic idea to get civilization
and nature working together we could do mind you know unthinkable things like
reaching them and start that shot and hearing you guys and ripples everywhere
and the ripples hit me and I love the show man and I just wanted to call in
hello we're very welcome so thank you for your call man and I also wanted to
ask you something I wanted to comment on the aspect that our first question
what's life's all about you know we live in this reality of the duality and that
brings choice we can't avoid it that's the free will and and we got the choice
to make the hate or to love and I think we're created to make that choice and
create and I say choose well and create love that's what we're here for because
this world tries to kill our love tries to kill the love between human and earth
you know this civilization that took the wrong turn trying to kill our love for
the earth and civilization and and we got to make the choice and keep the love
alive and that's why we are here so keep the love alive life is short choose
well and and and choose man you know bring it alive love alive like the heart
song you know yeah well think about this you made an interesting point there about
our reality is duality and I find whenever you're basically if you've got
the right idea about something you go through you accomplish it and it gets
finished but if you got the wrong idea about something you have to keep
repeating it so reality of duality I translate that as redoality because
that's what we're doing most of the time in our society isn't it we're redoing
things that have already been done that have already failed and I think that
what's happening here is that we were talking about these ancient technologies
ancient civilizations and what-have-you maybe they got it all figured out and
they're all of them and maybe peace and harmony or whatever this is just my
theory I don't have any evidence to support it maybe but let's say they had
it all figured out and some psychopathic scumbaggery control freak manipulative
evil council not entirely dissimilar to the type we've got today with the
Bilderberg groups and Council on Foreign Relations in the Vatican and the City
of London and Washington DC and Barack Obama and all these kind of eclectic
filth kind of get together and they're like you know what everybody's peaceful
loving happy it means we don't have any control over them because they've
managed to maintain control of themselves they're actually have capable
of existing and they don't need us that that really ticks me off let's mess
everything up and start over from scratch let's let's redo it okay and
this time instead of everybody being peaceful happy enlightened and getting
along sweet as and all is a nut with us having no extra power over them we
want everybody to be fighting each other all day long every day of every
century and I want all of the power that would normally be given to them
through the sheer love and competence to be given and usurped to us that's what I
think happened okay oh might be sounds like the thinking of a psychopath to me
Greg any thoughts oh yeah I've got a couple of thoughts first of all the
caller spot-on on the type of thinking that I'm trying to impart here you see
the other thought on that is yeah you're pretty close to it but it is the picture
remember it works on on both sides in other words yeah well let's just say
we're in a vicious circle right now that is that is one state one way to look at
it that anything you try to do actually just feeds that same direction and until
that circle is broken there is no advancement and there with that circle
will be broken and there will be advancement and it's coming in the next
two decades let's say but again the caller I want to commend him on his
perspective that was really good okay well we're coming to a break now have
you got anything any final words of wisdom or shout outs that you want to
give this is here yep yeah I just want to say it's a great show I'm glad I
found you thanks thanks for letting me speak I'm glad you I'm glad you found us
too man this is another thing this is the reason why the Vinny Eastwood social
network I think is gonna be really awesome because everybody who finds this
show really loves it because they like me they're real cool they like to have a
good time they're not they're not freaking stupid and they're not a
douchebag that's gonna screw you over or lie to you for personal gain if
anything your friends in the truth me or at least my friends in the truth
movement sacrifice almost as much for me as I do for them and that's I think the
way we should all really be living running our businesses running our lives
and running our families you've got to sacrifice for each other because you
find out that if it's all for one and one for all that bundle of sticks that
would snap individually is unbreakable you're listening to the Vinny Eastwood
show join us in the chat room at the Vinny Eastwood show doc calm the Greek
is my guest call another two one eight double three nine eighty five twenty five
number two of the fastest two hours and talk radio it's the Vinny Eastwood show
broadcasting live on American freedom radio.com and incidentally the Vinny
Eastwood show.com and if you can't remember the Vinny Eastwood show.com
just remember Vinny with a Y because it's the most important question and
Eastwood like Clint the guy who got shot while he was wearing some kind of a
boiler thing around his chest and a fistful of dollars and he actually
wasn't shot okay Vinny Eastwood but he with a Y with an Eastwood like Clint Eastwood
pretty straightforward Google that you're a Muslim and you'll find the website
pretty easy all right so my very special guest today is probably one of the most
enlightened intelligent people that I've ever had call into the show and
that includes the the long list of incredible guests that we've had as well
the Greek and as expected phone lines are lighting up so we're going to go to the
first one here has been holding on for about six minutes Freema Freema are you
on are you there? How's it going Vinny? Somewhat fabulous yeah loving your show
man listen to you every day every day every day every day and I'm getting a
little upset with all the repeats but that's cool I guess I have to agree with
you on your guest man I listened to him the other night on Santos and I was
really impressed I have a question for the Greek here do you do you think that
there's any validity to the fact that some of these kids these days and maybe
us also when we were in you know public schools not soaking up so much of this
information because for some reason that we know that it's incorrect oh yeah oh
yeah you know you definitely know because this this thing we call
consciousness is something streaming in it's it's not it's it's not only
captured by us and processed by us but it's constantly streaming in yeah I kind
of felt that way some of us felt like we were kind of retarded in school and as
we got older you know that's funny that's funny yeah I feel I felt like I
was retarded in school but after I got out of school I realized it was
everybody else that was retarded it's great you know it wasn't until later on
in life when I got into you know hiring and firing positions in the high-tech
industry and stuff where I realized that you had you know kind of a one to twenty
ratio for people that were likely to end up getting it eventually what do you say
to that that's really really high I think it would be like maybe one out of two
hundred really really small really really really small but it's growing
just like anything else again it's it's a streaming that's coming in we're
receiving it but there's the thing is the is your antenna in the right position
which is I don't want to say right position because there is no real you
can't explain it temporarily but just to just to say what they're doing in the
schools again to be a harsh critic of it is they're getting you used to being
manipulated and just like any addict you always want to get your fix so now
you're they have a culture of people on the planet they're addicted to being
manipulated so they're looking for manipulation it's it's more specific
than that the CIA have done it done a lot of tests on mind control under MK
ultra and they found out that mind control is addictive yes and mind
control being let's say a form of manipulation with impulses like we were
talking about earlier you suspend one part of the mind and and make another
part of the mind more receptive see my perspective on on high school at the
very least was that it is in fact not entirely dissimilar from MK ultra in
which it is a trauma-based mind control program to produce agents for the system
yeah I agree yeah I got one going into high school this after the summer here
and it was my other kids that had to get to re-educate it when they got home from
the school every day and seemed like him at least with my kids that they're
getting a different perspective and I worked for the school district out here
in California for a couple years before I actually had to quit couldn't see
myself spending another 20 years in that system man I'm telling you you
actually working in the in the maintenance you know in facilities area
you're always in different rooms and stuff and you end up hearing some of the
shit these teachers are telling these kids and and the way they try to you
know feed them propaganda manipulate their thought processes just a crack up
especially to someone who's listening you know from the outside yeah well see
this is something that has occurred to me recently and every single time I say
it to other truth is they go yes yes oh my god it's a brilliant idea a truth of
high school okay you send your kid your history teacher teaches real history
your science teacher teaches real science your biology teacher teaches
real biology that kind of stuff we need the Greek teaching here from what I can
well he's the dig okay what difference does it make if you're in a lecture
theater with 300 other people and you've got one lecturer in the front of you in
university whereas you could have a couple hundred people on a Skype call
from home with the Greek talking to you as an audience what's the difference the
difference is it doesn't cost you $10,000 a year okay and you actually get
knowledge that's of some benefit and you don't have to leave home that I mean
the truth of school if we were to create it and I think we're working on a few
things in the background with a few other of my mates and everything like
that in order to get this off the ground but if we were to do it it would have to
be a completely and utterly digital online school okay so if your kids were
to come to the school and it would probably have to be 10 pages and and
what-have-you to teach the sort of sophisticated information we've got
they'd have to be doing it as a home school program but then again the state
mandates particular curriculums and things of that nature so it'd be
interesting to find out the inner workings of it and whether or not such a
school educating children about the truth as opposed to brainwashing them to
be slaves for the state would be illegal wouldn't it good it's made illegal or at
least that's my perspective anyway we're gonna get to our next caller now
Freeman do you have anything any final comments or words or shout outs no man
I'm gonna drop you an email when you get the social network going yeah yeah I'll
say everybody's just going on to a list and so once that list gets going kind of
a big packer or whatever and I've got a whole bunch of people from different
cities I'm gonna read out that list of cities on air and ask people within
those cities that do listen to the show to quickly email me and I'll forward
their emails on to the other people on the social network so that way you can
actually meet up kind of thing yeah maybe we can get together out here and
make some truth or music yeah man and and and now with the internet we don't
have to travel everywhere to make music do we not at all
sorry man you have a good weekend thanks for your call brother all right
next caller now it's a new caller area code four five oh we're just gonna grab
your first name and what state are you calling from okay this is Johnny from
Montreal Canada all right welcome Johnny cool my French accent will come out so I
apologize but just as long as you don't reveal your croissant not from Paris but
I'm just calling about something you you touched on yesterday which is it would
be a good thing to take a break from all those magnificent Brutus Brutus shows
because it could get you down because I'm telling you if you saw my Facebook
page it's that's the only thing I do I mean is I give out information that's
been given to me which I double-check and triple-check it could be through you
through Alex Jones to Jack blood or whatever and I'm kind of I don't know
hooked on it and and demoralized also because I'm you know I'm 28 years old
I'm an eligible bachelor and I I don't even feel like getting a new girlfriend
or going back to the gym I'm not doing a hunger strike or whatever to not to
intake care what Bill Gates wants to give to me to eat but then again I guess
taking a break would be a good thing so that's what I wanted to call about and
get your take on it well let me ask you something any job you've ever had it's
work isn't it okay you're sitting there you're doing something regardless of
whether it's pushing papers marking a kids or grading children at school as the
Greg would like to say or anything of that nature it's still a job okay being
a truther being a patriot is a job but unlike normal employment there is duty
that forced you into that job okay you had the realization that oh my god
there's scumbaggery everywhere and nobody else is gonna solve this problem for me
I have to solve it right now that's a lot of personal responsibility to take on
your shoulders for something that ain't your fault you and I didn't set up this
system did we Jeremy no and you and I alone are not going to be able to
overthrow this system and so what it is I feel is a balance okay anytime you go
to work you take a weekend off but if you're if your work is being a truther
your work is at home and on the weekends you're still working aren't you so you
don't have a chance to give your brain time to rest or your heart time to slow
down and and things like that balance I believe is the ability to go from either
extreme and then come back to the center again so you can be extremely into the
truth movement and then go offline for a week or two and have some time off meet
your family have dinner and and watch some movies or anything you want to do
to relax and recharge your batteries and then you come back and you realize
that you're far more energized far more capable of doing even more work because
you took care of yourself right because we understand that there's a time
pressure here that the new world has got a timeline we feel that oh my god we
have to do everything now now now now now now but but they're working with a
massive apparatus they got lots of people who work and shifts they sleep
and stuff like that if we subtract our sleep in order to try and compete with
somebody who is then we're gonna burn out faster than they will won't we so we
have to learn how to take care of ourselves otherwise if you can't take
care of yourself how on earth are you gonna protect anybody else true but how
can I mean do you actually have hope that we're gonna see 2013 or 2014 or are
we gonna be is is the nuclear reactor number four gonna melt down totally and
we're gonna North America's gonna be on the inhibitor both what's what you can
in front of you and you can only make decisions based upon the exact reality
in front of you that you were forced to deal with like those are the only times
when you can actually do it like let's say for instance somebody tells you ten
years ago that in ten years time you're going to be hit by a car now does that
mean you worry about being hit by a car for a whole ten years or does that mean
that you perfectly fine and happy for nine and a half years and then about
half year leading into it you kind of think I'm gonna be a little bit more
cautious around cars I think right so you put yourself under undue stress by
reacting to things that aren't actually right there in front of you like the
Fukushima radiation thing it's an invisible menace and it's on top of
everybody right now so that means that there are currently probably radioactive
iodine particles in my thyroid glands in yours and it's and it's slowly sitting
there causing cancer so that's a very real reality so we can react to that
how do you react to detox your body from radiation well one of the most
efficient substances is marijuana marijuana is a incredible detoxifier for
radiation and in fact to the point where you can you can plant entire hemp fields
on radioactive soil and they will absorb the radioactivity into the plant matter
okay and then but you're not talking about smoking some joints like you're
talking about hemp oil yeah well no hemp oil smoking joints or all of that kind
of stuff it all it all works well and biochemical level does the same thing
because the human body is essentially an upside-down plant your brain is where
the is where the roots of that plant are and when you let's say you take that
analogy of the hemp plant that has its roots in the soil and it detoxifies takes
all the radiation out your brain is up here and the hemp will take or again all
those toxins out of that root system and on top of that there is do you like do
you like Indian food curry sorry on occasions do you like it to eat
no no all right well anyway for those who do who are you listening there's an
interesting herb called a turmeric it's a very very common spice that's used in
curries all over the place very good for getting rid of radiation if you like
oh yeah so it's really good and and also turmeric is very good for any wounds
you might have muscle bruising things like that mix it with a little bit of
water turn it into a paste and then if you got like a sprained ankle or
something like that rub it on and put a bandage over it and your foot will be
healed probably by morning and it does the same thing to your body detoxifies
it from radiation and it also gives you a better almost it gives you the
ability to manufacture more endorphins you know that kind of love drug that
makes you feel happy within your body there's also rosemary rosemary is really
good for getting rid of radiation ginger and garlic and ginkgo leaf ginkgo leaf
is very interesting there's only one type of plant that now grows near
Chernobyl the ginkgo tree everything else died isn't it interesting and this
stuff can detoxify the heck out of you so there's a reality and there's some
simple solutions and those solutions are all around you but if you worry about
the reality that you have to deal with instead of looking at the solutions to
those problems the problem seems much bigger than they actually are getting
rid of radiation and not dying is a lot easier than one would think and a lot
less stressful than we make it you listen to the Vinnie Eastwood show we'll
be right back after the break at the Vinnie Eastwood show dot-com
I'm gathering people wherever you roam and admit that the waters around you have
grown and accepted that soon you'll be drenched to the bone
if your time deal is worth saving then you better start swimming or you'll sink
like a stone
oh yeah times are changing it's and it's it's funny there because it's the
only constant in the universe we're talking over the break about memory and
the Greeks got a memory problem he remembers everything it's photographic
okay it's all a real vivid living quality and all of that sort of stuff
and most people are either a one out of focus and so whatever they do remember
it's kind of blurry and fuzzy or the aperture is not open enough and they
cannot see at all just think about that for a moment ladies and gentlemen about
capturing what you see and just how important it might wind up being trust
me little bits of information here and there can be very very very interesting
and if you actually instead of just listen to it and think about it and and
digest it and swallow it and actually use that information go out and make
something happen with it you're unstoppable there's a lot of knowledge
out there a lot of knowledge a lot of it's very useful some of it not so
useful my knowledge of the who's the Republican candidates and what have you
that's not useful information that's a waste of time Joe in LA calling in
what's up man real nice nice yeah absolutely yeah I was listening your
comment you know about losing hope and stuff like that but don't lose hope man
cuz my hope I told any before comes from people like yourself and people like
Vinny who take the time to spread the information that's vital you know for
humanity and for our friends and family I have a girlfriend for about two years
we're going to celebrate our two-year anniversary she's a non-truther she
doesn't really like to talk about a lot of stuff that I talked to her about
because it kind of depressing to her but I would suggest you know just have fun
whenever you can take some time away from the movement go out and date lots
of girls and meanwhile you know you still do what you're doing and with
your Facebook friends I'm the same way I almost my posting all about truth I've
taken about two months off of Facebook and don't want to overwhelm my friends
but at the same time I'm reinvigorated reinvigorated I'm gonna go back on
there and in two months worth of stuff that's been on the news I'm sure some
of the people that have been warning now are going to be probably listening a
little bit more since they see stuff on the news that's happening with the
drones and with the bottling of for the women and children in American airports
so just hang in there bro and don't don't lose hope man because I could say
15 years ago the movement was not even a fraction of what it is today I meet
people on the streets and it's just amazing sometimes they already know
what's going on and I think we we've already hit the 100th monkey and we're
about to the third world order there they're scared they know that we were on
to them and they're trying to figure out what what what their next move is going
to be but I keep spreading a word man and have fun as much as you can and try
to enjoy life as much as possible well that's that's sage advice and I follow
that advice to the letter every day I'm constantly attempting to amuse myself I
mean why do you think I deliver so many lame puns on this show because they
amuse me they may really tick people off that are listening in and what have you
but it amuses me so I do it and I'm acting under the assumption though that
it's the older people in the truth movement you're talking about how the
truth movement 10 15 years ago used to be a fraction well imagine somebody like
let's say who am I looking at on my desktop here G Edward Griffin I got a
picture of G Edward Griffin there and he'd been in the movement for like what 60
years something like that plus and yeah I mean doing all this hard-out work
exposing scumbaggery like to the ninth degree and the Quigley formula and or and
and and the creature from Jekyll Island and I asked him you know what's kind of
going on with this thing here how can you see us coming through I mean I'm young
I'm energetic I want to see everything happen now and he says well you know
when I was young and energetic and I wanted to see happen now I realized
something very important that the world doesn't move as fast as I want it to but
it does move what you got to do is instead of looking for exactly what you
want to see you look for the signs of what you want to see coming about all
right so if you want to have a look and and and be hopeful about the truth
movements and everything like that you need only look at your window you need
only tune in to radio we are everywhere now absolutely the same gentleman you
mentioned he he said it's taking the new world order a hundred years to put their
plan in motion least here in the United States of America and it's gonna take a
process of those of us who are aware to take back take back those chiefs of
power by running for office by becoming teachers by simply just speaking to
people and educated people around us and that's what's happening I could see it
happening even inside inside the Ron Paul movement with regard to what's
happening this week and a lot of states a lot of Ron Paul people are trying to
make a change from the inside I'm kind of losing hope as far as trying to
change establishment I'm almost on the point of preparing myself anarchist but
you know look for the signs is there any sign that the establishment has learned
its lesson and is changing itself no just think about this instead okay we
are the establishment now do you see us improving growing taking more control
becoming more visible becoming stronger yes in every single direction we are
taking over we are expanding every single corporation out there that works
for the new world order has truth is working for them now people who were
working there quietly happily slaving away and some truth just wouldn't let
them go and I'm just like take the DVD take the DVD we're so persistent and
that's what I like about people who have truth on their side versus those who
have eyes on their side those who have lies basically have an ideology built
upon sand and and it's very easy to tip those little houses over they have to
they have to say a thousand lies before somebody will believe it but somebody
with the truth can only say it once and it'll bowl that house of cards full of
BS and this is what is I find very encouraging ultimately is that they
have to try literally a thousand times as hard to be half as effective as all
of us because we're too many okay and I think that's why ultimately they want to
get rid of us all yeah I agree I think there's nothing more gratifying than
seeing the look on her face especially when you show the YouTube videos of
activists going and throwing a wrench into the machine on my television on the
radio and it's hilarious because like you said we're we're in there we have
moles everywhere we have people who are we're converting the mind even of those
who consider themselves part of the establishment because they realize that
their families are on the line as well so anyways Vinny and your guests my break
is over I usually call during work so I actually call during a break thanks for
the call another mole in the new world order system working away there all
right yeah yeah I love slavery it's good okay now we don't have any more callers
at this particular moment so one thing I wanted to ask you Greg I mean people
people keep asking me this question what gives you hope oh that's a really good
question and that's all I try to spread but it's it's it's more of it's not what
they think when I try to tell them what to have hope for and what one quick way
to look at it is if you look at a body of information that's been always right in
the past I mean spot-on in thousands of details you can pretty much count on it
being right about what it has to say about the future and that is the hope
that I'm that I'm referring to the problem with actually myself explaining
in shorthand where that hope actually lies is is difficult with most people
because it's based on their concept of time their concept of where they are and
the dominating primary forces and I believe once before we did discuss time
but the current time the way that people view time is completely engineered and
completely artificial yet a quick definition of time time is nothing more
than the recordation of events in in terms of the way we look at it in the
way we communicate and in the aspect of where we are in our existence if you
look at certain ancient bodies of knowledge they're called scriptures in
many part of the world they've been a hundred percent spot-on about events that
happened in the past and they're a hundred percent spot-on of events to
happen in the future the problem is we have like you mentioned the out-of-focus
everyone says well that's your interpretation everyone has an
interpretation but if you look at that word interpretation very carefully it
must be precise just like an ambassador who takes an interpreter with them you
know that interpreter must be precise it's not an opinion or a version it must
be precise so if we look at the ancient wisdom and what is coming upon us based
on a true measurement of time there's tremendous hope after this period and
one way to explain it is if you want to do a two-hour movie do you buy exactly
two hours of film or do you get a little extra film because you have to roll the
credits in the end we are in the credit part of this existence right now the
time ended let me just put it secularly I'll just get to the point time already
ended in 1998 the fall of 1998 you are in the credits part of the movie so you
have a movie here that's several millet many millennia long and the credits are
going to be rolling Oh roughly 30 to 45 years so you're you could judge based on
1998 coming on there is no such thing as 2012 or 1998 for that matter but I'm
just giving you a reference point kind of like converting inches to meters right
like you know for example yeah you see the real quick you know the the we this
they're teaching that is a heliocentric universe but from the earth it's a
geocentric in other words we see the Sun going around the earth from this
perspective and we see the stars in certain positions we're supposed to keep
record events with these precise instruments you know the day starts at
noon it doesn't start at midnight you see so that just changes things pretty
radically and your month starts with the moon and not the new moon the dark moon
but the full moon because the full moon rises in the east just like the Sun and
they're both exactly the same diameter and they switch places according to the
seasons so when you read ancient documents you won't find September or
October or November or December those are prefixes for September October November
December you see because September means 7 October means 8 November means 9 and
12 November as 11 when it really means 9 is 10 when it really means 8 you see so
it's all right in front of us you know are we gonna grab it and go or are we
gonna just leave it alone and let someone else deal with it now also I
find I was talking before about how I'm kind of like my own amusement generator
right well we also all have to understand that we are also our own hope generators
okay because you know what gives you hope either a one seeing something done
that gives you hope or doing something that gives you hope okay like let's say
for example if you never see anybody ambushing your politicians or your
corrupt scumbaggery in your particular town right and then you go out with a
camera you know what I'm gonna expose the scumbaggery myself and you do it you
upload it and not only have you given yourself hope self-positive reinforcement
but every single person who watches that video also gets to share in that hope
okay it's not difficult to generate it and it goes back to that old adage man
the only thing that is necessary for evil to succeed is for good men to do
nothing okay trust me ladies and gentlemen doing nothing is real easy can
you name me one easy road that leads to a good place no the good places are
always at the end of very long hard roads and you best be understanding of
that because the journey is what strengthens you is what builds you is
what makes you into who you are if you want to get from point A to point B what
is there in between is that connection between me thinking about something and
doing something the most important part okay the original concept doesn't matter
the action itself doesn't matter but when you bring them together when you
think and then you act you create something that didn't previously exist
that's what gives you hope creating something real via your own actions or
seeing somebody else do it and then that inspires you to do it yourself okay
it's real simple and I inspire myself every day
oh
welcome back ladies and gentlemen to the most operatic two hours in talk radio
broadcasting live on American freedom radio.com and incidentally the Vinnie
Eastwood show.com and now what was I talking to oh yeah yesterday after the
show had a Skype chat with a couple of the listeners and supporters and stuff
I think there was only like three of us there but we talked for like over
an hour and a half or something like that and and I liked it I like being
able to actually talk to the listeners you know just not be on air and nobody's
got any pressure there's no FCC regulations and they can ask me just
questions direct it's just a part of a discussion so I feel like doing that
again today so if you want to have a Skype chat with me and and some of the
other listeners or whatever that are in the chat room just go to the chat room
at the Vinnie Eastwood show.com and we'll give you the other Skype details
and and and all of that stuff there so just pop your Skype name in and I will
add you and then we'll have a convo after the show the Greek is my very
special guest and always awesome final segment here for final words of wisdom
the things that that really give us hope essentially I think I think that's what
a lot of truthers have been asking me predominantly lately they seem they seem
to ask me all the time about what gives me hope what encourages me or do I see
us winning or any stuff like that and I always give a really positive response
I'm very interested to know what the Greeks response to that kind of
questioning would be oh yeah yeah it's not a simple one but I could give you a
roundabout way that'll maybe convey what one approach let's say first of
all most people on this planet are living in an engineered reality what what
I mean by that is what they think they know doesn't even exist but they've been
sort of convinced that it does through the trickery of some sort of perception
of the senses and just they're either the level of apathy that's been instilled
or just ignorance of what is really going on once that once someone is
living in this engineered reality right and there's many many examples you've
given through the years as well whatever hope springs from that is is quickly
changed and and it becomes nothing more than hearsay rumor or gossip and you're
you're on this roller coaster you know we they promised us this and see it didn't
come and he promised us that it didn't come so the way we're what real hope is
the one way that I would convey it is to get your feet firmly planted on the
ground you know how many times do people you know just well here especially what
they call the the former US of a that someone asks you you know you ask them
you know how are you and then they say well I'm hanging in there and I say well
I like to have my feet on the ground so it just starts with the way you you think
the language that you use the next thing is can you start using objectivity to cut
through the information you're receiving and look at the sources objectively and
then start formulating a base of knowledge based on objectivity that would
be one approach and the other thing I would just I would say is is there are
three important things were the most important things to maintain a physical
body would be food clothing shelter right food clothing shelter so are you
optimizing your food are you optimizing your clothing and are you optimizing
your shelter your dwelling place and that would be a really good place to
start it and where you can actually see results and then you will build up the
hope and then you can ask anyone hey how is your hope going today you know great
man I found this out try that great you see it's not just a single thing we call
hope that we could just put up a banner and that's been done before no pun
intended but so that's just a quick roundabout way you see it's it's food
clothing shelter for the physical aspect and for the mental aspect are you being
objective or are you falling for a perceived engineered reality that's just
doesn't just doesn't exist and one way to explain that would be do as I say not
as I do right like you turn on the mainstream media everything's getting
better and you just you know turn off the TV look outside and everyone's
frowning and things are not getting better shops are closing you know people
are sicker and fatter and dumber and you know so which one is it mmm well I love
that I love that phrase I do as I say not as I do because I remember what was
it I was on Waiheke Island this one time and one of my mom's friends Gary he gets
out of the he gets out of the truck and he's going in to get a video and he took
and he tells us don't drive drunk boys and then as he gets back into the truck
after after getting his video he pulls a bottle of scotch out of it and takes a
sip and puts it back in the truck and he comes over to talk to us and he says do
as I say not as I do it's just great and it goes to show you that we're all
individuals right and drugs information love anger fear they all
react to different people differently because we're all snowflakes in a sense
aren't we like that yeah and here's the interesting part you see the once we
acknowledge this is on the subject of individuality that we are all are really
the same that's when the true individuality or the discrete benefit of
everyone sharing what they have will come forth you see when you force the
issue that we're all different and that you I mean when that's taught like for
example the the they teach competition is good but they never use the word
cooperation and when you look at when you look at the actual power base there
is no competition amongst them they're all cooperating but when they appear
they appear to be competing so they they never teach cooperation they teach
competition and if you go let's say the the finest restaurants are always in
what's called a restaurant district they're all right next to each other
they're not competing the finest clothing you find in the garment
districts you see you see they all group together so do you you know it does that
mean that this right here like an American Freedom Radio is part of the
truth district right and instead of having physical districts and outlet
shops and things of that nature we now have digital districts and what it does
is it allows people to shop for the finest information from from the home
essentially what it does is it brings the finest products within your reach
yeah it allows each one to excel and what they know and what they like to do
best and they don't feel hindered impaired or intimidated by someone else
in the same exact field right next to them who is also doing what they find
their best at doing it's working together it's the opposite what is the
opposite of something it can't be nothing no it can't be nothing it has to
be something else that allows equilibrium to happen right because
everything is moving and everything has a sense of opposition and attraction
well it's true nothing can't oppose something correct because nothing's
nothing doesn't exist correct so the the the so the whole concept of of the way
we view things is is very simple is if we don't know of certain process what we're
being told to do is correct or not how long do you have to observe its reaction
whether it's beneficial or not beneficial to say hey stop we can't we
shouldn't do things that way well I think it's about it's about you know
we're all searching for knowledge or whatever I'm starting to think that it's
it's not so much about searching for knowledge anymore it's about accepting
it's about accepting the realities like let's say for example you wanted to go
and accomplish something like I want to go be awesome the way to become awesome
is not to go and try and be awesome it's just to realize and accept that you
already are and you don't actually have to work that hard to be it and that
satisfaction really allows the awesomeness of Vinny Eastwood to come on
through absolutely and it's like that with everyone Vinny if you have an
inspiration when I say inspiration see all things come from inspiration it's a
feeling it's it's an and who and everyone's experienced at one point or
Dix some experience it more or less than others what we have you see such we've
got limited experience limited time but we've got infinite consciousness so
we've got infinite ability to explore okay it's kind of like wealth you can't
take it with you it only benefits you while you're still alive and that's what
knowledge does as well and just like wealth you can allow other people in
your descendants to inherit it and I think that's probably a good spot to
leave it Greg we are come to the end of the show thank you so much for coming on
for a full two hours it's been great man brilliant thanks very much man it's been
a privilege to be here thank you hmm and some people are asking are you ever
gonna get a website together because a lot of people were starting to ask me a
little bit about you as well yes yes I will but not now it's all about timing
though the right information at the right time and right now we'll just
trek along like this but you'll be one of the first to know thank you all right
well ladies and gentlemen best-case scenario you can hope for you can go to
the Vinny Eastwood show.com and up the very top there of the website there'll
be a little bar called featured interviews and the very first time I had
the Greek call in was after I interviewed George Norie so it's the
very top interview on that featured interviews page is me interviewing George
Norie and then the Greek calling in for about 40 minutes so there's some other
content there and so yeah I mean that's best I could do for you and and now we're
gonna have another archive and we're gonna have it on YouTube so when your
website is up and running Greek you'll have plenty of content to put on there
you'll see the Vinny Eastwood show ladies and gentlemen and we'll see you
again sometime enjoy your weekend