Unity is what we need with peace and love and harmony.
Unity is strength and assure success all for one and one for all.
Unity means solidarity.
United we stand, divided we fall.
Unity, please don't desert me.
You're the sweetest honey from the honey bee.
We need your sweetness like the core of the honey bee.
So please hear my plea.
Please don't desert me.
Another exciting edition.
Yes, I know you've all been waiting a very long time.
Since yesterday.
If you heard another episode of the Vinnie Eastwood Show live.
And all of those of you listening in on the archives,
think of maybe that one point or two, you know,
saying that you want to call in.
Let's say, for example, you listen to an archive show and you're like,
oh, man, I would have loved to have called in for that.
Well, seriously, hold that thought.
Whatever it was at the time that you wanted to say,
call up later about it, you know, send us a message.
We can get you up on air.
It'll be all good.
Because you understand how the platform of the show works, right?
It's about giving all those other people a voice.
You know, there's other people who don't have radio shows
and YouTube channels like I do.
You know, I may be able to put stuff together,
but ultimately I ain't got the info.
I don't have the content to fill that airtime with.
Conveniently, though, there's many activists and whistleblowers
all over the world who routinely donate extraordinarily large amounts
of their time to expose something that I've come to identify as scumbaggery.
Now, we were talking earlier with my mate Steve Moyer.
I think he's in Canada at the moment.
He lived in New Zealand a few years.
And he wants to put it in the dictionary.
You know, there's the UrbanDictionary.com.
You know, just put it on in there, add scumbaggery to the global language.
It'll be great.
Definitions, on the other hand, these are the ones that Steve's come up with.
One who steals from others' even close friends,
who rats out others' even close friends for small personal gain.
One who cheats, bribes, lies, and steals for personal gain.
One who offers other prizes to risk their own lives in the process
by eating a Cheetos bag.
One who threatens others with hired thugs
because he isn't man enough to do it himself.
I suppose, you know, those are things that do encompass
a lot of the general characteristics of somebody who engages in scumbaggery.
There are many dimensions to scumbaggery.
Like, for instance, the betraying other people,
which has been touched upon here.
Loyalty is something that kind of precludes you from being called a scumbag.
If you've got loyalty towards the human race and good stuff and what have you.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe it's kind of puritanical.
I'm not 100% sure what the definition should be.
I just created the word.
I don't know what the meaning is.
But it's pretty straightforward.
Somebody who engages in and acts like a scumbag, hence scumbaggery.
Scumbags are defined as low, disgusting individuals
who have no loyalty, no faith, no honor.
Literally only live to be a burden on mankind
through their various mechanical means, financial,
and manipulation through the media in general.
In fact, there's just been a new bit of legislation passed speaking of scumbaggery.
The Honorable Simon Power,
who, after a few short years in Parliament,
wound up getting the top job at Westpac Bank,
which incidentally does all the government's banking.
In Australia, that would be illegal.
He's got it under his head,
probably whispered in his ear by World Bank
or other intelligence agency-oriented organizations
and associated dignitaries.
But they're going to try and, well,
shall we say regulate social media?
Now, I think that the whole point of social media
is that it is unregulated.
People can say what they want and whatever.
If you want to be on mainstream media,
you have an awful lot of rules that you have to comply by, okay?
That's why they choose not to say a whole lot of stuff
because they don't know 100% whether or not it's true.
They could just add the tagline, allegedly.
But, of course, you don't want people to be enlightened
that there are deeper things afoot, really.
One chopper crash is one chopper crash.
It's random.
One chopper crashing with virtually all of SEAL Team 6 in it
after killing Osama bin Laden.
Well, about a month or some amount of time
after killing Osama bin Laden, allegedly,
against standard operating procedure,
loading too many troops onto a chopper.
Isn't that strange, you know?
But the media didn't report little details like that.
No, because that would make you think,
hmm, did they really kill bin Laden?
Is this boogeyman really dead?
It doesn't even matter because we've got another boogeyman.
We had that Qaddafi.
Oh, wait, now he's dead.
Who's the next boogeyman?
Oh, Syria.
They're having a civil war in Syria, aren't they?
Oh, yeah, that's what the UN general,
what's her name,
chief of some description of random,
obscure UN declaration name
of some faceless person you never probably ever elect,
that person says,
oh, Syria's in the middle of a civil war
and we have to intervene.
Well, hasn't their argument always been
we have to intervene?
Have they ever changed their tune?
This is what scumbaggery is about.
Somebody who consistently lies to you
and does the direct opposite.
And if they lie to you
and do something really good for you,
like, for example,
no, no, I'm not getting you a birthday present
and then you turn up with something really awesome.
That's not scumbaggery.
If you lie to somebody and say,
oh, there's huge amounts of Iraqi forces
mounting on your border,
Saudi Arabia,
and we want to put bases all through your country
to protect you.
And they'll be permanent bases, of course,
so that we can station US troops in Saudi Arabia
at all times.
Oh.
Well, can you show us the satellite photographs
to prove that those tanks from Iraq
are actually massing on our border?
Well, you're going to have to trust us.
That's scumbaggery.
It's not something that grinds on you in a good way.
In the deep in the middle of the night
clubbing sense of the word, grinding.
It doesn't feel that nice.
It's not terribly fantastic in any way, shape or form.
It hurts.
You lose money over it.
You have bad experiences because of it.
And ultimately, sometimes people really do get killed
because of this general rule of thumb
called scumbaggery,
which I believe quite possibly
would encompass virtually every single politician.
Perhaps a few exceptions,
but ultimately the signs will still be there
through the events that pass forward.
I think that's another thing that people really need to understand
about politics in general.
It's freaking boring.
These people are droning on about this, that and the other
way to enslave you and take away your rights.
It just gets dull after a while.
Yes, I get it.
You're repeating to me and consistently taking away my rights.
I know, I'm a slave.
I get it.
You don't need to harp on about it.
This is the kind of scumbaggery
that really, really goes on the whole time.
That's how you define parties.
Look at what they said, then look at what they did.
If they match up, then you can trust them again.
If they don't match up, and in some parties' cases,
not one single thing that they said they'd do,
they actually did.
Those kind of parties, those kind of politicians.
Track record is the surefire way
to see whether or not somebody is worth
placing even a modicum of trust in.
Because the absence of scumbaggery
is very rare in the political class
or the high-level business world,
finance and the media,
you'll often see a lot of backstabbing
and general scumbaggery that will go on
inside organizations at those very top levels.
They're not up front with each other.
They're not honest.
They're always thinking about themselves
and how they can get to the top,
as opposed to an activist,
which is on the other end of this polar extreme scale,
who doesn't think quite so much about themselves.
They're more thinking about what the ramifications are
for everybody else.
They say if nobody else is going to make
a huge song and a dance about it, then I have to
because I was the one who just realized
what was going on.
That's what makes it happen.
You have to realize that it's your job.
If you come up with an idea,
it's not your job to go tell somebody else
who's already big and what have you.
Don't go and tell them the idea.
What you do is you put your heart into it.
Develop it.
Don't just think about it.
If you want to do something great,
don't just put your mind to it.
Put your heart into it.
Really, really put some effort in
and help to develop that idea.
It doesn't matter whether you have an idea
for a radio show or a song or a video
or anything that you can do on a computer these days,
a picture, a video game.
There are so many ways of now manipulating
the human mind that the media
and massive entertainment companies are using,
like the 3D glasses, for example.
Mate, that stuff is mesmerizing.
It's like as if you'd never watched TV
and suddenly gotten sucked in like a zombie again.
Unbelievable amounts of manipulative power
can be in there.
Now, manipulation in itself is kind of inanimate.
It doesn't imply, per se,
not to a very strict definition
of a bad intention.
For example, someone could manipulate a pencil
to write a great screenplay.
I could manipulate you into thinking
that you're strong, powerful, intelligent,
and that you can get the job done
and make your community a better place.
That's manipulation on a good note.
On the bad note, and as we all should be realizing right now,
unless, of course, you're still utterly naive,
that the world is not run by nice people.
They have nice people that are masqueraded
around all the place,
but they're not the ones really running the show.
They're not the ones who get camera time, okay?
The people who really, really
have inordinate amounts of influence
don't really like having their names all over the tabloids.
Not generally.
The wealthiest of the wealthiest of the wealthy,
nobody ever heard of them.
That's what we talk about when we talk about
the hidden hand in politics,
and that's why all these political parties
always do the exact same thing.
If not worse than the last guy.
You nearly see any improvement
because that is how the structure is rigged.
Only scumbags rise to the top.
Have you ever seen a pond
and it hasn't been cleaned for a long time?
Where does the scum well up?
It wells up at the top of the water on the surface.
That is the reason why these people make it to the top.
It's because that's where they're naturally suited.
That's the natural mode of progression.
You understand your own needs and desires,
and that's about it.
As long as you don't give a crap about anybody else, really,
you make a great politician
because you just do precisely what your advisors
tell you to do.
Who appoints all these people?
Who decides the appointment?
It's not like the president himself
knows intricately each and every single one of these guys
in his background cabinet and what they're all about.
Maybe they've been working together
for a number of years or so,
but hey, what are their other connections?
Do you ever wonder about the other people
in the background?
Is that something that has ever glossed your mind?
What are they showing you on the TV?
What are they showing you on the news?
Does this make sense?
Why did he change his whole direction right then?
Right then we start talking about
international finance and the Federal Reserve.
Okay, I find that as a patriot filmmaker
or whatever you want to call yourself,
I think the labels are unnecessary entirely,
but everybody just loves them, don't they?
You know, I'm a business account manager.
As long as you've got several names
about what you are as your status or whatever,
that's very nice, isn't it?
So why don't you just call yourself
an admiral filmmaker or a presidential filmmaker?
This is something that you can
just have some fun with, I reckon.
Anyway, point is, if you want to go out
and if you want to have these politicians
ask questions that you want to see asked,
you have to do it.
It's unfortunate, but that's the reality.
If you see it and you want to see it done,
you can think you can do it better,
then by all means, go and do it,
and you'll feel really good about it too,
especially if you capture it on camera.
You listen to the Vinnie Eastwood Show,
we'll be right back.
402-237-2525.
Please call in.
Back in a moment.
Now you and your family and friends
can enjoy the cleanest, most delicious
and healthy drinking water anytime,
even while traveling, camping,
at sporting events or in emergency situations.
The Berkey Light removes bacteria, cysts,
parasites and harmful chemicals
to below detectable levels.
It also reduces nitrates and unhealthy minerals
like lead and mercury,
while leaving in the beneficial
and nutritional minerals your body needs.
Berkey Light is so powerful,
it can even purify raw, untreated water
from remote lakes and streams.
And the optional PF2 filters even remove fluoride.
The Berkey Light LED,
with its rechargeable lighting system,
can be used as a night light or camp light.
To view or purchase your Berkey water system
and replacement filters,
please visit American Freedom Radio's website
at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and click the Berkey banner.
Once again, that's AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and click the Berkey water banner.
Not yet available in Iowa.
Do you realize every day
we are being put under constant stress
from wireless radiation?
What's worse is that you don't even know
that it's happening.
It puts as much stress on our body
as if we had a constant viral infection,
draining our energy and samping our strength
or just making us irritable and fatigued.
These wireless fields are being emitted
from computers, microwaves, mobile phones,
power lines and any electrical appliance.
Now there is a solution.
A group of research engineers in New Zealand
have come up with an active shielding device
that shields you from wireless radiation
at a cellular level.
Blue Shield comes in three models,
a household, portable and USB
that plugs into any computer.
The great thing about Blue Shield
is it is very affordable and guaranteed to last.
A one-off purchase will see you being protected
for years to come.
Visit AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and click on the Blue Shield banner.
Blue Shield, brought to you by
TheVinnieEastwoodShow.com
Following a radiological or nuclear event,
radioactive iodine may be released into the air
and then be breathed into the lungs.
Radioactive iodine may also contaminate
the local food supply and get into the body
through food or through drink.
When radioactive materials get into the body
through breathing, eating or drinking,
the thyroid gland quickly absorbs the chemical.
Radioactive iodine absorbed by the thyroid
can then injure the gland.
But you can protect yourself with used potassium iodide
which acts to block radioactive iodine
from being taken into the thyroid gland
and can help protect this gland from injury.
To take advantage of very special rates,
click on the banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and don't forget our convenient delivery service,
Ideal Health New Zealand,
leaders in alternative health.
That's AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and click on the Ideal Health New Zealand button.
Proudly brought to you by TheVinnieEastwoodShow.com
Are you suffering from issues related to
angina pain, high blood pressure,
congestive heart failure, unbalanced cholesterol,
irregular heartbeats, clogged arteries?
If so, you are not alone.
Millions of people are suffering from
one or more of these problems.
If you'd like to live your life free of sickness,
pain and fear,
live your life with increased vitality,
energy and youthfulness
and experience your body healing itself,
then this might be the most important message
you'll ever hear.
An effective 100% organic nutritional supplement
is now available.
Heart and Body Extract is an exclusive formula
of wild crafted and organic herbs.
It is extremely effective and starts to work within days.
Get your Heart and Body Extract today
by visiting heartandbody.com
or by calling 866-295-5305,
866-295-5305
or heartandbody.com
Yo, what's up? Check this out.
The voice of the revolution.
American Freedom Radio.
Your life as it has been is over.
Radio Free Humanity on AMR.
Listen to The Paradigm Shift,
Saturday night, 10pm central.
www.frontierradio.com
Welcome back, oh yeah, I like that song, doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo, oh yeah, welcome back to the Vanilla
Eastwood show, taking it easy when you're a day ahead of the United States and it's
Friday, that would mean it's Saturday for me, yes, you guessed it, broadcasting live
from the future from the fabulously fluoridated capital of Auckland, New Zealand, the island
chained nation sitting pretty in the sunny slave South Pacific, and we often have lots
of international guests on the show, and I don't know, I like the idea of listening
to people who have different accents from all over the world and stuff like that, I
love accents, they're just fabulous to listen to, and I think that's true of everybody,
you know, somebody comes in with a nice accent of some description, it's like, oh wow, I
can listen to that, it's about right, isn't it, so you bring on people from the Uber kingdom,
from Ireland, Scotland, even some Dutch and some German people, you know, this is what's
very interesting about bringing on so many international guests, is that it's the same
story over and over again, it just sounds different, because the same crap that's going
down every day in your home country is going down to lesser or greater degrees, but it's
still going on, and you can see the very obvious similarities everywhere else too, that's why
they call it a new world order, because there ain't no place you can escape to, unless of
course you can manage to manifest some description of rocket ship, and get the F out of this
galaxy, which I don't think is a possibility, ergo, you've got to take back what should
be rightfully yours, okay, the system has gotten so bad that, well, it's basically,
you play in card games against somebody who can cheat, and if you call them a cheater,
he shoots you at the card table, that's how politics, isn't it, president can lie, in
fact, can they tell the truth, that's a better question, they can knowingly misrepresent
their policies, people still vote for them, and it just doesn't make any sense, I'm going
to see if the Greek can actually help me out with that, the Greek, welcome to the show mate,
hey Vinny, long time no speak, good to hear you're still on and doing well, oh yeah,
I want to tell you something man, there have been like a flood of donations that came through
after I announced last week I was getting kicked out of my house, nearly $1400 has been
donated in about a week and a bit, because I'm being kicked out, the target's like $2000,
but we're not too far off now, got about another 6-7 days in it, but I've got to confess something
man, I actually cried, it was so overwhelming, the huge amount of support that I was getting,
it just threw me for a lope. Well excellent man, that's great, and if I were to send you
anything it would be anonymous so you'd know, I just want to chime in and just say hello
and I'll tell you just personally some thoughts, it seems like this planet doesn't even feel like
we're on a planet, it feels like we're on an island, it feels like wherever you look all
over the world, whatever is being said, especially in the mainstream media, it seems like they're
all saying the same thing, it seems like the whole planet's been reduced to a little village
and it's bizarre to me, what happened to the diversity? Yeah, it's, I don't know,
the diversity is you get welcomed off a plane by a little person and he goes,
welcome to fantasy island, that's what we're living on now,
total fantasy island with a little midget guide. Right, yeah, because I kind of was curious about
New Zealand and we're watching it and just change New Zealand to US or EU or anywhere else,
it's the same stuff. Well this is great because our cultures are now interchangeable,
New Zealander can go straight to America and easily integrate the language and all of that,
vice versa, Americans can come to New Zealand, start hanging out with New Zealanders. Because
there's no language barrier and our cultures have been assimilated into more or less the
same homogenous stew of moronity, if that's even a word. McDonald's, Levi's, Walmart,
you mean like that? Yeah, with the statin drugs and the burgers and all. Yeah,
yeah, it's interesting, isn't it? In fact, they were proposing that in London, I think,
that they were going to give out statin drugs with the McDonald's, you know,
in a little thing like a salt shaker, there's a couple of pills in there. Really? Yeah. Yeah,
well, if you could count me out. Well, that's not the worst stuff I've heard,
the worst is the Belgian government, which is where the head of the EU is, of course,
they want to, instead of burying people, because it's bad for the environment,
dissolve them down and flush them into the sewer system. I don't think they'll be flushing them,
I think they might end up as protein supplements at McDonald's again. Yep,
soylent greeners, people. Yeah, you know, like, I've been reading some comments,
you know, on George Orwell, and he was seemingly part of the inside group,
and his writings of 1984 were actually, let's say, directed to be a disclosure, right? Yeah,
pretty much. It's like, this is, people, look, this is how you're gonna live unless you do
something, and naturally, people, thinking it's fiction, don't do anything, and it winds up.
The soylent green may not be that far off, huh? No, soylent green's already here,
there is, the Chinese are now breaking down and drying up and turning into a powder,
fetuses, and putting them into health supplements, so they just give you, like,
a capsule of ground-up dead baby fetus, and they've been, they're selling all over the world,
so there's a lot of women out there who are taking collagen capsules, and they don't realize
that they're eating dead Chinese babies. Same with McDonald's and what have you. Allegedly,
and this was, there was this video online, I can't 100% verify it, it shocked me,
but it wouldn't surprise me, of this Uber synagogue of Satan guy, some description of
Jewish satanic cult, that's very highly connected, allegedly, and they kidnap and sacrifice children,
and because they own all the meat grinding works and things like that for the big agribusiness
and what have you, they just toss the remains in with the cows, and now everybody, when they're
having their hamburger or their sausage at McDonald's, their own children's what they get.
So, Soylent Green's already here, in the very least, in a minor capacity, there's also some use of fetal
cells and things of that nature that go into flavorings for soft drinks, allegedly.
Well, I think it's part of this kind of sick plot to corrupt human DNA, there's even now baby fetus,
they use their kidneys or their livers, if they're aborted, to grow viruses on for the vaccines,
and so they take little chunks of that, so you're getting minuscule amounts of human DNA
injected directly into your bloodstream, so I'm not sure exactly what that causes,
but it certainly can't be good, let alone the formaldehyde and the thimerosal, which is 50%
mercury, that you also got dead baby fetal cells in there as well.
You know, I think it might be also part of their occult black magic practice, you know,
that's why the sheepskin diploma, right, has to be from an animal, right, where the blood is shed,
it's all ritual, that's why you have the spelling must be correct, the spell, get it?
So, yeah, so I think these things are actually part of an occult ritual, like
the cliché of the voodoo, you know, the chicken's blood, you know,
the voodoo stuff that everyone's kind of sort of familiar with, they're not really familiar with
how out of hand it's gone, you know, I mean, I wasn't really quite familiar with half of the
things you mentioned there, so. Well, you know, I think the person who
thinks that they know everything obviously knows nothing, and the person who believes that they
probably know nothing probably knows enough. Well, you know, I like to say I don't know
anything, but I can share with you what I found out. Yeah, and that's why I love the word allegedly.
You can tag it onto anything, it's brilliant, because you don't have to know exactly down to
a minutiae detail, like if you ask any physicist or anything, had they measured the sun's rotation
around the earth with a calculated tool and measuring device or what have you with opposite
double blind test to see whether or not the sun actually goes around the earth or the earth goes
around the sun, had they actually done that experiment to find out by themselves, none of them
would have, okay, it's just science just tells you this, okay, and you believe it because it seems
reasonable at the time, allegedly some other people used devices to figure this stuff out,
okay, it's knowledge, somebody comes out to you with new evidence on the other hand,
you can't stick to your original thing if your evidence has suddenly become defunct, oh,
they've actually never told us about that, tell me more, that should be the response,
as opposed to you're a kook, you're crazy, get the hell out of my office.
Yeah, well, all these measurements also are based on our perceptions and our senses, and our senses
can be subjective or deceived or, you know, inaccurate at the moment, so why say, you know,
when you're just really using your senses, right? Yeah, and you know, everybody says, you know,
you know? Well, hey, you know, like you mentioned earlier, you know, about previous shows,
I went back to the, I think it was Gorilla Media, forgive me if it's incorrect, but you have two
sites, and at one point we brought up the discussion of the earth not going around the sun, and you
promptly prompted, you posted a video, I believe it's a doctor something or other out of India,
was showing that we're just actually being trailing, we're trailing behind the sun,
because everything's moving. What did you think of that, and what prompted you to post that?
Well, I just thought it was interesting stuff, and if it's interesting to me, it'll probably
be interesting to other people. Well, okay, great, you know, I was just wondering if we
have a convert or not, that you need to be converted, but you know, the current models
they're showing us are absolutely false, the planetary models, and it gives you a little
bit more understanding of the things around you, too, you know, when you kind of, you know,
all the small stuff, all the big stuff is made up of small stuff, and everything is behaving the
same way, you know? Yeah, it's like the levels of micro-bioactivity or something like that.
There's this guy, I believe it was like 1910, 1914 or something, he created this microscope
using granite crystal, and he was able to get something like 50 to 60,000 times,
up to 180,000 times, allegedly, magnification. Oh, right, well, I mean, it might have been
life, right? Yeah, right, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, and I think standard scopes today
don't even approach that, yeah. 10,000, 10,000 times, and what he discovered is when he looked
inside a cell, he found out that that cell was made up of other cells, and then he looked inside
those other cells, and you find that those cells were made up of other cells, and he kept going,
you know, he was just keeping going down the magnification, and he said, basically, life is
life upon life upon life without end into infinity, both upwards and downwards, okay?
There are infinitesimally small to the infinite species of life, you know, levels of it,
and why wouldn't that be upwards as well? Because I kind of thought of, like,
everybody talks about God, right, and I thought that God was like this
macro-organism, like a cell is a micro-organism. A macro-organism is much, much larger, much bigger
that's comprised of all the current, say, life on the earth. That's what God is, and we're all
connected to each other because we're actually just this one giant organism with all this diversity
of life amongst it, just like when you look into the cells and find other ones.
I always thought that was the answer.
Yeah, you can actually do that experiment very simply by standing between two mirrors. You see
how it goes to infinity? That's my point with the solar system, you know, there's nothing orbiting
anything that I've noticed. You're either behind it, in front of it, or beside it, and everything
is dynamic and moving. So that energy level that you just spoke of, it's like a fractal. I think
the Mandelbrot fractals, you know, if you take a head of broccoli and you pull off a floret,
it looks like a head of broccoli, and if you take a tweezer and take off one of those little
tiny little buds, look at it under a magnifying glass, it looks like the whole head of broccoli,
and so on, and so on, and so forth. And then when you get down to the cellular level,
it no longer looks like a head of broccoli, but like you mentioned, those cells again repeat.
So where does it end?
It doesn't. Ultimately it doesn't. We're at one level of consciousness out of the
infinite amount of levels of consciousness as far as I'm concerned. We could wind up a bacteria
someday, or we could wind up a planet someday of a level of consciousness, and then you'd just
be one of the planets amongst all the others. Who knows?
Well, let me just propose this thought. Could we possibly just be a thought
emanation from the Creator? Because all evidence shows that everything is energy.
Well, I would never rule anything out, because that would mean I know more than God.
You listen to the Vinny Eastwood show. My guest caller is the Greek, and if he's willing,
we can probably stand on to the other side of this and continue this conversation.
You can join the conversation to 402-237-2525. That's 402-237-2525. We'll be right back.
What would your life be like if you woke up each morning with new vitality,
feeling better than you have in years, and you noticed a difference in your sleeping patterns,
blood sugar levels, and had a sense of well-being overall? There's something that is changing
thousands of people's lives, and you could be one of them. It's called Heart and Body
Extract. Sharon Harris, co-creator of Heart and Body Extract,
talks about the positive effects of Heart and Body Extract.
What happens with the formula Heart and Body Extract is it's giving the body the necessary
vitamins, minerals, amino acids, enzymes, and phytonutrients so the body will heal itself. And
yes, the body does have the ability to balance blood pressure, balance cholesterol, clean and
unclog the arteries. It can also work on balancing the circulation for diabetics. So the body is an
amazing thing. It simply needs some help so it has the tools to heal itself.
Heart and Body Extract gets results. To order your two-month supply, call now,
toll-free at 866-295-5305. Order online at HBextract.com.
The First Amendment and the Bill of Rights limits the government's power by ensuring
freedom of speech and preserves the rights of the people. Every day that passes,
our rights gradually slip away. It's time to take a stand and let the government know
that we are tired of losing our rights. LibertyStickers.com will allow you to express
your rights and allow millions of people to see you stand up for what you believe in.
LibertyStickers.com carries the largest selection of bumper stickers online,
ranging from political to humorous. As always, you can find your favorite stickers that protest
the war and the precedent. Don't see what you're looking for? LibertyStickers will custom-make
stickers that will get your message across for all Americans to see. Go to LibertyStickers.com
and see pre-made stickers that will get everyone talking. That's LibertyStickers.com,
or call 877-873-9626. LibertyStickers, the world's most dangerous stickers.
What is it that's in your home that causes grown men to cower and children to run for cover?
Food storage. That's right. Food storage shouldn't be scary. At Simply Your Food,
we are the premier providers of long-term, storable, GMO, and MSG-free meats, veggies,
fruit, dairy, and pantry essentials like powdered butter. We even have a gluten-free line.
Food storage shouldn't be scary. Let Simply Your Food help you with your food storage needs. Go to
SimplyYourFood.com or call 866-251-7511 and let us take the scary out of food storage. Go to
SimplyYourFood.com or call 866-251-7511 and let us take the scary out of food storage.
Now you and your family and friends can enjoy the cleanest, most delicious, and healthy drinking
water anytime, even while traveling, camping, at sporting events, or in emergency situations.
The percolite removes bacteria, cysts, parasites, and harmful chemicals to below detectable levels.
It also produces nitrates and unhealthy minerals like lead and mercury,
while leaving in the beneficial and nutritional minerals your body needs.
Percolite is so powerful it can even purify raw, untreated water from remote lakes and streams,
and the optional PF2 filters even remove fluoride. The percolite LED with its rechargeable lighting
system can be used as a nightlight or a camp light. To view or purchase your percolite water
system and replacement filters, please visit American Freedom Radio's website at American
Freedom Radio.com and click the percolite banner. Once again, that's AmericanFreedomRadio.com and
click the Berkey Water Banner. Not yet available in Iowa.
You're listening to the Future of Talk.
American Freedom Radio.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Listen to Time for Him, hosted by Casper Leach. Afternoons Monday through Friday,
12 p.m. to 1 p.m. Central, only on American Freedom Radio.
So
there must be some kind of way out of here
I said
I said a joker to the thief
There's too much confusion
I can't get no relief
Business man there will drink my wine
Clown man dig my earth
None will level on the mind
Nobody up in his place
Oh yeah, welcome back to the Vinnie Eastwood Show. Talking about scumbaggery
of varying degrees with my very special guest, the Greek. Now, you talk about existence and
you say you're here just to take notes. Does that mean that you're a student? And if so,
who's the teacher? Well, the student, I usually say, teaches the teacher.
It's called a feedback loop, isn't it? Apparently, yeah. The reason I say I'm taking notes as an
observer is I'm trying to be impeccable about being objective about things, you see.
How could you be impeccably objective? Well, discernment, asking questions and knowing the
history of things. Okay, okay. That's just one way. You know, it's kind of like going to the gym,
Vinnie. You know, it's like a muscle. And the more you use it, the stronger it gets. I don't know if
that's another way of describing it. And if you stop using it, it starts to get all floppy and
flabby and all over the place and causes you nothing but trouble. Yeah, it could, right?
Straight up. Well, you're talking about a fitness of the mind. Perhaps, yeah.
You know, there's an interesting concept there because a lot of people worry about their weight.
But how many people worry about how freaking stupid they are?
Well, I'm glad you said that and I didn't have to.
Well, that's something I like to do for people, just to say what they can't.
Because I always say, when in doubt, blame Vinnie.
So could it be that it's just laziness? You know, slothfulness, you think? Do you think it's
encouraged? I think it's encouraged. Oh, I'm not sure if it's encouraged per se, but it's
certainly facilitated. Look at the amount of offers you have every day of getting yourself fat.
Look at how many offers you have every day of keeping yourself fit. Not a lot in the fit
department, is there? You know, you go to a supermarket and you go through the impulse item
section. How many of those items are promoting healthy life and healthy living,
free of chemicals and poisons and sugars and sweets?
Yeah, you know, I've been looking very much at what they call the American obesity problem.
And then I looked at the actual intake, the quality of the intake of their food.
And they're obese, not only because they're eating too much, but
the mechanism that the food is so devoid of nutrition, they're actually malnourished.
That's why they're obese. For example, have you ever seen photographs of the,
I'm sure you have, of places in Africa and famine, and you see the children on the dirt
floor with their distended stomachs, right? There's a similar case where there's a balance
of toxicity and malnourishment that has led to the obesity. And you couple that with the paradox
how the more chemicals and the more devoid of nutrition the food is in the supermarket,
the cheaper it is. So you have more incentive of buying the cheaper,
more toxic, devoid of nutrition food. There's so many layers of incentive.
Like the first incentive that you see is the primary colors. You know, you'll see the
advertisements are always in a red, yellow or blue. These are the primary colors. These are
the things that get your attention. And, you know, have a look at all the major fast food chains.
Have they got red? What about KFC? What about Pizza Hut? What about McDonald's? What about
Burger King? There's a myriad of them. Have they got blue? You know, again, you've got Burger King,
you've got Pepsi. The list goes on. So maybe objectively, if people had an objective
approach to the food, they wouldn't recognize it as something, let's say, edible. So they
have to stimulate them, you think, with conviction of color and advertising?
When people diet, they have a couple of real strange reactions. Firstly,
they start to get a lot healthier. They have regular bowel movements. Their skin clears up
and they're able to breathe or walk again. And life just seems to be a lot more comfortable.
And then you take them back and you go give them some of this crap food and their body rejects it
and it makes them start feeling sick. Your body will adapt to whatever conditions or whatever
stuff that you're giving it and respond accordingly. If you want to live a life that's incredibly
depressing, hard to live through, tiring and exhausting, then you have a diet of absolute
crapola for you, which will also put you in grumpy moods and later on give you really bad,
debilitating diseases. You know, talk about quality of life and the type of drugs and
everything like that that they'll give with you. And don't tell you to cut out the crap diet. No,
don't do that because that'll just get rid of all your symptoms so we can't treat you for them
with expensive drugs. All right. You know, there's the good old one to see going on
with everything. And there's a good movie called Training Day with Denzel Washington.
I don't know if you've seen this movie, Greg, but he says this stuff is chest, not checkers.
And it's a very, very apt description of how drug companies, fast food companies and
all these other various, but which are all owned by a very small clique of people in the world
anyway, conspire on every single subset of level of your life experience, whether you're watching TV,
driving down the road, you're going to see their products, you're going to have them advertised
for them, you're going to be awash in them, they're going to tell you that they're cheap,
they're going to tell you that they're tasty, and they'll repeat it to you over and over and
over again. So it's virtually inevitable that you will have something. And only very few people I've
ever met either haven't tried it or have done it and just basically never will and stay healthy.
Interesting. That's an interesting analogy with chest because maybe there's a message in that,
right? You know, look at the player, the pieces in the chessboard versus the checkers, right?
The queen gets to go anywhere she wants, but taking the king, right, you see? So very interesting.
Yeah, well, queen can go anywhere she wants, except the city of London.
That's right. I think she has to walk behind the mayor, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the Lord Mayor. The Lord Mayor, of course.
Does DC have a Lord Mayor as well? Because I know Auckland now has one. We had like a
city of about 1.4 million people or something, and it was actually governed by seven different
city councils just for their particular areas, and they force amalgamated them all into one
against everybody's wishes, stole $28 billion worth of public assets. And now we have a Lord Mayor
who gets to handpick his unelected cabinet, and every single policy that they've been shunting out
ever since they got put into power had Agenda 21 written all over it.
Of course. Well, it goes back to the old thing. Why does the sun never set on the British Empire?
Because they've got land all around the world.
Well, because God doesn't trust the British in the dark, right?
Well, yeah. There was a great joke by a New Zealand comedian, Billy T. James,
a Maori comedian, and he's like, bro, us Maoris are going to go to the sun. What do you mean
you're talking about the sun? You'll get burned up. And he's like, no, no, bro, we're going to go
at night. That's right. Actually, there's a little bit of truth to that because the front of it is
black. Yeah, yeah. Allegedly. Yeah, allegedly. I haven't been there myself yet. Yeah, I was
thinking about taking my summer vacation on the sun, you know. I could get tanned in like
two microseconds. Well, here's the thing, you know, the sun's heat doesn't really materialize
until about 150 miles up. And, you know, NASA tried to take a little vacation near the sun
with their two SOHO stereo probes, and they admit on their website that they could never get any
position other than 180 degrees from the sun. But, you know, you know who's another interesting
character? Just a total segway to read up on his political notions was Winston Churchill. You know,
of course, he was part of the main crew there, you know, but he's, yeah, oh yeah, they all are.
They all are on some level, aren't they? I mean, well, there's no reason to even name call or point
out any names on who's a Freemason, because, you know, they all are. You don't even need to
blanketly point out to it anymore. Yeah, yeah, you see, well, years ago, the mastership was
retained in these types of societies. What I mean about mastership, when you wanted to become
a certain skilled tradesman or even a professional of intellectual right, like a doctor or a lawyer,
not an attorney, but a lawyer or a researcher, you learned from a master, not university. You
went to these mastership schools, and now they've all been just converted to the scumbaggery that we
all, you of course, talk about and we all sort of hear about, but don't do anything about it.
You know, about, you know, money. It's all about money. There's no more true mastership.
So, personally, I wouldn't hesitate to go into one of these groups if they actually did what
they were supposed to, but when you do some research, they're actually worshipping Satan
as the lord of the planet, and this, that, and the other, so. Yeah, and there's a whole lot of real
secretive stuff that goes on, and, you know, if you're doing something good, whatever, you don't
do it in the darkness, shut away in total secrecy. You do it out in the light, in public, so that
people can see you do it, or at least that's what I reckon, I mean, because that's what I do.
I'm trying to do something good, and I've exposed myself warts and all. I don't care,
you know. This is the way it's got to be. If you're not willing to go out on a limb,
how do you ever expect to accomplish anything? Nobody accomplishes things without taking any
risk, without devoting any time. That's how you do it. We'll be right back after the break.
Greg, you can hold on if you want. 402-237-2525.
Are you suffering from issues related to angina pain, high blood pressure, congestive heart
failure, unbalanced cholesterol, irregular heartbeats, clogged arteries? If so, you are
not alone. Millions of people are suffering from one or more of these problems. If you'd like to
live your life free of sickness, pain, and fear, live your life with increased vitality, energy,
and youthfulness, and experience your body healing itself, then this might be the most
important message you'll ever hear. An effective 100% organic nutritional supplement is now
available. Heart and Body Extract is an exclusive formula of wild, crafted, and organic herbs.
It is extremely effective and starts to work within days. Get your Heart and Body Extract
today by visiting heartandbody.com or by calling 866-295-5305, 866-295-5305, or heartandbody.com.
Most Americans know the significance of July 4th, 1776. However, few know the importance of
September 17th, 1787, the day the Constitution was written and adopted by our Founders.
Unfortunately, over 200 years later, this sacred document is under attack along with our beloved
Republic. Throughout the span of history, brave men and women have rallied behind banners,
which have served as symbols of liberty against the forces of tyranny. Today, we have the
Constitution Pride Flag to show our support for the Constitution, the Bill of Rights,
Freedom, Liberty, and Justice for We the People of the United States.
Now available at www.1787flags.com, get your very own Constitution Pride Flag today
and receive a free pocket constitution with your order. www.1787flags.com,
the official website of the Constitution Pride Flag. That's www.1787flags.com.
Feeling stressed, tired, lacking energy, or lacking libido? Now you can take control of
your healthcare goals in the privacy of your own home with the use of reliable,
high-quality health products from Ideal Health in New Zealand. Conveniently delivered to your
door anywhere in the world. You'll find our friendly health team offer well-researched
health information plus the highest quality health products. We want to ensure you not only
get the best value products available, but also ensure you get the fastest therapeutic results
with over 2600 pages of health information and natural products all compiled by our friendly
naturopathic team. To take advantage of very special rates, click on the banner at
www.americanfreedomradio.com. And don't forget our convenient delivery service,
Ideal Health New Zealand, leaders in alternative health. That's www.americanfreedomradio.com
and click on the Ideal Health New Zealand button. Proudly brought to you by the Vinnie Eastwood Show.
What would your life be like if you woke up each morning with new vitality, feeling better than you
have in years, and you noticed a difference in your sleeping patterns, blood sugar levels,
and had a sense of well-being overall? There's something that is changing thousands of people's
lives, and you could be one of them. It's called Heart and Body Extract. Sharon Harris, co-creator
of Heart and Body Extract, talks about the positive effects of Heart and Body Extract.
What happens with the formula Heart and Body Extract is it's giving the body the necessary
vitamins, minerals, amino acids, enzymes, and phytonutrients so the body will heal itself.
And yes, the body does have the ability to balance blood pressure, balance cholesterol,
clean and unclog the arteries. It can also work on balancing the circulation for diabetics. So
the body is an amazing thing. It simply needs some help so it has the tools to heal itself.
Heart and Body Extract gets results. To order your two-month supply, call now,
toll-free at 866-295-5305. Order online at HBextract.com.
No rules. No taboo topics. No fear of doom. We are American Freedom Radio.
Welcome back to the Vinnie Angstworth Show, the fastest two hours in talk radio.
Trying to take not being serious very seriously indeed. It's the most ironic kind of stuff. Hey,
if you want to call in, 402-237-2525. I want to know what people are getting up to
on their Friday nights or on their Saturdays or whatever because when you have a five-day-a-week
job and it's utter slavery and it sucks various expletives that you can't say on FCC-regulated
radio, what do you do with your time off? Do you kick back and listen to some radio archives
or watch a few documentaries? Do you go out partying and think, oh mate, spending an entire
week taking crap from scumbags is really not good for my G. I need to head out. I need to balance
that, she-eyed Muslim. That's what a lot of people are really up to, isn't it?
Trying to make sure that right now I am okay. And it's almost a struggle to make sure that
happens. Why is it such hard work to just be okay? Well, for a lot of people, maybe it's not.
They got it down. And maybe I'm just talking about other people who just,
I don't know, don't quite get it. They don't quite get that because they don't sit around
and learn things, like instead of watching a couple of soap operas in a row,
you could watch a documentary that will radically inform you
about something you previously knew nothing about. Which time is more valuable?
Something that enlightens you or something that only vaguely entertains you?
Something that only slowly draws you in, only to watch you in another episode,
always leaving on a cliffhanger at the end of every single one, every single ad break.
It's as if you've become Sylvester Stallone, you've done so much cliffhanging.
It's inextricable. The degree of manipulation that people have to be subjected to through
television has got a lot of people up in arms. Seriously, there was something like
ridiculous amounts, something like 40, 50, I don't know, however many million people
cancelled their cable in the US a year or two back. That was pretty ruthless, man. The
cable companies had no idea. All of a sudden, everybody's, nah, I'm sick of having 500 channels
of stuff that's going to brainwash me with vain entertainment and prevent me from spending any
time with my family or getting anything done around the house. I'm living in freaking squalor
watching the television. I could have vacuumed yesterday, but instead I watched two hours of
Roots. How can people put up with this kind of nonsense? There's some healthy families out there.
Really? People have such a problem actually having a healthy family unit. In fact,
there was a statistic that was released not too long ago, maybe like five, 10 years ago,
saying that the bulk, the majority of American families are now dysfunctional.
And I think television really represents that. Maybe one incredibly well-functioning family
has been featured on TV endlessly all over the place. Simpsons, dysfunctional family. Family
Guide, dysfunctional family. Titus from Christopher Titus, dysfunctional family. Everything.
Everything's about a family that can't function properly. So what kind of examples do people have
to go to? You go watch like Super Nanny or something of that description, how they teach
people how to raise better kids and whatnot. You see how bad things have gotten in America.
The same thing, of course, as is happening right here at home in New Zealand and
everywhere else. The whole mass of certain incentives that have been given to people
to instead of being diligent with their families and their homes and their own state of being
and accomplishing some form of growth personally, financially, they instead
choose to say, I'm too tired. I'm going to watch four hours of television.
Imagine what you could do with that four hours that you get back.
I could accomplish quite a bit. I could make a video. I could compose a song.
I could do two episodes of the Vinnie Eastwood Show back to back. I could write an article.
I could collaborate with an activist. I could go out to a protest and film some stuff and ambush
some various scumbags. There are all these things that you can do with the time that you would have
often instead spent watching television. And I've noticed this to a greater degree of late because
I'm watching a lot less television and noticing that I'm getting a lot more done.
And it's not even that hard. It's very simple. Yep. I'm now catching just the morning news
pretty much. That's about it for me at this point. All the rest is done online.
And just to monitor the enemy communique. It's not entirely dissimilar from the start of that
movie Shooter with Mark Wahlberg, incidentally directed by the same guy who directed Training
Day, going down to his computer in the morning and say, okay, let's see what lies they're telling
the world today. Words to that effect. That is a healthy way to look at news. I believe Mark,
oh no, it was Thomas Jefferson who said, a man who reads nothing is more informed than a man
who only reads newspapers. I hold that to be a very self-evident truth. You have conversations
with some of these people and they're just insane. I'm not being mean about it or anything.
They're just insane. Endlessly repeating something that they've heard or seen in a newspaper,
in some cases, word for word. It's been repeated to them that much. They have actually got it
memorized and they don't know anything about it. Whatever the case that they might be arguing
about, whether it be privatization or whatever, they have no idea. All they can do is repeat
the exact same thing over and over and over and over and over and over again. It's beyond a joke.
These are the kind of people that vote in massively damaging governments
because they have no quality of analysis, no common sense, no questioning capability to speak of,
and absolutely no concern for their fellow man. They only have concern for themselves.
They've devoted themselves to something that's a lie for so long that has become part of their
own identity, the man who tells a lie so often enough that he actually begins to believe it
himself, like Donnie Brasco. That's what these people are, Republican Donnie Brascos.
Absolute BS all the time. You see it spouted all over the media. You wonder how to counter it.
You don't have the huge mechanisms that mainstream media, news, studios do,
endless computers with hardline internet and all your stuff paid for, your fuel, your car,
your nice suits, your beautiful microphones and gargantuan cameras, your elderly cameramen who
won't say too much and you can order them around. They got it made. When you have to do it yourself,
that's when it gets really fun because you realize, oh my goodness, just with a home
computer and a camera, I can make news that is of better quality, better quality of information,
maybe not quite as much production, but you don't really need that.
It is form over substance for a lot of people and I take the substance over the form.
You don't judge people by what they look like, you judge them by what they say,
by what they do. But of course, some people say judge not lest ye be judged. I don't know.
I think everybody can be judged on their merits and their faults. Doesn't that sound reasonable?
I think it does. After all, being naive and trusting absolutely every politician with a
bad scope backdoor agenda is incredibly foolish and will lead you into very dark territory indeedy.
You have a criminal class running the political system, the media game.
They love doing so and they ain't going to let it go without a fight. And then of course,
you've got the people who oppose them, the people who do research. It was a very small
amount of people, extremely powerful. One of the most powerful groups in the world,
I'd probably say, would now be the conspiracy theorist growing inside everybody, like in the
movie Alien. It'll suddenly burst out of your chest at some point. And just suddenly everybody
will go, oh, oh, it's a truther. It's coming. We should have quarantined them and jettisoned them
into the dark void long ago. And that's what'll happen once you start telling the truth to people.
And if you're up front about it, you will offend both sides of every argument. That includes
family, friends. Your life will change dramatically. Not always for the better,
mind you. Knowing the truth is an incredible burden and you really get tested as a person.
Your perseverance, your strength, your abilities, everything that you are as a human being gets
tested when you go through discovering that 9-11 was an inside job, that the politicians are all
controlled, that the corporations, the politicians, and the varying other degrees of machinations of
scumbaggery in the military industrial complex sense have conspired and are conspiring to exterminate
you and all forms of freedom forever. And they have enough resources to do it.
That is a very scary, very burdensome thought. And you do lose your way sometimes when you get
that information into your head. That's why so many people react so violently to it. That's why
you get criticized and called a conspiracy theorist and various other, every name under the
sun, don't you? You're crazy. You've been smoking too much weed. You've been injecting MDMA caps
into your eyeballs. Whatever. I've heard them all. All they've got is name calling.
All I got is the truth. Which do you think is more powerful? Which do you think has staying
power? And which do you think is actually going to win out in the end? It's pretty obvious.
The truth always comes out sooner or later. And the modern media sense of the word is usually
much later, but that's the power of it. You can quash it if you want to, if you really want to,
but not if everybody's saying it. That's the problem they've got going on their hands right now.
Too many people are talking about the truth now. More people are waking up. More people are
figuring it out. And so every time that they pass a bit of legislation that violates your rights and
laws, within seconds, minutes, you have a myriad of different truth talkers and seekers in that
country or township or area of research screaming blue bloody murder all over the airwaves.
They don't like that very much. So that's why you keep doing it. We got this tiger by the tail.
We might as well just take him off. He's going to try and eat us anyway. Let's make his life
as miserable and annoying and frustrating as humanly possible. Because after all,
they have much worse planned and they're going to do it all incrementally.
So if you act like every single bit of legislation is the total takeover domination of fascism,
that's right. That's exactly what it is. Every bit of legislation that you accept
is you accepting fascism into your country. The fascist states of America. Have you ever seen
the Congress opposite sides of the Speaker of the House? What's up on that wall there?
It's a fash. You know what a fash is? It's a double headed axe that's wrapped with sticks.
It was the symbol of fascism in Nazi Germany. And it's on both sides of the Speaker of the
House and Congress. What does that tell you? It's the united fascist states of America.
The U.S.S.A. because it's all socialism anyway, which were created by the same freaking people.
You don't have any choices. None that are widely advertised with huge million dollar budgets.
Those aren't your choices. Those people are scumbags. Have a look for the grassroots
supported people. Ron Paul, for example, huge grassroots support versus, say,
the eye of Newt Gingrich, whatever his name is. No grassroots support whatsoever.
But he'll wind up getting financed by a huge major corporate banks as all these
Republican scumbags or Democrat scumbags always are so that they can advertise their BS to you
endlessly so that you'll vote for them because of the power of repetition.
You're listening to the Vinny Eastwood show 402 237 2525 is the number to ring.
And we'll be right back after the break.
Now, you and your family and friends can enjoy the cleanest, most delicious and healthy drinking
water any time, even while traveling, camping at sporting events or in emergency situations.
The Berkeley removes bacteria, parasites and harmful chemicals to below detectable levels.
It also produces nitrates and unhealthy minerals like lead and mercury, while leaving in the
beneficial and nutritional minerals your body needs. Berkeley is so powerful it can even purify
raw, untreated water from remote lakes and streams. And the optional PF2 filters even
remove fluoride. The Berkeley LED with its rechargeable lighting system can be used as
a nightlight or a camp light to view or purchase your Berkeley water system and replacement filters.
Please visit American Freedom Radio's website at American Freedom Radio dot com and click the
Berkeley banner. Once again, that's American Freedom Radio dot com and click the Berkeley water banner.
Not yet available in Iowa. Do you realize every day we are being put under constant stress from
wireless radiation? What's worse is that you don't even know that it's happening. It puts as much
stress on our body as if we had a constant viral infection, draining our energy and sapping our
strength or just making us irritable and fatigued. These wireless fields are being emitted from
computers, microwaves, mobile phones, power lines and any electrical appliance. Now there is a
solution. A group of research engineers in New Zealand have come up with an active shielding
device that shields you from wireless radiation at a cellular level. Blue Shield comes in three
models, a household, portable and USB that plugs into any computer. The great thing about Blue
Shield is it is very affordable and guaranteed to last. A one-off purchase will see you being
protected for years to come. Visit American Freedom Radio dot com and click on the Blue Shield
banner. Blue Shield brought to you by the Vinnie Eastwood Show dot com.
Following a radiological or nuclear event, radioactive iodine may be released into the
air and then be breathed into the lungs. Radioactive iodine may also contaminate the local food supply
and get into the body through food or through drink. When radioactive materials get into the
body through breathing, eating or drinking, the thyroid gland quickly absorbs the chemical.
Radioactive iodine absorbed by the thyroid can then injure the gland. But you can protect yourself
with used potassium iodide, which acts to block radioactive iodine from being taken into the
thyroid gland and can help protect this gland from injury. To take advantage of very special rates,
click on the banner at American Freedom Radio dot com. And don't forget our convenient delivery
service, Ideal Health New Zealand, Leaders in Alternative Health. That's American Freedom
Radio dot com and click on the Ideal Health New Zealand button. Proudly brought to you by
the Vinnie Eastwood Show dot com. Are you suffering from issues related to angina pain,
high blood pressure, congestive heart failure, unbalanced cholesterol, irregular heartbeats,
clogged arteries? If so, you are not alone. Millions of people are suffering from one or more
of these problems. If you'd like to live your life free of sickness, pain and fear, live your life
with increased vitality, energy and youthfulness and experience your body healing itself, then this
might be the most important message you'll ever hear. An effective 100 percent organic nutritional
supplement is now available. Heart and Body Extract is an exclusive formula of wild crafted
and organic herbs. It is extremely effective and starts to work within days. Get your heart and
body extract today by visiting Heart and Body dot com or by calling 866-295-5305, 866-295-5305
or Heart and Body dot com. News and information you can trust. This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom, freedom, American Freedom Radio. Radio. American Freedom Radio. Hi everybody,
I'm Christopher Green. Make sure to tune in to Green Wave Radio every Tuesday and Thursday
from 3 to 5 p.m. Central on American Freedom Radio. Heart hitting and interface America.
Black sunrise, black sunrise, shadow coming over the sky. Black sunrise, black sunrise,
always gonna be a surprise. Welcome back to the show that's all about being surprised but never
shocked. Or is it shocked but never surprised? It's the Vinnie Eastwood Show. The lighter side
of genocide because in a world so full of chaos and madness, if you lose your sense of humor,
you'll go friggin nuts. I have a caller in from New Zealand named Dean. Dean, welcome to the program.
Thanks Vinnie, how are you doing? Not doing too well, I'm thinking about that. You know what,
I'm just gonna do what everybody else says and take it as a rhetorical question. I'm good.
I always hate that question actually because the answer is automatically programmed into us as
fine thank you and you're essentially lying to people most of the time. Yeah, I remember
somebody asked me, Vinnie how are you? And I go, well do you want the long version or do you want
the short version? She goes, I want the short version. I say, I'm good. Exactly. What would you
like to talk about today? I've been writing a couple of blog posts recently and I've been going
through a bit of a journey of discovery and it's a journey that a lot of people have gone under
themselves over the last 2,000 years. But as I'm coming up with things, I'm publishing it and
I've identified really some of the keys of why we're in the position we're in at the moment as
far as society and economy and the way that we can actually get our lives back and our freedom back
and our links back to nature. And it's really, really simple. Yeah, I thought it was quite
simple too, just expose scumbaggery and everything will follow. Basically, yeah. Well they've only
got one weapon against us and all we really need to do is stop using that weapon and then there's
no power. Yep, yep. I mean seriously, if your enemy's using an energy weapon, what do you do,
is you just cut his power supply. Boom. No matter how much resources he spends on it,
you've got nothing. And at the moment, I think it's sort of the power over our minds that is
the greatest weapon that they have, where people just on a random brain spasm will go and assault
a 9-11 truther. Yeah and how even just words can provoke this surge of fear within us which
we instinctively try and avoid and that's really what it is, the strings are pulled
and we don't really have the sense to stop that. Do you feel like a couple of my big programmed
responses like they do in mind control programs like MK Ultra and stuff like that, just to a
lesser degree? Oh absolutely, we start when we're born. We generally start it formally when we're
about five years old. Yeah, for the education system. Exactly, it's training us to seek
careers and we're all told the dream is to have house and cars and children and that's
what everybody is supposed to aspire to. Yeah, I suppose it would be because the problem I find
really with society is that their priorities are all out of whack.
Like having home security, that kind of thing right here, right now is their only priority
because they've just distracted them from doing anything else, whereas improving themselves,
ensuring your country doesn't collapse into tyranny, making sure that you're kept healthy
so you don't get sick for the rest of your freaking natural life, that doesn't enter
into the equation. The only thing that people see as the way that they can
protect themselves is by getting a job, earning money to buy a house,
to set up a home for the family. So that they can drive past protesters and tell them to get a job?
Yes. That's one of the great benefits of having a job, is you can tell protesters to get one.
So it's one of the perks. I think that should be included in media pay packets or something of
that nature. One of the perks is they could tell protesters to go and get a job and call people
filthy hippies. Indeed, just sitting on top of a smug little room, poking your tongue out at people
saying no, no, no, no, no. Yeah, the koru club. We're talking about the mechanisms that enslave
us and as far as I'm concerned, it basically comes down to just common law and the issuance
of currency. That's basically the two ways that you're primarily physically enslaved.
One determines your economic output, which determines your level of survival, and the
other dictates whether or not you're allowed to freely go around in a slave society or be
incarcerated in a slave society. That's exactly the topic of my post that I started writing at
two o'clock this morning. Can I summarize or read some of that out? Go for your life.
Well, it was 2 a.m. and I was laying in bed trying to sleep, and I've been writing in a journal
only for the last few days, and I thought that sleep is something that's essential,
and I was thinking about that for a wee while, and then I started putting a few notes down and
I thought that you only really get to have sleep if you've paid money for the privilege of a place
to sleep, and I was thinking, where can you actually sleep that's free? I remembered I was
in another city in another country not too long ago, and I actually had no place to sleep there,
and I learned a valuable lesson. I actually started to feel trapped, and I kept on having
to walk down the footpath and walk around the block because I actually had nowhere to sit,
and I'd figured out that all the chairs were for rent. There was restaurants or even bus stops or
shopfronts and so forth, but nothing was actually free to really use,
but mostly for a place to sleep. You're not allowed to sleep in a public place
or on somebody else's property. So, I think there is some truth to that.
Where the heck do you sleep if you ain't got the money to pay for your bed?
That's right. Well, you can take a tent. You can take a tent somewhere, but where would you take
that? And how would you pay for the tent if you can't pay for your place to sleep?
Indeed. Well, you may already have one or it's something that you could build.
Going back to my, I've got a bit of a flow here with my blog. With the tent thing, you can't go
onto a business property with your tent, and you can't go onto a residential property with your
tent, because both of those properties have been bought by somebody else, and they are the ones
that have the right to sleep on that property. Okay.
But the main body which enforces this entire payment system is the government itself,
since they are the ultimate owners of every inch of land that you could possibly sleep on top of.
Well, that's why they have corporate policy officers to trespass people, isn't it?
Indeed. And there's many different types of that as well, from identifying if you've paid the right
amount of taxation, I suppose, which then they have the right to remove you from locations,
or if you haven't paid the right amount of rent, they can remove you. There's different
forces which can all do the same thing for a different reason.
Yeah. But the only way to avoid the payment of money is actually by asking the owner of that
land for a free favour to stay there. And in most cases, that's unlikely,
since, again, they've paid so much money themselves to be able to sleep there.
Or you can break the law by trespassing, but you risk a penalty.
The question that I have is, what gave them the right in the first place to own the land?
And the answer that I came up with was that they stole it aggressively from nature and simply
decided that it now belonged to them. And they brutally murdered anyone who challenged their
claim to ownership. Then they created rules for the people. And if you wish to lease parts of
that land from them, you need to follow those rules or you will be prosecuted, penalised, imprisoned.
This is how you make a landlord become a tenant.
Yes. What's the point here then?
Well, I actually started to think then about what are the other things that are essential to life
and what actually keeps our physical bodies moving. And the main things are air and sleep,
water, food and shelter. In my blog, I put another part about broadband internet access
as another thing that's essential today. And looking at the way society is currently today,
if we look around, the internet is... Actually, my question after that is, what of those things
is actually a right and which one is a privilege to have? And I'd written or thought that the
internet is a privilege. It's something that we choose to purchase if we want to use it.
Shelter is also a privilege at present. It's something that we must purchase if we want to
use it. Food presently is a privilege also. It's something that you must purchase from a store if
they allow you to purchase it. Water in cities is also a privilege. It's something that you have
to purchase if you want to use it. If you fail to pay that, the supply will cease.
Sleep, of course, we've gone over that. That's definitely a privilege. You're only
legally allowed to sleep on land that you've paid money for.
And not to mention with the amount of hours that people are working for crap pay these days
because they outsourced everything for free trade agreements, they aren't getting much sleep at all
anyway. So you're really just sitting on there thinking about why you're not sleeping and what
it is that you have to do the next day. I'm lying awake wondering why I can't sleep.
Yeah. Air is the last one. And that's the final thing which is borderline at the moment because
it's kind of a right and a privilege right now. It's in the process.
Well, we're going to be carbon taxed for polluting the air. So I think it's well on its way.
Exactly. They're measuring the amount of carbon dioxide we are using. Well,
we are expelling, we are breathing out. Do they even measure it? Like I haven't
seen no council guy go up to my tailpipe and go, oh, I think I'll give you this much
carbon tax this year. That's a pretty naughty tailpipe there.
It's like, thank you, Mr. Green-wrapped, jack-booted thug with a swastika made of leaves.
Yeah. What is the formula? Do they look at the size of the machine and punch some numbers into
a calculator and say, okay, this is our estimate? I reckon they just operate like the Federal
Reserve and make it up based upon a group of scumbags who work for international organizations
who have an interest in making sure that the prices are as such or whatever that they recommend.
You know, I'll short this option and then I'll crash the economy.
There's a huge amount of money for me and a huge amount of power and control too. Fabulous.
The thing is, how did we let this happen? How did we give all of this power to somebody else?
We've been a species for, and this is an open topic really, for 10,000 years, 50,000 years,
100,000, depends on where you want to draw that line of where we started.
But it's only in the last thousand or so years that we've been giving away our rights to these
privileges that we've been getting for free all of this time. I don't know. I mean, I don't think
anything's really free. Like, before people became slaves to Egypt, they were out in the middle of
land with their families and they had to work all day to keep fed, sheltered, and with water and
whatnot. Anyway, we're just subtracting one form of substituted slavery for another and that's what
history through for humanity has really seemed to be like for me. It's just these different forms
of slavery. It's like a corkscrew that weaves to one side and then comes back again and distorts and
gradually goes all the way through and then plucks out your freedom.
In certain circles, but not in all. And all of those, all of the circles that make it that way
are always led by one person at the top that's seeking the power and the control.
And if you look at smaller communities, native
villages and so forth that are not underneath the umbrella of one of these main leaders,
their systems are completely different and it's that lack of greed or seeking of ultimate power
that means that everybody can coexist. And that happens today still. There are some
parts of the world that it's done.
Well, I think that when we really want to get down to it, if you want to be free and if you
want to maintain that freedom, all those essentials of life should be something that's relatively easy
to get a hold of, right? It's now actually becoming quite difficult to find a place to live,
to have clean food, clean water, and be able to heat your property. I mean, thank you very much,
Dean, for your call there. And we'll have to let you go. We've got Chris Greenwave of
Greenwave Radio coming on in the last segment today. You're listening to The Vinnie Eastwood
Show at thevinnieeastwoodshow.com. Archiving at guerillamedia.co.nz and americanfreedomradio.com.
What would your life be like if you woke up each morning with new vitality,
feeling better than you have in years, and you noticed a difference in your sleeping patterns,
blood sugar levels, and had a sense of well-being overall? There's something that is changing
thousands of people's lives, and you could be one of them. It's called Heart and Body Extract.
Sharon Harris, co-creator of Heart and Body Extract, talks about the positive effects of
Heart and Body Extract. What happens with the formula Heart and Body Extract is it's giving
the body the necessary vitamins, minerals, amino acids, enzymes, and phytonutrients,
so the body will heal itself. And yes, the body does have the ability to balance blood pressure,
balance cholesterol, clean and unclog the arteries. It can also work on balancing the
circulation for diabetics, so the body is an amazing thing. It simply needs some help,
so it has the tools to heal itself. Heart and Body Extract gets results. To order your two-month
supply, call now, toll-free at 866-295-5305. Order online at hbextract.com.
The First Amendment in the Bill of Rights limits the government's power by ensuring freedom of
speech and preserves the rights of the people. Every day that passes, our rights gradually
slip away. It's time to take a stand and let the government know that we are tired of losing our
rights. LibertyStickers.com will allow you to express your rights and allow millions of people
to see you stand up for what you believe in. LibertyStickers.com carries the largest selection
of bumper stickers online, ranging from political to humorous. As always, you can find your favorite
stickers that protest the war and the president. Don't see what you're looking for? LibertyStickers
will custom make stickers that will get your message across for all Americans to see.
Go to LibertyStickers.com and see pre-made stickers that will get everyone talking.
That's LibertyStickers.com or call 877-873-9626. LibertyStickers,
the world's most dangerous stickers.
What is it that's in your home that causes grown men to cower and children to run for cover?
Food storage. That's right, food storage shouldn't be scary. At Simply Your Food,
we are the premier providers of long-term, storable, GMO and MSG-free meats, veggies,
fruit, dairy and pantry essentials like powdered butter. We even have a gluten-free line.
Food storage shouldn't be scary. Let Simply Your Food help you with your food storage needs. Go to
SimplyYourFood.com or call 866-251-7511 and let us take the scary out of food storage.
Go to SimplyYourFood.com or call 866-251-7511 and let us take the scary out of food storage.
Now you and your family and friends can enjoy the cleanest, most delicious and healthy drinking
water anytime, even while traveling, camping, at sporting events or in emergency situations.
The Berkey Light removes bacteria, cysts, parasites and harmful chemicals to below
detectable levels. It also reduces nitrates and unhealthy minerals like lead and mercury
while leaving in the beneficial and nutritional minerals your body needs. Berkey Light is so
powerful it can even purify raw, untreated water from remote lakes and streams. And the optional
PF2 filters even remove fluoride. The Berkey Light LED with its rechargeable lighting system
can be used as a night light or a camp light. To view or purchase your Berkey Water System
and replacement filters, please visit American Freedom Radio's website at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and click the Berkey banner. Once again, that's AmericanFreedomRadio.com and click the Berkey
Water Banner. Not yet available in Iowa. Welcome to the world's meeting place. American.
It's practically narcotic. Freedom. Oh, yes. I like very much. Radio. You're an American
institution. American Freedom Radio. Truth Brigade Radio, live Monday through Friday,
7 to 9 p.m., only on AmericanFreedomRadio.com. The truth has just gotten hotter.
I was putting my pack along the dusty. Welcome back to the show that's been everywhere, man.
It's the Vinnie Eastwood Show, broadcasting live from New Zealand, live from the future. It's all
ready tomorrow. And for those of you on the other side of the dateline, don't worry about it. I'm
sure you'll catch up eventually. I have a very special guest for you. It's Chris from Greenwave
Radio on AmericanFreedomRadio.com. And he's a fabulous new young full-time show host, and he is
kicking it and kicking it hard. Chris, welcome to the program. Vinnie, how are you doing? Thanks
for having me on. Well, tell us a little bit about yourself and what actually got you into
the radio. And we have a caller on the line as well, so we can take them when you wish.
All right. Well, sounds good. Well, I'm looking at this T-shirt you sent me. You sent me a link
to this. It says, I love scumbaggery. And you said that you love exposing it. Well,
I guess you can call me somebody that likes to expose scumbaggery as well.
You know, it's abundantly clear that we've got fraud and corruption at the
very top levels of the federal government and the banking system.
I was in the banking game myself for over 10 years. In fact, I worked as a broker at Merrill Lynch
during the height of the crisis in 2008. And I was so absolutely disgusted by what I saw,
I packed my bags, Vinnie, and I quit on the spot. And I started a YouTube channel
and really with the intention of helping to educate others to exactly what's been going
on in this country here in the United States of America and really around the world.
And here I am today. Yeah, absolutely. We have a caller on the line here. Caller,
area code 561. State your name and business. Caller number 561, area code.
Just calling in from somewhere. You don't want to speak, do you?
No. Yeah, I don't hear anyone there, Vinnie.
Oh, well, it must be the phantom caller of some description.
So let me ask you, what do you think of this indefinite detention bill that passed today?
What do you make of that? Well, I don't know about indefinite
detention, but I'm definitely going to pay some attention to it. You know what I'm saying?
There's some very, very nasty things that are happening with people's rights all day,
every day. And this basically turns the United States into a declared
war zone. And conveniently with the whole trialed enemy combatant in quotation marks
a scheme of just being able to grab anybody anywhere, anytime and hold them for all time.
It's been working quite well under Obama, don't you think? So this is just natural progression.
Yeah, it really is, you know, terrorism just against the regular people. I mean,
nobody at the top goes to jail, Vinnie, but they can they can send us to prison.
They can just call you a terrorist. Call Vinnie Eastwood a terrorist. They can call me a terrorist
and put us to jail just kind of like, you know, over at Guantanamo Bay. That other institution,
that fine institution that President Obama said he'd get rid of, that's still open to this day.
So the tyranny continues, that's for sure. Yeah. Well, there's no upper limit to tyranny.
And there's no end to it as well. It's a perennial problem. Every generation has their
own tyranny that they need to deal with, you know, whether it's just your tyrannical father
trying to stop you from becoming a radio show host or whatever, or whether it's massive,
big daddy, messianic leader telling you what you can and can't do all day long with his long leg
and mackdaddiness. Those are the types of tyrannies you really got to be watching out for
because it's a scalable model, you see. You can have tyranny in the home, you can have tyranny
on the playground, you can have tyranny in an organization, tyranny in a company,
tyranny in a country, tyranny in a globe. And that's what we're heading for. For the first time
ever, a total, complete world tyranny, the first that has ever been concocted that is actually
nearing completion. That's the scariest thing about it all, is that there's nowhere to run,
nowhere to hide. You don't really have much of a choice in the matter once you know what's going on.
And it gives you that impetus. I'm sure when you're in Merrill Lynch,
as soon as you knew what was going on, you got some motivation.
Absolutely, absolutely. And that's the truth. And there's millions of people around the world
that feel the same way I do, coming from all walks of life. And that's what the Warren Buffetts of
the world, these financial terrorists, just don't get, is that you've got an entire generation of
non-believers. You've got an entire generation of highly educated people like me, like myself.
Take myself as an example. I went to private school. I was in the game. I was in the real
world. Worked for these big international banks. And now I'm gone. And now I'm working full time to
expose truth and to educate people to the fraud and corruption. And Vinny, we want justice.
A lot of what we do, and I think a lot that's been overlooked with the OWS movement,
which by the way, they're quelling and removing those people from the streets because it's not
like we have those constitutional rights anymore. What people are missing is this is about justice.
I want to see these people go to jail. And millions more of us and millions alike of us,
they want to see the same thing. So until- Well, they want to see worse.
Hung in public square, buried in an unmarked shallow grave so the coyotes can get them.
Some people are calling for that. Yeah. Death by coyote. That would be the new
form of- I can see the state of Texas actually having a prison. You know how they have prisons
where they have death row and execution rooms and stuff like that? They'll just have another
one that just has a room full of coyotes. That would be a very gruesome death.
Potentially worse than the guillotine. Death by coyotes. But here's a question for you,
Vinny, and your listeners around the world. Is this prison? Are we living in a prison now?
It's the biggest open-air prison there is. It's good old planet prison earth.
Yeah, I was thinking about that today too. Of course, a lot of Americans, a lot of people
obviously still deal in credit. If they didn't have their credit cards, they wouldn't be able to
purchase goods and services. But every time you make a transaction, Vinny, whether or not
it's a credit card or a debit card, or they're just taking a snapshot or a picture of your
license plate as you're driving across the street past an intersection, or if you try to board a
plane nowadays, you're going to have a sexual relationship with the TSA worker. That's just
how things work here in the good old red, white, and blue free America. We're fighting overseas
in all these wars. We've got young men and women about our ages stepping on IEDs, getting their
arms and legs blown off if they're lucky, if they don't get killed by it. And they say we're
fighting these tyrannical dictatorships and regimes because we're trying to preserve freedom. We're
trying to liberate the rest of the world. Let me ask a fundamental question. Why don't we have
freedom here? If this is what young men and women are dying for across the world, then why is it
that we're in a prison? Why do we have this draconian legislation being passed? Why do we
have bills like SOPA aimed at threatening the very existence of alternative media,
shows like the Vinnie Eastwood show, shows like our show at greenwave.com?
Yeah, well, it's like Smedley Butler, the Medal of Honor winner, said when he was a Marine,
he was just basically working for United Fruit. Whenever there's a company interest in another
South American country where the certain Panamanian dictator or whatever was kicking
up a fuss and threatening their profit margin, in would go the boys. That's all that troops have
always been used for, always will, is to protect corporate interests. Not entirely dissimilar from
how police officers are today. They're not out there to help you, to serve or protect you in a
large amount of cases. They're really out there to just gather revenue from you for this all
overarching scumbaggery corporation that they want you to live in as a partner, which is called
fascism. They want you to be a part of the downfall of your own country, and they're going to use your
money to do it. And that's exactly what they are doing. We have a caller on the line there. If
you're on the line there, you can speak up if you like. If not, don't worry, we'll just talk over
the top of you. And Chris, I wanted to know, from getting up in the corporate sector and the banking
and all of that, I presume you probably found out like I did that the whole competitive environment
thing is one that might on occasion be riddled with a lot of mistrust?
Well yeah, I think there's a lot of mistrust. I think that people's priorities in America,
a lot of people at least, it's not everybody, it's dominated by greed, it's dominated by me or the
highway, it's dominated by the idea and the paradigm that I'm going to basically earn as much money as
I possibly can, and I'll step over you and stab you in the back and twist the knife if I have to.
You know, if I have to barter and sell my firstborn son for an extra million dollars,
I'm going to do it. And when I do do it and I collect that million dollars, or maybe it's even
10 million dollars, I'm going to build a gigantic house in suburbia and I'm going to have a gigantic
mortgage. I'm going to make it so big, I'm going to build a fence around it and I'm going to have
armed guards outside of it making sure nobody else can get in because that's the American dream.
I thought that was the Panamanian dictator's dream. Oh, wait.
That seems to be what it's all about nowadays. The guy with the most stuff when he dies
wins, and anybody else is going to go to a FEMA camp.
Yeah, well, that's a sad reality, I hope. My hope is, and I think this is starting to change,
even if it's just with a minority of people, is I think a lot of Americans,
after being brutalized by the downturn in the real economy, of course, they can fabricate and
manipulate a stock market, a Dow Jones Industrial Average of 12,000 on quantitative easing to
infinity, Operation Twist, and the latest wham, bam, thank you, ma'am manipulation program coming
out of Ben Bernanke. It will ultimately make the US dollar worthless and send millions of
Americans to poverty, which is what it's already doing. But I think the positive of it is after
being burned and things like real estate being off 50, 60, 70, 80% peak to trough in some parts
of our country, a lot of people, again, Vinny, they're just opting out of the program, my friend.
If you don't get people to buy in in this program, guess what? Everything crashes.
Everything goes down. I think that's what we've got. You've got a generation of nonbelievers.
Well, I love to be an unbeliever, and nobody expects the Spanish Inquisition.
Thanks, Chris Green, for coming on the show with us today. You can check him out
on Americanfreedomradio.com and Greenwaveradio.com, I believe.
Greenwave.com and on YouTube, Seagreen with an E-34.
Seagreen with an E-34. Seagreen with an E-34.
Seagreen with an E-34. Apparently, if you repeat things three times, people remember it a little
bit better. So we're glad to use that little bit of propagandistic brainwashing right here on the
Vinny Eastwood Show. And thanks very much, Chris. Thank you, American Freedom Radio,
and thank you, the listeners. Love you so much.